<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:45:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6691 | Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files &amp;amp; Subscriptions (eCommerce Store + Payments Made Easy) &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Currency Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6691</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files &amp; Subscriptions (eCommerce Store + Payments Made Easy) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the currency value in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6692 | Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files &amp;amp; Subscriptions (eCommerce Store + Payments Made Easy) &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Agreement Text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6692</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files &amp; Subscriptions (eCommerce Store + Payments Made Easy) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Agreement Text value in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7503 | WooCommerce - Social Login &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7503</link><description>The WooCommerce - Social Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.7.5. This is due to the use of loose comparison of the activation code in the 'woo_slg_confirm_email_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the userID. This requires the email module to be enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7621 | Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp;amp; Project Management – Atarim &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7621</link><description>The Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp; Project Management – Atarim plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the process_wpfeedback_misc_options() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins settings which can also be leveraged to gain access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41577 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Ueditor component of productinfoquick v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uplo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41577</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Ueditor component of productinfoquick v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42473 | OpenFGA Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42473</link><description>OpenFGA is an authorization/permission engine. OpenFGA v1.5.7 and v1.5.8 are vulnerable to authorization bypass when calling Check API with a model that uses `but not` and `from` expressions and a userset. Users should downgrade to v1.5.6 as soon as possible. This downgrade is backward compatible. As of time of publication, a patch is not available but OpenFGA's maintainers are planning a patch for inclusion in a future release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50809 | In certain Sonos products before S1 Release 11.12 and S2 release 15.9, the mt_7615.ko wireless driver does not properly validate an informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50809</link><description>In certain Sonos products before S1 Release 11.12 and S2 release 15.9, the mt_7615.ko wireless driver does not properly validate an information element during negotiation of a WPA2 four-way handshake. This lack of validation leads to a stack buffer overflow. This can result in remote code execution within the kernel. This affects Amp, Arc, Arc SL, Beam, Beam Gen 2, Beam SL, and Five.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50810 | In certain Sonos products before Sonos S1 Release 11.12 and S2 release 15.9, a vulnerability exists in the U-Boot component of the firmware ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50810</link><description>In certain Sonos products before Sonos S1 Release 11.12 and S2 release 15.9, a vulnerability exists in the U-Boot component of the firmware that allow persistent arbitrary code execution with Linux kernel privileges. A failure to correctly handle the return value of the setenv command can be used to override the kernel command-line parameters and ultimately bypass the Secure Boot implementation. This affects PLAY5 gen 2, PLAYBASE, PLAY:1, One, One SL, and Amp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42370 | Litestar vulnerable to Environment Variable injection in `docs-preview.yml` workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42370</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, Litestar's `docs-preview.yml` workflow is vulnerable to Environment Variable injection which may lead to secret exfiltration and repository manipulation. This issue will grant a malicious actor the permission to write issues, read metadata, and write pull requests. In addition, the `DOCS_PREVIEW_DEPLOY_TOKEN` is exposed to the attacker. Commit 84d351e96aaa2a1338006d6e7221eded161f517b contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42468 | Path traversal (CometVisu)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42468</link><description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. CometVisuServlet in versions prior to 4.2.1 is susceptible to an unauthenticated path traversal vulnerability. Local files on the server can be requested via HTTP GET on the CometVisuServlet. This issue may lead to information disclosure. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42469 | CometVisu Backend for openHAB affected by RCE through path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42469</link><description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Prior to version 4.2.1, CometVisu's file system endpoints don't require authentication and additionally the endpoint to update an existing file is susceptible to path traversal. This makes it possible for an attacker to overwrite existing files on the openHAB instance. If the overwritten file is a shell script that is executed at a later time, this vulnerability can allow remote code execution by an attacker. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42467 | CometVisu Backend for openHAB affected by SSRF/XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42467</link><description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Prior to version 4.2.1, the proxy endpoint of openHAB's CometVisu add-on can be accessed without authentication. This proxy-feature can be exploited as Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) to induce GET HTTP requests to internal-only servers, in case openHAB is exposed in a non-private network. Furthermore, this proxy-feature can also be exploited as a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, as an attacker is able to re-route a request to their server and return a page with malicious JavaScript code. Since the browser receives this data directly from the openHAB CometVisu UI, this JavaScript code will be executed with the origin of the CometVisu UI. This allows an attacker to exploit call endpoints on an openHAB server even if the openHAB server is located in a private network. (e.g. by sending an openHAB admin a link that proxies malicious JavaScript.) This issue may lead up to Remote Code Execution (RCE) when chained with other vulnerabilities. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42470 | CometVisu Backend for openHAB has a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42470</link><description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Several endpoints in versions prior to 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB don't require authentication. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify or to steal sensitive data. This issue may lead to sensitive information disclosure. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41570 | An Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in demon callback handling in Havoc 2 0.7 allows attackers to send arbitrary network t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41570</link><description>An Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in demon callback handling in Havoc 2 0.7 allows attackers to send arbitrary network traffic originating from the team server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42367 | In aiohttp, compressed files as symlinks are not protected from path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42367</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Prior to version 3.10.2, static routes which contain files with compressed variants (`.gz` or `.br` extension) are vulnerable to path traversal outside the root directory if those variants are symbolic links. The server protects static routes from path traversal outside the root directory when `follow_symlinks=False` (default).  It does this by resolving the requested URL to an absolute path and then checking that path relative to the root. However, these checks are not performed when looking for compressed variants in the `FileResponse` class, and symbolic links are then automatically followed when performing the `Path.stat()` and `Path.open()` to send the file. Version 3.10.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31315 | Improper validation in a model specific register (MSR) could allow a malicious program with ring0 access to modify SMM configuration while S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31315</link><description>Improper validation in a model specific register (MSR) could allow a malicious program with ring0 access to modify SMM configuration while SMI lock is enabled, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32765 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32765</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported to affect Network &amp; Virtual Switch. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local authenticated administrators to gain access to and execute certain functions via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.8.2823 build 20240712 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38989 | izatop bunt v0.29.19 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component /esm/qs.js. This vulnerability allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38989</link><description>izatop bunt v0.29.19 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the component /esm/qs.js. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38018 | IBM Aspera Shares session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38018</link><description>IBM Aspera Shares 1.10.0 PL2 does not invalidate session after a password change which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  260574.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41332 | Incorrect access control in the delete_category function of Sourcecodester Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41332</link><description>Incorrect access control in the delete_category function of Sourcecodester Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily delete categories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37826 | A NULL pointer dereference in vercot Serva v4.6.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted HTTP request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37826</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in vercot Serva v4.6.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40480 | A Broken Access Control vulnerability was found in /admin/update.php and /admin/dashboard.php in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0, which al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40480</link><description>A Broken Access Control vulnerability was found in /admin/update.php and /admin/dashboard.php in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0, which allows remote unauthenticated attackers to view administrator dashboard and delete valid user accounts via the direct URL access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7645 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System User Page users.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7645</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file users.php of the component User Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40479 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/admin/quizquestion.php" in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40479</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/admin/quizquestion.php" in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "eid" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7644 | SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool Add Leads add-leads.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7644</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-leads.php of the component Add Leads Handler. The manipulation of the argument leads_name/phone_number leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41476 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System (HiBOS) V3.0.3.151204 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /manager/card/card_detail.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41476</link><description>AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System (HiBOS) V3.0.3.151204 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /manager/card/card_detail.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39338 | axios 1.7.2 allows SSRF via unexpected behavior where requests for path relative URLs get processed as protocol relative URLs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39338</link><description>axios 1.7.2 allows SSRF via unexpected behavior where requests for path relative URLs get processed as protocol relative URLs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41888 | Apache Answer: The link for resetting user password is not Single-Use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41888</link><description>Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in Apache Answer.

This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.3.5.

The password reset link remains valid within its expiration period even after it has been used. This could potentially lead to the link being misused or hijacked.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.6, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7642 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System activate_act.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7642</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file activate_act.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7643 | SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool Delete Leads delete-leads.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7643</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Leads Manager Tool 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/delete-leads.php of the component Delete Leads Handler. The manipulation of the argument leads leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41890 | Apache Answer: The link to reset the user&amp;#x27;s password will remain valid after sending a new link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41890</link><description>Missing Release of Resource after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in Apache Answer.

This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.3.5.

User sends multiple password reset emails, each containing a valid link. Within the link's validity period, this could potentially lead to the link being misused or hijacked.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.6, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7641 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System deactivate_act.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7641</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file deactivate_act.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29831 | Apache DolphinScheduler: RCE by arbitrary js execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29831</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler. An authenticated user can cause arbitrary, unsandboxed javascript to be executed on the server. If you are using the switch task plugin, please upgrade to version 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30188 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Resource File Read And Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30188</link><description>File read and write vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler ,  authenticated users can illegally access additional resource files.
This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: from 3.1.0 before 3.2.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40478 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/afeedback.php" in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0, which allows rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40478</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/afeedback.php" in Kashipara Online Exam System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "rname" and "email" parameter fields</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7639 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System delete_act.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7639</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file delete_act.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7640 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System delete_register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7640</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file delete_register.php. The manipulation of the argument case_register_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40472 | Sourcecodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via "delete-calorie.php."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40472</link><description>Sourcecodester Daily Calories Monitoring Tool v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via "delete-calorie.php."</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7637 | code-projects Online Polling Registration registeracc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7637</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Polling 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file registeracc.php of the component Registration. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7638 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System delete_client.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7638</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file delete_client.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7636 | code-projects Simple Ticket Booking Login authenticate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7636</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Ticket Booking 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file authenticate.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7635 | code-projects Simple Ticket Booking Registration register_insert.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7635</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Ticket Booking 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file register_insert.php of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/email/dob/password/Gender/phone leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22123 | Zabbix Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22123</link><description>Setting SMS media allows to set GSM modem file. Later this file is used as Linux device. But due everything is a file for Linux, it is possible to set another file, e.g. log file and zabbix_server will try to communicate with it as modem. As a result, log file will be broken with AT commands and small part for log file content will be leaked to UI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7408 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Airveda Air Quality Monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7408</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Airveda Air Quality Monitor PM2.5 PM10 due to transmission of sensitive information in plain text during AP pairing mode. An attacker in close proximity could exploit this vulnerability by capturing Wi-Fi traffic of Airveda-AP.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to cause Evil Twin attack on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22114 | System Information Widget in Global View Dashboard exposes information about Hosts to Users without Permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22114</link><description>User with no permission to any of the Hosts can access and view host count &amp; other statistics through System Information Widget in Global View Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22116 | Remote code execution within ping script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22116</link><description>An administrator with restricted permissions can exploit the script execution functionality within the Monitoring Hosts section. The lack of default escaping for script parameters enabled this user ability to execute arbitrary code via the Ping script, thereby compromising infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36462 | Allocation of resources without limits or throttling (uncontrolled resource consumption)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36462</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption refers to a software vulnerability where a attacker or system uses excessive resources, such as CPU, memory, or network bandwidth, without proper limitations or controls. This can cause a denial-of-service (DoS) attack or degrade the performance of the affected system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36461 | Direct access to memory pointers within the JS engine for modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36461</link><description>Within Zabbix, users have the ability to directly modify memory pointers in the JavaScript engine.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6562 | affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6562</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5. This is due display_errors being set to true . This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7382 | Linkify Text &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7382</link><description>The Linkify Text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7410 | My Custom CSS PHP &amp;amp; ADS &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7410</link><description>The My Custom CSS PHP &amp; ADS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /my-custom-css/vendor/mobiledetect/mobiledetectlib/export/exportToJSON.php file and and the file displaying/generating the full path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7412 | No Update Nag &amp;lt;= 1.4.12 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7412</link><description>The No Update Nag plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.12. This is due to the plugin allowing direct access to the bootstrap.php file which has display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7413 | Obfuscate Email &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7413</link><description>The Obfuscate Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.1. This is due to the plugin allowing direct access to the bootstrap.php file which has display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7414 | PDF Builder for WPForms &amp;lt;= 1.2.116 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7414</link><description>The PDF Builder for WPForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.116. This is due to the plugin allowing direct access to the composer-setup.php file which has display_errors on.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7416 | Reveal Template &amp;lt;= 3.7 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7416</link><description>The Reveal Template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.7. This is due to the plugin allowing direct access to the bootstrap.php file which has display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36460 | Front-end audit log shows passwords in plaintext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36460</link><description>The front-end audit log allows viewing of unprotected plaintext passwords, where the passwords are displayed in plain text.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22122 | AT(GSM) Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22122</link><description>Zabbix allows to configure SMS notifications. AT command injection occurs on "Zabbix Server" because there is no validation of "Number" field on Web nor on Zabbix server side. Attacker can run test of SMS providing specially crafted phone number and execute additional AT commands on modem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22121 | Zabbix Agent MSI Installer Allows Non-Admin User to Access Change Option via msiexec.exe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22121</link><description>A non-admin user can change or remove important features within the Zabbix Agent application, thus impacting the integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6133 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.6 - Reflected XSS in Customer Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6133</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 06:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6136 | WP eStore &amp;lt; 8.5.6 - Settings Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6136</link><description>The wp-cart-for-digital-products WordPress plugin before 8.5.6 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6158 | Category Posts Widget (Free &amp;lt; 4.9.17, Pro &amp;lt; 4.9.13) - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6158</link><description>The Category Posts Widget WordPress plugin before 4.9.17, term-and-category-based-posts-widget WordPress plugin before 4.9.13 does not validate and escape some of its "Category Posts" widget settings before outputting them back in a page/post where the Widget is embed, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7399 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory vulnerability in Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server version before 21.1050 allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7399</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory vulnerability in Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server version before 21.1050 allows attackers to write arbitrary file as system authority.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4359 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4359</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file reads in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 via the SVG widget and a lack of sufficient file validation in the render_svg function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4360 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title_tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4360</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'title_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 04:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0113 | NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, and MetroX-3 XCC contain a vulnerability in the web support, where an attacker can cause a CGI path traver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0113</link><description>NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, and MetroX-3 XCC contain a vulnerability in the web support, where an attacker can cause a CGI path traversal by a specially crafted URI. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 02:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0115 | NVIDIA CV-CUDA for Ubuntu 20.04, Ubuntu 22.04, and Jetpack contains a vulnerability in Python APIs where a user may cause an uncontrolled re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0115</link><description>NVIDIA CV-CUDA for Ubuntu 20.04, Ubuntu 22.04, and Jetpack contains a vulnerability in Python APIs where a user may cause an uncontrolled resource consumption issue by a long running CV-CUDA Python process. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service and data loss.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 02:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4350 | Stored XSS in RSS Displayer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4350</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 to 9.3.2 and below 8.5.18 are vulnerable to Stored XSS in RSS Displayer when user input is stored and later embedded into responses. A rogue administrator could inject malicious code into fields due to insufficient input validation. The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability a CVSS v3.1 score of 3.0 with a vector of  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator  and a CVSS v4 score of 2.1 with vector  CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:N/VC:L/VI:N/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/4.0#CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:N/VC:L/VI:N/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N  Thanks, m3dium for reporting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3279 | Improper Access Control in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3279</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in the mintplex-labs/anything-llm application, specifically within the import endpoint. This vulnerability allows an anonymous attacker, without an account in the application, to import their own database file, leading to the deletion or spoofing of the existing `anythingllm.db` file. By exploiting this vulnerability, attackers can serve malicious data to users or collect information about them. The vulnerability stems from the application's failure to properly restrict access to the data-import functionality, allowing unauthorized database manipulation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7512 | Stored XSS in Board instances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7512</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 through 9.3.2 are affected by a stored XSS vulnerability in Board instances. A rogue administrator could inject malicious code. The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability a CVSS 4.0 Score of 1.8 with vector: CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:N/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA: N. Versions below 9 are not affected.  Thanks, m3dium for reporting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37283 | Elastic Agent Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37283</link><description>An issue was discovered whereby Elastic Agent will leak secrets from the agent policy elastic-agent.yml only when the log level is configured to debug. By default the log level is set to info, where no leak occurs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7616 | Edimax IC-6220DC/IC-5150W ipcam_cgi cgiFormString command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7616</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Edimax IC-6220DC and IC-5150W up to 3.06. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgiFormString of the file ipcam_cgi. The manipulation of the argument host leads to command injection. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7614 | Tenda FH1206 qossetting fromqossetting stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7614</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 1.2.0.8(8155). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromqossetting of the file /goform/qossetting. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7615 | Tenda FH1206 fromSafeUrlFilter stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7615</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 1.2.0.8. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSafeClientFilter/fromSafeMacFilter/fromSafeUrlFilter. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5445 | Ecosystem Agent Insufficient Transport Layer Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5445</link><description>Ecosystem Agent version 4 &lt; 4.5.1.2597 and Ecosystem Agent version 5 &lt; 5.1.4.2473 did not properly validate SSL/TLS certificates, which could allow a malicious actor to perform a Man-in-the-Middle and intercept traffic between the agent and N-able servers from a privileged network position.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7613 | Tenda FH1206 GstDhcpSetSer fromGstDhcpSetSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1206 1.2.0.8(8155) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function fromGstDhcpSetSer of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. The manipulation of the argument dips leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7557 | Odh-dashboard: odh-model-controller: cross-model authentication bypass in openshift ai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7557</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenShift AI that allows for authentication bypass and privilege escalation across models within the same namespace. When deploying AI models, the UI provides the option to protect models with authentication. However, credentials from one model can be used to access other models and APIs within the same namespace. The exposed ServiceAccount tokens, visible in the UI, can be utilized with oc --token={token} to exploit the elevated view privileges associated with the ServiceAccount, leading to unauthorized access to additional resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7006 | Libtiff: null pointer dereference in tif_dirinfo.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7006</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in Libtiff via `tif_dirinfo.c`. This issue may allow an attacker to trigger memory allocation failures through certain means, such as restricting the heap space size or injecting faults, causing a segmentation fault. This can cause an application crash, eventually leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38200 | Microsoft Office Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38200</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38218 | Microsoft Edge (HTML-based) Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38218</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38219 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38219</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41481 | Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Mermaid component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41481</link><description>Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Mermaid component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41482 | Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the MathJax component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41482</link><description>Typora before 1.9.3 Markdown editor has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the MathJax component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43167 | Unbound: null pointer dereference in unbound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43167</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the ub_ctx_set_fwd function in Unbound. This issue could allow an attacker who can invoke specific sequences of API calls to cause a segmentation fault. When certain API functions such as ub_ctx_set_fwd and ub_ctx_resolvconf are called in a particular order, the program attempts to read from a NULL pointer, leading to a crash. This issue can result in a denial of service by causing the application to terminate unexpectedly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43168 | Unbound: heap-buffer-overflow in unbound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43168</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow flaw was found in the cfg_mark_ports function within Unbound's config_file.c, which can lead to memory corruption. This issue could allow an attacker with local access to provide specially crafted input, potentially causing the application to crash or allowing arbitrary code execution. This could result in a denial of service or unauthorized actions on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40473 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "manage_houses.php" in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40473</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "manage_houses.php" in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via "House_no" and "Description" parameter fields.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40474 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "edit-cate.php" in SourceCodester House Rental Management System v1.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40474</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "edit-cate.php" in SourceCodester House Rental Management System v1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7272 | FFmpeg swresample.c fill_audiodata heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7272</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FFmpeg up to 5.1.5. This affects the function fill_audiodata of the file /libswresample/swresample.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This issue was fixed in version 6.0 by 9903ba28c28ab18dc7b7b6fb8571cc8b5caae1a6 but a backport for 5.1 was forgotten. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 5.1.6 and 6.0 9903ba28c28ab18dc7b7b6fb8571cc8b5caae1a6 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40475 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /rental/payment_report.php, /rental/ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40475</link><description>SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control via /rental/payment_report.php, /rental/balance_report.php, /rental/invoices.php, /rental/tenants.php, and /rental/users.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40476 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. This could lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40476</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tricking the administrator into adding/modifying/deleting valid tenant data via a crafted HTML page, as demonstrated by a Delete Tenant action at the /rental/ajax.php?action=delete_tenant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40481 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/view-enquiry.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40481</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/admin/view-enquiry.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the Contact Us page "message" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 20:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40477 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/oahms/admin/forgot-password.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40477</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/oahms/admin/forgot-password.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "email" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42001 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Forced Browsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42001</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability affecting Vonets





 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and wifi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
bypass authentication via a specially crafted direct request when 
another user has an active session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37023 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37023</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities affecting Vonets 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software 
versions 3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an authenticated remote attacker 
to execute arbitrary OS commands via various endpoint parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39791 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39791</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities affecting Vonets



 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and wifi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39815 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Improper Check or Handling of Exceptional Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39815</link><description>Improper check or handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability 
affecting Vonets

 

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enable an unauthenticated 
remote attacker to cause a denial of service. A specially-crafted 
HTTP request to pre-authentication resources can crash the service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29082 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29082</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability affecting Vonets

 industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 
and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to bypass 
authentication and factory reset the device via unprotected goform 
endpoints.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40482 | An Unrestricted file upload vulnerability was found in "/Membership/edit_member.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40482</link><description>An Unrestricted file upload vulnerability was found in "/Membership/edit_member.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40484 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/oahms/search.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40484</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/oahms/search.php" in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the "searchdata" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40486 | A SQL injection vulnerability in "/index.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL comm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40486</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in "/index.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and bypass Login via the email or password Login parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41936 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41936</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability affecting Vonets industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 3.3.23.6.9 
and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to read arbitrary 
files and bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40488 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in the Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40488</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was found in the Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0. This could lead to an attacker tricking the administrator into deleting valid member data via a crafted HTML page, as demonstrated by a Delete Member action at the /delete_members.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40487 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/view_type.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40487</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in "/view_type.php" of Kashipara Live Membership System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via membershipType parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40261 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR17, 4.0.0 SR07, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR04, and 4.3.0 SR03 fails to validate file at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40261</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR17, 4.0.0 SR07, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR04, and 4.3.0 SR03 fails to validate file attributes during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28865 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR15, 4.0.0 SR05, 4.1.0 SR03, and 4.2.0 SR02 fails to validate the directory conte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28865</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR15, 4.0.0 SR05, 4.1.0 SR03, and 4.2.0 SR02 fails to validate the directory contents of certain directories (e.g., ensuring the expected hash sum) during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33206 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR16, 4.0.0 SR06, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR03, and 4.3.0 SR01 fails to validate symlink...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33206</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR16, 4.0.0 SR06, 4.1.0 SR04, 4.2.0 SR03, and 4.3.0 SR01 fails to validate symlinks during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37382 | An issue discovered in import host feature in Ab Initio Metadata Hub and Authorization Gateway before 4.3.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37382</link><description>An issue discovered in import host feature in Ab Initio Metadata Hub and Authorization Gateway before 4.3.1.1 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted modification of server configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41161 | Vonets WiFi Bridges Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41161</link><description>Use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability affecting Vonets industrial wifi bridge relays and WiFi bridge repeaters, software versions 
3.3.23.6.9 and prior, enables an unauthenticated remote attacker to 
bypass authentication using hard-coded administrator credentials. These 
accounts cannot be disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24062 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR12, 4.0.0 SR04, 4.1.0 SR02, and 4.2.0 SR01 fails to validate the directory struc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24062</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR12, 4.0.0 SR04, 4.1.0 SR02, and 4.2.0 SR01 fails to validate the directory structure of the root file system during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24063 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR10 fails to validate /etc/mtab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24063</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR10 fails to validate /etc/mtab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24064 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR4 fails to validate /etc/initab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24064</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite (VSS) before 3.3.0 SR4 fails to validate /etc/initab during the Pre-Boot Authorization (PBA) process. This can be exploited by a physical attacker who is able to manipulate the contents of the system's hard disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39287 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Exposure of Sensitive Information To An Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39287</link><description>Dorsett Controls Central Server update server has potential information 
leaks with an unprotected file that contains passwords and API keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42408 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42408</link><description>The InfoScan client download page can be intercepted with a proxy, to 
expose filenames located on the system, which could lead to additional 
information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0104 | NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in the LDAP AAA component, where a user can cause imprope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0104</link><description>NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in the LDAP AAA component, where a user can cause improper access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure, data tampering, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42493 | Dorsett Controls InfoScan Exposure of Sensitive Information To An Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42493</link><description>Dorsett Controls InfoScan is vulnerable due to a leak of possible 
sensitive information through the response headers and the rendered 
JavaScript prior to user login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0101 | NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in ipfilter, where improper ipfilter definitions could en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0101</link><description>NVIDIA Mellanox OS, ONYX, Skyway, MetroX-2 and MetroX-3 XC contain a vulnerability in ipfilter, where improper ipfilter definitions could enable an attacker to cause a failure by attacking the switch. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0107 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0107</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability in the user mode layer, where an unprivileged regular user can cause an out-of-bounds read. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42366 | VR Overlay RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42366</link><description>VRCX is an assistant/companion application for VRChat. In versions prior to 2024.03.23, a CefSharp browser with over-permission and cross-site scripting via overlay notification can be combined to result in remote command execution. These vulnerabilities are patched in VRCX 2023.12.24. In addition to the patch, VRCX maintainers worked with the VRC team and blocked the older version of VRCX on the VRC's API side. Users who use the older version of VRCX must update their installation to continue using VRCX.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7394 | Stored XSS in getAttributeSetName()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7394</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9 through 9.3.2 and below 8.5.18 are vulnerable to Stored XSS in getAttributeSetName().  A rogue administrator could inject malicious code. The Concrete CMS team gave this a CVSS v3.1 rank of 2 with vector  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator  and a CVSS v4.0 rank of 1.8 with vector  CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/4.0#CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N . Thanks, m3dium for reporting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42365 | Asterisk allows `Write=originate` as sufficient permissions for code execution / `System()` dialplan</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42365</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange (PBX) and telephony toolkit. Prior to asterisk versions 18.24.2, 20.9.2, and 21.4.2 and certified-asterisk versions 18.9-cert11 and 20.7-cert2, an AMI user with `write=originate` may change all configuration files in the `/etc/asterisk/` directory. This occurs because they are able to curl remote files and write them to disk, but are also able to append to existing files using the `FILE` function inside the `SET` application. This issue may result in privilege escalation, remote code execution and/or blind server-side request forgery with arbitrary protocol. Asterisk versions 18.24.2, 20.9.2, and 21.4.2 and certified-asterisk versions 18.9-cert11 and 20.7-cert2 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0108 | NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in NvGPU where error handling paths in GPU MMU mapping code fail to clean up a failed mapping a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0108</link><description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in NvGPU where error handling paths in GPU MMU mapping code fail to clean up a failed mapping attempt. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, code execution, and escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0102 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm, where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read issue by decei...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0102</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in nvdisasm, where an attacker can cause an out-of-bounds read issue by deceiving a user into reading a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41238 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41238</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /smsa/student_login.php in Kashipara Responsive School Management System v1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the "username" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7477 | Avaya Aura System Manager SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7477</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was found which could allow a command line interface (CLI) user with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary queries against the Avaya Aura System Manager database. 

Affected versions include 10.1.x.x and 10.2.x.x. Versions prior to 10.1 are end of manufacturer support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7480 | Improper access control in Avaya Aura System Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7480</link><description>An Improper access control vulnerability was found in Avaya Aura System Manager which could allow a command-line interface (CLI) user with administrative privileges to read arbitrary files on the system. Affected versions include 10.1.x.x and 10.2.x.x. Versions prior to 10.1 are end of manufacturer support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42357 | Shopware vulnerable to blind SQL-injection in DAL aggregations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42357</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the Shopware application API contains a search functionality which enables users to search through information stored within their Shopware instance. The searches performed by this function can be aggregated using the parameters in the `aggregations` object. The `name` field in this `aggregations` object is vulnerable SQL-injection and can be exploited using SQL parameters. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, 6.3, and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7490 | Remote Code Execution in Advanced Software Framework DHCP server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7490</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Microchip Techology Advanced Software Framework example DHCP server can cause remote code execution through a buffer overflow.
 This vulnerability is associated with program files tinydhcpserver.C and program routines lwip_dhcp_find_option.

This issue affects Advanced Software Framework: through 3.52.0.2574.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42355 | Shopware vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in Twig using deprecation silence tag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42355</link><description>Shopware, an open ecommerce platform, has a new Twig Tag `sw_silent_feature_call` which silences deprecation messages while triggered in this tag. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, it accepts as parameter a string the feature flag name to silence, but this parameter is not escaped properly and allows execution of code. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.2, 6.3,  and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42356 | Shopware vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in Twig using Context functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42356</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the `context` variable is injected into almost any Twig Template and allows to access to current language, currency information. The context object allows also to switch for a short time the scope of the Context as a helper with a callable function. The function can be called also from Twig and as the second parameter allows any callable, it's possible to call from Twig any statically callable PHP function/method. It's not possible as customer to provide any Twig code, the attacker would require access to Administration to exploit it using Mail templates or using App Scripts. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, 6.3 and 6.4 corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42354 | Shopware vulnerable to Improper Access Control with ManyToMany associations in store-api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42354</link><description>Shopware is an open commerce platform. The store-API works with regular entities and not expose all fields for the public API; fields need to be marked as ApiAware in the EntityDefinition. So only ApiAware fields of the EntityDefinition will be encoded to the final JSON. Prior to versions 6.6.5.1 and 6.5.8.13, the processing of the Criteria did not considered ManyToMany associations and so they were not considered properly and the protections didn't get used. This issue cannot be reproduced with the default entities by Shopware, but can be triggered with extensions. Update to Shopware 6.6.5.1 or 6.5.8.13 to receive a patch. For older versions of 6.2, 6.3,  and 6.4, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41942 | JupyterHub has a privilege escalation vulnerability with the `admin:users` scope</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41942</link><description>JupyterHub is software that allows one to create a multi-user server for Jupyter notebooks. Prior to versions 4.1.6 and 5.1.0, if a user is granted the `admin:users` scope, they may escalate their own privileges by making themselves a full admin user. The impact is relatively small in that `admin:users` is already an extremely privileged scope only granted to trusted users.
In effect, `admin:users` is equivalent to `admin=True`, which is not intended. Note that the change here only prevents escalation to the built-in JupyterHub admin role that has unrestricted permissions. It does not prevent users with e.g. `groups` permissions from granting themselves or other users permissions via group membership, which is intentional. Versions 4.1.6 and 5.1.0 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7348 | PostgreSQL relation replacement during pg_dump executes arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7348</link><description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition in pg_dump in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the user running pg_dump, which is often a superuser. The attack involves replacing another relation type with a view or foreign table. The attack requires waiting for pg_dump to start, but winning the race condition is trivial if the attacker retains an open transaction. Versions before PostgreSQL 16.4, 15.8, 14.13, 13.16, and 12.20 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3659 | Command injection in KAON AR2140 routers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3659</link><description>Firmware in KAON AR2140 routers prior to version 4.2.16 is vulnerable to a shell command injection via sending a crafted request to one of the endpoints.
In order to exploit this vulnerability, one has to have access to the administrative portal of the router.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2800 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2800</link><description>ReDoS flaw in RefMatcher when matching branch names using wildcards in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions from 11.3 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2 allows denial of service via Regex backtracking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3035 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3035</link><description>A permission check vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.12 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2  allowed for LFS tokens to read and write to the user owned repositories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3114 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3114</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 11.10 prior to 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2, with the processing logic for parsing invalid commits can lead to a regular expression DoS attack on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3958 | Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3958</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. An issue was found that allows someone  to abuse a discrepancy between the Web application display and the git command line interface to social engineer victims into cloning non-trusted code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4207 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4207</link><description>A cross-site scripting issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions starting from 5.1 prior 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. When viewing an XML file in a repository in raw mode, it can be made to render as HTML if viewed under specific circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5423 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5423</link><description>Multiple Denial of Service (DoS) conditions has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 1.0 prior to 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2 which allowed an attacker to cause resource exhaustion via banzai pipeline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7554 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7554</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 13.9 before 17.0.6, all versions starting from 17.1 before 17.1.4, all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.2.2. Under certain conditions, access tokens may have been logged when an API request was made in a specific manner.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7610 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7610</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 15.9 before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. It is possible for an attacker to cause catastrophic backtracking while parsing results from Elasticsearch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4210 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4210</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) condition has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting with 12.6 before 17.0.6, 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and 17.2 prior to 17.2.2. It is possible for an attacker to cause a denial of service using crafted adoc files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4784 | Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4784</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE starting from version 16.7 before 17.0.6, version 17.1 before 17.1.4 and 17.2 before 17.2.2 that allowed bypassing the password re-entry requirement to approve a policy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6329 | Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6329</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.16 prior to 17.0.6, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.4, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.2, which causes the web interface to fail to render the diff correctly when the path is encoded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42037 | Vulnerability of uncaught exceptions in the Graphics module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42037</link><description>Vulnerability of uncaught exceptions in the Graphics module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42038 | Vulnerability of PIN enhancement failures in the screen lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42038</link><description>Vulnerability of PIN enhancement failures in the screen lock module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42033 | Access control vulnerability in the security verification module
mpact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42033</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the security verification module
mpact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42034 | LaunchAnywhere vulnerability in the account module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42034</link><description>LaunchAnywhere vulnerability in the account module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42035 | Permission control vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact:Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect functionality ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42035</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the App Multiplier module
Impact:Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect functionality and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42036 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Notepad module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42036</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Notepad module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42032 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42032</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Contacts module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42031 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42031</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the Settings module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42251 | mm: page_ref: remove folio_try_get_rcu()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42251</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: page_ref: remove folio_try_get_rcu()

The below bug was reported on a non-SMP kernel:

[  275.267158][ T4335] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  275.267949][ T4335] kernel BUG at include/linux/page_ref.h:275!
[  275.268526][ T4335] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] KASAN PTI
[  275.269001][ T4335] CPU: 0 PID: 4335 Comm: trinity-c3 Not tainted 6.7.0-rc4-00061-gefa7df3e3bb5 #1
[  275.269787][ T4335] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.2-debian-1.16.2-1 04/01/2014
[  275.270679][ T4335] RIP: 0010:try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[  275.272813][ T4335] RSP: 0018:ffffc90005dcf650 EFLAGS: 00010202
[  275.273346][ T4335] RAX: 0000000000000246 RBX: ffffea00066e0000 RCX: 0000000000000000
[  275.274032][ T4335] RDX: fffff94000cdc007 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffffea00066e0034
[  275.274719][ T4335] RBP: ffffea00066e0000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: fffff94000cdc006
[  275.275404][ T4335] R10: ffffea00066e0037 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000136
[  275.276106][ T4335] R13: ffffea00066e0034 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffffea00066e0008
[  275.276790][ T4335] FS:  00007fa2f9b61740(0000) GS:ffffffff89d0d000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  275.277570][ T4335] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  275.278143][ T4335] CR2: 00007fa2f6c00000 CR3: 0000000134b04000 CR4: 00000000000406f0
[  275.278833][ T4335] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[  275.279521][ T4335] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[  275.280201][ T4335] Call Trace:
[  275.280499][ T4335]  
[ 275.280751][ T4335] ? die (arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:421 arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:434 arch/x86/kernel/dumpstack.c:447)
[ 275.281087][ T4335] ? do_trap (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:112 arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:153)
[ 275.281463][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.281884][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.282300][ T4335] ? do_error_trap (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:174)
[ 275.282711][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.283129][ T4335] ? handle_invalid_op (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:212)
[ 275.283561][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.283990][ T4335] ? exc_invalid_op (arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:264)
[ 275.284415][ T4335] ? asm_exc_invalid_op (arch/x86/include/asm/idtentry.h:568)
[ 275.284859][ T4335] ? try_get_folio (include/linux/page_ref.h:275 (discriminator 3) mm/gup.c:79 (discriminator 3))
[ 275.285278][ T4335] try_grab_folio (mm/gup.c:148)
[ 275.285684][ T4335] __get_user_pages (mm/gup.c:1297 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.286111][ T4335] ? __pfx___get_user_pages (mm/gup.c:1188)
[ 275.286579][ T4335] ? __pfx_validate_chain (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:3825)
[ 275.287034][ T4335] ? mark_lock (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:4656 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.287416][ T4335] __gup_longterm_locked (mm/gup.c:1509 mm/gup.c:2209)
[ 275.288192][ T4335] ? __pfx___gup_longterm_locked (mm/gup.c:2204)
[ 275.288697][ T4335] ? __pfx_lock_acquire (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5722)
[ 275.289135][ T4335] ? __pfx___might_resched (kernel/sched/core.c:10106)
[ 275.289595][ T4335] pin_user_pages_remote (mm/gup.c:3350)
[ 275.290041][ T4335] ? __pfx_pin_user_pages_remote (mm/gup.c:3350)
[ 275.290545][ T4335] ? find_held_lock (kernel/locking/lockdep.c:5244 (discriminator 1))
[ 275.290961][ T4335] ? mm_access (kernel/fork.c:1573)
[ 275.291353][ T4335] process_vm_rw_single_vec+0x142/0x360
[ 275.291900][ T4335] ? __pfx_process_vm_rw_single_vec+0x10/0x10
[ 275.292471][ T4335] ? mm_access (kernel/fork.c:1573)
[ 275.292859][ T4335] process_vm_rw_core+0x272/0x4e0
[ 275.293384][ T4335] ? hlock_class (a
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42252 | closures: Change BUG_ON() to WARN_ON()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42252</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

closures: Change BUG_ON() to WARN_ON()

If a BUG_ON() can be hit in the wild, it shouldn't be a BUG_ON()

For reference, this has popped up once in the CI, and we'll need more
info to debug it:

03240 ------------[ cut here ]------------
03240 kernel BUG at lib/closure.c:21!
03240 kernel BUG at lib/closure.c:21!
03240 Internal error: Oops - BUG: 00000000f2000800 [#1] SMP
03240 Modules linked in:
03240 CPU: 15 PID: 40534 Comm: kworker/u80:1 Not tainted 6.10.0-rc4-ktest-ga56da69799bd #25570
03240 Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
03240 Workqueue: btree_update btree_interior_update_work
03240 pstate: 00001005 (nzcv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT +SSBS BTYPE=--)
03240 pc : closure_put+0x224/0x2a0
03240 lr : closure_put+0x24/0x2a0
03240 sp : ffff0000d12071c0
03240 x29: ffff0000d12071c0 x28: dfff800000000000 x27: ffff0000d1207360
03240 x26: 0000000000000040 x25: 0000000000000040 x24: 0000000000000040
03240 x23: ffff0000c1f20180 x22: 0000000000000000 x21: ffff0000c1f20168
03240 x20: 0000000040000000 x19: ffff0000c1f20140 x18: 0000000000000001
03240 x17: 0000000000003aa0 x16: 0000000000003ad0 x15: 1fffe0001c326974
03240 x14: 0000000000000a1e x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 1fffe000183e402d
03240 x11: ffff6000183e402d x10: dfff800000000000 x9 : ffff6000183e402e
03240 x8 : 0000000000000001 x7 : 00009fffe7c1bfd3 x6 : ffff0000c1f2016b
03240 x5 : ffff0000c1f20168 x4 : ffff6000183e402e x3 : ffff800081391954
03240 x2 : 0000000000000001 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : 00000000a8000000
03240 Call trace:
03240  closure_put+0x224/0x2a0
03240  bch2_check_for_deadlock+0x910/0x1028
03240  bch2_six_check_for_deadlock+0x1c/0x30
03240  six_lock_slowpath.isra.0+0x29c/0xed0
03240  six_lock_ip_waiter+0xa8/0xf8
03240  __bch2_btree_node_lock_write+0x14c/0x298
03240  bch2_trans_lock_write+0x6d4/0xb10
03240  __bch2_trans_commit+0x135c/0x5520
03240  btree_interior_update_work+0x1248/0x1c10
03240  process_scheduled_works+0x53c/0xd90
03240  worker_thread+0x370/0x8c8
03240  kthread+0x258/0x2e8
03240  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
03240 Code: aa1303e0 d63f0020 a94363f7 17ffff8c (d4210000)
03240 ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
03240 Kernel panic - not syncing: Oops - BUG: Fatal exception
03240 SMP: stopping secondary CPUs
03241 SMP: failed to stop secondary CPUs 13,15
03241 Kernel Offset: disabled
03241 CPU features: 0x00,00000003,80000008,4240500b
03241 Memory Limit: none
03241 ---[ end Kernel panic - not syncing: Oops - BUG: Fatal exception ]---
03246 ========= FAILED TIMEOUT copygc_torture_no_checksum in 7200s</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42253 | gpio: pca953x: fix pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42253</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: pca953x: fix pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock race

Ensure that `i2c_lock' is held when setting interrupt latch and mask in
pca953x_irq_bus_sync_unlock() in order to avoid races.

The other (non-probe) call site pca953x_gpio_set_multiple() ensures the
lock is held before calling pca953x_write_regs().

The problem occurred when a request raced against irq_bus_sync_unlock()
approximately once per thousand reboots on an i.MX8MP based system.

 * Normal case

   0-0022: write register AI|3a {03,02,00,00,01} Input latch P0
   0-0022: write register AI|49 {fc,fd,ff,ff,fe} Interrupt mask P0
   0-0022: write register AI|08 {ff,00,00,00,00} Output P3
   0-0022: write register AI|12 {fc,00,00,00,00} Config P3

 * Race case

   0-0022: write register AI|08 {ff,00,00,00,00} Output P3
   0-0022: write register AI|08 {03,02,00,00,01} *** Wrong register ***
   0-0022: write register AI|12 {fc,00,00,00,00} Config P3
   0-0022: write register AI|49 {fc,fd,ff,ff,fe} Interrupt mask P0</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42254 | io_uring: fix error pbuf checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42254</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: fix error pbuf checking

Syz reports a problem, which boils down to NULL vs IS_ERR inconsistent
error handling in io_alloc_pbuf_ring().

KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000000-0x0000000000000007]
RIP: 0010:__io_remove_buffers+0xac/0x700 io_uring/kbuf.c:341
Call Trace:
 
 io_put_bl io_uring/kbuf.c:378 [inline]
 io_destroy_buffers+0x14e/0x490 io_uring/kbuf.c:392
 io_ring_ctx_free+0xa00/0x1070 io_uring/io_uring.c:2613
 io_ring_exit_work+0x80f/0x8a0 io_uring/io_uring.c:2844
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3231 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0xa2c/0x1830 kernel/workqueue.c:3312
 worker_thread+0x86d/0xd40 kernel/workqueue.c:3390
 kthread+0x2f0/0x390 kernel/kthread.c:389
 ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:244</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42255 | tpm: Use auth only after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42255</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tpm: Use auth only after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response()

Dereference auth after NULL check in tpm_buf_check_hmac_response().
Otherwise, unless tpm2_sessions_init() was called, a call can cause NULL
dereference, when TCG_TPM2_HMAC is enabled.

[jarkko: adjusted the commit message.]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42256 | cifs: Fix server re-repick on subrequest retry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42256</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cifs: Fix server re-repick on subrequest retry

When a subrequest is marked for needing retry, netfs will call
cifs_prepare_write() which will make cifs repick the server for the op
before renegotiating credits; it then calls cifs_issue_write() which
invokes smb2_async_writev() - which re-repicks the server.

If a different server is then selected, this causes the increment of
server-&gt;in_flight to happen against one record and the decrement to happen
against another, leading to misaccounting.

Fix this by just removing the repick code in smb2_async_writev().  As this
is only called from netfslib-driven code, cifs_prepare_write() should
always have been called first, and so server should never be NULL and the
preparatory step is repeated in the event that we do a retry.

The problem manifests as a warning looking something like:

 WARNING: CPU: 4 PID: 72896 at fs/smb/client/smb2ops.c:97 smb2_add_credits+0x3f0/0x9e0 [cifs]
 ...
 RIP: 0010:smb2_add_credits+0x3f0/0x9e0 [cifs]
 ...
  smb2_writev_callback+0x334/0x560 [cifs]
  cifs_demultiplex_thread+0x77a/0x11b0 [cifs]
  kthread+0x187/0x1d0
  ret_from_fork+0x34/0x60
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30

Which may be triggered by a number of different xfstests running against an
Azure server in multichannel mode.  generic/249 seems the most repeatable,
but generic/215, generic/249 and generic/308 may also show it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42257 | ext4: use memtostr_pad() for s_volume_name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42257</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: use memtostr_pad() for s_volume_name

As with the other strings in struct ext4_super_block, s_volume_name is
not NUL terminated. The other strings were marked in commit 072ebb3bffe6
("ext4: add nonstring annotations to ext4.h"). Using strscpy() isn't
the right replacement for strncpy(); it should use memtostr_pad()
instead.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42030 | Access permission verification vulnerability in the content sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42030</link><description>Access permission verification vulnerability in the content sharing pop-up module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7265 | Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7265</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22069 | Permission and Access Control Vulnerability in ZXV10 XT802/ET301</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22069</link><description>There is a permission and access control vulnerability of ZTE's ZXV10 XT802/ET301 product.Attackers with common permissions can log in the terminal web and change the password of the administrator illegally by intercepting requests to change the passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6481 | Search Filter Pro &amp;lt; 2.5.18 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6481</link><description>The Search &amp; Filter Pro WordPress plugin before 2.5.18 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 06:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6884 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP &amp;lt; 3.2.39 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6884</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP  WordPress plugin before 3.2.39 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 06:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5226 | Fuse Social Floating Sidebar &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5226</link><description>The Fuse Social Floating Sidebar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the file upload functionality in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.10 due to insufficient validation of SVG files. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6824 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.38 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Content Deletion and Arbitrary Title Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6824</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'check_temp_validity' and 'update_template_title' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary content and update post and page titles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7150 | Slider by 10Web – Responsive Image Slider &amp;lt;= 1.2.57 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7150</link><description>The Slider by 10Web – Responsive Image Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.57 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7548 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.9.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7548</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.9.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5668 | Lightbox &amp;amp; Modal Popup WordPress Plugin – FooBox &amp;lt;= 2.7.28 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Data Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5668</link><description>The Lightbox &amp; Modal Popup WordPress Plugin – FooBox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML data attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6869 | Falang multilanguage for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.52 - Missing Authorization to Translation Update and Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6869</link><description>The Falang multilanguage for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.52. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update and delete translations and expose the administrator email address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6987 | Orchid Store &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 -  Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6987</link><description>The Orchid Store theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'orchid_store_activate_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate the Addonify Floating Cart For WooCommerce plugin if it is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6254 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6254</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on form submissions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit forms intended for public use as another user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. On sites where unfiltered_html is enabled, this can lead to the admin unknowingly adding a Stored Cross-Site Scripting payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6552 | Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6552</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to the plugin utilizing Symfony and leaving display_errors on within test files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7350 | Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress 1.1.6  - 1.1.7 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7350</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Online Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions 1.1.6 to 1.1.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to logging them in when completing a booking. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as registered users, including administrators, if they have access to that user's email.  This is only exploitable when the 'Auto login user after successful booking' setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7492 | MainWP Child Reports &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7492</link><description>The MainWP Child Reports plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the network_options_action() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options that can be leveraged for privilege escalation via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This is only exploitable on multisite instances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21302 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21302</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38202 | Windows Update Stack Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38202</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7486 | MultiPurpose &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7486</link><description>The MultiPurpose theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 via deserialization of untrusted input through the 'wpeden_post_meta' post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7560 | News Flash &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7560</link><description>The News Flash theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the newsflash_post_meta meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7561 | The Next &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7561</link><description>The The Next theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the wpeden_post_meta post meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>