<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 06:28:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11560 | Team Members Showcase &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11560</link><description>The Team Members Showcase WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to reflected cross-site scripting, which could be used against high-privilege users such as admins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 06:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12087 | Wishlist and Save for later for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.22 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Wishlist Item Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12087</link><description>The Wishlist and Save for later for Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.22 via the 'awwlm_remove_added_wishlist_page' AJAX action due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete wishlist items from other user's wishlists.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 04:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12833 | GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory &amp;lt;= 2.8.139 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary Image Attachment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12833</link><description>The GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.139 via the 'post_attachment_upload' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to attach arbitrary image files to arbitrary places.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 04:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12901 | Asgaros Forum &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Subscription Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12901</link><description>The Asgaros Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the set_subscription_level() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the subscription settings of authenticated users via a forged request granted they can trick a logged-in user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 04:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54983 | Health check port on ZCC allows tunnel bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54983</link><description>A health check port on Zscaler Client Connector on Windows, versions 4.6 &lt;  4.6.0.216 and 4.7 &lt; 4.7.0.47, which under specific circumstances was not released after use, allowed traffic to potentially bypass ZCC forwarding controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 03:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40110 | drm/vmwgfx: Fix a null-ptr access in the cursor snooper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40110</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Fix a null-ptr access in the cursor snooper

Check that the resource which is converted to a surface exists before
trying to use the cursor snooper on it.

vmw_cmd_res_check allows explicit invalid (SVGA3D_INVALID_ID) identifiers
because some svga commands accept SVGA3D_INVALID_ID to mean "no surface",
unfortunately functions that accept the actual surfaces as objects might
(and in case of the cursor snooper, do not) be able to handle null
objects. Make sure that we validate not only the identifier (via the
vmw_cmd_res_check) but also check that the actual resource exists before
trying to do something with it.

Fixes unchecked null-ptr reference in the snooping code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 02:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40111 | drm/vmwgfx: Fix Use-after-free in validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40111</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Fix Use-after-free in validation

Nodes stored in the validation duplicates hashtable come from an arena
allocator that is cleared at the end of vmw_execbuf_process. All nodes
are expected to be cleared in vmw_validation_drop_ht but this node escaped
because its resource was destroyed prematurely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 02:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43205 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.4, tvOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, iOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43205</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.4, tvOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4. An app may be able to bypass ASLR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61833 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61833</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.5 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61834 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61834</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61835 | Substance3D - Stager | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61835</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.5 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64531 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64531</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32008 | A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32008</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to a local privilege escalation due to an exposed debug interface on the localhost. This allows any local user to gain code execution as administrative application user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32009 | A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to a lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32009</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to a local privilege escalation due to wrongly set permissions to a binary which allows any local attacker to gain administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32010 | A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to extr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32010</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to extraction of database credentials via a world-readable credential file. This allows an attacker to connect to the database as privileged application user and to run system commands via the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32011 | A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to run ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32011</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to run arbitrary commands via the user interface. This user interface can be used via the network and allows the execution of commands as administrative application user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32014 | A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to alte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32014</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Spectrum Power 4 (All versions &lt; V4.70 SP12 Update 2). The affected application is vulnerable to alter the local database which contains the application credentials. This allows an attacker to gain administrative application privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40744 | A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 11). Affected applications do not properly validate c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40744</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 11). Affected applications do not properly validate client certificates to connect to License Service endpoint. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to perform man in the middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40760 | A vulnerability has been identified in Altair Grid Engine (All versions &lt; V2026.0.0). Affected products do not properly handle error message...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40760</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Altair Grid Engine (All versions &lt; V2026.0.0). Affected products do not properly handle error messages and discloses sensitive password hash information when processing user authentication requests.
This could allow a local attacker to extract password hashes for privileged accounts, which can then be subjected to offline brute-force attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40763 | A vulnerability has been identified in Altair Grid Engine (All versions &lt; V2026.0.0). Affected products do not properly validate environment...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40763</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Altair Grid Engine (All versions &lt; V2026.0.0). Affected products do not properly validate environment variables when loading shared libraries, allowing path hijacking through malicious library substitution.
This could allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code with superuser privileges by manipulating the environment variable and placing a malicious library in the controlled path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40815 | A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40815</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCE (6ED1052-1FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCEo (6ED1052-2FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CE (6ED1052-1CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CEo (6ED1052-2CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCE (6ED1052-1HB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCEo (6ED1052-2HB08-0BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCE (6AG1052-1MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6AG1052-2MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCE (6AG1052-1FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCEo (6AG1052-2FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CE (6AG1052-1CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CEo (6AG1052-2CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCE (6AG1052-1HB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCEo (6AG1052-2HB08-7BA2) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly validate the structure of TCP packets in several methods. This could allow an attacker to cause buffer overflows, get control over the instruction counter and run custom code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40816 | A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40816</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCE (6ED1052-1FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCEo (6ED1052-2FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CE (6ED1052-1CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CEo (6ED1052-2CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCE (6ED1052-1HB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCEo (6ED1052-2HB08-0BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCE (6AG1052-1MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6AG1052-2MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCE (6AG1052-1FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCEo (6AG1052-2FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CE (6AG1052-1CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CEo (6AG1052-2CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCE (6AG1052-1HB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCEo (6AG1052-2HB08-7BA2) (All versions). Affected devices do not conduct certain validations when interacting with them. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to manipulate the devices IP address, which means the device would not be reachable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40817 | A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40817</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in LOGO! 12/24RCE (6ED1052-1MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6ED1052-2MD08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCE (6ED1052-1FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 230RCEo (6ED1052-2FB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CE (6ED1052-1CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24CEo (6ED1052-2CC08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCE (6ED1052-1HB08-0BA2) (All versions), LOGO! 24RCEo (6ED1052-2HB08-0BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCE (6AG1052-1MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 12/24RCEo (6AG1052-2MD08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCE (6AG1052-1FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 230RCEo (6AG1052-2FB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CE (6AG1052-1CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24CEo (6AG1052-2CC08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCE (6AG1052-1HB08-7BA2) (All versions), SIPLUS LOGO! 24RCEo (6AG1052-2HB08-7BA2) (All versions). Affected devices do not conduct certain validations when interacting with them. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to change time of the device, which means the device could behave differently.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40827 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens Software Center (All versions &lt; V3.5), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 10). T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40827</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens Software Center (All versions &lt; V3.5), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 10). The affected application is vulnerable to DLL hijacking. This could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code via placing a crafted DLL file on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3717 | Incorrect oauth passthrough in Grafana Snowflake Datasource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3717</link><description>When using the Grafana Snowflake Datasource Plugin,
if Oauth passthrough is enabled on the datasource, and multiple users are using the same datasource at the same time on a single Grafana instance, it  could result in 

the wrong user identifier being used, and information for which the viewer is not authorized being returned. 

This issue affects Grafana Snowflake Datasource Plugin: from 1.5.0 before 1.14.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41116 | Incorrect oauth passthrough in Grafana Snowflake Datasource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41116</link><description>When using the Grafana Databricks Datasource Plugin,
if Oauth passthrough is enabled on the datasource, and multiple users are using the same datasource at the same time on a single Grafana instance, it  could result in 

the wrong user identifier being used, and information for which the viewer is not authorized being returned. 

This issue affects Grafana Databricks Datasource Plugin: from 1.12.1 before 1.12.0</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12748 | Libvirt: denial of service in xml parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12748</link><description>A flaw was discovered in libvirt in the XML file processing. More specifically, the parsing of user provided XML files was performed before the ACL checks. A malicious user with limited permissions could exploit this flaw by submitting a specially crafted XML file, causing libvirt to allocate too much memory on the host. The excessive memory consumption could lead to a libvirt process crash on the host, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61837 | Format Plugins | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61837</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61838 | Format Plugins | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61838</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61839 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61839</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61840 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61840</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61841 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61841</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to access sensitive memory information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61842 | Format Plugins | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61842</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61843 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61843</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61844 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61844</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61845 | Format Plugins | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61845</link><description>Format Plugins versions 1.1.1 and earlier are affected by an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability that could lead to memory exposure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information stored in memory. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61830 | Adobe Pass | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61830</link><description>Adobe Pass versions 3.7.3 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read and write access. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must install a malicious SDK.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30398 | Nuance PowerScribe 360 Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30398</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47179 | Configuration Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47179</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59240 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59240</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59499 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59499</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59504 | Azure Monitor Agent Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59504</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59505 | Windows Smart Card Reader Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59505</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59506 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59506</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59507 | Windows Speech Runtime Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59507</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59508 | Windows Speech Recognition Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59508</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59509 | Windows Speech Recognition Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59509</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59510 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59510</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59511 | Windows WLAN Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59511</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59512 | Customer Experience Improvement Program (CEIP) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59512</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59513 | Windows Bluetooth RFCOM Protocol Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59513</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59514 | Microsoft Streaming Service Proxy Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59514</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59515 | Windows Broadcast DVR User Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59515</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60703 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60703</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60704 | Windows Kerberos Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60704</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60705 | Windows Client-Side Caching Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60705</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60706 | Windows Hyper-V Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60706</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60707 | Multimedia Class Scheduler Service (MMCSS) Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60707</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60708 | Storvsp.sys Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60708</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60709 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60709</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60710 | Host Process for Windows Tasks Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60710</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60713 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60713</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60714 | Windows OLE Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60714</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60715 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60715</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60716 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60716</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60717 | Windows Broadcast DVR User Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60717</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60718 | Windows Administrator Protection Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60718</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60719 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60719</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60720 | Windows Transport Driver Interface (TDI) Translation Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60720</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60721 | Windows Administrator Protection Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60721</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60722 | Microsoft OneDrive for Android Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60722</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60723 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60723</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60724 | GDI+ Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60724</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60726 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60726</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60727 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60727</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60728 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60728</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62199 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62199</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62200 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62200</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62201 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62201</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62202 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62202</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62203 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62203</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62204 | Microsoft SharePoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62204</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62205 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62205</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62206 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (On-Premises) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62206</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62208 | Windows License Manager Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62208</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62209 | Windows License Manager Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62209</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62210 | Dynamics 365 Field Service (online) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62210</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62211 | Dynamics 365 Field Service (online) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62211</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62213 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62213</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62214 | Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62214</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62215 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62215</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62216 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62216</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62217 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62217</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62218 | Microsoft Wireless Provisioning System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62218</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62219 | Microsoft Wireless Provisioning System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62219</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62220 | Windows Subsystem for Linux GUI Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62220</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62222 | Agentic AI and Visual Studio Code Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62222</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62449 | Microsoft Visual Studio Code CoPilot Chat Extension Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62449</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62452 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62452</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62453 | GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio Code Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62453</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61826 | Illustrator on iPad | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61826</link><description>Illustrator on iPad versions 3.0.9 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61827 | Illustrator on iPad | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61827</link><description>Illustrator on iPad versions 3.0.9 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61828 | Illustrator on iPad | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61828</link><description>Illustrator on iPad versions 3.0.9 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61829 | Illustrator on iPad | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61829</link><description>Illustrator on iPad versions 3.0.9 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61836 | Illustrator on iPad | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61836</link><description>Illustrator on iPad versions 3.0.9 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61819 | Photoshop Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61819</link><description>Photoshop Desktop versions 26.8.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61820 | Illustrator | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61820</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.7.10, 29.8.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61831 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61831</link><description>Illustrator versions 28.7.10, 29.8.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61814 | InDesign Desktop | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61814</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61815 | InDesign Desktop | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61815</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61816 | InCopy | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61816</link><description>InCopy versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61817 | InCopy | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61817</link><description>InCopy versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61818 | InCopy | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61818</link><description>InCopy versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61824 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61824</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61832 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61832</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 20.5, 19.5.5 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20010 | Use of unmaintained third party components for some Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Appl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20010</link><description>Use of unmaintained third party components for some Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20050 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20050</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20056 | Improper input validation for some Intel VTune Profiler before version 2025.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20056</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel VTune Profiler before version 2025.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20065 | Uncontrolled search path for some Display Virtualization for Windows OS software before version 1797 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20065</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Display Virtualization for Windows OS software before version 1797 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20614 | External control of file name or path for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20614</link><description>External control of file name or path for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20622 | Sensitive information uncleared in resource before release for reuse for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers for Windows before version 32.0.100.4023 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20622</link><description>Sensitive information uncleared in resource before release for reuse for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers for Windows before version 32.0.100.4023 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22391 | Improper access control for some SigTest before version 6.1.10 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unpriv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22391</link><description>Improper access control for some SigTest before version 6.1.10 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24299 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24299</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24307 | Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24307</link><description>Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24314 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24314</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24327 | Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Rapid Storage Technology Application before version 20.0.1021 within Ring 3: User Applicati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24327</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Rapid Storage Technology Application before version 20.0.1021 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24491 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Killer(TM) Performance Suite software before version killer 4.0 40.25.509.1465 within Ring 3: Use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24491</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Killer(TM) Performance Suite software before version killer 4.0 40.25.509.1465 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24512 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24512</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Authorized adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24516 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24516</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24519 | Buffer overflow for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24519</link><description>Buffer overflow for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (high) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24834 | Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24834</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24838 | Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24838</link><description>Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24842 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) System Support Utility before version 4.1.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24842</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) System Support Utility before version 4.1.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24847 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24847</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24848 | Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24848</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24862 | Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24862</link><description>Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24863 | Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24863</link><description>Improper privilege management for some Intel(R) CIP software before version WIN_DCA_2.4.0.11001 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24918 | Improper link resolution before file access ('link following') for some Intel(R) Server Configuration Utility software and Intel(R) Server F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24918</link><description>Improper link resolution before file access ('link following') for some Intel(R) Server Configuration Utility software and Intel(R) Server Firmware Update Utility software before version 16.0.12. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25059 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) One Boot Flash Update (Intel(R) OFU) software before version 14.1.31 within Ring 3: User Applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25059</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) One Boot Flash Update (Intel(R) OFU) software before version 14.1.31 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25216 | Improper input validation in some firmware for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers and Intel LTS kernels within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25216</link><description>Improper input validation in some firmware for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers and Intel LTS kernels within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26402 | Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged soft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26402</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26405 | Improper control of dynamically-managed code resources for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26405</link><description>Improper control of dynamically-managed code resources for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26694 | Null pointer dereference for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26694</link><description>Null pointer dereference for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27246 | Incorrect default permissions for the Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Applications may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27246</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for the Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27249 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Gaudi software before version 1.21.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27249</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Gaudi software before version 1.21.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27710 | Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27710</link><description>Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an information disclosure. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27711 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) One Boot Flash Update (Intel(R) OFU) software before version 14.1.31 within Ring 3: User App...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27711</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) One Boot Flash Update (Intel(R) OFU) software before version 14.1.31 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27712 | Improper neutralization for some Intel(R) Neural Compressor software before version v3.4 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27712</link><description>Improper neutralization for some Intel(R) Neural Compressor software before version v3.4 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (low) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27713 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27713</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27725 | Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some ACAT before version 3.13 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27725</link><description>Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some ACAT before version 3.13 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30182 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Distribution for Python software installers before version 2025.2.0 within Ring 3: User Applicati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30182</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Distribution for Python software installers before version 2025.2.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30185 | Active debug code for some Intel UEFI reference platforms within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service and escalation of privilege. S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30185</link><description>Active debug code for some Intel UEFI reference platforms within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service and escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data alteration. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (high) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30255 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30255</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30506 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel Driver and Support Assistant before version 25.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30506</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel Driver and Support Assistant before version 25.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30509 | Improper input validation for some Intel QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30509</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30518 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) PresentMon before version 2.3.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30518</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) PresentMon before version 2.3.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31146 | Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack software before version 1.5.1.0 within Ring 3:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31146</link><description>Time-of-check time-of-use race condition for some Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack software before version 1.5.1.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31645 | Uncontrolled search path for some System Event Log Viewer Utility software for all versions within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31645</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some System Event Log Viewer Utility software for all versions within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31647 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics Software before version 25.22.1502.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31647</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) Graphics Software before version 25.22.1502.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31931 | Uncontrolled search path for the Instrumentation and Tracing Technology API (ITT API) software before version 3.25.4 within Ring 3: User App...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31931</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Instrumentation and Tracing Technology API (ITT API) software before version 3.25.4 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31937 | Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31937</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31940 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Thread Director Visualizer software before version 1.1.1 within Ring 3: User Applications ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31940</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Thread Director Visualizer software before version 1.1.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31948 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library before version 2025.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31948</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) oneAPI Math Kernel Library before version 2025.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32001 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32001</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel(R) Processor Identification Utility before version 8.0.43 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32037 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) PresentMon before version 2.3.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32037</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) PresentMon before version 2.3.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Network adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32038 | Uncontrolled search path for some FPGA Support Package for the Intel oneAPI DPC++C++ Compiler software before version 2025.0.1 within Ring 3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32038</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some FPGA Support Package for the Intel oneAPI DPC++C++ Compiler software before version 2025.0.1 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32088 | Improper conditions check for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32088</link><description>Improper conditions check for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32091 | Incorrect default permissions in some firmware for the Intel(R) Arc(TM) B-series GPUs within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow an escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32091</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some firmware for the Intel(R) Arc(TM) B-series GPUs within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32446 | Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32446</link><description>Untrusted pointer dereference for some Intel QuickAssist Technology software before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data manipulation. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (high) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32449 | Unquoted search path for some PRI Driver software before version 03.03.1002 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32449</link><description>Unquoted search path for some PRI Driver software before version 03.03.1002 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32732 | Buffer overflow for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32732</link><description>Buffer overflow for some Intel(R) QAT Windows software before version 2.6.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (low) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33000 | Improper input validation for some Intel QuickAssist Technology before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33000</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel QuickAssist Technology before version 2.6.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33029 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33029</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35963 | Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35963</link><description>Insufficient control flow management for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35967 | Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35967</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35968 | Protection mechanism failure in the UEFI firmware for the Slim Bootloader within firmware may allow an escalation of privilege. Startup code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35968</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in the UEFI firmware for the Slim Bootloader within firmware may allow an escalation of privilege. Startup code and smm adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35971 | Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35971</link><description>Out-of-bounds write for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless WiFi Software for Windows before version 23.160 within Ring 2: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via adjacent access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35972 | Uncontrolled search path for the Intel MPI Library before version 2021.16 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35972</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for the Intel MPI Library before version 2021.16 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12942 | Improper input validation in NETGEAR R6260 and R6850</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12942</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in NETGEAR R6260 and NETGEAR R6850 allows unauthenticated attackers connected to LAN with ability to perform MiTM attacks and control over DNS Server to perform command execution.This issue affects R6260: through 1.1.0.86; R6850: through 1.1.0.86.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12943 | Improper certificate validation in firmware update logic in NETGEAR RAX30 and RAXE300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12943</link><description>Improper certificate
validation in firmware update logic in NETGEAR RAX30 (Nighthawk AX5 5-Stream
AX2400 WiFi 6 Router) and RAXE300 (Nighthawk AXE7800 Tri-Band
WiFi 6E Router) allows attackers with the ability to intercept and
tamper traffic destined to the device to execute arbitrary commands on the
device.

Devices
with automatic updates enabled may already have this patch applied. If not,
please check the firmware version and update to the
latest.



Fixed in:



RAX30 firmware
1.0.14.108 or later.



RAXE300 firmware
1.0.9.82 or later</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12944 | Improper input validation in NETGEAR DGN2200v4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12944</link><description>Improper input validation
in NETGEAR DGN2200v4 (N300 Wireless ADSL2+ Modem Router) allows attackers with
direct network access to the device to potentially execute code on the device.

Please check the firmware version and update to the latest.



Fixed
in:



 DGN2200v4
firmware 1.0.0.132 or later</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23361 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a script, where malicious input created by an attacker may cause imprope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23361</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a script, where malicious input created by an attacker may cause improper control of code generation. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33178 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the bert services component where malicious data created by an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33178</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the bert services component where malicious data created by an attacker may cause a code injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to Code execution, Escalation of privileges, Information disclosure, and Data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33185 | NVIDIA AIStore contains a vulnerability in AuthN where an unauthenticated user may cause information disclosure.  A successful exploit of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33185</link><description>NVIDIA AIStore contains a vulnerability in AuthN where an unauthenticated user may cause information disclosure.  A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33186 | NVIDIA AIStore contains a vulnerability in AuthN. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges, informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33186</link><description>NVIDIA AIStore contains a vulnerability in AuthN. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33202 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a stack overflow by sending extr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33202</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause a stack overflow by sending extra-large payloads. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12940 | Credentials recorded in logs in NETGEAR WAX610 and WAX610Y</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12940</link><description>Login credentials are inadvertently recorded in logs if a Syslog Server is configured in NETGEAR WAX610
and WAX610Y (AX1800 Dual Band PoE Multi-Gig Insight Managed WiFi 6
Access Points). An user having access to the syslog server can read the logs containing these credentials. 

This issue affects WAX610: before 10.8.11.4; WAX610Y: before 10.8.11.4.


Devices
managed with Insight get automatic updates. If not, please check the firmware version
and update to the latest. 





Fixed in:



WAX610 firmware
11.8.0.10 or later.



WAX610Y firmware
11.8.0.10 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13032 | Double fetch in sandbox kernel driver in Avast/AVG Antivirus &lt;25.3  on windows allows local attacker to escalate privelages via pool overflo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13032</link><description>Double fetch in sandbox kernel driver in Avast/AVG Antivirus &lt;25.3  on windows allows local attacker to escalate privelages via pool overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23357 | NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a script, where malicious data created by an attacker may cause a code inje...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23357</link><description>NVIDIA Megatron-LM for all platforms contains a vulnerability in a script, where malicious data created by an attacker may cause a code injection issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10905 | Collision in minifilter driver of Avast Free Antivirus results in disabling of real-time protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10905</link><description>Collision in MiniFilter driver in Avast Software Avast Free Antivirus  before 25.9  on Windows allows a local attacker with administrative privileges to disable real-time protection and self-defense mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13012 | Race condition in the Graphics component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13012</link><description>Race condition in the Graphics component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13013 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Core &amp;amp; HTML component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13013</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Core &amp; HTML component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13014 | Use-after-free in the Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13014</link><description>Use-after-free in the Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13015 | Spoofing issue in Firefox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13015</link><description>Spoofing issue in Firefox. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13016 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13016</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the JavaScript: WebAssembly component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13017 | Same-origin policy bypass in the DOM: Notifications component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13017</link><description>Same-origin policy bypass in the DOM: Notifications component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13018 | Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13018</link><description>Mitigation bypass in the DOM: Security component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13019 | Same-origin policy bypass in the DOM: Workers component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13019</link><description>Same-origin policy bypass in the DOM: Workers component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13020 | Use-after-free in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13020</link><description>Use-after-free in the WebRTC: Audio/Video component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145 and Firefox ESR &lt; 140.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13021 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13021</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13022 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13022</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13023 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13023</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13024 | JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13024</link><description>JIT miscompilation in the JavaScript Engine: JIT component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13025 | Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13025</link><description>Incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13026 | Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13026</link><description>Sandbox escape due to incorrect boundary conditions in the Graphics: WebGPU component. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13027 | Memory safety bugs fixed in Firefox 145 and Thunderbird 145</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13027</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 144 and Thunderbird 144. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 145.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10918 | Insecure default permissions in the agent of Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU4 allows a local authenticated attacker to write ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10918</link><description>Insecure default permissions in the agent of Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU4 allows a local authenticated attacker to write arbitrary files anywhere on disk</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9408 | Userspace privilege escalation vulnerability on Cortex M</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9408</link><description>System call entry on Cortex M (and possibly R and A, but I think not) has a race which allows very practical privilege escalation for malicious userspace processes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64773 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 a race condition allowed bypass of helpdesk Agent limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64773</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 a race condition allowed bypass of helpdesk Agent limit</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57695 | An issue in Agnitum Outpost Security Suite 7.5.3 (3942.608.1810) and 7.6 (3984.693.1842) allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57695</link><description>An issue in Agnitum Outpost Security Suite 7.5.3 (3942.608.1810) and 7.6 (3984.693.1842) allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lock function. The manufacturer fixed the vulnerability in version 8.0 (4164.652.1856) from December 17, 2012.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11959 | Improper Access Control in Premierturk&amp;#x27;s Excavation Management Information System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11959</link><description>Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties, Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Premierturk Information Technologies Inc. Excavation Management Information System allows Footprinting, Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Excavation Management Information System: before v.10.2025.01.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11697 | Studio 5000 ® Simulation Interface Local Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11697</link><description>A local code execution security issue exists within Studio 5000® Simulation Interface™ via the API. This vulnerability allows any Windows user on the system to extract files using path traversal sequences, resulting in execution of scripts with Administrator privileges on system reboot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11696 | Studio 5000 ® Simulation Interface SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11696</link><description>A local server-side request forgery (SSRF) security issue exists within Studio 5000® Simulation Interface™ via the API. This vulnerability allows any Windows user on the system to trigger outbound SMB requests, enabling the capture of NTLM hashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11862 | Verve Asset Manager Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11862</link><description>A security issue was discovered within Verve Asset Manager allowing unauthorized read-only users to read, update, and delete users via the API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12101 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12101</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway when the appliance is configured as a Gateway (VPN virtual server, ICA Proxy, CVPN, RDP Proxy) OR AAA virtual server</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11084 | FactoryTalk® DataMosaix™ Private Cloud – Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11084</link><description>A security issue exists within DataMosaix™ Private Cloud, allowing attackers to bypass MFA during setup and obtain a valid login-token cookie without knowing the users password. This vulnerability occurs when MFA is enabled but not completed within a 7-day period.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11085 | FactoryTalk® DataMosaix™ Private Cloud – Persistent XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11085</link><description>A security issue exists within DataMosaix™ Private Cloud allowing for Persistent XSS. This vulnerability can result in the execution of malicious JavaScript, allowing for account takeover, credential theft, or redirection to a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9227 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9227</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine OpManager versions 128609 and below are vulnerable to Stored XSS Vulnerability in the SNMP trap processor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9223 | Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9223</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 178100 and below are vulnerable to authenticated command injection vulnerability due to the improper configuration in the execute program action feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8324 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8324</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Analytics Plus versions 6170 and below are vulnerable to Unauthenticated SQL Injection due to the improper filter configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10161 | Authentication Bypass in Turkguven&amp;#x27;s Perfektive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10161</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts, Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security, Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision vulnerability in Turkguven Software Technologies Inc. Perfektive allows Brute Force, Authentication Bypass, Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Perfektive: before Version: 12574 Build: 2701.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41103 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41103</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'reply_message' in '/messages/reply'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41104 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41104</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'custom_field_1' in '/estimate_requests/save_estimate_request'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41105 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41105</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'title' in '/tickets/save'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41106 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41106</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'first_name' in '/clients/save_contact/'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41102 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41102</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'title' in '/events/save'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11960 | Reflected XSS in Aryom&amp;#x27;s KVKNET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11960</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aryom Software High Technology Systems Inc. KVKNET allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects KVKNET: before 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41101 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Fairsketch&amp;#x27;s RISE CRM Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41101</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability found in Fairsketch's RISE CRM Framework v3.8.1, which consist of an HTML code injection due to lack of proper validation of user inputs by sending a POST request in parameter 'title' in'/projects/save'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12539 | TNC Toolbox: Web Performance &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation/cPanel Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12539</link><description>The TNC Toolbox: Web Performance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to the plugin storing cPanel API credentials (hostname, username, and API key) in files within the web-accessible wp-content directory without adequate protection in the "Tnc_Wp_Toolbox_Settings::save_settings" function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve these credentials and use them to interact with the cPanel API, which can lead to arbitrary file uploads, remote code execution, and full compromise of the hosting environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12787 | Hydra Booking – All in One Appointment Booking System | Appointment Scheduling, Booking Calendar &amp;amp; WooCommerce Bookings &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Booking Cancellation via Weak Hash Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12787</link><description>The Hydra Booking — Appointment Scheduling &amp; Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized booking cancellation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27. This is due to the plugin's "tfhb_meeting_form_submit_callback" function using insufficiently random values to generate booking cancellation tokens, combined with a globally shared nonce. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to cancel arbitrary bookings via brute force attacks against the tfhb_meeting_form_cencel AJAX endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12788 | Hydra Booking – All in One Appointment Booking System | Appointment Scheduling, Booking Calendar &amp;amp; WooCommerce Bookings &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Missing Payment Verification to Unauthenticated Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12788</link><description>The Hydra Booking — Appointment Scheduling &amp; Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to missing payment verification to unauthenticated payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27. This is due to the plugin accepting client-controlled payment confirmation data in the tfhb_meeting_paypal_payment_confirmation_callback function without server-side verification with PayPal's API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass payment requirements and confirm bookings as paid without any actual payment transaction occurring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12846 | Blocksy Companion &amp;lt;= 2.1.19 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via SVG Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12846</link><description>The Blocksy Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.19. This is due to insufficient file type validation detecting SVG files, allowing double extension files to bypass sanitization while being accepted as a valid SVG file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12953 | Classified Listing – AI-Powered Classified ads &amp;amp; Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Listing Types Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12953</link><description>The Classified Listing – AI-Powered Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the "rtcl_ajax_add_listing_type", "rtcl_ajax_update_listing_type", and "rtcl_ajax_delete_listing_type" function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to add, update, or delete listing types.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7430 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7430</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5723 and below are vulnerable to the Stored XSS Vulnerability in the Folder Message Count and Size report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7632 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7632</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5723 and below are vulnerable to the Stored XSS Vulnerability in the Public Folders report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7633 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7633</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5723 and below are vulnerable to the Stored XSS Vulnerability in the Custom report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20210 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20210</link><description>Photo Station 5.4.1 &amp; 5.2.7 include the security fix for the vulnerability related to the XMR mining programs identified by internal research.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 09:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5317 | Improper access restriction to critical folder in Bitdefender Endpoint Security Tools for Mac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5317</link><description>An improper access restriction to a folder in Bitdefender Endpoint Security Tools for Mac (BEST) before 7.20.52.200087 allows local users with administrative privileges to bypass the configured uninstall password protection. An unauthorized user with sudo privileges can manually remove the application directory (/Applications/Endpoint Security for Mac.app/) and the related directories within /Library/Bitdefender/AVP without needing the uninstall password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7429 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7429</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5723 and below are vulnerable to the Stored XSS Vulnerability in the Mails Deleted or Moved report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8998 | It was possible to upload files with a specific name to a temporary directory, which may result in process crashes and impact usability. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8998</link><description>It was possible to upload files with a specific name to a temporary directory, which may result in process crashes and impact usability. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator-privileged service account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9055 | The VAPIX Edge storage API that allowed a privilege escalation, enabling a VAPIX administrator-privileged user to gain Linux Root privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9055</link><description>The VAPIX Edge storage API that allowed a privilege escalation, enabling a VAPIX administrator-privileged user to gain Linux Root privileges. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an administrator-privileged service account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9524 | The VAPIX API port.cgi did not have sufficient input validation, which may result in process crashes and impact usability. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9524</link><description>The VAPIX API port.cgi did not have sufficient input validation, which may result in process crashes and impact usability. This vulnerability can only be exploited after authenticating with a viewer- operator- or administrator-privileged service account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10714 | AXIS Optimizer was vulnerable to an unquoted search path vulnerability, which could potentially lead to privilege escalation within Microsof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10714</link><description>AXIS Optimizer was vulnerable to an unquoted search path vulnerability, which could potentially lead to privilege escalation within Microsoft Windows operating system. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the attacker has access to the local Windows machine and sufficient access rights (administrator) to write data into the installation path of AXIS Optimizer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6571 | A 3rd-party component exposed its password in process arguments, allowing for low-privileged users to access it.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6571</link><description>A 3rd-party component exposed its password in process arguments, allowing for low-privileged users to access it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6779 | An ACAP configuration file has improper permissions, which could allow command injection and potentially lead to privilege escalation. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6779</link><description>An ACAP configuration file has improper permissions, which could allow command injection and potentially lead to privilege escalation. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8108 | An ACAP configuration file has improper permissions and lacks input validation, which could potentially lead to privilege escalation. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8108</link><description>An ACAP configuration file has improper permissions and lacks input validation, which could potentially lead to privilege escalation. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5452 | A malicious ACAP application can gain access to admin-level service account credentials used by legitimate ACAP applications, leading to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5452</link><description>A malicious ACAP application can gain access to admin-level service account credentials used by legitimate ACAP applications, leading to potential privilege escalation of the malicious ACAP application. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6298 | ACAP applications can gain elevated privileges due to improper input validation, potentially leading to privilege escalation. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6298</link><description>ACAP applications can gain elevated privileges due to improper input validation, potentially leading to privilege escalation. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4645 | An ACAP configuration file lacked sufficient input validation, which could allow for arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability can only b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4645</link><description>An ACAP configuration file lacked sufficient input validation, which could allow for arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5454 | An ACAP configuration file lacked sufficient input validation, which could allow a path traversal attack leading to potential privilege esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5454</link><description>An ACAP configuration file lacked sufficient input validation, which could allow a path traversal attack leading to potential privilege escalation. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5718 | The ACAP Application framework could allow privilege escalation through a symlink attack. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Ax...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5718</link><description>The ACAP Application framework could allow privilege escalation through a symlink attack. This vulnerability can only be exploited if the Axis device is configured to allow the installation of unsigned ACAP applications, and if an attacker convinces the victim to install a malicious ACAP application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11237 | Make Email Customizer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11237</link><description>The Make Email Customizer for WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 lacks proper authorization checks and option validation in its AJAX actions, allowing any authenticated user, such as a Subscriber, to update arbitrary WordPress options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11307 | WP Google Maps &amp;lt; 9.0.48 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11307</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) WordPress plugin before 9.0.48 does not sanitize user input provided via an AJAX action, allowing unauthenticated users to store XSS payloads which are later retrieved from another AJAX call and output unescaped.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11855 | Age Restriction &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Subscriber+ Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11855</link><description>The age-restriction WordPress plugin through 3.0.2 does not have authorisation in the age_restrictionRemoteSupportRequest function, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to create an admin user with a hardcoded username and arbitrary password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11129 | Include fussball.de Widgets &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;api&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;type&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11129</link><description>The Include Fussball.de Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'api' and 'type' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11168 | Mementor Core &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11168</link><description>The Mementor Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.5. This is due to plugin not properly handling the user switch back function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges by accessing an administrator account through the switch back functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11170 | WP移行専用プラグイン for CPI &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11170</link><description>The WP移行専用プラグイン for CPI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the Cpiwm_Import_Controller::import function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11451 | Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11451</link><description>The Auto Amazon Links – Amazon Associates Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary files reads in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.3 via the '/wp-json/wp/v2/aal_ajax_unit_loading' RST API endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11457 | EasyCommerce – AI-Powered, Blazing-Fast &amp;amp; Beautiful WordPress Ecommerce Plugin 0.9.0-beta2 - 1.5.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11457</link><description>The EasyCommerce – AI-Powered, Fast &amp; Beautiful WordPress Ecommerce Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in versions 0.9.0-beta2 to 1.5.0. This is due to the /easycommerce/v1/orders REST API endpoint not properly restricting the ability for users to select roles during registration. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain administrator-level access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11521 | Astra Security Suite – Firewall &amp;amp; Malware Scan &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11521</link><description>The Astra Security Suite – Firewall &amp; Malware Scan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient validation of remote URLs for zip downloads and an easily guessable key in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11532 | Wisly &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Wishlist Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11532</link><description>The Wisly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to missing validation on the 'wishlist_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove and add items to other user's wishlists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11805 | Skip to Timestamp &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11805</link><description>The Skip to Timestamp plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'skipto' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'time' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11821 | Woocommerce – Products By Custom Tax &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11821</link><description>The Woocommerce – Products By Custom Tax plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'woo_products_custom_tax' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11822 | WP Bootstrap Tabs &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11822</link><description>The WP Bootstrap Tabs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'bootstrap_tab' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11828 | Magazine Companion &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11828</link><description>The Magazine Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'headerHtmlTag' attribute in the bnm-blocks/featured-posts-1 block in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when using user-supplied values as HTML tag names. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11829 | Five9 Live Chat &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11829</link><description>The Five9 Live Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'toolbar' attribute of the [five9-chat] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11856 | Eventbee Ticketing Widget &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11856</link><description>The Eventbee Ticketing Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'eventbeeticketwidget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of several parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11859 | Paypal Donation Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11859</link><description>The Paypal Donation Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'paypal' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of the 'title' and 'text' parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11860 | Twitter Feed &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11860</link><description>The Twitter Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ottwitter_feed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of the 'width' and 'height' parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11863 | My Geo Posts Free &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11863</link><description>The My Geo Posts Free plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mygeo_city' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input or escaping output of the 'default' shortcode attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11869 | Precise Columns &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11869</link><description>The Precise Columns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `wrap_id` shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input or escaping output when inserting the wrapper ID into the generated HTML. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11873 | WP BBCode &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11873</link><description>The WP BBCode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'url' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11874 | Slippy Slider – Responsive Touch Navigation Slider &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11874</link><description>The Slippy Slider – Responsive Touch Navigation Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'slippy-slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11882 | Simple Donate &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11882</link><description>The Simple Donate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's simpledonate shortcode in versions less than, or equal to, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11886 | CTL Arcade Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Activation and Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11886</link><description>The CTL Arcade Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ctl_arcade_lite_page_manage_games' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate and activate arbitrary plugins via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11891 | Shelf Planner &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11891</link><description>The Shelf Planner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11894 | Shelf Planner &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11894</link><description>The Shelf Planner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify several of the plugin's settings like the ServerKey and LicenseKey.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11986 | Crypto Tool &amp;lt;= 2.22 -  Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Global Authentication State</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11986</link><description>The Crypto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.22. This is due to the plugin registering an unauthenticated AJAX action (wp_ajax_nopriv_crypto_connect_ajax_process) that allows calling the register and savenft methods with only a publicly-available nonce check and no wallet signature verification. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set a site-wide global authentication state via a single transient, bypassing all access controls for ALL visitors to the site. The impact is complete bypass of [crypto-block] shortcode restrictions and page-level access controls, affecting all site visitors for one hour, plus the ability to inject arbitrary data into the plugin's custom_users table.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11988 | Crypto Tool &amp;lt;= 2.22 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Limited File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11988</link><description>The Crypto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized manipulation of data in all versions up to, and including, 2.22. This is due to the plugin registering an unauthenticated AJAX action (wp_ajax_nopriv_crypto_connect_ajax_process) that allows calling the crypto_delete_json method with only a publicly-available nonce check. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete specific JSON files matching the pattern *_pending.json within the wp-content/uploads/yak/ directory, causing data loss and denial of service for plugin workflows that rely on these artifacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11996 | Find Unused Images &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11996</link><description>The Find Unused Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the fui_delete_image() and fui_delete_all_images() functiosn in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete all of a site's attachments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11997 | Document Pro Elementor – Documentation &amp;amp; Knowledge Base &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11997</link><description>The Document Pro Elementor – Documentation &amp; Knowledge Base plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This is due to the plugin exposing sensitive Algolia API keys through the frontend JavaScript code via wp_localize_script without proper access restrictions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view sensitive API keys in the page source, which could be leveraged to make unauthorized API calls to the configured Algolia search service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11999 | Add Multiple Marker &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11999</link><description>The Add Multiple Marker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to due to a missing capability check on the addmultiplemarker_reset_map() and amm_save_map_api() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the map API and reset maps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12010 | Authors List &amp;lt;= 2.0.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Limited Method Call in Plugin&amp;#x27;s Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12010</link><description>The Authors List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6.1 via the via arbitrary method call from Authors_List_Shortcode class. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to call methods such as get_meta to extract sensitive user data including password hashes, email addresses, usernames, and activation keys via specially crafted shortcode attributes</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12019 | Featured Image &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12019</link><description>The Featured Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image metadata in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12020 | Double the Donation &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12020</link><description>The Double the Donation – A workplace giving tool to help your fundraising efforts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12021 | WP-OAuth &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12021</link><description>The WP-OAuth plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'error_description' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12126 | The Total Book Project &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Book Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12126</link><description>The The Total Book Project plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via several functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to perform several actions like moving/deleting/creating chapters in books that do not belong to them.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12132 | WP Custom Admin Login Page Logo &amp;lt;= 1.4.8.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12132</link><description>The WP Custom Admin Login Page Logo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpclpl_save functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12526 | Private Google Calendars &amp;lt;= 20250811 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12526</link><description>The Private Google Calendars plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'pgc_remove' action in all versions up to, and including, 20250811. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12538 | Fleet Manager &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12538</link><description>The Fleet Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12588 | USB Qr Code Scanner For Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12588</link><description>The USB Qr Code Scanner For Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12589 | WP-Walla &amp;lt;= 0.5.3.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12589</link><description>The WP-Walla plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.3.5. This is due to missing nonce verification on the settings page and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12590 | YSlider &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12590</link><description>The YSlider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing nonce verification on the content configuration page and insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. The injected scripts will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12631 | Squirrels Auto Inventory &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12631</link><description>The Squirrels Auto Inventory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12632 | RandomQuotr &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12632</link><description>The RandomQuotr plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12637 | Elastic Theme Editor &amp;lt;= 0.0.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12637</link><description>The Elastic Theme Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a dynamic code generation feature in the process_theme function in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12644 | Nonaki – Drag and Drop Email Template builder and Newsletter plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12644</link><description>The Nonaki – Drag and Drop Email Template builder and Newsletter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'nonaki' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied custom field values that are retrieved and rendered by the shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12651 | Live Photos on WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12651</link><description>The Live Photos on WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'video_src', 'img_src', and 'class' parameters in the livephotos_photo shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12652 | Ungapped Widgets &amp;lt;= 1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12652</link><description>The Ungapped Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'prefillvalues' parameter in the ungapped-form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12658 | Preload Current Images &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12658</link><description>The Preload Current Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'complete' parameter in the 'preload_progress_bar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12662 | Coon Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12662</link><description>The Coon Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' parameter in the 'map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12663 | Jeba Cute forkit &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12663</link><description>The Jeba Cute forkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'text' parameter in the 'jeba_forkit' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12665 | Ninja Countdown &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Countdown Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12665</link><description>The Ninja Countdown | Fastest Countdown Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ninja_countdown_admin_ajax' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary countdowns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12667 | GitHub Gist Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12667</link><description>The GitHub Gist Shortcode Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter of the 'gist' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12668 | WP Count Down Timer &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12668</link><description>The WP Count Down Timer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters of the 'wp_countdown_timer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12671 | WP-Iconics &amp;lt;= 0.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12671</link><description>The WP-Iconics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters of the 'wp_iconics' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12672 | Flickr Show &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12672</link><description>The Flickr Show plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'div_height' parameter of the 'flickrshow' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12711 | Share to Google Classroom &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via share_to_google Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12711</link><description>The Share to Google Classroom plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the share_to_google shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12753 | Chart Expert &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12753</link><description>The Chart Expert plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pmzez_chart' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied shortcode attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12754 | Geopost &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12754</link><description>The Geopost plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' parameter of the 'geopost' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12813 | Holiday class post calendar &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via &amp;#x27;contents&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12813</link><description>The Holiday class post calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 7.1 via the 'contents' parameter. This is due to a lack of sanitization of user-supplied data when creating a cache file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12880 | Progress Bar Blocks for Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12880</link><description>The Progress Bar Blocks for Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 04:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31719 | In TEE EcDSA algorithm, there is a possible memory consistency issue. This could lead to generated incorrect signature results with low prob...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31719</link><description>In TEE EcDSA algorithm, there is a possible memory consistency issue. This could lead to generated incorrect signature results with low probability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42882 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42882</link><description>Due to a missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP, an authenticated attacker with basic privileges could execute a specific function module in ABAP to retrieve restricted technical information from the system. This disclosure of environment details of the system could further assist this attacker to plan subsequent attacks. As a result, this vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality, with no impact on the integrity or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42883 | Insecure File Operations vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP (Migration Workbench)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42883</link><description>Migration Workbench (DX Workbench) in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP fails to trigger a malware scan when an attacker with administrative privileges uploads files to the application server. An attacker could leverage this and upload a malicious file into the system. This results in a low impact on the integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42884 | JNDI Injection vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42884</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject JNDI environment properties or pass a URL used during JNDI lookup operations, enabling access to an unintended JNDI provider.�This could further lead to disclosure or modification of information about the server. There is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42885 | Missing authentication in SAP HANA 2.0 (hdbrss)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42885</link><description>Due to missing authentication, SAP HANA 2.0 (hdbrss) allows an unauthenticated attacker to call a remote-enabled function that will enable them to view information. As a result, it has a low impact on the confidentiality but no impact on the integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42886 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42886</link><description>Due to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Business Connector, an unauthenticated attacker could generate a malicious link and make it publicly accessible. If an authenticated victim accesses this link, the injected input is processed during web page generation, resulting in the execution of malicious content in the victim's browser context. This could allow the attacker to access or modify information within the victim�s browser scope, impacting confidentiality and integrity, while availability remains unaffected</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42887 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP Solution Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42887</link><description>Due to missing input sanitation, SAP Solution Manager allows an authenticated attacker to insert malicious code when calling a remote-enabled function module. This could provide the attacker with full control of the system hence leading to high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42888 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP GUI for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42888</link><description>SAP GUI for Windows may allow a highly privileged user on the affected client PC to locally access sensitive information stored in process memory during runtime.This vulnerability has a high impact on confidentiality, with no impact on integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42889 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SAP Starter Solution (PL SAFT)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42889</link><description>SAP Starter Solution allows an authenticated attacker to execute crafted database queries, thereby exposing the back-end database. As a result, this vulnerability has a low impact on the application's confidentiality and integrity but no impact on its availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42890 | Insecure key &amp;amp; Secret Management vulnerability in SQL Anywhere Monitor (Non-Gui)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42890</link><description>SQL Anywhere Monitor (Non-GUI) baked credentials into the code,exposing the resources or functionality to unintended users and providing attackers with the possibility of arbitrary code execution.This could cause high impact on confidentiality integrity and availability of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42892 | OS Command Injection vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42892</link><description>Due to an OS Command Injection vulnerability in SAP Business Connector, an authenticated attacker with administrative access and adjacent network access could upload specially crafted content to the server. If processed by the application, this content enables execution of arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation could lead to full compromise of the system�s confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42893 | Open Redirect vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42893</link><description>Due to an Open Redirect vulnerability in SAP Business Connector, an unauthenticated attacker could craft a malicious URL that, if accessed by a victim, redirects them to an attacker-controlled site displayed within an embedded frame. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to steal sensitive information and perform unauthorized actions, impacting the confidentiality and integrity of web client data. There is no impact to system availability resulting from this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42894 | Path Traversal vulnerability in SAP Business Connector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42894</link><description>Due to a Path Traversal vulnerability in SAP Business Connector, an attacker authenticated as an administrator with adjacent access could read, write, overwrite, and delete arbitrary files on the host system. Successful exploitation could enable the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the server, resulting in a complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42895 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP HANA JDBC Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42895</link><description>Due to insufficient validation of connection property values, the SAP HANA JDBC Client allows a high-privilege locally authenticated user to supply crafted parameters that lead to unauthorized code loading, resulting in low impact on confidentiality and integrity and high impact on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42897 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Business One (SLD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42897</link><description>Due to information disclosure vulnerability in anonymous API provided by SAP Business One (SLD), an attacker with normal user access could gain access to unauthorized information. As a result, it has a low impact on the confidentiality of the application but no impact on the integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42899 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S4CORE (Manage Journal Entries)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42899</link><description>SAP S4CORE (Manage journal entries) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user resulting in escalation of privileges. This has low impact on confidentiality of the application with no impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42919 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42919</link><description>Due to an Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java, internal metadata files could be accessed via manipulated URLs. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting arbitrary path components in the request, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive application metadata. This results in a partial compromise of the confidentiality of the information without affecting the integrity or availability of the application server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42924 | Open Redirect vulnerabilities in SAP S/4HANA landscape (SAP E-Recruiting BSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42924</link><description>SAP S/4HANA landscape SAP E-Recruiting BSP allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft malicious links, when clicked the victim could be redirected to the page controlled by the attacker. This has low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application with no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42940 | Memory Corruption vulnerability in SAP CommonCryptoLib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42940</link><description>SAP CommonCryptoLib does not perform necessary boundary checks during pre-authentication parsing of manipulated ASN.1 data over the network. This may result in memory corruption followed by an application crash, hence leading to a high impact on availability. There is no impact on confidentiality or integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63678 | An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /uploads/ endpoint of CMS Made Simple Foundation File Manager v2.2.22 allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63678</link><description>An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the /uploads/ endpoint of CMS Made Simple Foundation File Manager v2.2.22 allows attackers with Administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11578 | Pre-Receive Hook Path Collision Vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server Allowing Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11578</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an authenticated Enterprise admin to gain root SSH access to the appliance by exploiting a symlink escape in pre-receive hook environments. By crafting a malicious repository and environment, an attacker could replace system binaries during hook cleanup and execute a payload that adds their own SSH key to the root user’s authorized keys—thereby granting themselves root SSH access to the server. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker needed to have enterprise admin privileges. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.19, and was fixed in versions 3.14.19, 3.15.14, 3.16.10, 3.17.7 and 3.18.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11892 | DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server Issues search allows privilege escalation and unauthorized workflow triggers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11892</link><description>An improper neutralization of input vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allows DOM-based cross-site scripting via Issues search label filter that could lead to privilege escalation and unauthorized workflow triggers. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to have access to the target GitHub Enterprise Server instance and to entice a user, while operating in sudo mode, to click on a crafted malicious link to perform actions that require elevated privileges. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.18.1, 3.17.7, 3.16.10, 3.15.14, 3.14.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25124 | PacsOne Server 6.6.2 DICOM Web Viewer Directory Traversal LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25124</link><description>PacsOne Server version 6.6.2 (prior versions are likely affected) contains a directory traversal vulnerability within the web-based DICOM viewer component. Successful exploitation allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files via the 'nocache.php' endpoint with a crafted 'path' parameter. Exploitation evidence was observed by the Shadowserver Foundation on 2025-02-07 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4462 | Employee Records System v1.0 Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4462</link><description>Employee Records System version 1.0 contains an unrestricted file upload vulnerability that allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files via the uploadID.php endpoint; uploaded files can be executed because the application does not perform proper server-side validation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64529 | SpiceDB&amp;#x27;s WriteRelationships fails silently if payload is too big</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64529</link><description>SpiceDB is an open source database system for creating and managing security-critical application permissions. In versions prior to 1.45.2, users who use the exclusion operator somewhere in their authorization schema; have configured their SpiceDB server such that `--write-relationships-max-updates-per-call` is bigger than 6500; and issue calls to WriteRelationships with a large enough number of updates that cause the payload to be bigger than what their datastore allows; will receive a successful response from their `WriteRelationships` call, when in reality that call failed, and receive incorrect permission check results, if those relationships had to be read to resolve the relation involving the exclusion. Version 1.45.2 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, set `--write-relationships-max-updates-per-call` to `1000`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64519 | TorrentPier is Vulnerable to Authenticated SQL Injection through Moderator Control Panel&amp;#x27;s topic_id parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64519</link><description>TorrentPier is an open source BitTorrent Public/Private tracker engine, written in php. In versions up to and including 2.8.8, an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in the moderator control panel (`modcp.php`). Users with moderator permissions can exploit this vulnerability by supplying a malicious `topic_id` (`t`) parameter. This allows an authenticated moderator to execute arbitrary SQL queries, leading to the potential disclosure, modification, or deletion of any data in the database. Although it requires moderator privileges, it is still severe. A malicious or compromised moderator account can leverage this vulnerability to read, modify, or delete data. A patch is available at commit 6a0f6499d89fa5d6e2afa8ee53802a1ad11ece80.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64522 | Soft Serve is vulnerable to SSRF through its Webhooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64522</link><description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. Versions prior to 0.11.1 have a SSRF vulnerability where webhook URLs are not validated, allowing repository administrators to create webhooks targeting internal services, private networks, and cloud metadata endpoints. Version 0.11.1 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64513 | Milvus Proxy has Critical Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64513</link><description>Milvus is an open-source vector database built for generative AI applications. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit a vulnerability in versions prior to 2.4.24, 2.5.21, and 2.6.5 to bypass all authentication mechanisms in the Milvus Proxy component, gaining full administrative access to the Milvus cluster. This grants the attacker the ability to read, modify, or delete data, and to perform privileged administrative operations such as database or collection management. This issue has been fixed in Milvus 2.4.24, 2.5.21, and 2.6.5. If immediate upgrade is not possible, a temporary mitigation can be applied by removing the sourceID header from all incoming requests at the gateway, API gateway, or load balancer level before they reach the Milvus Proxy. This prevents attackers from exploiting the authentication bypass behavior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64518 | CycloneDX Core (Java): BOM validation is vulnerable to XML External Entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64518</link><description>The CycloneDX core module provides a model representation of the SBOM along with utilities to assist in creating, validating, and parsing SBOMs. Starting in version 2.1.0 and prior to version 11.0.1, the XML `Validator` used by cyclonedx-core-java was not configured securely, making the library vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) injection. The fix for GHSA-683x-4444-jxh8 / CVE-2024-38374 was incomplete in that it only fixed parsing of XML BOMs, but not validation. The vulnerability has been fixed in cyclonedx-core-java version 11.0.1. As a workaround, applications can reject XML documents before handing them to cyclonedx-core-java for validation. This may be an option if incoming CycloneDX BOMs are known to be in JSON format.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64507 | Incus vulnerable to local privilege escalation through custom storage volumes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64507</link><description>Incus is a system container and virtual machine manager. An issue in versions prior to 6.0.6 and 6.19.0 affects any Incus user in an environment where an unprivileged user may have root access to a container with an attached custom storage volume that has the `security.shifted` property set to `true` as well as access to the host as an unprivileged user. The most common case for this would be systems using `incus-user` with the less privileged `incus` group to provide unprivileged users with an isolated restricted access to Incus. Such users may be able to create a custom storage volume with the necessary property (depending on kernel and filesystem support) and can then write a setuid binary from within the container which can be executed as an unprivileged user on the host to gain root privileges. A patch for this issue is expected in versions 6.0.6 and 6.19.0. As a workaround, permissions can be manually restricted until a patched version of Incus is deployed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64512 | pdfminer.six vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution via Crafted PDF Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64512</link><description>Pdfminer.six is a community maintained fork of the original PDFMiner, a tool for extracting information from PDF documents. Prior to version 20251107, pdfminer.six will execute arbitrary code from a malicious pickle file if provided with a malicious PDF file. The `CMapDB._load_data()` function in pdfminer.six uses `pickle.loads()` to deserialize pickle files. These pickle files are supposed to be part of the pdfminer.six distribution stored in the `cmap/` directory, but a malicious PDF can specify an alternative directory and filename as long as the filename ends in `.pickle.gz`. A malicious, zipped pickle file can then contain code which will automatically execute when the PDF is processed. Version 20251107 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64504 | Langfuse vulnerable to cross‑organization enumeration of member &amp;amp; invitation lists via project membership APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64504</link><description>Langfuse is an open source large language model engineering platform. Starting in version 2.70.0 and prior to versions 2.95.11 and 3.124.1, in certain project membership APIs, the server trusted a user‑controlled orgId and used it in authorization checks. As a result, any authenticated user on the same Langfuse instance could enumerate names and email addresses of users in another organization if they knew the target organization’s ID. Disclosure is limited to names and email addresses of members/invitees. No customer data such as traces, prompts, or evaluations is exposed or accessible. For Langfuse Cloud, the maintainers ran a thorough investigation of access logs of the last 30 days and could not find any evidence that this vulnerability was exploited. For most self-hosting deployments, the attack surface is significantly reduced given an SSO provider is configured and email/password sign-up is disabled. In these cases, only users who authenticate via the Enterprise SSO IdP (e.g. Okta) would be able to exploit this vulnerability to access the member list, i.e. internal users getting access to a list of other internal users. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the actor must have a valid Langfuse user account within the same instance, know the target orgId, and use the request made to the API that powers the frontend membership tables, including their project/user authentication token, while changing the orgId to the target organization. Langfuse Cloud (EU, US, HIPAA) were affected until fix deployment on November 1, 2025. The maintainers reviewed the Langfuse Cloud access logs from the past 30 days and found no evidence that this vulnerability was exploited. Self-Hosted versions which contain patches include v2.95.11 for major version 2 and v3.124.1 for major version 3. There are no known workarounds. Upgrading is required to fully mitigate this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64508 | Bugsink vulnerable to unauthenticated remote DoS via crafted Brotli input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64508</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking tool. In versions prior to 2.0.5, brotli "bombs" (highly compressed brotli streams, such as many zeros) can be sent to the server. Since the server will attempt to decompress these streams before applying various maximums, this can lead to exhaustion of the available memory and thus a Denial of Service. This can be done if the `DSN` is known, which it is in many common setups (JavaScript, Mobile Apps). The issue is patched in Bugsink version `2.0.5`. The vulnerability is similar to, but distinct from, another brotli-related problem in Bugsink, GHSA-rrx3-2x4g-mq2h/CVE-2025-64509.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64509 | Bugsink vulnerable to unauthenticated remote DoS via crafted Brotli input (via CPU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64509</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking tool. In versions prior to 2.0.6, a specially crafted Brotli-compressed envelope can cause Bugsink to spend excessive CPU time in decompression, leading to denial of service. This can be done if the DSN is known, which it is in many common setups (JavaScript, Mobile Apps). The issue is patched in Bugsink 2.0.6. The vulnerability is similar to, but distinct from, another brotli-related problem in Bugsink, GHSA-fc2v-vcwj-269v/CVE-2025-64508.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64501 | ProsemirrorToHtml: Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability through unescaped HTML attribute values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64501</link><description>ProsemirrorToHtml is a JSON converter which takes ProseMirror-compatible JSON and outputs HTML. In versions 0.2.0 and below, the `prosemirror_to_html` gem is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks through malicious HTML attribute values. While tag content is properly escaped, attribute values are not, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code. Applications that use `prosemirror_to_html` to convert ProseMirror documents to HTML, user-generated ProseMirror content, and end users viewing the rendered HTML output are all at risk of attack. This issue is fixed in version 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64502 | Parse Server allows public `explain` queries which may expose sensitive database performance information and schema details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64502</link><description>Parse Server is an open source backend that can be deployed to any infrastructure that can run Node.js. The MongoDB `explain()` method provides detailed information about query execution plans, including index usage, collection scanning behavior, and performance metrics. Prior to version 8.5.0-alpha.5, Parse Server permits any client to execute explain queries without requiring the master key. This exposes database schema structure and field names, index configurations and query optimization details, query execution statistics and performance metrics, and potential attack vectors for database performance exploitation. In version 8.5.0-alpha.5, a new `databaseOptions.allowPublicExplain` configuration option has been introduced that allows to restrict `explain` queries to the master key. The option defaults to `true` for now to avoid a breaking change in production systems that depends on public `explain` availability. In addition, a security warning is logged when the option is not explicitly set, or set to `true`. In a future major release of Parse Server, the default will change to `false`. As a workaround, implement middleware to block explain queries from non-master-key requests, or monitor and alert on explain query usage in production environments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64182 | OpenEXR has buffer overflow in PyOpenEXR_old&amp;#x27;s channels() and channel()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64182</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.2.0 through 3.2.4, 3.3.0 through 3.3.5, and 3.4.0 through 3.4.2, a memory safety bug in the legacy OpenEXR Python adapter (the deprecated OpenEXR.InputFile wrapper) allow crashes and likely code execution when opening attacker-controlled EXR files or when passing crafted Python objects. Integer overflow and unchecked allocation in InputFile.channel() and InputFile.channels() can lead to heap overflow (32 bit) or a NULL deref (64 bit). Versions 3.2.5, 3.3.6, and 3.4.3 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64183 | OpenEXR has use after free in PyObject_StealAttrString</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64183</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.2.0 through 3.2.4, 3.3.0 through 3.3.5, and 3.4.0 through 3.4.2, there is a use-after-free in PyObject_StealAttrString of pyOpenEXR_old.cpp. The legacy adapter defines PyObject_StealAttrString that calls PyObject_GetAttrString to obtain a new reference, immediately decrefs it, and returns the pointer. Callers then pass this dangling pointer to APIs like PyLong_AsLong/PyFloat_AsDouble, resulting in a use-after-free. This is invoked in multiple places (e.g., reading PixelType.v, Box2i, V2f, etc.) Versions 3.2.5, 3.3.6, and 3.4.3 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64484 | OAuth2-Proxy vulnerable to header smuggling via underscore, leading to potential privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64484</link><description>OAuth2-Proxy is an open-source tool that can act as either a standalone reverse proxy or a middleware component integrated into existing reverse proxy or load balancer setups. In versions prior to 7.13.0, all deployments of OAuth2 Proxy in front of applications that normalize underscores to dashes in HTTP headers (e.g., WSGI-based frameworks such as Django, Flask, FastAPI, and PHP applications). Authenticated users can inject underscore variants of X-Forwarded-* headers that bypass the proxy’s filtering logic, potentially escalating privileges in the upstream app. OAuth2 Proxy authentication/authorization itself is not compromised. The problem has been patched with v7.13.0. By default all specified headers will now be normalized, meaning that both capitalization and the use of underscores (_) versus dashes (-) will be ignored when matching headers to be stripped. For example, both `X-Forwarded-For` and `X_Forwarded-for` will now be treated as equivalent and stripped away. For those who have a rational that requires keeping a similar looking header and not stripping it, the maintainers introduced a new configuration field for Headers managed through the AlphaConfig called `InsecureSkipHeaderNormalization`. As a workaround, ensure filtering and processing logic in upstream services don't treat underscores and hyphens in Headers the same way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62780 | changedetection.io vulnerable to stored XSS in Watch update via API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62780</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection tool. A Stored Cross Site Scripting is present in changedetection.io Watch update API in versions prior to 0.50.34 due to insufficient security checks. Two scenarios are possible. In the first, an attacker can insert a new watch with an arbitrary URL which really points to a web page. Once the HTML content is retrieved, the attacker updates the URL with a JavaScript payload. In the second, an attacker substitutes the URL in an existing watch with a new URL that is in reality a JavaScript payload. When the user clicks on *Preview* and then on the malicious link, the JavaScript malicious code is executed. Version 0.50.34 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64181 | OpenEXR Makes Use of Uninitialized Memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64181</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.3.0 through 3.3.5 and 3.4.0 through 3.4.2, while fuzzing `openexr_exrcheck_fuzzer`, Valgrind reports a conditional branch depending on uninitialized data inside `generic_unpack`. This indicates a use of uninitialized memory. The issue can result in undefined behavior and/or a potential crash/denial of service. Versions 3.3.6 and 3.4.3 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49145 | iTop admin can drop iTop database using webhooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49145</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. In versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2, a user that has enough rights to create webhooks (mostly administrators) can drop the database. This is fixed in iTop 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 by verifying callback signature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63397 | Improper input validation in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a segmentation fault via adding a Python sequence to the native code d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63397</link><description>Improper input validation in OneFlow v0.9.0 allows attackers to cause a segmentation fault via adding a Python sequence to the native code during broadcasting/type conversion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64167 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to reflected XSS in webservices/export.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64167</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. Versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 are vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack (leading to JS execution) when editing the URL parameter. Versions 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 don't use export.php, which was deprecated. They use export-v2.php instead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63296 | KERUI K259 5MP Wi-Fi / Tuya Smart Security Camera firmware v33.53.87 contains a code execution vulnerability in its boot/update logic: durin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63296</link><description>KERUI K259 5MP Wi-Fi / Tuya Smart Security Camera firmware v33.53.87 contains a code execution vulnerability in its boot/update logic: during startup /usr/sbin/anyka_service.sh scans mounted TF/SD cards and, if /mnt/update.nor.sh is present, copies it to /tmp/net.sh and executes it as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48065 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to reflected XSS via objection edition form error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48065</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. Versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when a field with an error contains malicious content. Versions 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 protect rendered HTML content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:54:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48878 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to IDOR with ModuleInstallation object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48878</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. In versions on the 3.x branch prior to 3.2.2, an insecure direct object reference allows a user (e.g. with Service desk agent profile) to create a ModuleInstallation object when they shouldn't be able to do so. Version 3.2.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48055 | Combodo iTop has stored XSS in user portal&amp;#x27;s browse brick</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48055</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. In versions prior to 3.2.2, when displaying content in a browse brick in the user portal, a cross-site scripting attack can occur. This is fixed in versions 3.2.2 and 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63617 | ktg-mes before commit a484f96 (2025-07-03) has a fastjson deserialization vulnerability. This is because it uses a vulnerable version of fas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63617</link><description>ktg-mes before commit a484f96 (2025-07-03) has a fastjson deserialization vulnerability. This is because it uses a vulnerable version of fastjson and deserializes unsafe input data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63384 | A vulnerability was discovered in RISC-V Rocket-Chip v1.6 and before implementation where the SRET (Supervisor-mode Exception Return) instru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63384</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in RISC-V Rocket-Chip v1.6 and before implementation where the SRET (Supervisor-mode Exception Return) instruction fails to correctly transition the processor's privilege level. Instead of downgrading from Machine-mode (M-mode) to Supervisor-mode (S-mode) as specified by the sstatus.SPP bit, the processor incorrectly remains in M-mode, leading to a critical privilege retention vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12428 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12428</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12429 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12429</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12430 | Object lifecycle issue in Media in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12430</link><description>Object lifecycle issue in Media in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12431 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a mal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12431</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to bypass navigation restrictions via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12432 | Race in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12432</link><description>Race in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12433 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12433</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12434 | Race in Storage in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12434</link><description>Race in Storage in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12435 | Incorrect security UI in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12435</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12436 | Policy bypass in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extensio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12436</link><description>Policy bypass in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to obtain potentially sensitive information from process memory via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12437 | Use after free in PageInfo in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12437</link><description>Use after free in PageInfo in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12438 | Use after free in Ozone in Google Chrome on Linux and ChromeOS prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit objec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12438</link><description>Use after free in Ozone in Google Chrome on Linux and ChromeOS prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12439 | Inappropriate implementation in App-Bound Encryption in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a local attacker to obtain p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12439</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in App-Bound Encryption in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a local attacker to obtain potentially sensitive information from process memory via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12440 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12440</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to obtain potentially sensitive information from process memory via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12441 | Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12441</link><description>Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12443 | Out of bounds read in WebXR in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12443</link><description>Out of bounds read in WebXR in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory read via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12444 | Incorrect security UI in Fullscreen UI in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12444</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Fullscreen UI in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12445 | Policy bypass in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extensio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12445</link><description>Policy bypass in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to leak cross-origin data via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12446 | Incorrect security UI in SplitView in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12446</link><description>Incorrect security UI in SplitView in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted domain name. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12447 | Incorrect security UI in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12447</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.59 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12725 | Out of bounds read in WebGPU in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12725</link><description>Out of bounds read in WebGPU in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12726 | Inappropriate implementation in Views in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12726</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Views in Google Chrome on Windows prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to perform privilege escalation via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12727 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12727</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12728 | Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12728</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12729 | Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12729</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Omnibox in Google Chrome on Android prior to 142.0.7444.137 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56503 | An issue in Sublime HQ Pty Ltd Sublime Text 4 4200 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges to Admini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56503</link><description>An issue in Sublime HQ Pty Ltd Sublime Text 4 4200 allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to escalate privileges to Administrator via replacing the uninstall file with a crafted binary in the installation folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60876 | BusyBox wget thru 1.3.7 accepted raw CR (0x0D)/LF (0x0A) and other C0 control bytes in the HTTP request-target (path/query), allowing the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60876</link><description>BusyBox wget thru 1.3.7 accepted raw CR (0x0D)/LF (0x0A) and other C0 control bytes in the HTTP request-target (path/query), allowing the request line to be split and attacker-controlled headers to be injected. To preserve the HTTP/1.1 request-line shape METHOD SP request-target SP HTTP/1.1, a raw space (0x20) in the request-target must also be rejected (clients should use %20).</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33150 | IBM Cognos Analytics Certified Containers information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33150</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics Certified Containers 12.1.0 could disclose package parameter information due to the presence of hidden pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63149 | Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the urls parameter of the get_parentControl_list_Info function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63149</link><description>Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the urls parameter of the get_parentControl_list_Info function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47932 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to reflected XSS in ajax.render.php render_dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47932</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. Versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting  when a dashboard is rendered via an AJAX call. Versions 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 sanitize the var responsible for the attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43723 | Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions prior to 9.10.1.3 and versions 9.11.0.0 through 9.12.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43723</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS, versions prior to 9.10.1.3 and versions 9.11.0.0 through 9.12.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47773 | Combodo iTop has XSS vulnerability in /pages/ajax.render.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47773</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. Versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when a dashboard is edited via an AJAX call. Versions 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 protect rendered HTML content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63288 | In Open5GS 2.7.6, AMF crashes when receiving an abnormal NGSetupRequest message, resulting in denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63288</link><description>In Open5GS 2.7.6, AMF crashes when receiving an abnormal NGSetupRequest message, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47286 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in the backup creation functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47286</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. In versions prior to 2.7.13 and 3.2.2, an administrator can, by editing the configuration of the iTop instance, execute code on the server. Versions 2.7.13 and 3.2.2 escape and check the config parameter before executing a command based on it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12967 | An issue in AWS Wrappers for Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL may allow for privilege escalation to rds_superuser role. A low privilege authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12967</link><description>An issue in AWS Wrappers for Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL may allow for privilege escalation to rds_superuser role. A low privilege authenticated user can create a crafted function that could be executed with permissions of other Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) users.

We recommend customers upgrade to the following versions: AWS JDBC Wrapper to v2.6.5, AWS Go Wrapper to 2025-10-17, AWS NodeJS Wrapper to v2.01, AWS Python Wrapper to v1.4.0 and AWS PGSQL ODBC driver to v1.0.1</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43079 | Local Privilege Escalation via qagent_uninstall.sh Qualys Cloud Agents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43079</link><description>The Qualys Cloud Agent included a bundled uninstall script (qagent_uninstall.sh), specific to MacOS and Linux supported versions that invoked multiple system commands without using absolute paths and without sanitizing the $PATH environment. If the uninstall script is executed with elevated privileges (e.g., via sudo) in an environment where $PATH has been manipulated, an attacker with root/sudo privileges could cause malicious executables to be run in place of the intended system binaries. This behavior can be leveraged for local privilege escalation and arbitrary command execution under elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63497 | The patient prescription viewing functionality in his_doc_view_single_patient.php of rickxy Hospital Management System version 1.0 contains ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63497</link><description>The patient prescription viewing functionality in his_doc_view_single_patient.php of rickxy Hospital Management System version 1.0 contains an SQL injection vulnerability. The pat_number GET parameter is directly concatenated into SQL queries without proper sanitization, allowing authenticated attackers (doctor role) to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63455 | Tenda AX-3 v16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the fromSetWifiGusetBasic function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63455</link><description>Tenda AX-3 v16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the fromSetWifiGusetBasic function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63456 | Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the SetSysTimeCfg function. This vulnerability a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63456</link><description>Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the time parameter in the SetSysTimeCfg function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63834 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05_multi. The vulnerability exists in the ssid para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63834</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05_multi. The vulnerability exists in the ssid parameter of the wireless settings. Remote attackers can inject malicious payloads that execute when any user visits the router's homepage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63147 | Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the deviceId parameter of the saveParentControlInfo function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63147</link><description>Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the deviceId parameter of the saveParentControlInfo function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63835 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05_multi. The vulnerability exists in the guestSsid param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63835</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Tenda AC18 v15.03.05.05_multi. The vulnerability exists in the guestSsid parameter of the /goform/WifiGuestSet interface. Remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability by sending oversized data to the guestSsid parameter, leading to denial of service (device crash) or potential remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63457 | Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanMTU parameter in the sub_4F55C function. This vulnerability all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63457</link><description>Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wanMTU parameter in the sub_4F55C function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63152 | Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the wpapsk_crypto parameter of the wlSetExternParameter function. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63152</link><description>Tenda AX3 V16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the wpapsk_crypto parameter of the wlSetExternParameter function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63153 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the ssid parameter of the urldecode function. This vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63153</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the ssid parameter of the urldecode function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63154 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the addEffect parameter of the urldecode function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63154</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow in the addEffect parameter of the urldecode function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46430 | Dell Display and Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 2.1.2.12, contains an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability in the Inst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46430</link><description>Dell Display and Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 2.1.2.12, contains an Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability in the Installer. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63709 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System 1.0 in the "Add Tasks" text input. An authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63709</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SourceCodester Simple To-Do List System 1.0 in the "Add Tasks" text input. An authenticated user can submit HTML/JavaScript that is not correctly sanitized or encoded on output. The injected script is stored and later rendered in the browser of any user who views the task, allowing execution of arbitrary script in the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63710 | The send_message.php endpoint in SourceCodester Simple Public Chat Room 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). The applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63710</link><description>The send_message.php endpoint in SourceCodester Simple Public Chat Room 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). The application does not implement any CSRF-protection mechanisms such as tokens, nonces, or same-site cookie restrictions. An attacker can create a malicious HTML page that, when visited by an authenticated user, will automatically submit a forged POST request to the vulnerable endpoint. This request will be executed with the victim's privileges, allowing the attacker to perform unauthorized actions on their behalf, such as sending arbitrary messages in any chat room.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63712 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in SourceCodester Product Expiry Management System. The User Management module (delete-user.php) allows re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63712</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in SourceCodester Product Expiry Management System. The User Management module (delete-user.php) allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts via forged cross-origin GET requests because the endpoint relies solely on session cookies and lacks CSRF protection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63711 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to cause an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63711</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0 allows an attacker to cause an authenticated administrative user to perform user deletion actions without their consent. The application's user deletion endpoint (e.g., superadmin_user_delete.php) accepts POST requests containing a user_id parameter and does not enforce request origin or anti-CSRF tokens. Because the endpoint lacks proper authentication/authorization checks and CSRF protections, a remote attacker can craft a malicious page that triggers deletion when visited by an authenticated admin, resulting in arbitrary removal of user accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12480 | Triofox versions prior to 16.7.10368.56560, are vulnerable to an Improper Access Control flaw that allows access to initial setup pages even...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12480</link><description>Triofox versions prior to 16.7.10368.56560, are vulnerable to an Improper Access Control flaw that allows access to initial setup pages even after setup is complete.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64456 | In JetBrains ReSharper before 2025.2.4 missing signature verification in DPA Collector allows local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64456</link><description>In JetBrains ReSharper before 2025.2.4 missing signature verification in DPA Collector allows local privilege escalation</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64457 | In JetBrains dotTrace before 2025.2.5 local privilege escalation possible via race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64457</link><description>In JetBrains dotTrace before 2025.2.5 local privilege escalation possible via race condition</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64681 | In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104992 a race condition allowed bypass of the user limit via invitations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64681</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104992 a race condition allowed bypass of the user limit via invitations</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64682 | In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104432 a race condition allowed bypass of the Agent-user limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64682</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104432 a race condition allowed bypass of the Agent-user limit</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64683 | In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104432 information disclosure was possible via the Users API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64683</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.104432 information disclosure was possible via the Users API</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64684 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 information disclosure was possible via the feedback form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64684</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 information disclosure was possible via the feedback form</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64685 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing TLS certificate validation enabled data disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64685</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing TLS certificate validation enabled data disclosure</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64686 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing user principal cleanup led to reuse of incorrect authorization context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64686</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing user principal cleanup led to reuse of incorrect authorization context</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64687 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 improper access control allowed modify MCP tool logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64687</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 improper access control allowed modify MCP tool logic</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64688 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing VCS URL validation allowed delegation to unauthorized repositories from the Junie widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64688</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 missing VCS URL validation allowed delegation to unauthorized repositories from the Junie widget</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64689 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 misconfiguration in the Junie could lead to exposure of the global Junie token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64689</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 misconfiguration in the Junie could lead to exposure of the global Junie token</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64690 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 insecure Junie configuration could lead to data exposure and unauthorized changes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64690</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.104432 insecure Junie configuration could lead to data exposure and unauthorized changes</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12939 | SourceCodester Interview Management System addCandidate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12939</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Interview Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addCandidate.php. The manipulation of the argument candName results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12938 | projectworlds Online Admission System process_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12938</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /process_login.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41001 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41001</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in SOPlanning v1.53.02, which consist of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the 'LOGOUT_REDIRECT' parameter in '/soplanning/www/process/options.php'. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 10:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12405 | Unauthorized access through stored credentials in Looker Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12405</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability was found in Looker Studio. It impacted all JDBC-based connectors.

A Looker Studio user with report view access could make a copy of the report and execute arbitrary SQL that would run on the data source database due to the stored credentials attached to the report.

This vulnerability was patched on 21 July 2025, and no customer action is needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41107 | Stored XSS in Smart School</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41107</link><description>Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Smart School 7.0 due to lack of proper validation of user input when sending a POST request to '/online_admission', wich affects the parameters 'firstname', 'lastname', 'guardian_name' and others. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal his/her session cookie details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12397 | SQL Injection in Looker Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12397</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was found in Looker Studio.

A Looker Studio user with report view access could inject malicious SQL that would execute with the report owner's permissions. The vulnerability affected to reports with BigQuery as the data source.

This vulnerability was patched on 21 July 2025, and no customer action is needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12409 | SQL Injection in Looker Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12409</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Looker Studio that allowed for data exfiltration from BigQuery data sources.
 
By creating a malicious report with native functions enabled, and having the victim access the report, an attacker could execute injected SQL queries with the victim's permissions in BigQuery.

This vulnerability was patched on 07 July 2025, and no customer action is needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12155 | Command Injection in Looker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12155</link><description>A Command Injection vulnerability, resulting from improper file path sanitization (Directory Traversal) in Looker allows an attacker with Developer permission to execute arbitrary shell commands when a user is deleted on the host system.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.

Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.100+
  *  24.18.192+
  *  25.0.69+
  *  25.6.57+
  *  25.8.39+
  *  25.10.22+</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 08:54:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41731 | Jumo: Insufficient entropy in PRNG may lead to root access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41731</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the password generation algorithm when accessing the debug-interface. An unauthenticated local attacker with knowledge of the password generation timeframe might be able to brute force the password in a timely manner and thus gain root access to the device if the debug interface is still enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 07:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12933 | SourceCodester Baby Care System updatewelcome.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12933</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Baby Care System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /updatewelcome.php?id=siteoptions&amp;amp;action=welcome. Such manipulation of the argument roleid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12613 | Versions of the package cloudinary before 2.7.0 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Argument Injection due to improper parsing of parameter values c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12613</link><description>Versions of the package cloudinary before 2.7.0 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Argument Injection due to improper parsing of parameter values containing an ampersand. An attacker can inject additional, unintended parameters. This could lead to a variety of malicious outcomes, such as bypassing security checks, altering data, or manipulating the application's behavior.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;Following our established security policy, we attempted to contact the maintainer regarding this vulnerability, but haven't received a response.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 05:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12932 | SourceCodester Baby Care System admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12932</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Baby Care System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin.php?id=inbox. This manipulation of the argument msgid causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 05:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12931 | SourceCodester Food Ordering System edit-orders.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12931</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /routers/edit-orders.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59777 | NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59777</link><description>NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the master branch of the libmicrohttpd Git repository, after the v1.0.2 tag. A specially crafted packet sent by an attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62689 | NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62689</link><description>NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in GNU libmicrohttpd v1.0.2 and earlier. The vulnerability was fixed in commit ff13abc on the master branch of the libmicrohttpd Git repository, after the v1.0.2 tag. A specially crafted packet sent by an attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12930 | SourceCodester Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12930</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12929 | SourceCodester Survey Application System LoginRegistration.php update_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12929</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Survey Application System 1.0. This impacts the function save_user/update_user of the file /LoginRegistration.php. Executing manipulation of the argument fullname can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been published and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 04:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12867 | Hundred Plus｜EIP Plus - Arbitrary File Uplaod</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12867</link><description>EIP Plus developed by Hundred Plus has an Arbitrary File Uplaod vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12868 | CyberTutor｜New Site Server - Use of Client-Side Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12868</link><description>New Site Server developed by CyberTutor has a Use of Client-Side Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to modify the frontend code to gain administrator privileges on the website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12928 | code-projects Online Job Search Engine login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12928</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Online Job Search Engine 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument username/phone results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12866 | Hundred Plus｜EIP Plus - Weak Password Recovery Mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12866</link><description>EIP Plus developed by Hundred Plus has a Weak Password Recovery Mechanism vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attacker to predict or brute-force the 'forgot password' link, thereby successfully resetting any user's password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12927 | DedeBIZ archives_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12927</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in DedeBIZ up to 6.3.2. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/archives_add.php. Such manipulation of the argument flags[] leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12864 | e-Excellence｜U-Office Force - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12864</link><description>U-Office Force developed by e-Excellence has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12865 | e-Excellence｜U-Office Force - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12865</link><description>U-Office Force developed by e-Excellence has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attacker to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12926 | SourceCodester Farm Management System review.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12926</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Farm Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /review.php. This manipulation of the argument pid causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12924 | rymcu forest BankController.java GlobalResult authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12924</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in rymcu forest up to de53ce79db9faa2efc4e79ce1077a302c42a1224. This issue affects the function GlobalResult of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/web/api/bank/BankController.java. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12925 | rymcu forest UserDicController.java deleteDic authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12925</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in rymcu forest up to de53ce79db9faa2efc4e79ce1077a302c42a1224. Impacted is the function getAll/addDic/getAllDic/deleteDic of the file src/main/java/com/rymcu/forest/lucene/api/UserDicController.java. The manipulation results in missing authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 02:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12922 | OpenClinica Community Edition CRF Data Import ImportCRFData path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12922</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenClinica Community Edition up to 3.12.2/3.13. This affects an unknown part of the file /ImportCRFData?action=confirm of the component CRF Data Import. Performing manipulation of the argument xml_file results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 01:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12923 | liweiyi ChestnutCMS download resourceDownload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12923</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in liweiyi ChestnutCMS up to 1.5.8. This vulnerability affects the function resourceDownload of the file /dev-api/common/download. Executing manipulation of the argument path can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 01:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>