<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-28054 | Amavis before 2.12.3 and 2.13.x before 2.13.1, in part because of its use of MIME-tools, has an Interpretation Conflict (relative to some ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28054</link><description>Amavis before 2.12.3 and 2.13.x before 2.13.1, in part because of its use of MIME-tools, has an Interpretation Conflict (relative to some mail user agents) when there are multiple boundary parameters in a MIME email message. Consequently, there can be an incorrect check for banned files or malware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27096 | SQL Injection in through the search engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27096</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the search engine to extract data from the database. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27098 | Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) using Arbitrary Object Instantiation in GLPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27098</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can execute a SSRF based attack using Arbitrary Object Instantiation. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27104 | Stored XSS in dashboards in GLPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27104</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. A user with rights to create and share dashboards can build a dashboard containing javascript code. Any user that will open this dashboard will be subject to an XSS attack. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27914 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in search engine when debug mode is enabled in GLPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27914</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An unauthenticated user can provide a malicious link to a GLPI administrator in order to exploit a reflected XSS  vulnerability. The XSS will only trigger if the administrator navigates through the debug bar. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2050 | CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an attacker injects t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2050</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (‘Cross-site Scripting’)
vulnerability exists when an attacker injects then executes arbitrary malicious JavaScript code
within the context of the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2051 | CWE-307: Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability exists that
could cause account takeover and unauthorized a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2051</link><description>CWE-307: Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability exists that
could cause account takeover and unauthorized access to the system when an attacker
conducts brute-force attacks against the login form.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2052 | CWE-552: Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability exists that could allow
unauthenticated files and logs exfiltrati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2052</link><description>CWE-552: Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability exists that could allow
unauthenticated files and logs exfiltration and download of files when an attacker modifies the
URL to download to a different location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2229 | CWE-502: Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists that could cause remote code
execution when a malicious project file is load...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2229</link><description>CWE-502: Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists that could cause remote code
execution when a malicious project file is loaded into the application by a valid user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20752 | ZDI-CAN-22653: Adobe Bridge PS File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20752</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.5, 14.0.1 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20755 | Adobe Bridge PDF Parsing Heap Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20755</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.5, 14.0.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20756 | Adobe Bridge 2024 Out of Bound Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20756</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.5, 14.0.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20757 | Bridge 2024 TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bound Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20757</link><description>Bridge versions 13.0.5, 14.0.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2390 | Local Privilege Escalation </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2390</link><description>As a part of Tenable’s vulnerability disclosure program, a vulnerability in a Nessus plugin was identified and reported. This vulnerability could allow a malicious actor with sufficient permissions on a scan target to place a binary in a specific filesystem location, and abuse the impacted plugin in order to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27930 | Sensitive fields access through dropdowns in GLPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27930</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can access sensitive fields data from items on which he has read access. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1331 | Team Members &amp;lt; 5.3.2 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1331</link><description>The Team Members WordPress plugin before 5.3.2 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the author role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1333 | Responsive Pricing Table &amp;lt; 5.1.11 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1333</link><description>The Responsive Pricing Table WordPress plugin before 5.1.11 does not validate and escape some of its Pricing Table options before outputting them back in a page/post where the related shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the author role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1658 | Grid Shortcodes &amp;lt; 1.1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1658</link><description>The Grid Shortcodes WordPress plugin before 1.1.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27937 | glpi Users emails enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27937</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can obtain the email address of all GLPI users. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20745 | ZDI-CAN-22671: Adobe Premiere Pro AVI File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20745</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 24.1, 23.6.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20746 | Adobe Premiere Pro Out-of-bounds Write Arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20746</link><description>Premiere Pro versions 24.1, 23.6.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1753 | Buildah: full container escape at build time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1753</link><description>A flaw was found in Buildah (and subsequently Podman Build) which allows containers to mount arbitrary locations on the host filesystem into build containers. A malicious Containerfile can use a dummy image with a symbolic link to the root filesystem as a mount source and cause the mount operation to mount the host root filesystem inside the RUN step. The commands inside the RUN step will then have read-write access to the host filesystem, allowing for full container escape at build time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22257 | In Spring Security, versions 5.7.x prior to 5.7.12, 5.8.x prior to 
5.8.11, versions 6.0.x prior to 6.0.9, versions 6.1.x prior to 6.1.8, 
v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22257</link><description>In Spring Security, versions 5.7.x prior to 5.7.12, 5.8.x prior to 
5.8.11, versions 6.0.x prior to 6.0.9, versions 6.1.x prior to 6.1.8, 
versions 6.2.x prior to 6.2.3, an application is possible vulnerable to 
broken access control when it directly uses the AuthenticatedVoter#vote passing a null Authentication parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2593 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2593</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_group.php, in the 'b_id' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2594 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2594</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/admin/index.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2595 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2595</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_khet_person.php, in the 'b_id' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2596 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2596</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/modules/mail/main/select_send.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2597 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2597</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_school_person.php, in the 'b_id' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2598 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2598</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31, which does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability through /amssplus/modules/book/main/select_send_2.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2599 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2599</link><description>File upload restriction evasion vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31. This vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to potentially obtain RCE through webshell, compromising the entire infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2587 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2587</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_khet_person.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2588 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2588</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/admin/index.php, in the 'id' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2589 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2589</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_school_person.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2590 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2590</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/mail/main/select_send.php, in the 'sd_index' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2591 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2591</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/book/main/bookdetail_group.php, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2592 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2592</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/person/pic_show.php, in the 'person_id' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2584 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2584</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/book/main/select_send.php, in the 'sd_index' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2585 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2585</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/modules/book/main/select_send_2.php, in the 'sd_index' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2586 | SQL injection vulnerability in AMSS++</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2586</link><description>Vulnerability in AMSS++ version 4.31 that allows SQL injection through /amssplus/index.php, in the 'username' parameter. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the server and retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27773 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-348: Use of Less Trusted Source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27773</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 -

CWE-348: Use of Less Trusted Source may allow RCE</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27774 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-259: Use of Hard-coded Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27774</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 -

CWE-259: Use of Hard-coded Password may allow disclosing Sensitive Information Embedded inside Device's Firmware</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28537 | Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the page parameter of fromNatStaticSetting function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28537</link><description>Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the page parameter of fromNatStaticSetting function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27771 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-22: &amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27771</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 -

CWE-22: 'Path Traversal' may allow RCE</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27772 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-78: &amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27772</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 -

CWE-78: 'OS Command Injection' may allow RCE</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27768 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-22: &amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27768</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 - CWE-22: 'Path Traversal' may allow RCE</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27769 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27769</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 - 

CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor may allow Taking Ownership Over Devices</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27770 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-23: Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27770</link><description>Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227 - 

CWE-23: Relative Path Traversal</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27767 | Unitronics Unistream Unilogic – Versions prior to 1.35.227  CWE-287: Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27767</link><description>CWE-287: Improper Authentication may allow Authentication Bypass</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28547 | Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the firewallEn parameter of formSetFirewallCfg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28547</link><description>Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the firewallEn parameter of formSetFirewallCfg function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28550 | Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the filePath parameter of formExpandDlnaFile function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28550</link><description>Tenda AC18 V15.03.05.05 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the filePath parameter of formExpandDlnaFile function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2496 | Libvirt: null pointer dereference in udevconnectlistallinterfaces()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2496</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference flaw was found in the udevConnectListAllInterfaces() function in libvirt. This issue can occur when detaching a host interface while at the same time collecting the list of interfaces via virConnectListAllInterfaces API. This flaw could be used to perform a denial of service attack by causing the libvirt daemon to crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2002 | Libdwarf: crashes randomly on fuzzed object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2002</link><description>A double-free vulnerability was found in libdwarf. In a multiply-corrupted DWARF object, libdwarf may try to dealloc(free) an allocation twice, potentially causing unpredictable and various results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7250 | Iperf3: possible denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7250</link><description>A flaw was found in iperf, a utility for testing network performance using TCP, UDP, and SCTP. A malicious or malfunctioning client can send less than the expected amount of data to the iperf server, which can cause the server to hang indefinitely waiting for the remainder or until the connection gets closed. This will prevent other connections to the server, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20767 | Coldfusion 2023/2021 Pre-Auth monitor uuid leak  lead to arbitrary file read/write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20767</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2023.6, 2021.12 and earlier are affected by an Improper Access Control vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized access to sensitive files and perform arbitrary file system write. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 11:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1013 | Unixodbc: out of bounds stack write due to pointer-to-integer types conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1013</link><description>An out-of-bounds stack write flaw was found in unixODBC on 64-bit architectures where the caller has 4 bytes and callee writes 8 bytes. This issue may go unnoticed on little-endian architectures, while big-endian architectures can be broken.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52617 | PCI: switchtec: Fix stdev_release() crash after surprise hot remove</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52617</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: switchtec: Fix stdev_release() crash after surprise hot remove

A PCI device hot removal may occur while stdev-&gt;cdev is held open. The call
to stdev_release() then happens during close or exit, at a point way past
switchtec_pci_remove(). Otherwise the last ref would vanish with the
trailing put_device(), just before return.

At that later point in time, the devm cleanup has already removed the
stdev-&gt;mmio_mrpc mapping. Also, the stdev-&gt;pdev reference was not a counted
one. Therefore, in DMA mode, the iowrite32() in stdev_release() will cause
a fatal page fault, and the subsequent dma_free_coherent(), if reached,
would pass a stale &amp;stdev-&gt;pdev-&gt;dev pointer.

Fix by moving MRPC DMA shutdown into switchtec_pci_remove(), after
stdev_kill(). Counting the stdev-&gt;pdev ref is now optional, but may prevent
future accidents.

Reproducible via the script at
https://lore.kernel.org/r/20231113212150.96410-1-dns@arista.com</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52618 | block/rnbd-srv: Check for unlikely string overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52618</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

block/rnbd-srv: Check for unlikely string overflow

Since "dev_search_path" can technically be as large as PATH_MAX,
there was a risk of truncation when copying it and a second string
into "full_path" since it was also PATH_MAX sized. The W=1 builds were
reporting this warning:

drivers/block/rnbd/rnbd-srv.c: In function 'process_msg_open.isra':
drivers/block/rnbd/rnbd-srv.c:616:51: warning: '%s' directive output may be truncated writing up to 254 bytes into a region of size between 0 and 4095 [-Wformat-truncation=]
  616 |                 snprintf(full_path, PATH_MAX, "%s/%s",
      |                                                   ^~
In function 'rnbd_srv_get_full_path',
    inlined from 'process_msg_open.isra' at drivers/block/rnbd/rnbd-srv.c:721:14: drivers/block/rnbd/rnbd-srv.c:616:17: note: 'snprintf' output between 2 and 4351 bytes into a destination of size 4096
  616 |                 snprintf(full_path, PATH_MAX, "%s/%s",
      |                 ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
  617 |                          dev_search_path, dev_name);
      |                          ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

To fix this, unconditionally check for truncation (as was already done
for the case where "%SESSNAME%" was present).</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52619 | pstore/ram: Fix crash when setting number of cpus to an odd number</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52619</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pstore/ram: Fix crash when setting number of cpus to an odd number

When the number of cpu cores is adjusted to 7 or other odd numbers,
the zone size will become an odd number.
The address of the zone will become:
    addr of zone0 = BASE
    addr of zone1 = BASE + zone_size
    addr of zone2 = BASE + zone_size*2
    ...
The address of zone1/3/5/7 will be mapped to non-alignment va.
Eventually crashes will occur when accessing these va.

So, use ALIGN_DOWN() to make sure the zone size is even
to avoid this bug.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26639 | mm, kmsan: fix infinite recursion due to RCU critical section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26639</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm, kmsan: fix infinite recursion due to RCU critical section

Alexander Potapenko writes in [1]: "For every memory access in the code
instrumented by KMSAN we call kmsan_get_metadata() to obtain the metadata
for the memory being accessed.  For virtual memory the metadata pointers
are stored in the corresponding `struct page`, therefore we need to call
virt_to_page() to get them.

According to the comment in arch/x86/include/asm/page.h,
virt_to_page(kaddr) returns a valid pointer iff virt_addr_valid(kaddr) is
true, so KMSAN needs to call virt_addr_valid() as well.

To avoid recursion, kmsan_get_metadata() must not call instrumented code,
therefore ./arch/x86/include/asm/kmsan.h forks parts of
arch/x86/mm/physaddr.c to check whether a virtual address is valid or not.

But the introduction of rcu_read_lock() to pfn_valid() added instrumented
RCU API calls to virt_to_page_or_null(), which is called by
kmsan_get_metadata(), so there is an infinite recursion now.  I do not
think it is correct to stop that recursion by doing
kmsan_enter_runtime()/kmsan_exit_runtime() in kmsan_get_metadata(): that
would prevent instrumented functions called from within the runtime from
tracking the shadow values, which might introduce false positives."

Fix the issue by switching pfn_valid() to the _sched() variant of
rcu_read_lock/unlock(), which does not require calling into RCU.  Given
the critical section in pfn_valid() is very small, this is a reasonable
trade-off (with preemptible RCU).

KMSAN further needs to be careful to suppress calls into the scheduler,
which would be another source of recursion.  This can be done by wrapping
the call to pfn_valid() into preempt_disable/enable_no_resched().  The
downside is that this sacrifices breaking scheduling guarantees; however,
a kernel compiled with KMSAN has already given up any performance
guarantees due to being heavily instrumented.

Note, KMSAN code already disables tracing via Makefile, and since mmzone.h
is included, it is not necessary to use the notrace variant, which is
generally preferred in all other cases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26640 | tcp: add sanity checks to rx zerocopy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26640</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: add sanity checks to rx zerocopy

TCP rx zerocopy intent is to map pages initially allocated
from NIC drivers, not pages owned by a fs.

This patch adds to can_map_frag() these additional checks:

- Page must not be a compound one.
- page-&gt;mapping must be NULL.

This fixes the panic reported by ZhangPeng.

syzbot was able to loopback packets built with sendfile(),
mapping pages owned by an ext4 file to TCP rx zerocopy.

r3 = socket$inet_tcp(0x2, 0x1, 0x0)
mmap(&amp;(0x7f0000ff9000/0x4000)=nil, 0x4000, 0x0, 0x12, r3, 0x0)
r4 = socket$inet_tcp(0x2, 0x1, 0x0)
bind$inet(r4, &amp;(0x7f0000000000)={0x2, 0x4e24, @multicast1}, 0x10)
connect$inet(r4, &amp;(0x7f00000006c0)={0x2, 0x4e24, @empty}, 0x10)
r5 = openat$dir(0xffffffffffffff9c, &amp;(0x7f00000000c0)='./file0\x00',
    0x181e42, 0x0)
fallocate(r5, 0x0, 0x0, 0x85b8)
sendfile(r4, r5, 0x0, 0x8ba0)
getsockopt$inet_tcp_TCP_ZEROCOPY_RECEIVE(r4, 0x6, 0x23,
    &amp;(0x7f00000001c0)={&amp;(0x7f0000ffb000/0x3000)=nil, 0x3000, 0x0, 0x0, 0x0,
    0x0, 0x0, 0x0, 0x0}, &amp;(0x7f0000000440)=0x40)
r6 = openat$dir(0xffffffffffffff9c, &amp;(0x7f00000000c0)='./file0\x00',
    0x181e42, 0x0)</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26641 | ip6_tunnel: make sure to pull inner header in __ip6_tnl_rcv()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26641</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ip6_tunnel: make sure to pull inner header in __ip6_tnl_rcv()

syzbot found __ip6_tnl_rcv() could access unitiliazed data [1].

Call pskb_inet_may_pull() to fix this, and initialize ipv6h
variable after this call as it can change skb-&gt;head.

[1]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in __INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:253 [inline]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:275 [inline]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in IP6_ECN_decapsulate+0x7df/0x1e50 include/net/inet_ecn.h:321
  __INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:253 [inline]
  INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:275 [inline]
  IP6_ECN_decapsulate+0x7df/0x1e50 include/net/inet_ecn.h:321
  ip6ip6_dscp_ecn_decapsulate+0x178/0x1b0 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:727
  __ip6_tnl_rcv+0xd4e/0x1590 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:845
  ip6_tnl_rcv+0xce/0x100 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:888
 gre_rcv+0x143f/0x1870
  ip6_protocol_deliver_rcu+0xda6/0x2a60 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:438
  ip6_input_finish net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:483 [inline]
  NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:314 [inline]
  ip6_input+0x15d/0x430 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:492
  ip6_mc_input+0xa7e/0xc80 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:586
  dst_input include/net/dst.h:461 [inline]
  ip6_rcv_finish+0x5db/0x870 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:79
  NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:314 [inline]
  ipv6_rcv+0xda/0x390 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:310
  __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5532 [inline]
  __netif_receive_skb+0x1a6/0x5a0 net/core/dev.c:5646
  netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:5732 [inline]
  netif_receive_skb+0x58/0x660 net/core/dev.c:5791
  tun_rx_batched+0x3ee/0x980 drivers/net/tun.c:1555
  tun_get_user+0x53af/0x66d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2002
  tun_chr_write_iter+0x3af/0x5d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2048
  call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:2084 [inline]
  new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:497 [inline]
  vfs_write+0x786/0x1200 fs/read_write.c:590
  ksys_write+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:643
  __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:655 [inline]
  __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:652 [inline]
  __x64_sys_write+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:652
  do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
  do_syscall_64+0x6d/0x140 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Uninit was created at:
  slab_post_alloc_hook+0x129/0xa70 mm/slab.h:768
  slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3478 [inline]
  kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x5e9/0xb10 mm/slub.c:3523
  kmalloc_reserve+0x13d/0x4a0 net/core/skbuff.c:560
  __alloc_skb+0x318/0x740 net/core/skbuff.c:651
  alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:1286 [inline]
  alloc_skb_with_frags+0xc8/0xbd0 net/core/skbuff.c:6334
  sock_alloc_send_pskb+0xa80/0xbf0 net/core/sock.c:2787
  tun_alloc_skb drivers/net/tun.c:1531 [inline]
  tun_get_user+0x1e8a/0x66d0 drivers/net/tun.c:1846
  tun_chr_write_iter+0x3af/0x5d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2048
  call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:2084 [inline]
  new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:497 [inline]
  vfs_write+0x786/0x1200 fs/read_write.c:590
  ksys_write+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:643
  __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:655 [inline]
  __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:652 [inline]
  __x64_sys_write+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:652
  do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
  do_syscall_64+0x6d/0x140 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

CPU: 0 PID: 5034 Comm: syz-executor331 Not tainted 6.7.0-syzkaller-00562-g9f8413c4a66f #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/17/2023</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52609 | binder: fix race between mmput() and do_exit()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52609</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

binder: fix race between mmput() and do_exit()

Task A calls binder_update_page_range() to allocate and insert pages on
a remote address space from Task B. For this, Task A pins the remote mm
via mmget_not_zero() first. This can race with Task B do_exit() and the
final mmput() refcount decrement will come from Task A.

  Task A            | Task B
  ------------------+------------------
  mmget_not_zero()  |
                    |  do_exit()
                    |    exit_mm()
                    |      mmput()
  mmput()           |
    exit_mmap()     |
      remove_vma()  |
        fput()      |

In this case, the work of ____fput() from Task B is queued up in Task A
as TWA_RESUME. So in theory, Task A returns to userspace and the cleanup
work gets executed. However, Task A instead sleep, waiting for a reply
from Task B that never comes (it's dead).

This means the binder_deferred_release() is blocked until an unrelated
binder event forces Task A to go back to userspace. All the associated
death notifications will also be delayed until then.

In order to fix this use mmput_async() that will schedule the work in
the corresponding mm-&gt;async_put_work WQ instead of Task A.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52610 | net/sched: act_ct: fix skb leak and crash on ooo frags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52610</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: act_ct: fix skb leak and crash on ooo frags

act_ct adds skb-&gt;users before defragmentation. If frags arrive in order,
the last frag's reference is reset in:

  inet_frag_reasm_prepare
    skb_morph

which is not straightforward.

However when frags arrive out of order, nobody unref the last frag, and
all frags are leaked. The situation is even worse, as initiating packet
capture can lead to a crash[0] when skb has been cloned and shared at the
same time.

Fix the issue by removing skb_get() before defragmentation. act_ct
returns TC_ACT_CONSUMED when defrag failed or in progress.

[0]:
[  843.804823] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  843.809659] kernel BUG at net/core/skbuff.c:2091!
[  843.814516] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[  843.819296] CPU: 7 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/7 Kdump: loaded Tainted: G S 6.7.0-rc3 #2
[  843.824107] Hardware name: XFUSION 1288H V6/BC13MBSBD, BIOS 1.29 11/25/2022
[  843.828953] RIP: 0010:pskb_expand_head+0x2ac/0x300
[  843.833805] Code: 8b 70 28 48 85 f6 74 82 48 83 c6 08 bf 01 00 00 00 e8 38 bd ff ff 8b 83 c0 00 00 00 48 03 83 c8 00 00 00 e9 62 ff ff ff 0f 0b &lt;0f&gt; 0b e8 8d d0 ff ff e9 b3 fd ff ff 81 7c 24 14 40 01 00 00 4c 89
[  843.843698] RSP: 0018:ffffc9000cce07c0 EFLAGS: 00010202
[  843.848524] RAX: 0000000000000002 RBX: ffff88811a211d00 RCX: 0000000000000820
[  843.853299] RDX: 0000000000000640 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffff88811a211d00
[  843.857974] RBP: ffff888127d39518 R08: 00000000bee97314 R09: 0000000000000000
[  843.862584] R10: 0000000000000000 R11: ffff8881109f0000 R12: 0000000000000880
[  843.867147] R13: ffff888127d39580 R14: 0000000000000640 R15: ffff888170f7b900
[  843.871680] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff889ffffc0000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  843.876242] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  843.880778] CR2: 00007fa42affcfb8 CR3: 000000011433a002 CR4: 0000000000770ef0
[  843.885336] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[  843.889809] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[  843.894229] PKRU: 55555554
[  843.898539] Call Trace:
[  843.902772]  &lt;IRQ&gt;
[  843.906922]  ? __die_body+0x1e/0x60
[  843.911032]  ? die+0x3c/0x60
[  843.915037]  ? do_trap+0xe2/0x110
[  843.918911]  ? pskb_expand_head+0x2ac/0x300
[  843.922687]  ? do_error_trap+0x65/0x80
[  843.926342]  ? pskb_expand_head+0x2ac/0x300
[  843.929905]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x50/0x60
[  843.933398]  ? pskb_expand_head+0x2ac/0x300
[  843.936835]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
[  843.940226]  ? pskb_expand_head+0x2ac/0x300
[  843.943580]  inet_frag_reasm_prepare+0xd1/0x240
[  843.946904]  ip_defrag+0x5d4/0x870
[  843.950132]  nf_ct_handle_fragments+0xec/0x130 [nf_conntrack]
[  843.953334]  tcf_ct_act+0x252/0xd90 [act_ct]
[  843.956473]  ? tcf_mirred_act+0x516/0x5a0 [act_mirred]
[  843.959657]  tcf_action_exec+0xa1/0x160
[  843.962823]  fl_classify+0x1db/0x1f0 [cls_flower]
[  843.966010]  ? skb_clone+0x53/0xc0
[  843.969173]  tcf_classify+0x24d/0x420
[  843.972333]  tc_run+0x8f/0xf0
[  843.975465]  __netif_receive_skb_core+0x67a/0x1080
[  843.978634]  ? dev_gro_receive+0x249/0x730
[  843.981759]  __netif_receive_skb_list_core+0x12d/0x260
[  843.984869]  netif_receive_skb_list_internal+0x1cb/0x2f0
[  843.987957]  ? mlx5e_handle_rx_cqe_mpwrq_rep+0xfa/0x1a0 [mlx5_core]
[  843.991170]  napi_complete_done+0x72/0x1a0
[  843.994305]  mlx5e_napi_poll+0x28c/0x6d0 [mlx5_core]
[  843.997501]  __napi_poll+0x25/0x1b0
[  844.000627]  net_rx_action+0x256/0x330
[  844.003705]  __do_softirq+0xb3/0x29b
[  844.006718]  irq_exit_rcu+0x9e/0xc0
[  844.009672]  common_interrupt+0x86/0xa0
[  844.012537]  &lt;/IRQ&gt;
[  844.015285]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[  844.017937]  asm_common_interrupt+0x26/0x40
[  844.020591] RIP: 0010:acpi_safe_halt+0x1b/0x20
[  844.023247] Code: ff 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 40 00 65 48 8b 04 25 00 18 03 00 48 8b 00 a8 08 75 0c 66 90 0f 00 2d 81 d0 44 00 fb
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52611 | wifi: rtw88: sdio: Honor the host max_req_size in the RX path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52611</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: rtw88: sdio: Honor the host max_req_size in the RX path

Lukas reports skb_over_panic errors on his Banana Pi BPI-CM4 which comes
with an Amlogic A311D (G12B) SoC and a RTL8822CS SDIO wifi/Bluetooth
combo card. The error he observed is identical to what has been fixed
in commit e967229ead0e ("wifi: rtw88: sdio: Check the HISR RX_REQUEST
bit in rtw_sdio_rx_isr()") but that commit didn't fix Lukas' problem.

Lukas found that disabling or limiting RX aggregation works around the
problem for some time (but does not fully fix it). In the following
discussion a few key topics have been discussed which have an impact on
this problem:
- The Amlogic A311D (G12B) SoC has a hardware bug in the SDIO controller
  which prevents DMA transfers. Instead all transfers need to go through
  the controller SRAM which limits transfers to 1536 bytes
- rtw88 chips don't split incoming (RX) packets, so if a big packet is
  received this is forwarded to the host in it's original form
- rtw88 chips can do RX aggregation, meaning more multiple incoming
  packets can be pulled by the host from the card with one MMC/SDIO
  transfer. This Depends on settings in the REG_RXDMA_AGG_PG_TH
  register (BIT_RXDMA_AGG_PG_TH limits the number of packets that will
  be aggregated, BIT_DMA_AGG_TO_V1 configures a timeout for aggregation
  and BIT_EN_PRE_CALC makes the chip honor the limits more effectively)

Use multiple consecutive reads in rtw_sdio_read_port() and limit the
number of bytes which are copied by the host from the card in one
MMC/SDIO transfer. This allows receiving a buffer that's larger than
the hosts max_req_size (number of bytes which can be transferred in
one MMC/SDIO transfer). As a result of this the skb_over_panic error
is gone as the rtw88 driver is now able to receive more than 1536 bytes
from the card (either because the incoming packet is larger than that
or because multiple packets have been aggregated).

In case of an receive errors (-EILSEQ has been observed by Lukas) we
need to drain the remaining data from the card's buffer, otherwise the
card will return corrupt data for the next rtw_sdio_read_port() call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52612 | crypto: scomp - fix req-&amp;gt;dst buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52612</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: scomp - fix req-&gt;dst buffer overflow

The req-&gt;dst buffer size should be checked before copying from the
scomp_scratch-&gt;dst to avoid req-&gt;dst buffer overflow problem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52613 | drivers/thermal/loongson2_thermal: Fix incorrect PTR_ERR() judgment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52613</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drivers/thermal/loongson2_thermal: Fix incorrect PTR_ERR() judgment

PTR_ERR() returns -ENODEV when thermal-zones are undefined, and we need
-ENODEV as the right value for comparison.

Otherwise, tz-&gt;type is NULL when thermal-zones is undefined, resulting
in the following error:

[   12.290030] CPU 1 Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address fffffffffffffff1, era == 900000000355f410, ra == 90000000031579b8
[   12.302877] Oops[#1]:
[   12.305190] CPU: 1 PID: 181 Comm: systemd-udevd Not tainted 6.6.0-rc7+ #5385
[   12.312304] pc 900000000355f410 ra 90000000031579b8 tp 90000001069e8000 sp 90000001069eba10
[   12.320739] a0 0000000000000000 a1 fffffffffffffff1 a2 0000000000000014 a3 0000000000000001
[   12.329173] a4 90000001069eb990 a5 0000000000000001 a6 0000000000001001 a7 900000010003431c
[   12.337606] t0 fffffffffffffff1 t1 54567fd5da9b4fd4 t2 900000010614ec40 t3 00000000000dc901
[   12.346041] t4 0000000000000000 t5 0000000000000004 t6 900000010614ee20 t7 900000000d00b790
[   12.354472] t8 00000000000dc901 u0 54567fd5da9b4fd4 s9 900000000402ae10 s0 900000010614ec40
[   12.362916] s1 90000000039fced0 s2 ffffffffffffffed s3 ffffffffffffffed s4 9000000003acc000
[   12.362931] s5 0000000000000004 s6 fffffffffffff000 s7 0000000000000490 s8 90000001028b2ec8
[   12.362938]    ra: 90000000031579b8 thermal_add_hwmon_sysfs+0x258/0x300
[   12.386411]   ERA: 900000000355f410 strscpy+0xf0/0x160
[   12.391626]  CRMD: 000000b0 (PLV0 -IE -DA +PG DACF=CC DACM=CC -WE)
[   12.397898]  PRMD: 00000004 (PPLV0 +PIE -PWE)
[   12.403678]  EUEN: 00000000 (-FPE -SXE -ASXE -BTE)
[   12.409859]  ECFG: 00071c1c (LIE=2-4,10-12 VS=7)
[   12.415882] ESTAT: 00010000 [PIL] (IS= ECode=1 EsubCode=0)
[   12.415907]  BADV: fffffffffffffff1
[   12.415911]  PRID: 0014a000 (Loongson-64bit, Loongson-2K1000)
[   12.415917] Modules linked in: loongson2_thermal(+) vfat fat uio_pdrv_genirq uio fuse zram zsmalloc
[   12.415950] Process systemd-udevd (pid: 181, threadinfo=00000000358b9718, task=00000000ace72fe3)
[   12.415961] Stack : 0000000000000dc0 54567fd5da9b4fd4 900000000402ae10 9000000002df9358
[   12.415982]         ffffffffffffffed 0000000000000004 9000000107a10aa8 90000001002a3410
[   12.415999]         ffffffffffffffed ffffffffffffffed 9000000107a11268 9000000003157ab0
[   12.416016]         9000000107a10aa8 ffffff80020fc0c8 90000001002a3410 ffffffffffffffed
[   12.416032]         0000000000000024 ffffff80020cc1e8 900000000402b2a0 9000000003acc000
[   12.416048]         90000001002a3410 0000000000000000 ffffff80020f4030 90000001002a3410
[   12.416065]         0000000000000000 9000000002df6808 90000001002a3410 0000000000000000
[   12.416081]         ffffff80020f4030 0000000000000000 90000001002a3410 9000000002df2ba8
[   12.416097]         00000000000000b4 90000001002a34f4 90000001002a3410 0000000000000002
[   12.416114]         ffffff80020f4030 fffffffffffffff0 90000001002a3410 9000000002df2f30
[   12.416131]         ...
[   12.416138] Call Trace:
[   12.416142] [&lt;900000000355f410&gt;] strscpy+0xf0/0x160
[   12.416167] [&lt;90000000031579b8&gt;] thermal_add_hwmon_sysfs+0x258/0x300
[   12.416183] [&lt;9000000003157ab0&gt;] devm_thermal_add_hwmon_sysfs+0x50/0xe0
[   12.416200] [&lt;ffffff80020cc1e8&gt;] loongson2_thermal_probe+0x128/0x200 [loongson2_thermal]
[   12.416232] [&lt;9000000002df6808&gt;] platform_probe+0x68/0x140
[   12.416249] [&lt;9000000002df2ba8&gt;] really_probe+0xc8/0x3c0
[   12.416269] [&lt;9000000002df2f30&gt;] __driver_probe_device+0x90/0x180
[   12.416286] [&lt;9000000002df3058&gt;] driver_probe_device+0x38/0x160
[   12.416302] [&lt;9000000002df33a8&gt;] __driver_attach+0xa8/0x200
[   12.416314] [&lt;9000000002deffec&gt;] bus_for_each_dev+0x8c/0x120
[   12.416330] [&lt;9000000002df198c&gt;] bus_add_driver+0x10c/0x2a0
[   12.416346] [&lt;9000000002df46b4&gt;] driver_register+0x74/0x160
[   12.416358] [&lt;90000000022201a4&gt;] do_one_initcall+0x84/0x220
[   12.416372] [&lt;90000000022f3ab8&gt;] do_init_module+0x58/0x2c0
[
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52614 | PM / devfreq: Fix buffer overflow in trans_stat_show</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52614</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PM / devfreq: Fix buffer overflow in trans_stat_show

Fix buffer overflow in trans_stat_show().

Convert simple snprintf to the more secure scnprintf with size of
PAGE_SIZE.

Add condition checking if we are exceeding PAGE_SIZE and exit early from
loop. Also add at the end a warning that we exceeded PAGE_SIZE and that
stats is disabled.

Return -EFBIG in the case where we don't have enough space to write the
full transition table.

Also document in the ABI that this function can return -EFBIG error.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52615 | hwrng: core - Fix page fault dead lock on mmap-ed hwrng</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52615</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hwrng: core - Fix page fault dead lock on mmap-ed hwrng

There is a dead-lock in the hwrng device read path.  This triggers
when the user reads from /dev/hwrng into memory also mmap-ed from
/dev/hwrng.  The resulting page fault triggers a recursive read
which then dead-locks.

Fix this by using a stack buffer when calling copy_to_user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52616 | crypto: lib/mpi - Fix unexpected pointer access in mpi_ec_init</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52616</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: lib/mpi - Fix unexpected pointer access in mpi_ec_init

When the mpi_ec_ctx structure is initialized, some fields are not
cleared, causing a crash when referencing the field when the
structure was released. Initially, this issue was ignored because
memory for mpi_ec_ctx is allocated with the __GFP_ZERO flag.
For example, this error will be triggered when calculating the
Za value for SM2 separately.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26631 | ipv6: mcast: fix data-race in ipv6_mc_down / mld_ifc_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26631</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: mcast: fix data-race in ipv6_mc_down / mld_ifc_work

idev-&gt;mc_ifc_count can be written over without proper locking.

Originally found by syzbot [1], fix this issue by encapsulating calls
to mld_ifc_stop_work() (and mld_gq_stop_work() for good measure) with
mutex_lock() and mutex_unlock() accordingly as these functions
should only be called with mc_lock per their declarations.

[1]
BUG: KCSAN: data-race in ipv6_mc_down / mld_ifc_work

write to 0xffff88813a80c832 of 1 bytes by task 3771 on cpu 0:
 mld_ifc_stop_work net/ipv6/mcast.c:1080 [inline]
 ipv6_mc_down+0x10a/0x280 net/ipv6/mcast.c:2725
 addrconf_ifdown+0xe32/0xf10 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3949
 addrconf_notify+0x310/0x980
 notifier_call_chain kernel/notifier.c:93 [inline]
 raw_notifier_call_chain+0x6b/0x1c0 kernel/notifier.c:461
 __dev_notify_flags+0x205/0x3d0
 dev_change_flags+0xab/0xd0 net/core/dev.c:8685
 do_setlink+0x9f6/0x2430 net/core/rtnetlink.c:2916
 rtnl_group_changelink net/core/rtnetlink.c:3458 [inline]
 __rtnl_newlink net/core/rtnetlink.c:3717 [inline]
 rtnl_newlink+0xbb3/0x1670 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3754
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x807/0x8c0 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6558
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x126/0x220 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2545
 rtnetlink_rcv+0x1c/0x20 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6576
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1342 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x589/0x650 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1368
 netlink_sendmsg+0x66e/0x770 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1910
 ...

write to 0xffff88813a80c832 of 1 bytes by task 22 on cpu 1:
 mld_ifc_work+0x54c/0x7b0 net/ipv6/mcast.c:2653
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:2627 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0x5b8/0xa30 kernel/workqueue.c:2700
 worker_thread+0x525/0x730 kernel/workqueue.c:2781
 ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26632 | block: Fix iterating over an empty bio with bio_for_each_folio_all</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26632</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

block: Fix iterating over an empty bio with bio_for_each_folio_all

If the bio contains no data, bio_first_folio() calls page_folio() on a
NULL pointer and oopses.  Move the test that we've reached the end of
the bio from bio_next_folio() to bio_first_folio().

[axboe: add unlikely() to error case]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26633 | ip6_tunnel: fix NEXTHDR_FRAGMENT handling in ip6_tnl_parse_tlv_enc_lim()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26633</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ip6_tunnel: fix NEXTHDR_FRAGMENT handling in ip6_tnl_parse_tlv_enc_lim()

syzbot pointed out [1] that NEXTHDR_FRAGMENT handling is broken.

Reading frag_off can only be done if we pulled enough bytes
to skb-&gt;head. Currently we might access garbage.

[1]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in ip6_tnl_parse_tlv_enc_lim+0x94f/0xbb0
ip6_tnl_parse_tlv_enc_lim+0x94f/0xbb0
ipxip6_tnl_xmit net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:1326 [inline]
ip6_tnl_start_xmit+0xab2/0x1a70 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:1432
__netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4940 [inline]
netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4954 [inline]
xmit_one net/core/dev.c:3548 [inline]
dev_hard_start_xmit+0x247/0xa10 net/core/dev.c:3564
__dev_queue_xmit+0x33b8/0x5130 net/core/dev.c:4349
dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3134 [inline]
neigh_connected_output+0x569/0x660 net/core/neighbour.c:1592
neigh_output include/net/neighbour.h:542 [inline]
ip6_finish_output2+0x23a9/0x2b30 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:137
ip6_finish_output+0x855/0x12b0 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:222
NF_HOOK_COND include/linux/netfilter.h:303 [inline]
ip6_output+0x323/0x610 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:243
dst_output include/net/dst.h:451 [inline]
ip6_local_out+0xe9/0x140 net/ipv6/output_core.c:155
ip6_send_skb net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1952 [inline]
ip6_push_pending_frames+0x1f9/0x560 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1972
rawv6_push_pending_frames+0xbe8/0xdf0 net/ipv6/raw.c:582
rawv6_sendmsg+0x2b66/0x2e70 net/ipv6/raw.c:920
inet_sendmsg+0x105/0x190 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:847
sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
__sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
____sys_sendmsg+0x9c2/0xd60 net/socket.c:2584
___sys_sendmsg+0x28d/0x3c0 net/socket.c:2638
__sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2667 [inline]
__do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2676 [inline]
__se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2674 [inline]
__x64_sys_sendmsg+0x307/0x490 net/socket.c:2674
do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
do_syscall_64+0x44/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Uninit was created at:
slab_post_alloc_hook+0x129/0xa70 mm/slab.h:768
slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3478 [inline]
__kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x5c9/0x970 mm/slub.c:3517
__do_kmalloc_node mm/slab_common.c:1006 [inline]
__kmalloc_node_track_caller+0x118/0x3c0 mm/slab_common.c:1027
kmalloc_reserve+0x249/0x4a0 net/core/skbuff.c:582
pskb_expand_head+0x226/0x1a00 net/core/skbuff.c:2098
__pskb_pull_tail+0x13b/0x2310 net/core/skbuff.c:2655
pskb_may_pull_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:2673 [inline]
pskb_may_pull include/linux/skbuff.h:2681 [inline]
ip6_tnl_parse_tlv_enc_lim+0x901/0xbb0 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:408
ipxip6_tnl_xmit net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:1326 [inline]
ip6_tnl_start_xmit+0xab2/0x1a70 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:1432
__netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4940 [inline]
netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4954 [inline]
xmit_one net/core/dev.c:3548 [inline]
dev_hard_start_xmit+0x247/0xa10 net/core/dev.c:3564
__dev_queue_xmit+0x33b8/0x5130 net/core/dev.c:4349
dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3134 [inline]
neigh_connected_output+0x569/0x660 net/core/neighbour.c:1592
neigh_output include/net/neighbour.h:542 [inline]
ip6_finish_output2+0x23a9/0x2b30 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:137
ip6_finish_output+0x855/0x12b0 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:222
NF_HOOK_COND include/linux/netfilter.h:303 [inline]
ip6_output+0x323/0x610 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:243
dst_output include/net/dst.h:451 [inline]
ip6_local_out+0xe9/0x140 net/ipv6/output_core.c:155
ip6_send_skb net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1952 [inline]
ip6_push_pending_frames+0x1f9/0x560 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1972
rawv6_push_pending_frames+0xbe8/0xdf0 net/ipv6/raw.c:582
rawv6_sendmsg+0x2b66/0x2e70 net/ipv6/raw.c:920
inet_sendmsg+0x105/0x190 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:847
sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
__sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
____sys_sendmsg+0x9c2/0xd60 net/socket.c:2584
___sys_sendmsg+0x28d/0x3c0 net/socket.c:2638
__sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2667 [inline]
__do_sys_sendms
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26634 | net: fix removing a namespace with conflicting altnames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26634</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: fix removing a namespace with conflicting altnames

Mark reports a BUG() when a net namespace is removed.

    kernel BUG at net/core/dev.c:11520!

Physical interfaces moved outside of init_net get "refunded"
to init_net when that namespace disappears. The main interface
name may get overwritten in the process if it would have
conflicted. We need to also discard all conflicting altnames.
Recent fixes addressed ensuring that altnames get moved
with the main interface, which surfaced this problem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26635 | llc: Drop support for ETH_P_TR_802_2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26635</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

llc: Drop support for ETH_P_TR_802_2.

syzbot reported an uninit-value bug below. [0]

llc supports ETH_P_802_2 (0x0004) and used to support ETH_P_TR_802_2
(0x0011), and syzbot abused the latter to trigger the bug.

  write$tun(r0, &amp;(0x7f0000000040)={@val={0x0, 0x11}, @val, @mpls={[], @llc={@snap={0xaa, 0x1, ')', "90e5dd"}}}}, 0x16)

llc_conn_handler() initialises local variables {saddr,daddr}.mac
based on skb in llc_pdu_decode_sa()/llc_pdu_decode_da() and passes
them to __llc_lookup().

However, the initialisation is done only when skb-&gt;protocol is
htons(ETH_P_802_2), otherwise, __llc_lookup_established() and
__llc_lookup_listener() will read garbage.

The missing initialisation existed prior to commit 211ed865108e
("net: delete all instances of special processing for token ring").

It removed the part to kick out the token ring stuff but forgot to
close the door allowing ETH_P_TR_802_2 packets to sneak into llc_rcv().

Let's remove llc_tr_packet_type and complete the deprecation.

[0]:
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in __llc_lookup_established+0xe9d/0xf90
 __llc_lookup_established+0xe9d/0xf90
 __llc_lookup net/llc/llc_conn.c:611 [inline]
 llc_conn_handler+0x4bd/0x1360 net/llc/llc_conn.c:791
 llc_rcv+0xfbb/0x14a0 net/llc/llc_input.c:206
 __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:5527 [inline]
 __netif_receive_skb+0x1a6/0x5a0 net/core/dev.c:5641
 netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:5727 [inline]
 netif_receive_skb+0x58/0x660 net/core/dev.c:5786
 tun_rx_batched+0x3ee/0x980 drivers/net/tun.c:1555
 tun_get_user+0x53af/0x66d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2002
 tun_chr_write_iter+0x3af/0x5d0 drivers/net/tun.c:2048
 call_write_iter include/linux/fs.h:2020 [inline]
 new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:491 [inline]
 vfs_write+0x8ef/0x1490 fs/read_write.c:584
 ksys_write+0x20f/0x4c0 fs/read_write.c:637
 __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:649 [inline]
 __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:646 [inline]
 __x64_sys_write+0x93/0xd0 fs/read_write.c:646
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:51 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x44/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:82
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

Local variable daddr created at:
 llc_conn_handler+0x53/0x1360 net/llc/llc_conn.c:783
 llc_rcv+0xfbb/0x14a0 net/llc/llc_input.c:206

CPU: 1 PID: 5004 Comm: syz-executor994 Not tainted 6.6.0-syzkaller-14500-g1c41041124bd #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/09/2023</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26636 | llc: make llc_ui_sendmsg() more robust against bonding changes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26636</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

llc: make llc_ui_sendmsg() more robust against bonding changes

syzbot was able to trick llc_ui_sendmsg(), allocating an skb with no
headroom, but subsequently trying to push 14 bytes of Ethernet header [1]

Like some others, llc_ui_sendmsg() releases the socket lock before
calling sock_alloc_send_skb().
Then it acquires it again, but does not redo all the sanity checks
that were performed.

This fix:

- Uses LL_RESERVED_SPACE() to reserve space.
- Check all conditions again after socket lock is held again.
- Do not account Ethernet header for mtu limitation.

[1]

skbuff: skb_under_panic: text:ffff800088baa334 len:1514 put:14 head:ffff0000c9c37000 data:ffff0000c9c36ff2 tail:0x5dc end:0x6c0 dev:bond0

 kernel BUG at net/core/skbuff.c:193 !
Internal error: Oops - BUG: 00000000f2000800 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 PID: 6875 Comm: syz-executor.0 Not tainted 6.7.0-rc8-syzkaller-00101-g0802e17d9aca-dirty #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/17/2023
pstate: 60400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
 pc : skb_panic net/core/skbuff.c:189 [inline]
 pc : skb_under_panic+0x13c/0x140 net/core/skbuff.c:203
 lr : skb_panic net/core/skbuff.c:189 [inline]
 lr : skb_under_panic+0x13c/0x140 net/core/skbuff.c:203
sp : ffff800096f97000
x29: ffff800096f97010 x28: ffff80008cc8d668 x27: dfff800000000000
x26: ffff0000cb970c90 x25: 00000000000005dc x24: ffff0000c9c36ff2
x23: ffff0000c9c37000 x22: 00000000000005ea x21: 00000000000006c0
x20: 000000000000000e x19: ffff800088baa334 x18: 1fffe000368261ce
x17: ffff80008e4ed000 x16: ffff80008a8310f8 x15: 0000000000000001
x14: 1ffff00012df2d58 x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 0000000000000000
x11: 0000000000000001 x10: 0000000000ff0100 x9 : e28a51f1087e8400
x8 : e28a51f1087e8400 x7 : ffff80008028f8d0 x6 : 0000000000000000
x5 : 0000000000000001 x4 : 0000000000000001 x3 : ffff800082b78714
x2 : 0000000000000001 x1 : 0000000100000000 x0 : 0000000000000089
Call trace:
  skb_panic net/core/skbuff.c:189 [inline]
  skb_under_panic+0x13c/0x140 net/core/skbuff.c:203
  skb_push+0xf0/0x108 net/core/skbuff.c:2451
  eth_header+0x44/0x1f8 net/ethernet/eth.c:83
  dev_hard_header include/linux/netdevice.h:3188 [inline]
  llc_mac_hdr_init+0x110/0x17c net/llc/llc_output.c:33
  llc_sap_action_send_xid_c+0x170/0x344 net/llc/llc_s_ac.c:85
  llc_exec_sap_trans_actions net/llc/llc_sap.c:153 [inline]
  llc_sap_next_state net/llc/llc_sap.c:182 [inline]
  llc_sap_state_process+0x1ec/0x774 net/llc/llc_sap.c:209
  llc_build_and_send_xid_pkt+0x12c/0x1c0 net/llc/llc_sap.c:270
  llc_ui_sendmsg+0x7bc/0xb1c net/llc/af_llc.c:997
  sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
  __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
  sock_sendmsg+0x194/0x274 net/socket.c:767
  splice_to_socket+0x7cc/0xd58 fs/splice.c:881
  do_splice_from fs/splice.c:933 [inline]
  direct_splice_actor+0xe4/0x1c0 fs/splice.c:1142
  splice_direct_to_actor+0x2a0/0x7e4 fs/splice.c:1088
  do_splice_direct+0x20c/0x348 fs/splice.c:1194
  do_sendfile+0x4bc/0xc70 fs/read_write.c:1254
  __do_sys_sendfile64 fs/read_write.c:1322 [inline]
  __se_sys_sendfile64 fs/read_write.c:1308 [inline]
  __arm64_sys_sendfile64+0x160/0x3b4 fs/read_write.c:1308
  __invoke_syscall arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:37 [inline]
  invoke_syscall+0x98/0x2b8 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:51
  el0_svc_common+0x130/0x23c arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:136
  do_el0_svc+0x48/0x58 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:155
  el0_svc+0x54/0x158 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:678
  el0t_64_sync_handler+0x84/0xfc arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:696
  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:595
Code: aa1803e6 aa1903e7 a90023f5 94792f6a (d4210000)</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26637 | wifi: ath11k: rely on mac80211 debugfs handling for vif</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26637</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath11k: rely on mac80211 debugfs handling for vif

mac80211 started to delete debugfs entries in certain cases, causing a
ath11k to crash when it tried to delete the entries later. Fix this by
relying on mac80211 to delete the entries when appropriate and adding
them from the vif_add_debugfs handler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26638 | nbd: always initialize struct msghdr completely</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26638</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nbd: always initialize struct msghdr completely

syzbot complains that msg-&gt;msg_get_inq value can be uninitialized [1]

struct msghdr got many new fields recently, we should always make
sure their values is zero by default.

[1]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in tcp_recvmsg+0x686/0xac0 net/ipv4/tcp.c:2571
  tcp_recvmsg+0x686/0xac0 net/ipv4/tcp.c:2571
  inet_recvmsg+0x131/0x580 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:879
  sock_recvmsg_nosec net/socket.c:1044 [inline]
  sock_recvmsg+0x12b/0x1e0 net/socket.c:1066
  __sock_xmit+0x236/0x5c0 drivers/block/nbd.c:538
  nbd_read_reply drivers/block/nbd.c:732 [inline]
  recv_work+0x262/0x3100 drivers/block/nbd.c:863
  process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:2627 [inline]
  process_scheduled_works+0x104e/0x1e70 kernel/workqueue.c:2700
  worker_thread+0xf45/0x1490 kernel/workqueue.c:2781
  kthread+0x3ed/0x540 kernel/kthread.c:388
  ret_from_fork+0x66/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:242

Local variable msg created at:
  __sock_xmit+0x4c/0x5c0 drivers/block/nbd.c:513
  nbd_read_reply drivers/block/nbd.c:732 [inline]
  recv_work+0x262/0x3100 drivers/block/nbd.c:863

CPU: 1 PID: 7465 Comm: kworker/u5:1 Not tainted 6.7.0-rc7-syzkaller-00041-gf016f7547aee #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/17/2023
Workqueue: nbd5-recv recv_work</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:28:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1604 | Incorrect authorization in BMC Control-M</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1604</link><description>Improper authorization in the report management and creation module of BMC Control-M branches 9.0.20 and 9.0.21 allows logged-in users to read and make unauthorized changes to any reports available within the application, even without proper permissions. The attacker must know the unique identifier of the report they want to manipulate.

Fix for 9.0.20 branch was released in version 9.0.20.238. Fix for 9.0.21 branch was released in version 9.0.21.201.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1605 | DLL side-loading in BMC Control-M</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1605</link><description>BMC Control-M  branches 9.0.20 and 9.0.21 upon user login load all Dynamic Link Libraries (DLL)  from a directory that grants Write and Read permissions to all users. Leveraging it leads to loading of a potentially malicious libraries, which will execute with the application's privileges. 

Fix for 9.0.20 branch was released in version 9.0.20.238. Fix for 9.0.21 branch was released in version 9.0.21.201.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1606 | HTML injection in BMC Control-M</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1606</link><description>Lack of input sanitization in BMC Control-M  branches 9.0.20 and 9.0.21 allows logged-in users for manipulation of generated  web pages via injection of  HTML code. This might lead to a successful phishing attack for example by tricking users into using a hyperlink pointing to a website controlled by an attacker.

Fix for 9.0.20 branch was released in version 9.0.20.238. Fix for 9.0.21 branch was released in version 9.0.21.200.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28039 | Improper restriction of XML external entity references vulnerability exists in FitNesse all releases, which allows a remote unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28039</link><description>Improper restriction of XML external entity references vulnerability exists in FitNesse all releases, which allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information, alter data, or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 08:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21824 | Improper authentication vulnerability in exists in multiple printers and scanners which implement Web Based Management provided by BROTHER I...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21824</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in exists in multiple printers and scanners which implement Web Based Management provided by BROTHER INDUSTRIES, LTD. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent user who can access the product may impersonate an administrative user. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 08:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22475 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in multiple printers and scanners which implement Web Based Management provided by BROTHER INDUSTRI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22475</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in multiple printers and scanners which implement Web Based Management provided by BROTHER INDUSTRIES, LTD. allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to perform unintended operations on the affected product. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the respective vendors listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 08:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27974 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in FUJIFILM printers which implement CentreWare Internet Services or Internet Services allows a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27974</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in FUJIFILM printers which implement CentreWare Internet Services or Internet Services allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to alter user information. In the case the user is an administrator, the settings such as the administrator's ID, password, etc. may be altered. As for the details of affected product names, model numbers, and versions, refer to the information provided by the vendor listed under [References].</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 08:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28128 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in FitNesse releases prior to 20220319, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28128</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in FitNesse releases prior to 20220319, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is using the product and accessing a link with a specially crafted certain parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23604 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in FitNesse all releases, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23604</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in FitNesse all releases, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is using the product and accessing a link with specially crafted multiple parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28125 | FitNesse all releases allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28125</link><description>FitNesse all releases allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29156 | In OpenStack Murano through 16.0.0, when YAQL before 3.0.0 is used, the Murano service's MuranoPL extension to the YAQL language fails to sa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29156</link><description>In OpenStack Murano through 16.0.0, when YAQL before 3.0.0 is used, the Murano service's MuranoPL extension to the YAQL language fails to sanitize the supplied environment, leading to potential leakage of sensitive service account information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 06:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29154 | danielmiessler fabric through 1.3.0 allows installer/client/gui/static/js/index.js XSS because of innerHTML mishandling, such as in htmlToPl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29154</link><description>danielmiessler fabric through 1.3.0 allows installer/client/gui/static/js/index.js XSS because of innerHTML mishandling, such as in htmlToPlainText.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29151 | Rocket.Chat.Audit through 5ad78e8 depends on filecachetools, which does not exist in PyPI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29151</link><description>Rocket.Chat.Audit through 5ad78e8 depends on filecachetools, which does not exist in PyPI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25099 | In the CryptX module before 0.062 for Perl, gcm_decrypt_verify() and chacha20poly1305_decrypt_verify() do not verify the tag.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25099</link><description>In the CryptX module before 0.062 for Perl, gcm_decrypt_verify() and chacha20poly1305_decrypt_verify() do not verify the tag.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47154 | The Net::CIDR::Lite module before 0.22 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters at the beginning of an IP address stri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47154</link><description>The Net::CIDR::Lite module before 0.22 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters at the beginning of an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47155 | The Net::IPV4Addr module 0.10 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47155</link><description>The Net::IPV4Addr module 0.10 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47156 | The Net::IPAddress::Util module before 5.000 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47156</link><description>The Net::IPAddress::Util module before 5.000 for Perl does not properly consider extraneous zero characters in an IP address string, which (in some situations) allows attackers to bypass access control that is based on IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47157 | The Kossy module before 0.60 for Perl allows JSON hijacking because of X-Requested-With mishandling.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47157</link><description>The Kossy module before 0.60 for Perl allows JSON hijacking because of X-Requested-With mishandling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27757 | flusity CMS through 2.45 allows tools/addons_model.php Gallery Name XSS. The reporter indicates that this product "ceased its development as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27757</link><description>flusity CMS through 2.45 allows tools/addons_model.php Gallery Name XSS. The reporter indicates that this product "ceased its development as of February 2024."</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28745 | Improper export of Android application components issue exists in 'ABEMA' App for Android prior to 10.65.0 allowing another app installed on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28745</link><description>Improper export of Android application components issue exists in 'ABEMA' App for Android prior to 10.65.0 allowing another app installed on the user's device to access an arbitrary URL on 'ABEMA' App for Android via Intent. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary website may be displayed on the app, and as a result, the user may become a victim of a phishing attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47037 | Siklu TG Terragraph devices before 2.1.1 allow attackers to discover valid, randomly generated credentials via GetCredentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47037</link><description>Siklu TG Terragraph devices before 2.1.1 allow attackers to discover valid, randomly generated credentials via GetCredentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47036 | Siklu TG Terragraph devices before approximately 2.1.1 have a hardcoded root password that has been revealed via a brute force attack on an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47036</link><description>Siklu TG Terragraph devices before approximately 2.1.1 have a hardcoded root password that has been revealed via a brute force attack on an MD5 hash. It can be used for "debug login" by an admin. NOTE: the vulnerability is not fixed by the 2.1.1 firmware; instead, it is fixed in newer hardware, which would typically be used with firmware 2.1.1 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2581 | Tenda AC10 SetStaticRouteCfg fromSetRouteStatic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function fromSetRouteStatic of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257081 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 03:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24539 | FusionPBX before 5.2.0 does not validate a session.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24539</link><description>FusionPBX before 5.2.0 does not validate a session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2577 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-employee.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2577</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /update-employee.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257080.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2575 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-details.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2575</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /task-details.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257078 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2576 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-admin.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2576</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /update-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to authorization bypass. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257079.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52159 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in gross 0.9.3 through 1.x before 1.0.4 allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52159</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in gross 0.9.3 through 1.x before 1.0.4 allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (grossd daemon crash) or potentially execute arbitrary code in grossd via crafted SMTP transaction parameters that cause an incorrect strncat for a log entry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:05:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24230 | Komm.One CMS 10.4.2.14 has a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the Velocity template engine. It allows remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24230</link><description>Komm.One CMS 10.4.2.14 has a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the Velocity template engine. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a URL that specifies java.lang.Runtime in conjunction with getRuntime().exec followed by an OS command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2574 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System edit-task.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2574</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257077 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2572 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-details.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /task-details.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257075.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2573 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System task-info.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2573</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /task-info.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257076.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 01:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39223 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in CGIs included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39223</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in CGIs included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39933 | Insufficient verification vulnerability exists in Broadcast Mail CGI (pmc.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 product...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39933</link><description>Insufficient verification vulnerability exists in Broadcast Mail CGI (pmc.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user who can upload files through the product may execute an arbitrary executable file with the web server's execution privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40160 | Directory traversal vulnerability exists in Mailing List Search CGI (pmmls.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 produc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40160</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability exists in Mailing List Search CGI (pmmls.exe) included in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40747 | Directory traversal vulnerability exists in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products' CGIs included in Internal Simple Webserver. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40747</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability exists in A.K.I Software's PMailServer/PMailServer2 products' CGIs included in Internal Simple Webserver. If this vulnerability is exploited, a  remote attacker may access arbitrary files outside DocumentRoot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2571 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System manage-admin.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage-admin.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257074 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23138 | A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed through Autodesk DWG TrueView can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23138</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG file when parsed through Autodesk DWG TrueView can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23139 | An Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk FBX Review version 1.5.3.0 and prior may lead to code execution or information disclosure t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23139</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk FBX Review version 1.5.3.0 and prior may lead to code execution or information disclosure through maliciously crafted ActionScript Byte Code “ABC” files. ABC files are created by the Flash compiler and contain executable code. This vulnerability in conjunction with other vulnerabilities could lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2570 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System edit-task.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit-task.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257073 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2569 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System admin-manage-user.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2569</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin-manage-user.php. The manipulation leads to execution after redirect. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257072.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2568 | heyewei JFinalCMS Custom Data Page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2568</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in heyewei JFinalCMS 5.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/div_data/delete?divId=9 of the component Custom Data Page. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257071.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 23:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2567 | jurecapuder AndroidWeatherApp Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2567</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in jurecapuder AndroidWeatherApp 1.0.0 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257070 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: The code maintainer was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. Instead the GitHub repository got deleted after a few days. We have to assume that the product is not supported anymore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27961 | WordPress AntiSpam for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codekraft AntiSpam for Contact Form 7 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AntiSpam for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 0.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27960 | WordPress Email Subscription Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27960</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in I Thirteen Web Solution Email Subscription Popup allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Email Subscription Popup: from n/a through 1.2.20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27957 | WordPress Pie Register plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27957</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pie Register.This issue affects Pie Register: from n/a through 3.8.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27958 | WordPress Visualizer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27958</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeisle Visualizer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Visualizer: from n/a through 3.10.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27959 | WordPress APIExperts Square for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27959</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wpexpertsio WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management: from n/a through 4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25591 | WordPress WP Editor plugin &amp;lt;=1.2.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25591</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Benjamin Rojas WP Editor.This issue affects WP Editor: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25903 | WordPress Frontend File Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 22.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25903</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in N-Media Frontend File Manager.This issue affects Frontend File Manager: from n/a through 22.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24867 | WordPress WP Stats Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24867</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Osamaesh WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic).This issue affects WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic): from n/a through 6.9.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25933 | WordPress PeproDev Ultimate Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25933</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev Ultimate Invoice.This issue affects PeproDev Ultimate Invoice: from n/a through 1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2566 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform get_extension_yl.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2566</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240313. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/client/get_extension_yl.php. The manipulation of the argument imei leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257065 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2565 | PandaXGO PandaX File Extension upload.go unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2565</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /apps/system/router/upload.go of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257064.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2564 | PandaXGO PandaX user.go ExportUser path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function ExportUser of the file /apps/system/api/user.go. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257063.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2563 | PandaXGO PandaX upload.go DeleteImage path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2563</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function DeleteImage of the file /apps/system/router/upload.go. The manipulation of the argument fileName with the input ../../../../../../../../../tmp/1.txt leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257062 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 12:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2562 | PandaXGO PandaX role_menu.go InsertRole sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2562</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PandaXGO PandaX up to 20240310. This affects the function InsertRole of the file /apps/system/services/role_menu.go. The manipulation of the argument roleKey leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257061 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2561 | 74CMS Company Logo Index.php#sendCompanyLogo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2561</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 74CMS 3.28.0. Affected by this issue is the function sendCompanyLogo of the file /controller/company/Index.php#sendCompanyLogo of the component Company Logo Handler. The manipulation of the argument imgBase64 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257060.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 11:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2560 | Tenda AC18 SysToolRestoreSet fromSysToolRestoreSet cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2560</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSysToolRestoreSet of the file /goform/SysToolRestoreSet. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257059. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 10:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2559 | Tenda AC18 SysToolReboot fromSysToolReboot cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2559</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function fromSysToolReboot of the file /goform/SysToolReboot. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2558 | Tenda AC18 execCommand formexeCommand stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257057 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2557 | kishor-23 Food Waste Management System admin.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2557</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kishor-23 Food Waste Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/admin.php. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257056. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2556 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2556</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257055.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2555 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2555</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file update-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257054 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2554 | SourceCodester Employee Task Management System update-employee.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2554</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file update-employee.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257053 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2553 | SourceCodester Product Review Rating System Rate Product cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2553</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Product Review Rating System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Rate Product Handler. The manipulation of the argument Your Name/Comment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257052.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2547 | Tenda AC18 R7WebsSecurityHandler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2547</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function R7WebsSecurityHandler. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257000. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2546 | Tenda AC18 fromSetWirelessRepeat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC18 15.13.07.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256999. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 01:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2535 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2535</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256972. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 01:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2534 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2534</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256971. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 23:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2533 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2533</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256970 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 22:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2532 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2532</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update-users.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256969 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 22:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2531 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2531</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256968. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 21:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2530 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2530</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256967. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 21:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2529 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2529</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256966 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 20:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2528 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System update-rooms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2528</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update-rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256965 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2527 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2527</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256964. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:07:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2526 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System rooms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2526</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/rooms.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256963. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2525 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2525</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256962 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2524 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2524</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/receipt.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256961 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2523 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2523</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256960. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2522 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System booktime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2522</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/booktime.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256959. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2521 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2521</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256958 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2520 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System bookdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2520</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/bookdate.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256957 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2519 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System navbar.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2519</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file navbar.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256956. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 14:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2518 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2518</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256955. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2517 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System book_history.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2517</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file book_history.php. The manipulation of the argument del_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256954 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 12:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2516 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2516</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256953 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 11:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2515 | MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System home.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2515</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MAGESH-K21 Online-College-Event-Hall-Reservation-System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file home.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256952. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1857 | The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1857</link><description>The Ultimate Gift Cards for WooCommerce – Create, Redeem &amp; Manage Digital Gift Certificates with Personalized Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 via the wps_wgm_preview_email_template(). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read password protected and draft posts that may contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22513 | djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22513</link><description>djangorestframework-simplejwt version 5.3.1 and before is vulnerable to information disclosure. A user can access web application resources even after their account has been disabled due to missing user validation checks via the for_user method.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28640 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28640</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service (D0S) via the command field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28639 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28639</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in TOTOLink X5000R V9.1.0u.6118-B20201102 and A7000R V9.1.0u.6115-B20201022, allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the IP field.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 06:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24156 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24156</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gnuboard g6 before Github commit 58c737a263ac0c523592fd87ff71b9e3c07d7cf5, allows remote attackers execute arbitrary code via the wr_content parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1685 | The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1685</link><description>The Social Media Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input through the attachmentUrl parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1733 | The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1733</link><description>The Word Replacer Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the word_replacer_ultra() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary content on the affected WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28070 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28070</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) attack due to insufficient input validation. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28069 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28069</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.0.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an information disclosure attack due to improper configuration. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and potentially conduct unauthorized actions within the vulnerable component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36483 | An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app throu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36483</link><description>An authorization bypass was discovered in the Carrier MASmobile Classic application through 1.16.18 for Android, MASmobile Classic app through 1.7.24 for iOS, and MAS ASP.Net Services through 1.9. It can be achieved via session ID prediction, allowing remote attackers to retrieve sensitive data including customer data, security system status, and event history. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. The affected products cannot simply be updated; they must be removed, but can be replaced by other Carrier software as explained in the Carrier advisory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22259 | CVE-2024-22259: Spring Framework URL Parsing with Host Validation (2nd report)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22259</link><description>Applications that use UriComponentsBuilder in Spring Framework to parse an externally provided URL (e.g. through a query parameter) AND perform validation checks on the host of the parsed URL may be vulnerable to a  open redirect https://cwe.mitre.org/data/definitions/601.html  attack or to a SSRF attack if the URL is used after passing validation checks.

This is the same as  CVE-2024-22243 https://spring.io/security/cve-2024-22243 , but with different input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23523 | WordPress Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.2 - Contributor+ Arbitrary User Meta Data Retrieval vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23523</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Elementor Pro.This issue affects Elementor Pro: from n/a through 3.19.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24845 | WordPress Post Thumbnail Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24845</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Sewpafly Post Thumbnail Editor.This issue affects Post Thumbnail Editor: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 04:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6525 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6525</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This primarily affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1239 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1239</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2042 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2042</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2294 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2294</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.7 via the backup_name parameter in the backuply_download_backup function. This makes it possible for attackers to have an account with only activate_plugins capability to access arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information. This only impacts sites hosted on Windows servers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2308 | The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2308</link><description>The ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button link in the EliSlider in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51474 | WordPress TerraClassifieds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51474</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pixelemu TerraClassifieds.This issue affects TerraClassifieds: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51486 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder, Create invoices, packing slips and more plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.101 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51486</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RedNao WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Invoice Builder: from n/a through 1.2.101.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51487 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.32 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51487</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz: from n/a through 1.2.32.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27194 | WordPress Fontific plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.6 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27194</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andrei Ivasiuc Fontific | Google Fonts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fontific | Google Fonts: from n/a through 0.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27195 | WordPress Watermark RELOADED plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27195</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sandi Verdev Watermark RELOADED allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Watermark RELOADED: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27197 | WordPress BeePress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9.8 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27197</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bee BeePress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BeePress: from n/a through 6.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51407 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51407</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rocket Elements Split Test For Elementor.This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51489 | WordPress Crowdsignal Polls &amp;amp; Ratings plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51489</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic, Inc. Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more.This issue affects Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51491 | WordPress Depicter Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51491</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Averta Depicter Slider.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51510 | WordPress Export Media URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51510</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Atlas Gondal Export Media URLs.This issue affects Export Media URLs: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51512 | WordPress Product Table by WBW plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51512</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WBW Product Table by WBW.This issue affects Product Table by WBW: from n/a through 1.8.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51521 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.18 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51521</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.1.18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 01:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>