<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:26:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12660 | IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate IOCTL AscRegistryFilter.sys 0x8001E018 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12660</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate up to 17.0.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function 0x8001E018 in the library AscRegistryFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12658 | IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate IOCTL AscRegistryFilter.sys 0x8001E01C null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12658</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate up to 17.0.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function 0x8001E01C in the library AscRegistryFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12659 | IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate IOCTL AscRegistryFilter.sys 0x8001E004 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12659</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate up to 17.0.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function 0x8001E004 in the library AscRegistryFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10095 | Progress UI for WPF format provider unsafe deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10095</link><description>In Progress Telerik UI for WPF versions prior to 2024 Q4 (2024.4.1213), a code execution attack is possible through an insecure deserialization vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11144 | Race Condition with LightFTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11144</link><description>The server lacks thread safety and can be crashed by anomalous data sent by an anonymous user from a remote network. The crash causes the FTP service to become unavailable, affecting all users and processes that rely on it for file transfers. If the crash occurs during file upload or download, it could lead to incomplete file transfers, potentially corrupting data. The repeated crash might also affect the stability of the underlying system, especially if it leads to resource leaks or affects other services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12656 | FabulaTech USB over Network IOCT ftusbbus2.sys 0x220448 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12656</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FabulaTech USB over Network 6.0.6.1. This affects the function 0x220448 in the library ftusbbus2.sys of the component IOCT Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12657 | IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate IOCTL AscRegistryFilter.sys 0x8001E000 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12657</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in IObit Advanced SystemCare Utimate up to 17.0.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function 0x8001E000 in the library AscRegistryFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4762 | An improper validation vulnerability was reported in the firmware update mechanism of LADM and LDCC that could allow a local attacker to esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4762</link><description>An improper validation vulnerability was reported in the firmware update mechanism of LADM and LDCC that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6001 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability was reported in LADM that could allow a network attacker with the ability to redirect an up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6001</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability was reported in LADM that could allow a network attacker with the ability to redirect an update request to a remote server and execute code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8058 | An improper parsing vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow a crafted file in the FileZ directory to read arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8058</link><description>An improper parsing vulnerability was reported in the FileZ client that could allow a crafted file in the FileZ directory to read arbitrary files on the device due to URL preloading.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11358 | Insecure Android File Provider Paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11358</link><description>Mattermost Android Mobile Apps versions &lt;=2.21.0 fail to properly configure file providers which allows an attacker with local access to access files via file provider.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12655 | FabulaTech USB over Network IOCT ftusbbus2.sys 0x220420 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12655</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FabulaTech USB over Network 6.0.6.1. Affected by this issue is the function 0x220420 in the library ftusbbus2.sys of the component IOCT Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12654 | FabulaTech USB over Network IOCT ftusbbus2.sys 0x220408 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FabulaTech USB over Network 6.0.6.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function 0x220408 in the library ftusbbus2.sys of the component IOCT Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54357 | WordPress Avada theme &amp;lt;= 7.11.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54357</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeFusion Avada.This issue affects Avada: from n/a through 7.11.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54376 | WordPress EazyDocs plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54376</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Spider-themes EazyDocs.This issue affects EazyDocs: from n/a through 2.5.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55999 | WordPress XML Multilanguage Sitemap Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55999</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Marco Giannini XML Multilanguage Sitemap Generator.This issue affects XML Multilanguage Sitemap Generator: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56003 | WordPress Caldera SMTP Mailer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56003</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in David Cramer Caldera SMTP Mailer.This issue affects Caldera SMTP Mailer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54283 | WordPress SeedProd Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 6.18.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SeedProd LLC SeedProd Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SeedProd Pro: from n/a through 6.18.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54284 | WordPress SeedProd Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 6.18.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54284</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SeedProd LLC SeedProd Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SeedProd Pro: from n/a through 6.18.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54285 | WordPress SeedProd Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 6.18.10 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54285</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in SeedProd LLC SeedProd Pro allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects SeedProd Pro: from n/a through 6.18.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54348 | WordPress Brandy theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in YayCommerce Brand allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Brand: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54257 | WordPress tydskrif theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54257</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Molefed allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects tydskrif: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54279 | WordPress  WP-NERD Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54279</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in WPNERD WP-NERD Toolkit.This issue affects WP-NERD Toolkit: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54280 | WordPress WPBookit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54280</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Iqonic Design WPBookit allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WPBookit: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12653 | FabulaTech USB over Network IOCT ftusbbus2.sys 0x22040C null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12653</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FabulaTech USB over Network 6.0.6.1. Affected is the function 0x22040C in the library ftusbbus2.sys of the component IOCT Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43234 | WordPress Woffice theme &amp;lt;= 5.4.14 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43234</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Envato Security Team Woffice allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Woffice: from n/a through 5.4.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54249 | WordPress Advanced Options Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54249</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jules Colle Advanced Options Editor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Advanced Options Editor: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54229 | WordPress SV100 Companion plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.02 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54229</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Straightvisions GmbH SV100 Companion allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SV100 Companion: from n/a through 2.0.02.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12089 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12089</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12090 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12090</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12091 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12091</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12092 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12092</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37251 | WordPress Advanced Custom Fields Pro plugin &amp;lt; 6.3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37251</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPENGINE, INC. Advanced Custom Fields PRO.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO: from n/a before 6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49775 | A vulnerability has been identified in Opcenter Execution Foundation (All versions), Opcenter Intelligence (All versions), Opcenter Quality ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49775</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Opcenter Execution Foundation (All versions), Opcenter Intelligence (All versions), Opcenter Quality (All versions), Opcenter RDL (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V4.0 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions &lt; V5.0 Update 1), SINEC NMS (All versions if operated in conjunction with UMC &lt; V2.15), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V16 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V17 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V18 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V19 (All versions). Affected products contain a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component.
This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12668 | Velocidex WinPmem Out of Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12668</link><description>Velocidex WinPmem versions below 4.1 suffer from an Out of Bounds Write vulnerability whereby an attacker can subvert code-signing facilities leading to the ability to write the value zero anywhere in memory with the driver – without using the\nPMEM_WRITE_ENABLED compilation flag. This issue is remediated in version 4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10972 | WinPmem Improper Input Validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10972</link><description>Velocidex WinPmem versions below 4.1 suffer from an Improper Input Validation vulnerability whereby an attacker can directly communicate with the driver by accessing the \"\\\\.\\pmem\" device. From that point, it is possible to communicate with the driver via regular device operations, starting with a system of IOCTLs. To send specific orders to the driver, one can use IRP_MJ_DEVICE_CONTROL control code. This issue is remediated in version 4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56015 | WordPress Tidy Up Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56015</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in John Godley Tidy Up allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tidy Up: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:48:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54354 | WordPress Termin-Kalender plugin &amp;lt;= 0.99.47 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54354</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Beat Kueffer Termin-Kalender allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Termin-Kalender: from n/a through 0.99.47.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54358 | WordPress 3D Avatar User Profile plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54358</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Avatar 3D Creator 3D Avatar User Profile allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects 3D Avatar User Profile: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54359 | WordPress Banner System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54359</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saul Morales Pacheco Banner System allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Banner System: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54361 | WordPress Instant Appointment plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54361</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in outstrip Instant Appointment allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Instant Appointment: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54363 | WordPress Wp NssUser Register plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54363</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in nssTheme Wp NssUser Register allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Wp NssUser Register: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54364 | WordPress Feedpress Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54364</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spartac Feedpress Generator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Feedpress Generator: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54365 | WordPress KH Easy User Settings plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54365</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Halim KH Easy User Settings allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects KH Easy User Settings: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54367 | WordPress ForumWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54367</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ForumWP ForumWP allows Object Injection.This issue affects ForumWP: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54368 | WordPress GitSync plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - CSRF to Remote Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54368</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ruben Garza, Jr. GitSync allows Code Injection.This issue affects GitSync: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54369 | WordPress Zita Site Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary Plugin Installation and Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54369</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeHunk Zita Site Builder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Zita Site Builder: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54370 | WordPress Video &amp;amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54370</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in SuitePlugins Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54374 | WordPress Sogrid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54374</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Sabri Taieb Sogrid allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Sogrid: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54375 | WordPress Woolook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54375</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Sabri Taieb Woolook allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Woolook: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54378 | WordPress Quietly Insights plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54378</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quietly Quietly Insights allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Quietly Insights: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54379 | WordPress Minterpress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54379</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Blokhaus Minterpress allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Minterpress: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54380 | WordPress WP Cookies Enabler plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54380</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Filippo Bodei WP Cookies Enabler allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects WP Cookies Enabler: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54382 | WordPress Bold Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.5 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54382</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Page Builder allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through 5.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54385 | WordPress Radio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.82 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54385</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in SoftLab Radio Player allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Radio Player: from n/a through 2.0.82.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54387 | WordPress Posts Date Ranges plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54387</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jaytesh Barange Posts Date Ranges allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Posts Date Ranges: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54390 | WordPress TagGator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.54 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54390</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bouzid Nazim Zitouni TagGator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects TagGator: from n/a through 1.54.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54395 | WordPress Increase Sociability plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54395</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Becky Sanders Increase Sociability allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Increase Sociability: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54403 | WordPress Visual Recent Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54403</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryan Scott Visual Recent Posts allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Visual Recent Posts: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54406 | WordPress Comments On Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54406</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Reza Moallemi Comments On Feed allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Comments On Feed: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54422 | WordPress Evernote Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54422</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gaowei Tang Evernote Sync allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Evernote Sync: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55972 | WordPress eTemplates plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55972</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Chris Carvache eTemplates allows SQL Injection.This issue affects eTemplates: from n/a through 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55973 | WordPress TSB Occasion Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55973</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ryan Nystrom TSB Occasion Editor allows SQL Injection.This issue affects TSB Occasion Editor: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55974 | WordPress Mimoos plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55974</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AMS Nexe Iberica Mimoos allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Mimoos: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55976 | WordPress Critical Site Intel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55976</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mike Leembruggen Critical Site Intel allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Critical Site Intel: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55977 | WordPress LaunchPage.app Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55977</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in launch-page-importer LaunchPage.app Importer allows SQL Injection.This issue affects LaunchPage.app Importer: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55978 | WordPress Code Generator Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55978</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WalletStation.com Code Generator Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Code Generator Pro: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55979 | WordPress Wr Age Verification plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55979</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Webriderz Wr Age Verification allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Wr Age Verification: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55980 | WordPress Wr Age Verification plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55980</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Webriderz Wr Age Verification allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Wr Age Verification: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55981 | WordPress Nabz Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= v1.00 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55981</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Nabajit Roy Nabz Image Gallery allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Nabz Image Gallery: from n/a through v1.00.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55982 | WordPress Share Buttons – Social Media plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55982</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in richteam Share Buttons – Social Media allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Share Buttons – Social Media: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55986 | WordPress Service plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55986</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in serviceonline Service allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Service: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55987 | WordPress Advanced What should we write next about plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ritesh Sanap Advanced What should we write next about allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Advanced What should we write next about: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55988 | WordPress Navayan CSV Export Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Amol Nirmala Waman Navayan CSV Export allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Navayan CSV Export: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55996 | WordPress Payment gateway per Product for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55996</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dreamfox Dreamfox Media Payment gateway per Product for Woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Dreamfox Media Payment gateway per Product for Woocommerce: from n/a through 3.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56013 | WordPress Wovax IDX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56013</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Wovax, LLC. Wovax IDX allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Wovax IDX: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54331 | WordPress I Plant A Tree plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54331</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Micha I Plant A Tree allows Stored XSS.This issue affects I Plant A Tree: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54332 | WordPress WP Currency Exchange Rates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54332</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPFactory WP Currency Exchange Rates allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Currency Exchange Rates: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54352 | WordPress Sogrid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54352</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sabri Taieb Sogrid allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Sogrid: from n/a through 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54353 | WordPress Hack-Info plugin &amp;lt;= 3.17 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54353</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPGear Hack-Info allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Hack-Info: from n/a through 3.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54355 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.17.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54355</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54356 | WordPress Online Booking &amp;amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54356</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in vCita.com Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita: from n/a through 4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54360 | WordPress Gutensee plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54360</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in premila Gutensee allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Gutensee: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54366 | WordPress Vimeography plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Full Path Disclosure (FPD)  vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54366</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Dave Kiss Vimeography allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Vimeography: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54372 | WordPress Insertify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - CSRF to Remote Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54372</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sourov Amin Insertify allows Code Injection.This issue affects Insertify: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54373 | WordPress EduAdmin Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54373</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Chris Gårdenberg, MultiNet Interactive AB EduAdmin Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects EduAdmin Booking: from n/a through 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54384 | WordPress Falcon – WordPress Optimizations &amp;amp; Tweaks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54384</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in eLightUp Falcon – WordPress Optimizations &amp; Tweaks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Falcon – WordPress Optimizations &amp; Tweaks: from n/a through 2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54386 | WordPress Push Monkey Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54386</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Get Push Monkey LLC Push Monkey Pro – Web Push Notifications and WooCommerce Abandoned Cart allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Push Monkey Pro – Web Push Notifications and WooCommerce Abandoned Cart: from n/a through 3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54388 | WordPress Multiple Admin Emails plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54388</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Phuc Pham Multiple Admin Emails allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Multiple Admin Emails: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54389 | WordPress addWeather plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54389</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Eduardo Chiaro addWeather allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects addWeather: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54391 | WordPress WordPress Filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54391</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Matt Walters WordPress Filter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Filter: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54392 | WordPress WP微信机器人 plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54392</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Midoks WP微信机器人 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP微信机器人: from n/a through 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54393 | WordPress WP Fiddle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54393</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sheikh Heera WP Fiddle allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Fiddle: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54394 | WordPress Mandrill WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54394</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Web solution soft Mandrill WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mandrill WP: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54396 | WordPress Bet sport Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0  - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54396</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ryan Bet sport Free allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Bet sport Free: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54397 | WordPress Go Animate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54397</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Antonio Gocaj Go Animate allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Go Animate: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54398 | WordPress Flaming Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54398</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Project Caruso Flaming Forms allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Flaming Forms: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54399 | WordPress CRUDLab Google Plus Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54399</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CRUDLab CRUDLab Google Plus Button allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CRUDLab Google Plus Button: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54400 | WordPress AppMaps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54400</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MELONIQ.NET AppMaps allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AppMaps: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54401 | WordPress Advanced Fancybox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54401</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Turcu Ciprian Advanced Fancybox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Fancybox: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54402 | WordPress Arabic Webfonts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54402</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jozoor Arabic Webfonts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Arabic Webfonts: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54404 | WordPress MDC Comment Toolbar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54404</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Nazmul Ahsan MDC Comment Toolbar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MDC Comment Toolbar: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54405 | WordPress ECT Social Share plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54405</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andy Chapman ECT Social Share allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ECT Social Share: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54407 | WordPress CK and SyntaxHighlighter plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54407</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in 随意的风 CK and SyntaxHighlighter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CK and SyntaxHighlighter: from n/a through 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54408 | WordPress Youtube Video Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54408</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jake H. Youtube Video Grid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Youtube Video Grid: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54409 | WordPress XPD Reduce Image Filesize plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54409</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in fzmaster @ XPD XPD Reduce Image Filesize allows Stored XSS.This issue affects XPD Reduce Image Filesize: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54410 | WordPress SOPA Blackout plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54410</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Toby Cox SOPA Blackout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SOPA Blackout: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54411 | WordPress WP Controller plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54411</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in hosting.io, campaigns.io WP Controller allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Controller: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54412 | WordPress ECT Product Carousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54412</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ecommerce Templates ECT Product Carousel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ECT Product Carousel: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54413 | WordPress Display Future Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.3 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54413</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Stefan Brandt Display Future Posts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Display Future Posts: from n/a through 0.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54414 | WordPress Geoportail Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54414</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in geoWP Geoportail Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Geoportail Shortcode: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54415 | WordPress WP-HideThat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54415</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cyle Conoly WP-HideThat allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-HideThat: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54416 | WordPress Wp Login with Ajax plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54416</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Navdeep Kumar Wp Login with Ajax allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wp Login with Ajax: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54417 | WordPress PixProof plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54417</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pixelgrade PixProof allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects PixProof: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54418 | WordPress DTC Documents plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.05 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54418</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Diversified Technology Corp., WPYog, and Gagan Deep Singh DTC Documents allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects DTC Documents: from n/a through 1.1.05.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54419 | WordPress Ui Slider Filter By Price plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54419</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mansur Ahamed Ui Slider Filter By Price allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Ui Slider Filter By Price: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54420 | WordPress Metrika plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54420</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aleksander Novikov Metrika allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Metrika: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54421 | WordPress Floating Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54421</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sanjay Singh Negi Floating Video Player allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Floating Video Player: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54423 | WordPress Social Media Sharing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54423</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jesse Overright Social Media Sharing allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Social Media Sharing: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54424 | WordPress Like in Vk.com plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54424</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ilya Chekalskiy Like in Vk.com allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Like in Vk.com: from n/a through 0.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54425 | WordPress LionScripts: Site Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54425</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in LionScripts.com LionScripts: Site Maintenance &amp; Noindex Nofollow Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LionScripts: Site Maintenance &amp; Noindex Nofollow Plugin: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54426 | WordPress LeaderBoard Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54426</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Andy Fradelakis LeaderBoard Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LeaderBoard Plugin: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54427 | WordPress Category of Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54427</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Linda MacPhee-Cobb Category of Posts allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Category of Posts: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54428 | WordPress Add image to Post plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54428</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in onigetoc Add image to Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Add image to Post: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54429 | WordPress Aphorismus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54429</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ivan Ovsyannikov Aphorismus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Aphorismus: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54430 | WordPress EELV Newsletter  plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54430</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bastien Ho EELV Newsletter allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects EELV Newsletter: from n/a through 4.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54431 | WordPress Admin Customization plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54431</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mohamed Riyaz Admin Customization allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Admin Customization: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54432 | WordPress WP Flipkart Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54432</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shambhu Prasad Patnaik WP Flipkart Importer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Flipkart Importer: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54433 | WordPress Simple Booking – Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54433</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Simple Booking Simple Booking Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Booking Widget: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54434 | WordPress phZoom plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.92 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54434</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Phoetry phZoom allows Stored XSS.This issue affects phZoom: from n/a through 1.2.92.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54435 | WordPress Onlywire Multi Autosubmitter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54435</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Thomas Hoefter Onlywire Multi Autosubmitter allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Onlywire Multi Autosubmitter: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54436 | WordPress Jet Footer Code plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54436</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jettochkin Jet Footer Code allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jet Footer Code: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54437 | WordPress jCarousel for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Merrill M. Mayer jCarousel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects jCarousel: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54438 | WordPress Gaxx Keywords plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54438</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in GAxx Gaxx Keywords allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gaxx Keywords: from n/a through 0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54439 | WordPress Amazon Product Price plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54439</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alok Tiwari Amazon Product Price allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Amazon Product Price: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54440 | WordPress WP-Ban-User plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54440</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in blueskyy WP-Ban-User allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP-Ban-User: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54441 | WordPress Utech World Time Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54441</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Meini Utech World Time allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Utech World Time: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54442 | WordPress Better WP Login Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54442</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lluís Cortès Better WP Login Page allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Better WP Login Page: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54443 | WordPress Advanced Data Table For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54443</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pluginscafe Advanced Data Table For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Data Table For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55989 | WordPress WP Simple Pay Lite Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Kyle M. Brown WP Simple Pay Lite Manager allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Simple Pay Lite Manager: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55990 | WordPress Mollie for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55990</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ewald Harmsen Mollie for Contact Form 7 allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Mollie for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55992 | WordPress WooCommerce Basic Ordernumbers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55992</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Open Tools WooCommerce Basic Ordernumbers allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Basic Ordernumbers: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55993 | WordPress Job Board Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.60 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55993</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.60.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55994 | WordPress 畅言评论系统 plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 -  Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55994</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 搜狐畅言 畅言评论系统 allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects 畅言评论系统: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55998 | WordPress Popup Surveys &amp;amp; Polls for WordPress (Mare.io) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.36 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55998</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dusthazard Popup Surveys &amp; Polls for WordPress (Mare.io) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Popup Surveys &amp; Polls for WordPress (Mare.io): from n/a through 1.36.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56001 | WordPress Ksher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56001</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ksher Ksher allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ksher: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56004 | WordPress Easy Site Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56004</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex W Fowler Easy Site Importer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Site Importer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56005 | WordPress Posti Shipping Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.3 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56005</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Posti Posti Shipping allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Posti Shipping: from n/a through 3.10.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56007 | WordPress Leader plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56007</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ram Segev Leader allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Leader: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56009 | WordPress Spreadr Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56009</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spreadr Spreadr Woocommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Spreadr Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56011 | WordPress Responsive Google Maps | by imbaa plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56011</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ilja Zaglov | IMBAA GmbH Responsive Google Maps | by imbaa allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Google Maps | by imbaa: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56012 | WordPress Flash News / Post (Responsive) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56012</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pearlbells Flash News / Post (Responsive) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Flash News / Post (Responsive): from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12478 | InvoicePlane 1 upload_file unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12478</link><description>A vulnerability was found in InvoicePlane up to 1.6.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function upload_file of the file /index.php/upload/upload_file/1/1. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.6.2-beta-1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early, responded in a very professional manner and quickly released a fixed version of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 10:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12362 | InvoicePlane invoices.php download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in InvoicePlane up to 1.6.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function download of the file invoices.php. The manipulation of the argument invoice leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.6.2-beta-1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early, responded in a very professional manner and quickly released a fixed version of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 10:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48872 | Bypass of &amp;quot;Max failed attempts&amp;quot; restriction via race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48872</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.2, 10.0.x &lt;= 10.0.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.4, and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.12 fail to prevent concurrently checking and updating the failed login attempts. which allows an attacker to bypass of "Max failed attempts" restriction and send a big number of login attempts before being blocked via simultaneously sending multiple login requests</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 08:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54083 | DoS via lack of type validation in Calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54083</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.2, 10.0.x &lt;= 10.0.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.4, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.12 fail to properly validate the type of callProps which allows a user to cause a client side (webapp and mobile) DoS to users of particular channels, by sending a specially crafted post.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 08:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54682 | Zipbomb DoS via Missing Slack Import Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54682</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.2, 10.0.x &lt;= 10.0.2, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.4, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.12 fail to limit the file size for slack import file uploads which allows a user to cause a DoS via zip bomb by importing data in a team they are a team admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 08:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12646 | Chunghwa Telecom topm-client - Arbitrary File Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12646</link><description>The topm-client from Chunghwa Telecom has an Arbitrary File Delete vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection in the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to delete arbitrary files on the user's system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9679 | A Hardcoded Cryptographic key vulnerability existed in DLP Extension 11.11.1.3 which allowed the decryption of previously encrypted user cre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9679</link><description>A Hardcoded Cryptographic key vulnerability existed in DLP Extension 11.11.1.3 which allowed the decryption of previously encrypted user credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12644 | Chunghwa Telecom tbm-client - Arbitrary File Copy and Paste</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12644</link><description>The tbm-client from Chunghwa Telecom has an Arbitrary File vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection in the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability. Attackers can copy arbitrary files on the user's system and paste them into any path, which poses a potential risk of information leakage or could consume hard drive space by copying files in large volumes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12645 | Chunghwa Telecom topm-client - Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12645</link><description>The topm-client from Chunghwa Telecom has an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection for the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains a Relative Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to read arbitrary files on the user's system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12642 | Chunghwa Telecom TenderDocTransfer - Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12642</link><description>TenderDocTransfer from Chunghwa Telecom has an Arbitrary File Write vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection for the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains a Relative Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to write arbitrary files to any path on the user's system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12643 | Chunghwa Telecom tbm-client - Arbitrary File Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12643</link><description>The tbm-client from Chunghwa Telecom has an Arbitrary File Delete vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection in the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use these APIs through phishing. Additionally, one of the APIs contains an Absolute Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to delete arbitrary files on the user's system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9678 | An SQL Injection vulnerability existed in DLP Extension 11.11.1.3.  The vulnerability allowed an attacker to perform arbitrary SQL queries p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9678</link><description>An SQL Injection vulnerability existed in DLP Extension 11.11.1.3.  The vulnerability allowed an attacker to perform arbitrary SQL queries potentially leading to command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12641 | Chunghwa Telecom TenderDocTransfer - Reflected Cross-site Scripting to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12641</link><description>TenderDocTransfer from Chunghwa Telecom has a Reflected Cross-site scripting vulnerability. The application sets up a simple local web server and provides APIs for communication with the target website. Due to the lack of CSRF protection for the APIs, unauthenticated remote attackers could use specific APIs through phishing to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the user’s browser. Since the web server set by the application supports Node.Js features, attackers can further leverage this to run OS commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56084 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint UniversalNormalizer before 5.7.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Universal Norma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56084</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint UniversalNormalizer before 5.7.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Universal Normalizer. These are executed, leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56085 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Search Template Dashboard. These ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56085</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while creating Search Template Dashboard. These are executed, leading to Server-Side Template Injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56086 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads in Report Templates. These are executed when the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56086</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads in Report Templates. These are executed when the backup process is initiated, leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56087 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while querying Search Template Dashboard. These ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56087</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.5.0. Authenticated users can inject payloads while querying Search Template Dashboard. These are executed, leading to Server-Side Template Injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56112 | CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before f0cf648 allows XSS via token or username to plogical/phpmyadminsignin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56112</link><description>CyberPanel (aka Cyber Panel) before f0cf648 allows XSS via token or username to plogical/phpmyadminsignin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11841 | Tithe.ly Giving Button &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11841</link><description>The Tithe.ly Giving Button WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5333 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt; 6.8.2.1 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Event Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5333</link><description>The Events Calendar WordPress plugin before 6.8.2.1 is missing access checks in the REST API, allowing for unauthenticated users to access information about password protected events.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8116 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8116</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.9 before 17.4.6, 17.5 before 17.5.4, and 17.6 before 17.6.2. By using a specific GraphQL query, under specific conditions an unauthorized user can retrieve branch names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 04:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8650 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8650</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.0 prior to 17.4.6, 17.5 prior to 17.5.4, and 17.6 prior to 17.6.2 that allowed non-member users to view unresolved threads marked as internal notes in public projects merge requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 04:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53376 | CyberPanel before 2.3.8 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the phpSelection field t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53376</link><description>CyberPanel before 2.3.8 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the phpSelection field to the websites/submitWebsiteCreation URI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 03:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56083 | Cognition Devin before 2024-12-12 provides write access to code by an attacker who discovers the https://vscode-randomly_generated_string.de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56083</link><description>Cognition Devin before 2024-12-12 provides write access to code by an attacker who discovers the https://vscode-randomly_generated_string.devinapps.com URL (aka the VSCode live share URL) for a specific "Use Devin's Machine" session. For example, this URL may be discovered if a customer posts a screenshot of a Devin session to social media, or publicly streams their Devin session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 02:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8798 | Bluetooth: classic: avdtp: missing buffer length check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8798</link><description>No proper validation of the length of user input in olcp_ind_handler in zephyr/subsys/bluetooth/services/ots/ots_client.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11858 | Radare2: command injection via pebble application files in radare2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11858</link><description>A flaw was found in Radare2, which contains a command injection vulnerability caused by insufficient input validation when handling Pebble Application files. Maliciously crafted inputs can inject shell commands during command parsing, leading to unintended behavior during file processing​</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7701 | Misuse of SHA256 to create an encryption key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7701</link><description>Use of Password Hash With Insufficient Computational Effort vulnerability in percona percona-toolkit allows Encryption Brute Forcing.This issue affects percona-toolkit: 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56082 | ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56082</link><description>ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set to true.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 04:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55969 | DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an exter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55969</link><description>DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an external reference XML, aka I640714.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56074 | gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56074</link><description>gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55970 | File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55970</link><description>File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, aka I644734.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56072 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56072</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted packet that specifies many sFlow samples.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56073 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56073</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (divide-by-zero error and application crash).</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31891 | IBM Storage Scale privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31891</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 

contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with command line access to the 'scalemgmt' user can elevate privileges to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31892 | IBM Storage Scale SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31892</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 could allow a user to perform unauthorized actions after intercepting and modifying a csv file due to improper neutralization of formula elements.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11720 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11720</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via submission forms in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the new Taxonomy form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when lower-level users have been granted access to submit specific forms, which is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11721 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11721</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5. This is due to insufficient controls on the user role select field when utilizing the 'Role' field in a form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new administrative user accounts, even when the administrative user role has not been provided as an option to the user, granted that unauthenticated users have been provided access to the form.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11710 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11710</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'fieldfor', 'visibleParent' and 'id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11711 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11711</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'resumeid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11712 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Resume Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11712</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the getResumeFileDownloadById() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download other users resumes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11713 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via wpjobportal_deactivate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11713</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'page_id' parameter of the wpjobportal_deactivate() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11714 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via getFieldsForVisibleCombobox()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11714</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'ff' parameter of the getFieldsForVisibleCombobox() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11715 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11715</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the assignUserRole() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an employer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12446 | Post to Pdf &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12446</link><description>The Post to Pdf plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gmptp_single_post' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12628 | bodi0’s Easy Cache &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12628</link><description>The bodi0`s Easy cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cache-folder' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10646 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.2.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Form Subject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10646</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form's subject parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10690 | Shortcodes for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10690</link><description>The Shortcodes for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 via the 'SHORTCODE_ELEMENTOR' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private and draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11752 | Eveeno &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11752</link><description>The Eveeno plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'eveeno' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12422 | Import Eventbrite Events &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12422</link><description>The Import Eventbrite Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12459 | Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12459</link><description>The Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'toggle' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12474 | GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12474</link><description>The GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gds-country-dropdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12501 | Simple Locator &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12501</link><description>The Simple Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11095 | Visualmodo Elements &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11095</link><description>The Visualmodo Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11462 | Filestack Official &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11462</link><description>The Filestack Official plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'fstab' and 'filestack_options' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11751 | TCBD Popover &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11751</link><description>The TCBD Popover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbd-popover-image ' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11755 | IMS Countdown &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11755</link><description>The IMS Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown post settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11759 | Bukza &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11759</link><description>The Bukza plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bukza' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11763 | Plezi &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11763</link><description>The Plezi plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'plezi' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11770 | Post Carousel &amp;amp; Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11770</link><description>The Post Carousel &amp; Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'post-cs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11855 | Koalendar – Events &amp;amp; Appointments Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11855</link><description>The Koalendar – Events &amp; Appointments Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11865 | Tabs Maker &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11865</link><description>The Tabs Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on tab descriptions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11867 | Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11867</link><description>The Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'companion-portfolio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11869 | Buk for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11869</link><description>The Buk for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buk' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11873 | glomex oEmbed &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11873</link><description>The glomex oEmbed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'glomex_integration' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11876 | Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11876</link><description>The Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'kredeum_opensky' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11877 | Cricket Live Score &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11877</link><description>The Cricket Live Score plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cricket_score' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11879 | Stripe Donation &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11879</link><description>The Stripe Donation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stripe_donation' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11883 | Connatix Video Embed &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11883</link><description>The Connatix Video Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cnx_script_code' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11884 | Wp photo text slider 50 &amp;lt;= 8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11884</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp-photo-slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11888 | IDer Login for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11888</link><description>The IDer Login for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ider_login_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11889 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11889</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11894 | The Permalinker &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11894</link><description>The The Permalinker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'permalink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12411 | WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12411</link><description>The WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12447 | Get Post Content Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via post_content Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12447</link><description>The Get Post Content Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 via the 'post-content' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the content of password-protected, private, draft, and pending posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12448 | Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12448</link><description>The Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'papvfwc_views' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12458 | Smart PopUp Blaster &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12458</link><description>The Smart PopUp Blaster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spb-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12502 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12502</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-landing' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12517 | WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12517</link><description>The WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cart_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12523 | States Map US &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12523</link><description>The States Map US plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'states_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12555 | SIP Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12555</link><description>The SIP Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12578 | Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.8 - Unauthenticated Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12578</link><description>The Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.8 via the 'tickera_tickets_info' endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from bookings like full names, email addresses, check-in/out timestamps and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9698 | Crafthemes Demo Import &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload in process_uploaded_files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9698</link><description>The Crafthemes Demo Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'process_uploaded_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29476 | In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29476</link><description>In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. This is fixed in 2.88.2+, 2.89.1+, and 2.90.1+.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>