<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1403 | Qiskit SDK denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1403</link><description>Qiskit SDK 0.45.0 through 1.2.4 could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service using a maliciously crafted QPY file containing a malformed symengine serialization stream which can cause a segfault within the symengine library.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45673 | IBM Security Verify Bridge information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45673</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge Directory Sync 1.0.1 through 1.0.12, IBM Security Verify Gateway for Windows Login 1.0.1 through 1.0.10, and IBM Security Verify Gateway for Radius 1.0.1 through 1.0.11 stores user credentials in configuration files which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1546 | BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System operate.mds log_operate_clear os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in BDCOM Behavior Management and Auditing System up to 20250210 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function log_operate_clear of the file /webui/modules/log/operate.mds. The manipulation of the argument start_code leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26014 | A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26014</link><description>A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26013 | An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26013</link><description>An issue in Loggrove v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the read.py component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1543 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS ueditor-1.4.3.3 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1543</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS 4.1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /resource/js/ueditor-1.4.3.3. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1544 | dingfanzu CMS loadShopInfo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1544</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in dingfanzu CMS up to 20250210. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ajax/loadShopInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument shopId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1538 | D-Link DAP-1320 api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1538</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this vulnerability is the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1539 | D-Link DAP-1320 storagein.pd-XXXXXX replace_special_char stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1539</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAP-1320 1.00. Affected by this issue is the function replace_special_char of the file /storagein.pd-XXXXXX. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1536 | Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway Request Parameter vpn_template_style.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1536</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom Multi-Service Intelligent Gateway up to 20250208. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /vpn/vpn_template_style.php of the component Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1537 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1537</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument codexame leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0838 | Heap Buffer overflow in Abseil</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0838</link><description>There exists a heap buffer overflow vulnerable in Abseil-cpp. The sized constructors, reserve(), and rehash() methods of absl::{flat,node}hash{set,map} did not impose an upper bound on their size argument. As a result, it was possible for a caller to pass a very large size that would cause an integer overflow when computing the size of the container's backing store, and a subsequent out-of-bounds memory write. Subsequent accesses to the container might also access out-of-bounds memory. We recommend upgrading past commit 5a0e2cb5e3958dd90bb8569a2766622cb74d90c1</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10222 | SVG Support &amp;lt;= 2.5.10 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10222</link><description>The SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to upload SVG files can be extended to authors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-6158 | Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6158</link><description>Opera Mini for Android before version 52.2 is vulnerable to an address bar spoofing attack. The vulnerability allows a malicious page to trick the browser into showing an address of a different page. This may allow the malicious page to impersonate another page and trick a user into providing sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26794 | Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26794</link><description>Exim 4.98 before 4.98.1, when SQLite hints and ETRN serialization are used, allows remote SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1535 | Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System admin.ticket.close.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1535</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System 8.142.100.161. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /wuser/admin.ticket.close.php. The manipulation of the argument ticket_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9150 | Code Injection in Wyn Enterprise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9150</link><description>Report generation functionality in Wyn Enterprise allows for code inclusion, but not sufficiently limits what code might be included. An attacker is able use a low privileges account in order to abuse this functionality and execute malicious code, load DLL libraries and executing OS commands on a host system with applications high privileges.
This issue has been fixed in version 8.0.00204.0</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13455 | igumbi Online Booking &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13455</link><description>The igumbi Online Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'igumbi_calendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13713 | WPExperts Square For GiveWP &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13713</link><description>The WPExperts Square For GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13846 | Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro &amp;lt;= 3.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via post_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13846</link><description>The Indeed Ultimate Learning Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘post_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13900 | Head, Footer and Post Injections &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Code Injection in Multisite Environments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13900</link><description>The Head, Footer and Post Injections plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject PHP Code in multisite environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1402 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.19.1.1 - Missing Authorization to Ticket Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1402</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_ticket_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.19.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary Attendee tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1489 | WP-Appbox &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via appbox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1489</link><description>The WP-Appbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's appbox shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1470 | Eclipse OMR: Null pointer dereference vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1470</link><description>In Eclipse OMR, from the initial contribution to version 0.4.0, some OMR internal port library and utilities consumers of z/OS atoe functions do not check their return values for NULL memory pointers or for memory allocation failures.  This can lead to NULL pointer dereference crashes.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, internal OMR consumers of atoe functions handle NULL return values and memory allocation failures correctly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1471 | Eclipse OMR: Buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1471</link><description>In Eclipse OMR versions 0.2.0 to 0.4.0, some of the z/OS atoe print functions use a constant length buffer for string conversion. If the input format string and arguments are larger than the buffer size then buffer overflow occurs.  Beginning in version 0.5.0, the conversion buffers are sized correctly and checked appropriately to prevent buffer overflows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12276 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12276</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to second-order SQL Injection via filenames in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with  access to upload files and manage filenames through a third-party plugin like a File Manager, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The risk of this vulnerability is very minimal as it requires a user to be able to manipulate filenames in order to successfully exploit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12452 | Ziggeo &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12452</link><description>The Ziggeo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ziggeo_event' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13353 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13353</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 via several widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13461 | Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13461</link><description>The Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'autoship-create-scheduled-order-action' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13648 | Maps for WP &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13648</link><description>The Maps for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'MapOnePoint' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0727 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0727</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length in one packet smaller than the data 
request size of the other packet. A possible workaround is to disable 
HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0728 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server single PUT request integer underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0728</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause an integer underflow and a 
subsequent denial of service by writing a very large file, by specially 
crafted packets with Content-Length smaller than the data request size. A
 possible workaround is to disable HTTP PUT support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1410 | Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via piecal Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1410</link><description>The Events Calendar Made Simple – Pie Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's piecal shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0726 | Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo HTTP server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0726</link><description>In NetX HTTP server functionality of Eclipse ThreadX NetX Duo before 
version 6.4.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service by specially 
crafted packets. The core issue is missing closing of a file in case of 
an error condition, resulting in the 404 error for each further file 
request. Users can work-around the issue by disabling the PUT request 
support.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13314 | Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel &amp;lt; 2.7.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13314</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel  WordPress plugin before 2.7.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13585 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt; 4.12.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13585</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite  WordPress plugin before 4.12.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11260 | Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! &amp;lt;= 6.6.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via Event Status Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11260</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the active_status parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 05:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13235 | Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13235</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'language' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13379 | C9 Admin Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13379</link><description>The C9 Admin Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13388 | TCBD Tooltip &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13388</link><description>The TCBD Tooltip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbdtooltip_text' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13537 | C9 Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13537</link><description>The C9 Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.7. This is due the plugin containing a publicly accessible composer-setup.php file with error display enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13672 | Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13672</link><description>The Mini Course Generator | Embed mini-courses and interactive content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mcg' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13751 | 3D Photo Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13751</link><description>The 3D Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'des[]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13818 | Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.9 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13818</link><description>The Registration Forms – User Registration Forms, Invitation-Based Registrations, Front-end User Profile, Login Form &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3.9 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information about users contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13883 | WPUpper Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 3.51 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom CSS Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13883</link><description>The WPUpper Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.51. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_custom_css_request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject custom CSS to modify a site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1406 | Newpost Catch &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via npc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1406</link><description>The Newpost Catch plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's npc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1407 | AMO Team Showcase &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via amoteam_skills Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1407</link><description>The AMO Team Showcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's amoteam_skills shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 03:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38657 | External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38657</link><description>External control of a file name in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.4 and Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1001 | Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1001</link><description>Medixant RadiAnt DICOM Viewer is vulnerable due to failure of the update mechanism to verify the update server's certificate which could allow an attacker to alter network traffic and carry out a machine-in-the-middle attack (MITM). An attacker could modify the server's response and deliver a malicious update to the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27100 | An authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27100</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms your object storage into a Git-like repository. In affected versions an authenticated user can crash lakeFS by exhausting server memory.  This is an authenticated denial-of-service issue. This problem has been patched in version 1.50.0. Users on versions 1.49.1 and below are affected. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should either set the environment variable `LAKEFS_BLOCKSTORE_S3_DISABLE_PRE_SIGNED_MULTIPART` to `true` or configure the `disable_pre_signed_multipart` key to true in their config yaml.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54756 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the ZScript function of ZDoom Team GZDoom v4.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54756</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the ZScript function of ZDoom Team GZDoom v4.13.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted PK3 file containing a malicious ZScript source file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27088 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in template implementation in oxyno-zeta/s3-proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27088</link><description>oxyno-zeta/s3-proxy is an aws s3 proxy written in go. In affected versions a Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability enables attackers to create malicious URLs that, when visited, inject scripts into the web application. This can lead to session hijacking or phishing attacks on a trusted domain, posing a moderate risk to all users. It's possible to inject html elements, including scripts through the folder-list template. The affected template allows users to interact with the URL path provided by the `Request.URL.Path` variable, which is then rendered directly into the HTML without proper sanitization or escaping. This can be abused by attackers who craft a malicious URL containing injected HTML or JavaScript. When users visit such a URL, the malicious script will be executed in the user's context. This issue has been addressed in version 4.18.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25663 | A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06. Affected is the function SUB_0046AC38 of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25663</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06. Affected is the function SUB_0046AC38 of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25664 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_49E098 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25664</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_49E098 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25667 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25667</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the urls parameter in the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25668 | Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_47D878 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25668</link><description>Tenda AC8V4 V16.03.34.06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the shareSpeed parameter in the sub_47D878 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25678 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the funcpara1 parameter in the formSetCfm function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25678</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the funcpara1 parameter in the formSetCfm function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25679 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the index parameter in the formWifiMacFilterSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25679</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the index parameter in the formWifiMacFilterSet function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22973 | An issue in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the http_curl() function in the '/application...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22973</link><description>An issue in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the http_curl() function in the '/application/common. php' file that directly retrieves the URL request response content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25662 | Tenda O4 V3.0 V1.0.0.10(2936) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function SafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterList via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25662</link><description>Tenda O4 V3.0 V1.0.0.10(2936) is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the function SafeSetMacFilter of the file /goform/setMacFilterList via the argument remark/type/time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25674 | Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in form_fast_setting_wifi_set via the parameter ssid.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25674</link><description>Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in form_fast_setting_wifi_set via the parameter ssid.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25675 | Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 has a command injection vulnerablility located in the formexeCommand function. The str variable receives the cm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25675</link><description>Tenda AC10 V1.0 V15.03.06.23 has a command injection vulnerablility located in the formexeCommand function. The str variable receives the cmdinput parameter from a POST request and is later assigned to the cmd_buf variable, which is directly used in the doSystemCmd function, causing an arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25676 | Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the formwrlSSIDset function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25676</link><description>Tenda i12 V1.0.0.10(3805) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the list parameter in the formwrlSSIDset function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25957 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in Xunruicms v.4.6.3 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25957</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in Xunruicms v.4.6.3 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25958 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25958</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerabilities in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25960 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the menu interface of the member ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25960</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in phpcmsv9 v.9.6.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the menu interface of the member center of the background administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27097 | Cache variables with the operations when transforms exist on the root level even if variables change in the further requests with the same operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27097</link><description>GraphQL Mesh is a GraphQL Federation framework and gateway for both GraphQL Federation and non-GraphQL Federation subgraphs, non-GraphQL services, such as REST and gRPC, and also databases such as MongoDB, MySQL, and PostgreSQL. When a user transforms on the root level or single source with transforms, and the client sends the same query with different variables, the initial variables are used in all following requests until the cache evicts DocumentNode. If a token is sent via variables, the following requests will act like the same token is sent even if the following requests have different tokens. This can cause a short memory leak but it won't grow per each request but per different operation until the cache evicts DocumentNode by LRU mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27098 | Unwanted access to the entire file system vulnerability due to a missing check in `staticFiles` HTTP handler in graphql-mesh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27098</link><description>GraphQL Mesh is a GraphQL Federation framework and gateway for both GraphQL Federation and non-GraphQL Federation subgraphs, non-GraphQL services, such as REST and gRPC, and also databases such as MongoDB, MySQL, and PostgreSQL. Missing check vulnerability in the static file handler allows any client to access the files in the server's file system. When `staticFiles` is set in the `serve` settings in the configuration file, the following handler doesn't check if `absolutePath` is still under the directory provided as `staticFiles`. Users have two options to fix vulnerability; 1. Update `@graphql-mesh/cli` to a version higher than `0.82.21`, and if you use `@graphql-mesh/http`, update it to a version higher than `0.3.18` 2. Remove `staticFiles` option from the configuration, and use other solutions to serve static files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24893 | Remote code execution as guest via SolrSearchMacros request in xwiki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24893</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any guest can perform arbitrary remote code execution through a request to `SolrSearch`. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. To reproduce on an instance, without being logged in, go to `/xwiki/bin/get/Main/SolrSearch?media=rss&amp;amp;text=%7D%7D%7D%7B%7Basync%20async%3Dfalse%7D%7D%7B%7Bgroovy%7D%7Dprintln%28"Hello%20from"%20%2B%20"%20search%20text%3A"%20%2B%20%2823%20%2B%2019%29%29%7B%7B%2Fgroovy%7D%7D%7B%7B%2Fasync%7D%7D%20`. If there is an output, and the title of the RSS feed contains `Hello from search text:42`, then the instance is vulnerable. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.10.11, 16.4.1 and 16.5.0RC1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may edit `Main.SolrSearchMacros` in `SolrSearchMacros.xml` on line 955 to match the `rawResponse` macro in `macros.vm#L2824` with a content type of `application/xml`, instead of simply outputting the content of the feed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25299 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) in the real-time collaboration package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25299</link><description>CKEditor 5 is a modern JavaScript rich-text editor with an MVC architecture. During a recent internal audit, a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the CKEditor 5 real-time collaboration package. This vulnerability affects user markers, which represent users' positions within the document. It can lead to unauthorized JavaScript code execution, which might happen with a very specific editor and token endpoint configuration. This vulnerability affects only installations with Real-time collaborative editing enabled. The problem has been recognized and patched. The fix is available in version 44.2.1 (and above). Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0352 | Rapid Response Monitoring My Security Account App Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0352</link><description>Rapid Response Monitoring My Security Account App utilizes an API that could be exploited by an attacker to modify request data, potentially causing the API to return information about other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1265 | Elseta Vinci Protocol Analyzer OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1265</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Vinci Protocol Analyzer that could allow an attacker to escalate privileges and perform code execution on affected system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26618 | SSH SFTP packet size not verified properly in Erlang OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26618</link><description>Erlang is a programming language and runtime system for building massively scalable soft real-time systems with requirements on high availability. OTP is a set of Erlang libraries, which consists of the Erlang runtime system, a number of ready-to-use components mainly written in Erlang. Packet size is not verified properly for SFTP packets. As a result when multiple SSH packets (conforming to max SSH packet size) are received by ssh, they might be combined into an SFTP packet which will exceed the max allowed packet size and potentially cause large amount of memory to be allocated. Note that situation described above can only happen for successfully authenticated users after completing the SSH handshake. This issue has been patched in OTP versions 27.2.4, 26.2.5.9, and 25.3.2.18. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27096 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;html/personalizacao_upload.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_campo&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27096</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, personalizacao_upload.php endpoint. This vulnerability allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.14 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51338 | PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters of&amp;n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51338</link><description>PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters of&amp;nbsp;index.php&amp;nbsp;page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51339 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51339</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7141 | CSRF in Gliffy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7141</link><description>Versions of Gliffy Online prior to versions 4.14.0-7 contains a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) flaw.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51336 | PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51336</link><description>PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51337 | PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in "lid" parameter in index.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51337</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in "lid" parameter in index.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54958 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is susceptible to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Tools page. This flaw allows an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54958</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is susceptible to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Tools page. This flaw allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the Tools interface, which are then stored and executed in the context of other users accessing the page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54960 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute SQL injection via a crafted payload in the History...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54960</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 allows a remote attacker to execute SQL injection via a crafted payload in the History Tab component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54961 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated users to access multiple pages displaying the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54961</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 has an Information Disclosure vulnerability, which allows unauthenticated users to access multiple pages displaying the usernames and email addresses of all current users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54959 | Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack through the Favorites component, enabling POST-based Cross-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54959</link><description>Nagios XI 2024R1.2.2 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack through the Favorites component, enabling POST-based Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27091 | OpenH264 Decoding Functions Heap Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27091</link><description>OpenH264 is a free license codec library which supports H.264 encoding and decoding. A vulnerability in the decoding functions of OpenH264 codec library could allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a heap overflow. This vulnerability is due to a race condition between a Sequence Parameter Set (SPS) memory allocation and a subsequent non Instantaneous Decoder Refresh (non-IDR) Network Abstraction Layer (NAL) unit memory usage. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious bitstream and tricking a victim user into processing an arbitrary video containing the malicious bistream. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause an unexpected crash in the victim's user decoding client and, possibly, perform arbitrary commands on the victim's host by abusing the heap overflow. This vulnerability affects OpenH264 2.5.0 and earlier releases. Both Scalable Video Coding (SVC) mode and Advanced Video Coding (AVC) mode are affected by this vulnerability. OpenH264 software releases 2.6.0 and later contained the fix for this vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.

### For more information

If you have any questions or comments about this advisory:
* [Open an issue in cisco/openh264](https://github.com/cisco/openh264/issues)
* Email Cisco Open Source Security ([oss-security@cisco.com](mailto:oss-security@cisco.com)) and Cisco PSIRT ([psirt@cisco.com](mailto:psirt@cisco.com))

### Credits:

* **Research:** Octavian Guzu and Andrew Calvano of Meta
* **Fix ideation:** Philipp Hancke and Shyam Sadhwani of Meta
* **Fix implementation:** Benzheng Zhang (@BenzhengZhang)
* **Release engineering:** Benzheng Zhang (@BenzhengZhang)</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:58:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55457 | MasterSAM Star Gate 11 is vulnerable to directory traversal via /adama/adama/downloadService. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55457</link><description>MasterSAM Star Gate 11 is vulnerable to directory traversal via /adama/adama/downloadService. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the file parameter to access arbitrary files on the server, potentially exposing sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46933 | An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden BullSequana XH2140 BMC before C4EM-125: OMF_C4E 101.05.0014. Some BullSequana XH products were shippe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46933</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden BullSequana XH2140 BMC before C4EM-125: OMF_C4E 101.05.0014. Some BullSequana XH products were shipped without proper hardware programming, leading to a potential denial-of-service with privileged access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25968 | DDSN Interactive cm3 Acora CMS version 10.1.1 contains an improper access control vulnerability. An editor-privileged user can access sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25968</link><description>DDSN Interactive cm3 Acora CMS version 10.1.1 contains an improper access control vulnerability. An editor-privileged user can access sensitive information, such as system administrator credentials, by force browsing the endpoint and exploiting the 'file' parameter. By referencing specific files (e.g., cm3.xml), attackers can bypass access controls, leading to account takeover and potential privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51333 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51333</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51334 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51334</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51335 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51335</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25973 | A stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the "related recommendations" feature in Ppress v.0.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25973</link><description>A stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in the "related recommendations" feature in Ppress v.0.0.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the article.title, article.category, and article.tags parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26308 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_FILTERLIST function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26308</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_FILTERLIST function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26311 | Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the clip actions parsing functions (parseSWF_CLIPACTIONS and parseSWF_CLIPACTIONRECORD) in uti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26311</link><description>Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the clip actions parsing functions (parseSWF_CLIPACTIONS and parseSWF_CLIPACTIONRECORD) in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allow attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26306 | A memory leak has been identified in the readSizedString function in util/read.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26306</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the readSizedString function in util/read.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26307 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_IMPORTASSETS2 function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26307</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_IMPORTASSETS2 function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26310 | Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the ABC file parsing functions (parseABC_CONSTANT_POOL and `parseABC_FILE) in util/parser.c of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26310</link><description>Multiple memory leaks have been identified in the ABC file parsing functions (parseABC_CONSTANT_POOL and `parseABC_FILE) in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allow attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted ABC file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26304 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_EXPORTASSETS function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26304</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_EXPORTASSETS function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26305 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_SOUNDINFO function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26305</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_SOUNDINFO function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26309 | A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_DEFINESCENEANDFRAMEDATA function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26309</link><description>A memory leak has been identified in the parseSWF_DEFINESCENEANDFRAMEDATA function in util/parser.c of libming v0.4.8, which allows attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted SWF file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57716 | An issue in trenoncourt AutoQueryable v.1.7.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Unselectable function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57716</link><description>An issue in trenoncourt AutoQueryable v.1.7.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Unselectable function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51331 | PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51331</link><description>PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51332 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51332</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Meeting Room Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0161 | IBM Security Verify Access Appliance code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0161</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.0.9 and 11.0.0.0 could allow a local user to execute arbitrary code due to improper restrictions on code generation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51330 | PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Now Showing menu "date" parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51330</link><description>PHPJabbers Cinema Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Now Showing menu "date" parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51327 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51327</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51326 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51326</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Cleaning Business Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51323 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51323</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51324 | PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51324</link><description>PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51325 | PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51325</link><description>PHPJabbers Shared Asset Booking System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51317 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51317</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51318 | PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51318</link><description>PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51319 | PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51319</link><description>PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51320 | PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51320</link><description>PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51321 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51321</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Night Club Booking Software v1.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51316 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51316</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password' feature of PHPJabbers Bus Reservation System v1.1 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51312 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Reservations menu, Schedule section date ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51312</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Reservations menu, Schedule section date parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51313 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51313</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51314 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51314</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51315 | PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "seat_name, plugin_sms_api_key,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51315</link><description>PHPJabbers Restaurant Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "seat_name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, name" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57401 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Uniclare Student portal v.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Forgot Pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57401</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Uniclare Student portal v.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Forgot Password function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51310 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51310</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51311 | PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51311</link><description>PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51306 | PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, title" parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51306</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51308 | PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51308</link><description>PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51309 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51309</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20059 | PingAM Java Policy Agent path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20059</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Ping Identity PingAM Java Policy Agent allows Parameter Injection.This issue affects PingAM Java Policy Agent: through 5.10.3, through 2023.11.1, through 2024.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1039 | Lenix Elementor Leads addon &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URL Form Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1039</link><description>The Lenix Elementor Leads addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a URL form field in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49337 | IBM OpenPages HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49337</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 





is vulnerable to HTML injection, caused by improper validation of user-supplied input of text fields used to construct workflow email notifications. A remote authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability using HTML tags in a text field of an object to inject malicious script into an email which would be executed in a victim's mail client within the security context of the OpenPages mail message. An attacker could use this for phishing or identity theft attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49344 | IBM OpenPages session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49344</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 



with Watson Assistant chat feature enabled the application establishes a session when a user logs in and uses chat, but the chat session is still left active after logout.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49779 | IBM OpenPages cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49779</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages 

could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by improper validation and management of authentication cookies. By modifying the CSRF token and Session Id cookie parameters using the cookies of another user, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass security restrictions and gain unauthorized access to the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49781 | IBM OpenPages XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49781</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 IBM OpenPages is vulnerable to an XML external entity injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21105 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a command execution vulnerability. A Low privileged malicious user with local access c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21105</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a command execution vulnerability. A Low privileged malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability by running the specific binary and perform any administrative action permitted by it resulting in shutting down the server, modifying the configuration leading to gain access to unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21106 | Dell Recover Point for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a Weak file system permission vulnerability. A low privileged Local attacker could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21106</link><description>Dell Recover Point for Virtual Machines 6.0.X contains a Weak file system permission vulnerability. A low privileged Local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to impacting only non-sensitive resources in the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0868 | Remote Code Execution in DocsGPT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0868</link><description>A vulnerability, that could result in Remote Code Execution (RCE), has been found in DocsGPT. Due to improper parsing of JSON data using eval() an unauthorized attacker could send arbitrary Python code to be executed via /api/remote endpoint.

This issue affects DocsGPT: from 0.8.1 through 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1043 | Embed Any Document – Embed PDF, Word, PowerPoint and Excel Files &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via embeddoc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1043</link><description>The Embed Any Document – Embed PDF, Word, PowerPoint and Excel Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 via the 'embeddoc' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13476 | LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13476</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'engtz_wd_save_dropship' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13520 | Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) &amp;lt;= 4.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Price, Date, and Note Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13520</link><description>The Gift Cards (Gift Vouchers and Packages) (WooCommerce Supported) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data|loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_voucher_price', 'update_voucher_date', 'update_voucher_note' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the value, expiration date, and user note for any gift voucher.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13748 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.4 Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13748</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Title parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13753 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13753</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the update_profile function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify victim's email via a forged request, which might lead to account takeover, granted they can trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13789 | Ravpage &amp;lt;= 2.31 - PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13789</link><description>The ravpage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.31 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'paramsv2' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13792 | WooCommerce Food - Restaurant Menu &amp;amp; Food ordering &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via ids</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13792</link><description>The WooCommerce Food - Restaurant Menu &amp; Food ordering plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13802 | Bandsintown Events &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13802</link><description>The Bandsintown Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bandsintown_events' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13849 | Cookie Notice Bar &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13849</link><description>The Cookie Notice Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13855 | Prime Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via pae_global_block Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13855</link><description>The Prime Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 via the pae_global_block shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract information from posts that are not public, including drafts, private, password protected, and restricted posts. This applies to posts created with Elementor only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6432 | Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) &amp;lt;= 3.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via content Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6432</link><description>The Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter within the plugin's shortcode Content Block in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0866 | Legoeso PDF Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Author+) SQL Injection via checkedVals Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0866</link><description>The Legoeso PDF Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘checkedVals’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1328 | Typed JS: A typewriter style animation &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via typespeed Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1328</link><description>The Typed JS: A typewriter style animation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘typespeed’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1483 | LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition &amp;lt;= 2.3.12 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1483</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – GlobalTranz Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the engtz_wd_save_dropship AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the drop shipping settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 09:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13888 | WPMobile.App &amp;lt;= 11.56 - Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13888</link><description>The WPMobile.App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 11.56. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect URL supplied via the 'redirect' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0897 | Modal Window &amp;lt;= 6.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via iframeBox Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0897</link><description>The Modal Window – create popup modal window plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'iframeBox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1064 | Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) &amp;lt;= 2.8.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via xoo_el_action Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1064</link><description>The Login/Signup Popup ( Inline Form + Woocommerce ) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's xoo_el_action shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13155 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.140 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Transparent Split Hero Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13155</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Transparent Split Hero widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.140 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note: Since the widget code isn't part of the code base, to apply the patch, the affected widget: Transparent Split Hero must be deleted and reinstalled manually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 07:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26856 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26856</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If an attacker logs in to the affected product with an administrative account and manipulates requests for a certain screen operation, an arbitrary OS command may be executed. This vulnerability was reported on a different screen operation from CVE-2025-20617.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13445 | Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.27.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13445</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the border, margin and gap parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.27.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 04:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27218 | Sitecore Experience Manager (XM) and Experience Platform (XP) 10.4 before KB1002844 allow remote code execution through insecure deserializa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27218</link><description>Sitecore Experience Manager (XM) and Experience Platform (XP) 10.4 before KB1002844 allow remote code execution through insecure deserialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 04:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49780 | IBM OpenPages path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49780</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 

IBM OpenPages could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker with privileges to perform Import Configuration could send a specially crafted http request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) in the file name parameter used in Import Configuration to write files to arbitrary locations outside of the specified directory and possibly overwrite arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49782 | IBM OpenPages improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49782</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 



could allow a remote attacker to spoof mail server identity when using SSL/TLS security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to gain access to sensitive information disclosed through email notifications generated by OpenPages or disrupt notification delivery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43196 | IBM OpenPages data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43196</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 

application could allow an authenticated user to manipulate data in the Questionnaires application allowing the user to spoof other users' responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49355 | IBM OpenPages log manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49355</link><description>IBM OpenPages with Watson 8.3 and 9.0 may write improperly neutralized data to server log files when the tracing is enabled per the System Tracing feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24947 | A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) in LSQUIC (aka LiteSpeed QUIC) before 4.2.0 allows remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24947</link><description>A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) in LSQUIC (aka LiteSpeed QUIC) before 4.2.0 allows remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs). This is caused by XXH32 usage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23020 | An issue was discovered in Kwik before 0.10.1. A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) allows remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23020</link><description>An issue was discovered in Kwik before 0.10.1. A hash collision vulnerability (in the hash table used to manage connections) allows remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24946 | The hash table used to manage connections in picoquic before b80fd3f uses a weak hash function, allowing remote attackers to cause a conside...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24946</link><description>The hash table used to manage connections in picoquic before b80fd3f uses a weak hash function, allowing remote attackers to cause a considerable CPU load on the server (a Hash DoS attack) by initiating connections with colliding Source Connection IDs (SCIDs).</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:02:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1492 | Uncontrolled Recursion in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1492</link><description>Bundle Protocol and CBOR dissector crashes in Wireshark 4.4.0 to 4.4.3 and 4.2.0 to 4.2.10 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1222 | An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1222</link><description>An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data in Citrix Secure Access Client for Mac</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1223 | An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1223</link><description>An attacker can gain application privileges in order to perform limited modification and/or read arbitrary data in Citrix Secure Access Client for Mac</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1293 | HashiCorp Hermes Improperly Validates AWS ALB JWTs, which May Lead to Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1293</link><description>Hermes versions up to 0.4.0 improperly validated the JWT provided when using the AWS ALB authentication mode, potentially allowing for authentication bypass. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-1293, was fixed in Hermes 0.5.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0112 | Cortex XDR Agent: Local Windows User Can Disable the Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0112</link><description>A problem with a detection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a user with Windows non-administrative privileges to disable the agent. This vulnerability can also be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then perform malicious activity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37363 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37363</link><description>The product does not perform an authorization check when an actor attempts to access a resource or perform an action. (CWE-862)






 Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.8, including 8.3.x, do not correctly perform an authorization check in the data source management service.








When access control checks are incorrectly applied, users can access data or perform actions that they should not be allowed to perform. This can lead to a wide range of problems, including information exposures and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37362 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp;amp; Analytics - Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37362</link><description>The product transmits or stores authentication credentials, but it uses an insecure method that is susceptible to unauthorized interception and/or retrieval. (CWE-522) 



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp; Analytics versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.8, including 8.3.x, discloses database passwords when saving connections to RedShift.



 



Products must not disclose sensitive information without cause. Disclosure of sensitive information can lead to further exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6697 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6697</link><description>The product does not handle or incorrectly handles when it has insufficient privileges to access resources or functionality as specified by their permissions. This may cause it to follow unexpected code paths that may leave the product in an invalid state. (CWE-280)



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, do not handle invalid and missing permissions correctly, resulting in a denial of service.



 



An adversary leverages a legitimate capability of an application in such a way as to achieve a negative technical impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12284 | Authenticated privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12284</link><description>Authenticated privilege escalation in NetScaler Console and NetScaler Agent allows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37361 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37361</link><description>The application deserializes untrusted data without sufficiently verifying that the resulting data will be valid. (CWE-502)



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, deserialize untrusted JSON data without constraining the parser to approved classes and methods.



 



When developers place no restrictions on "gadget chains," or series of instances and method invocations that can self-execute during the deserialization process (i.e., before the object is returned to the caller), it is sometimes possible for attackers to leverage them to perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6696 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Insufficient Granularity of Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6696</link><description>The product implements access controls via a policy or other feature with the intention to disable or restrict accesses (reads and/or writes) to assets in a system from untrusted agents. However, implemented access controls lack required granularity, which renders the control policy too broad because it allows accesses from unauthorized agents to the security-sensitive assets. (CWE-1220) 






Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, do not correctly perform an authorization check in the user console trash content






 An attacker exploits a weakness in the configuration of access controls and is able to bypass the intended protection that these measures guard against and thereby obtain unauthorized access to the system or network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37359 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server – Server Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37359</link><description>The web server receives a URL or similar request from an upstream component and retrieves the contents of this URL, but it does not sufficiently ensure that the request is being sent to the expected destination. (CWE-918) 



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, do not validate the Host header of incoming HTTP/HTTPS requests.



 



By providing URLs to unexpected hosts or ports, attackers can make it appear that the server is sending the request, possibly bypassing access controls such as firewalls that prevent the attackers from accessing the URLs directly. The server can be used as a proxy to conduct port scanning of hosts in internal networks, use other URLs such as that can access documents on the system (using file://), or use other protocols such as gopher:// or tftp://, which may provide greater control over the contents of requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37360 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37360</link><description>Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') 



 



The software does not neutralize or incorrectly neutralize user-controllable input before it is placed in output that is used as a web page that is served to other users. (CWE-79)



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server prior to versions 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, allow a malicious URL to inject content into the Analyzer plugin interface.



 




Once the malicious script is injected, the attacker can perform a variety of malicious activities. The attacker could transfer private information, such as cookies that may include session information, from the victim's machine to the attacker. The attacker could send malicious requests to a web site on behalf of the victim, which could be especially dangerous to the site if the victim has administrator privileges to manage that site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25942 | An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the the mp4fragment tool when processing invalid files....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25942</link><description>An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the the mp4fragment tool when processing invalid files. Specifically, memory allocated in SampleArray::SampleArray in Mp4Fragment.cpp is not properly released.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25945 | An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the the Mp4Fragment.cpp and in AP4_DescriptorFactory::C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25945</link><description>An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the the Mp4Fragment.cpp and in AP4_DescriptorFactory::CreateDescriptorFromStream at Ap4DescriptorFactory.cpp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25946 | An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to cause a memory leak via Ap4Marlin.cpp and Ap4Processor.cpp, specifically in AP4_MarlinIp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25946</link><description>An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to cause a memory leak via Ap4Marlin.cpp and Ap4Processor.cpp, specifically in AP4_MarlinIpmpEncryptingProcessor::Initialize and AP4_Processor::Process, during the execution of mp4encrypt with a specially crafted MP4 input file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25947 | An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to trigger a segmentation fault via Ap4Atom.cpp, specifically in AP4_AtomParent::RemoveChil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25947</link><description>An issue in Bento4 v1.6.0-641 allows an attacker to trigger a segmentation fault via Ap4Atom.cpp, specifically in AP4_AtomParent::RemoveChild, during the execution of mp4encrypt with a specially crafted MP4 input file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5705 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server - Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5705</link><description>The product performs an authorization check when an actor attempts to access a resource or perform an action, but it does not correctly perform the check. This allows attackers to bypass intended access restrictions. (CWE-863) 



 



 



Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Business Analytics Server versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, have modules enabled by default that allow execution of system level processes. 



 








When access control checks are incorrectly applied, users can access data or perform actions that they should not be allowed to perform. This can lead to a wide range of problems, including information exposures and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25943 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 v.1.6.0-641 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_Stz2Atom::AP4_Stz2Atom com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25943</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 v.1.6.0-641 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_Stz2Atom::AP4_Stz2Atom component located in Ap4Stz2Atom.cpp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25944 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 v.1.6.0-641 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4RtpAtom.cpp, specifically i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25944</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 v.1.6.0-641 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4RtpAtom.cpp, specifically in AP4_RtpAtom::AP4_RtpAtom, during the execution of mp4fragment with a crafted MP4 input file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5706 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp;amp; Analytics - Improper Control of Resource Identifiers (&amp;#x27;Resource Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5706</link><description>The product receives input from an upstream component, but it does not restrict or incorrectly restricts the input before it is used as an identifier for a resource that may be outside the intended sphere of control. (CWE-99) 






Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp; Analytics versions before 10.2.0.0 and 9.3.0.9, including 8.3.x, do not restrict JNDI identifiers during the creation of Community Dashboards, allowing control of system-level data sources. 







An attacker could gain access to or modify sensitive data or system resources. This could allow access to protected files or directories including configuration files and files containing sensitive information, which can lead to remote code execution by unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51305 | PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51305</link><description>PHPJabbers Car Park Booking System v3.0 is vulnerable to Multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key" parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21355 | Microsoft Bing Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21355</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24989 | Microsoft Power Pages Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24989</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27092 | Path Traversal Vulnerability in GHOSTS Photo Retrieval Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27092</link><description>GHOSTS is an open source user simulation framework for cyber experimentation, simulation, training, and exercise. A path traversal vulnerability was discovered in GHOSTS version 8.0.0.0 that allows an attacker to access files outside of the intended directory through the photo retrieval endpoint. The vulnerability exists in the /api/npcs/{id}/photo endpoint, which is designed to serve profile photos for NPCs (Non-Player Characters) but fails to properly validate and sanitize file paths. When an NPC is created with a specially crafted photoLink value containing path traversal sequences (../, ..\, etc.), the application processes these sequences without proper sanitization. This allows an attacker to traverse directory structures and access files outside of the intended photo directory, potentially exposing sensitive system files. The vulnerability is particularly severe because it allows reading arbitrary files from the server's filesystem with the permissions of the web application process, which could include configuration files, credentials, or other sensitive data. This issue has been addressed in version 8.2.7.90 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27090 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in sliver teamserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27090</link><description>Sliver is an open source cross-platform adversary emulation/red team framework, it can be used by organizations of all sizes to perform security testing. The reverse port forwarding in sliver teamserver allows the implant to open a reverse tunnel on the sliver teamserver without verifying if the operator instructed the implant to do so. The only impact that has been shown is the exposure of the server's IP address to a third party. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.43 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 21:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51300 | PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51300</link><description>PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key" parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51301 | A lack of rate limiting in the "Login Section, Forgot Email" feature of PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 allows attackers to send an exc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51301</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the "Login Section, Forgot Email" feature of PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of reset requests for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51302 | PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51302</link><description>PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51303 | PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "lid, name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51303</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Ticketing System v1.0 is vulnerable to Multiple HTML Injection in the "lid, name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25196 | OpenFGA Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25196</link><description>OpenFGA is a high-performance and flexible authorization/permission engine built for developers and inspired by Google Zanzibar. OpenFGA &lt; v1.8.4 (Helm chart &lt; openfga-0.2.22, docker &lt; v.1.8.4) are vulnerable to authorization bypass when certain Check and ListObject calls are executed. Users on OpenFGA v1.8.4 or previous, specifically under the following conditions are affected by this authorization bypass vulnerability: 1. Calling Check API or ListObjects with a model that has a relation directly assignable to both public access AND userset with the same type. 2. A type bound public access tuple is assigned to an object. 3. userset tuple is not assigned to the same object. and 4. Check request's user field is a userset that has the same type as the type bound public access tuple's user type. Users are advised to upgrade to v1.8.5 which is backwards compatible. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51299 | PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51299</link><description>PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 is vulnerable to HTML Injection in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key, title" parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51298 | PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51298</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection vulnerability which allows an attacker to execute remote code. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient input validation on Languages section Labels any parameters field in System Options that is used to construct CSV file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51297 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51297</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Hotel Booking System v4.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51296 | PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51296</link><description>PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the "name, plugin_sms_api_key, plugin_sms_country_code, title, plugin_sms_api_key" parameters which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46272 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Extreme Networks IQ Engine before 10.6r1a, and through 10.6r4 before 10.6r5, allows an attacker to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46272</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Extreme Networks IQ Engine before 10.6r1a, and through 10.6r4 before 10.6r5, allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the implementation of the ah_auth service</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51293 | A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 allows attackers to sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51293</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the 'Forgot Password', 'Email Settings' feature of PHPJabbers Event Booking Calendar v4.0 allows attackers to send an excessive amount of email for a legitimate user, leading to a possible Denial of Service (DoS) via a large amount of generated e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-13481 | Certain Lexmark products through 2020-05-25 allow XSS which allows an attacker to obtain session credentials and other sensitive information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-13481</link><description>Certain Lexmark products through 2020-05-25 allow XSS which allows an attacker to obtain session credentials and other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-35546 | Lexmark MX6500 LW75.JD.P296 and previous devices have Incorrect Access Control via the access control settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-35546</link><description>Lexmark MX6500 LW75.JD.P296 and previous devices have Incorrect Access Control via the access control settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46271 | Extreme Networks IQ Engine before 10.6r1a, and through 10.6r4 before 10.6r5, has a buffer overflow. This issue arises from the ah_webui serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46271</link><description>Extreme Networks IQ Engine before 10.6r1a, and through 10.6r4 before 10.6r5, has a buffer overflow. This issue arises from the ah_webui service, which listens on TCP port 3009 by default.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0624 | Grub2: net: out-of-bounds write in grub_net_search_config_file()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0624</link><description>A flaw was found in grub2. During the network boot process, when trying to search for the configuration file, grub copies data from a user controlled environment variable into an internal buffer using the grub_strcpy() function. During this step, it fails to consider the environment variable length when allocating the internal buffer, resulting in an out-of-bounds write. If correctly exploited, this issue may result in remote code execution through the same network segment grub is searching for the boot information, which can be used to by-pass secure boot protections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0677 | Grub2: ufs: integer overflow may lead to heap based out-of-bounds write when handling symlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0677</link><description>A flaw was found in grub2. When performing a symlink lookup, the grub's UFS module checks the inode's data size to allocate the internal buffer to read the file content, however, it fails to check if the symlink data size has overflown. When this occurs, grub_malloc() may be called with a smaller value than needed. When further reading the data from the disk into the buffer, the grub_ufs_lookup_symlink() function will write past the end of the allocated size. An attack can leverage this by crafting a malicious filesystem, and as a result, it will corrupt data stored in the heap, allowing for arbitrary code execution used to by-pass secure boot mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-10095 | Various Lexmark devices have CSRF that allows an attacker to modify the configuration of the device.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10095</link><description>Various Lexmark devices have CSRF that allows an attacker to modify the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0893 | Symantec Diagnostic Tool (SymDiag), prior to 3.0.79, may be susceptible to a Privilege Escalation vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0893</link><description>Symantec Diagnostic Tool (SymDiag), prior to 3.0.79, may be susceptible to a Privilege Escalation vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1118 | Grub2: commands/dump: the dump command is not in lockdown when secure boot is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1118</link><description>A flaw was found in grub2. Grub's dump command is not blocked when grub is in lockdown mode, which allows the user to read any memory information, and an attacker may leverage this in order to extract signatures, salts, and other sensitive information from the memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45777 | Grub2: grub-core/gettext: integer overflow leads to heap oob write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45777</link><description>A flaw was found in grub2. The calculation of the translation buffer when reading a language .mo file in grub_gettext_getstr_from_position() may overflow, leading to a Out-of-bound write. This issue can be leveraged by an attacker to overwrite grub2's sensitive heap data, eventually leading to the circumvention of secure boot protections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53974 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53974</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.21 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24806 | Regulation applies separately to Username-based logins to Email-based logins in authelia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24806</link><description>Authelia is an open-source authentication and authorization server providing two-factor authentication and single sign-on (SSO) for applications via a web portal. If users are allowed to sign in via both username and email the regulation system treats these as separate login events. This leads to the regulation limitations being effectively doubled assuming an attacker using brute-force to find a user password. It's important to note that due to the effective operation of regulation where no user-facing sign of their regulation ban being visible either via timing or via API responses, it's effectively impossible to determine if a failure occurs due to a bad username password combination, or a effective ban blocking the attempt which heavily mitigates any form of brute-force. This occurs because the records and counting process for this system uses the method utilized for sign in rather than the effective username attribute. This has a minimal impact on account security, this impact is increased naturally in scenarios when there is no two-factor authentication required and weak passwords are used. This makes it a bit easier to brute-force a password. A patch for this issue has been applied to versions 4.38.19, and 4.39.0. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should 1. Not heavily modify the default settings in a way that ends up with shorter or less frequent regulation bans. The default settings effectively mitigate any potential for this issue to be exploited. and 2. Disable the ability for users to login via an email address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0999 | Heap buffer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0999</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1006 | Use after free in Network in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1006</link><description>Use after free in Network in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted web app. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1426 | Heap buffer overflow in GPU in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrup...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1426</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in GPU in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52541 | Dell Client Platform BIOS contains a Weak Authentication vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52541</link><description>Dell Client Platform BIOS contains a Weak Authentication vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24965 | .krun_config.json symlink attack creates or overwrites file on the host in crun</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24965</link><description>crun is an open source OCI Container Runtime fully written in C. In affected versions A malicious container image could trick the krun handler into escaping the root filesystem, allowing file creation or modification on the host. No special permissions are needed, only the ability for the current user to write to the target file. The problem is fixed in crun 1.20 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27089 | Overlapping policies allow update to non-allowed fields in directus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27089</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. In affected versions if there are two overlapping policies for the `update` action that allow access to different fields, instead of correctly checking access permissions against the item they apply for the user is allowed to update the superset of fields allowed by any of the policies. E.g. have one policy allowing update access to `field_a` if the `id == 1` and one policy allowing update access to `field_b` if the `id == 2`. The user with both these policies is allowed to update both `field_a` and `field_b` for the items with ids `1` and `2`. Before v11, if a user was allowed to update an item they were allowed to update the fields that the single permission, that applied to that item, listed. With overlapping permissions this isn't as clear cut anymore and the union of fields might not be the fields the user is allowed to update for that specific item. The solution that this PR introduces is to evaluate the permissions for each field that the user tries to update in the validateItemAccess DB query, instead of only verifying access to the item as a whole. This is done by, instead of returning the actual field value, returning a flag that indicates if the user has access to that field. This uses the same case/when mechanism that is used for stripping out non permitted field that is at the core of the permissions engine. As a result, for every item that the access is validated for, the expected result is an item that has either 1 or null for all the "requested" fields instead of any of the actual field values. These results are not useful for anything other than verifying the field level access permissions. The final check in validateItemAccess can either fail if the number of items does not match the number of items the access is checked for (ie. the user does not have access to the item at all) or if not all of the passed in fields have access permissions for any of the returned items. This is a vulnerability that allows update access to unintended fields, potentially impacting the password field for user accounts. This has been addressed in version 11.1.2 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47160 | IBM Cognos Controller XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47160</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 





is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28776 | IBM Cognos Controller cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28776</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 

is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28777 | IBM Cognos Controller code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28777</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 



is vulnerable to unrestricted deserialization. This vulnerability allows users to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, or cause denial of service attacks by exploiting the unrestricted deserialization of types in the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20153 | Cisco ESA mail Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20153</link><description>A vulnerability in the email filtering mechanism of Cisco Secure Email Gateway could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the configured rules and allow emails that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. &amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of email that passes through an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted email through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass email filters on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20158 | Cisco Video Phone 8875 and Desk Phone 9800 Series Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20158</link><description>A vulnerability in the debug shell of Cisco Video Phone 8875 and Cisco Desk Phone 9800 Series could allow an authenticated, local attacker to access sensitive information on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials with SSH access on the affected device. SSH access is disabled by default.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the debug shell of an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SSH client command to the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive information on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20211 | Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20211</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco BroadWorks Application Delivery Platform could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting attack against a user of the interface.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28780 | IBM Cognos Controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28780</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 Rich Client 





uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45081 | IBM Cognos Controller incorrect authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45081</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 



could allow an authenticated user to modify restricted content due to incorrect authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1465 | lmxcms Maintenance db.inc.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1465</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in lmxcms 1.41. Affected is an unknown function of the file db.inc.php of the component Maintenance. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45084 | IBM Cognos Controller CSV injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45084</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 

could allow an authenticated attacker to conduct formula injection. An attacker could execute arbitrary commands on the system, caused by improper validation of file contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52902 | IBM Cognos Controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52902</link><description>IBM Cognos Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 FP3 and IBM Controller 11.1.0 client application contains hard coded database passwords in source code which could be used for unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1464 | Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System admin.house.collect.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1464</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Baiyi Cloud Asset Management System up to 20250204. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /wuser/admin.house.collect.php. The manipulation of the argument project_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13478 | LTL Freight Quotes – TForce Edition &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13478</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – TForce Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13479 | LTL Freight Quotes – SEFL Edition &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13479</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – SEFL Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13481 | LTL Freight Quotes – R+L Carriers Edition &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13481</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – R+L Carriers Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13483 | LTL Freight Quotes – SAIA Edition &amp;lt;= 2.2.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13483</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – SAIA Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13485 | LTL Freight Quotes – ABF Freight Edition &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13485</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – ABF Freight Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13491 | Small Package Quotes – For Customers of FedEx &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13491</link><description>The Small Package Quotes – For Customers of FedEx plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13533 | Small Package Quotes – USPS Edition &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13533</link><description>The Small Package Quotes – USPS Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13534 | Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition &amp;lt;= 5.2.18 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13534</link><description>The Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.18 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0916 | YaySMTP 2.4.9 - 2.6.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0916</link><description>The YaySMTP and Email Logs: Amazon SES, SendGrid, Outlook, Mailgun, Brevo, Google and Any SMTP Service plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions 2.4.9 to 2.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note: The vulnerability has been initially patched in version 2.4.8 and was reintroduced in version 2.4.9 with the removal of the wp_kses_post() built-in WordPress sanitization function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0968 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via get_megamenu_content Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0968</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0  due to a missing capability checks on the get_megamenu_content() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view any item created in Elementor, such as posts, pages and templates including drafts, trashed and private items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:25:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1075 | LDAP credentials logged to Apache error log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1075</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p27, &lt;2.2.0p40, and 2.1.0p51 (EOL) causes LDAP credentials to be written to Apache error log file accessible to administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13489 | LTL Freight Quotes – Old Dominion Edition &amp;lt;= 4.2.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13489</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Old Dominion Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_id' and 'dropship_edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1134 | SQL Injection in ChurchCRM CurrentFundraiser Parameter via DonatedItemEditor.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1134</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ChurchCRM 5.13.0 and prior that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries by exploiting a boolean-based and time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability in the DonatedItemEditor functionality. The CurrentFundraiser parameter is directly concatenated into an SQL query without sufficient sanitization, allowing an attacker to manipulate database queries and execute arbitrary commands, potentially leading to data exfiltration, modification, or deletion. Please note that this vulnerability requires Administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1135 | SQL Injection in ChurchCRM CurrentFundraiser Parameter via BatchWinnerEntry.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1135</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ChurchCRM 5.13.0. and prior that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries by exploiting a boolean-based and time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability in the BatchWinnerEntry functionality. The CurrentFundraiser parameter is directly concatenated into an SQL query without sufficient sanitization, allowing an attacker to manipulate database queries and execute arbitrary commands, potentially leading to data exfiltration, modification, or deletion. Please note the vulnerability requires Administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1133 | SQL Injection in ChurchCRM EID Parameter via EditEventAttendees.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1133</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ChurchCRM 5.13.0 and prior that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries by exploiting a boolean-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability in the EditEventAttendees functionality. The EID parameter is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization, making it susceptible to SQL injection attacks. An attacker can manipulate the query, potentially leading to data exfiltration, modification, or deletion.  Please note that this vulnerability requires Administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 09:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1132 | SQL Injection in ChurchCRM EN_tyid Parameter via EditEventAttendees.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1132</link><description>A time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the ChurchCRM 5.13.0 and prior EditEventAttendees.php within the EN_tyid parameter. The parameter is directly inserted into an SQL query without proper sanitization, allowing attackers to inject malicious SQL commands. Please note that the vulnerability requires Administrator permissions. This flaw can potentially allow attackers to delay the response, indicating the presence of an SQL injection vulnerability. While it is a time-based blind injection, it can be exploited to gain insights into the underlying database, and with further exploitation, sensitive data could be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1007 | Improper Authorization in /user/namespace/{namespace}/details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1007</link><description>In OpenVSX version v0.9.0 to v0.20.0, the 
/user/namespace/{namespace}/details API allows a user to edit all 
namespace details, even if the user is not a namespace Owner or 
Contributor. The details include: name, description, website, support 
link and social media links. The same issues existed in 
/user/namespace/{namespace}/details/logo and allowed a user to change 
the logo.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1024 | Session Hijacking via Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in ChurchCRM EditEventAttendees.php EID Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1024</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ChurchCRM 5.13.0 that allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser via Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the EditEventAttendees.php page. This requires Administration privileges and affects the EID parameter. The flaw allows an attacker to steal session cookies, perform actions on behalf of an authenticated user, and gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13231 | WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Portfolio Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13231</link><description>The WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'add_video' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary videos to any portfolio gallery.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13336 | Disable Auto Updates &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Auto-update Disable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13336</link><description>The Disable Auto Updates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'disable-auto-updates' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable all auto updates via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13339 | DeBounce Email Validator &amp;lt;= 5.6.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13339</link><description>The DeBounce Email Validator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'debounce_email_validator' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13363 | Raptive Ads &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13363</link><description>The Raptive Ads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'poc' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:36:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13364 | Raptive Ads &amp;lt;= 3.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Data/Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13364</link><description>The Raptive Ads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the site_ads_files_reset() and cls_file_reset() functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the ad and cls files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 08:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11335 | UltraEmbed – Advanced Iframe Plugin For WordPress with Gutenberg Block Included &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11335</link><description>The UltraEmbed – Advanced Iframe Plugin For WordPress with Gutenberg Block Included plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11753 | UMich OIDC Login &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11753</link><description>The UMich OIDC Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'umich_oidc_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11778 | CanadaHelps Embedded Donation &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11778</link><description>The CanadaHelps Embedded Donation Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'embedcdn' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12069 | Lexicata &amp;lt;= 1.0.16 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12069</link><description>The Lexicata plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.16. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action, such as clicking on a specially crafted link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12339 | Digihood HTML Sitemap &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;channel&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12339</link><description>The Digihood HTML Sitemap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘channel' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12522 | Yay! Forms | Embed Custom Forms, Surveys, and Quizzes Easily &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12522</link><description>The Yay! Forms | Embed Custom Forms, Surveys, and Quizzes Easily plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'yayforms' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13390 | ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13390</link><description>The ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'adfo_list' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13405 | Apptivo Business Site CRM &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to IP Address Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13405</link><description>The Apptivo Business Site CRM plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'awp_ip_deny' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to block IP addresses via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13462 | WP Wiki Tooltip &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13462</link><description>The WP Wiki Tooltip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wiki' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13468 | Trash Duplicate and 301 Redirect &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13468</link><description>The Trash Duplicate and 301 Redirect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'duplicates-action-top' action in all versions up to, and including, 1.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts/pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13589 | YouTube Playlists with Schema &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13589</link><description>The YouTube Playlists with Schema plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'yt_grid' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13591 | Team Builder For WPBakery Page Builder(Formerly Visual Composer) &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13591</link><description>The Team Builder For WPBakery Page Builder(Formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'team-builder-vc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13592 | Team Builder For WPBakery Page Builder(Formerly Visual Composer) &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13592</link><description>The Team Builder For WPBakery Page Builder(Formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via the 'team-builder-vc' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13657 | Store Locator Widget &amp;lt;= 20200131 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13657</link><description>The Store Locator Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'storelocatorwidget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 20200131 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13660 | Responsive Flickr Slideshow &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13660</link><description>The Responsive Flickr Slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fshow' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13663 | Coaching Staffs &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13663</link><description>The Coaching Staffs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mstw-cs-table' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13674 | Cosmic Blocks (40+) Content Editor Blocks Collection &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13674</link><description>The Cosmic Blocks (40+) Content Editor Blocks Collection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cwp_social_share' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13676 | Categorized Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13676</link><description>The Categorized Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'field' attribute of the 'image_gallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13679 | Widget BUY.BOX &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13679</link><description>The Widget BUY.BOX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buybox-widget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13711 | Pollin &amp;lt;= 1.01.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13711</link><description>The Pollin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'question' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.01.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13712 | Pollin &amp;lt;= 1.01.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13712</link><description>The Pollin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'question' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.01.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13719 | PeproDev Ultimate Invoice &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Order Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13719</link><description>The PeproDev Ultimate Invoice plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.8 via the invoicing viewer due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view invoices for completed orders which can contain PII of users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13736 | Pure Chat – Live Chat &amp;amp; More! &amp;lt;= 2.31 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via purechatWidgetName Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13736</link><description>The Pure Chat – Live Chat &amp; More! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘purechatWidgetName’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13854 | Education Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via naedu_elementor_template Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13854</link><description>The Education Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 via the naedu_elementor_template shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract information from posts that are not public, including drafts, password protected, and restricted posts. This applies to posts created with Elementor only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0865 | WP Media Category Management 2.0 - 2.3.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0865</link><description>The WP Media Category Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions 2.0 to 2.3.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wp_mcm_handle_action_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to alter plugin settings, such as the taxonomy used for media, the base slug for media categories, and the default media category via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0633 | Heap Overflow in iniparser.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0633</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in iniparser_dumpsection_ini() in iniparser allows attacker to read out of bound memory</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 07:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12173 | Master Slider &amp;lt; 3.10.5 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12173</link><description>The Master Slider  WordPress plugin before 3.10.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Editor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22888 | Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the custom block edit page of MT Block Editor. If exploited, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22888</link><description>Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the custom block edit page of MT Block Editor. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24841 | Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the HTML edit mode of MT Block Editor. It is exploitable when TinyMCE6 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24841</link><description>Movable Type contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the HTML edit mode of MT Block Editor. It is exploitable when TinyMCE6 is used as a rich text editor and an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25054 | Movable Type contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the user information edit page. When Multi-Factor authentication plu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25054</link><description>Movable Type contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the user information edit page. When Multi-Factor authentication plugin is enabled and a user accesses a crafted page while logged in to the affected product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 06:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13799 | User Private Files – File Upload &amp;amp; Download Manager with Secure File Sharing &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13799</link><description>The User Private Files – File Upload &amp; Download Manager with Secure File Sharing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘new-fldr-name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1065 | Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.11.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Import Data From File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1065</link><description>The Visualizer: Tables and Charts Manager for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Import Data From File feature in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 05:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1441 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1007 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1441</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1007. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'wpr_filter_woo_products' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 04:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22622 | Age Verification - Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22622</link><description>Age Verification for your checkout page. Verify your customer's identity 1.20.0 was found to be vulnerable. The web application dynamically generates web content without validating the source of the potentially untrusted data in myapp/class-wc-integration-agechecker-integration.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11582 | Subscribe2 – Form, Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters &amp;lt;= 10.43 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via IP Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11582</link><description>The Subscribe2 – Form, Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ip parameter in all versions up to, and including, 10.43 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13443 | Easypromos Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13443</link><description>The Easypromos Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Easypromos shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57261 | In barebox before 2025.01.0, request2size in common/dlmalloc.c has an integer overflow, a related issue to CVE-2024-57258.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57261</link><description>In barebox before 2025.01.0, request2size in common/dlmalloc.c has an integer overflow, a related issue to CVE-2024-57258.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57262 | In barebox before 2025.01.0, ext4fs_read_symlink has an integer overflow for zalloc (adding one to an le32 variable) via a crafted ext4 file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57262</link><description>In barebox before 2025.01.0, ext4fs_read_symlink has an integer overflow for zalloc (adding one to an le32 variable) via a crafted ext4 filesystem with an inode size of 0xffffffff, resulting in a malloc of zero and resultant memory overwrite, a related issue to CVE-2024-57256.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1448 | Synway SMG Gateway Management Software 9-12ping.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1448</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Synway SMG Gateway Management Software up to 20250204. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file 9-12ping.php. The manipulation of the argument retry leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1447 | kasuganosoras Pigeon index.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1447</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kasuganosoras Pigeon 1.0.177. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pigeon/imgproxy/index.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.181 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 84cea5fe73141689da2e7ec8676d47435bd6423e. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>