<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-26923 | af_unix: Fix garbage collector racing against connect()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26923</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Fix garbage collector racing against connect()

Garbage collector does not take into account the risk of embryo getting
enqueued during the garbage collection. If such embryo has a peer that
carries SCM_RIGHTS, two consecutive passes of scan_children() may see a
different set of children. Leading to an incorrectly elevated inflight
count, and then a dangling pointer within the gc_inflight_list.

sockets are AF_UNIX/SOCK_STREAM
S is an unconnected socket
L is a listening in-flight socket bound to addr, not in fdtable
V's fd will be passed via sendmsg(), gets inflight count bumped

connect(S, addr)	sendmsg(S, [V]); close(V)	__unix_gc()
----------------	-------------------------	-----------

NS = unix_create1()
skb1 = sock_wmalloc(NS)
L = unix_find_other(addr)
unix_state_lock(L)
unix_peer(S) = NS
			// V count=1 inflight=0

 			NS = unix_peer(S)
 			skb2 = sock_alloc()
			skb_queue_tail(NS, skb2[V])

			// V became in-flight
			// V count=2 inflight=1

			close(V)

			// V count=1 inflight=1
			// GC candidate condition met

						for u in gc_inflight_list:
						  if (total_refs == inflight_refs)
						    add u to gc_candidates

						// gc_candidates={L, V}

						for u in gc_candidates:
						  scan_children(u, dec_inflight)

						// embryo (skb1) was not
						// reachable from L yet, so V's
						// inflight remains unchanged
__skb_queue_tail(L, skb1)
unix_state_unlock(L)
						for u in gc_candidates:
						  if (u.inflight)
						    scan_children(u, inc_inflight_move_tail)

						// V count=1 inflight=2 (!)

If there is a GC-candidate listening socket, lock/unlock its state. This
makes GC wait until the end of any ongoing connect() to that socket. After
flipping the lock, a possibly SCM-laden embryo is already enqueued. And if
there is another embryo coming, it can not possibly carry SCM_RIGHTS. At
this point, unix_inflight() can not happen because unix_gc_lock is already
taken. Inflight graph remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26924 | netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: do not free live element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26924</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: do not free live element

Pablo reports a crash with large batches of elements with a
back-to-back add/remove pattern.  Quoting Pablo:

  add_elem("00000000") timeout 100 ms
  ...
  add_elem("0000000X") timeout 100 ms
  del_elem("0000000X") &lt;---------------- delete one that was just added
  ...
  add_elem("00005000") timeout 100 ms

  1) nft_pipapo_remove() removes element 0000000X
  Then, KASAN shows a splat.

Looking at the remove function there is a chance that we will drop a
rule that maps to a non-deactivated element.

Removal happens in two steps, first we do a lookup for key k and return the
to-be-removed element and mark it as inactive in the next generation.
Then, in a second step, the element gets removed from the set/map.

The _remove function does not work correctly if we have more than one
element that share the same key.

This can happen if we insert an element into a set when the set already
holds an element with same key, but the element mapping to the existing
key has timed out or is not active in the next generation.

In such case its possible that removal will unmap the wrong element.
If this happens, we will leak the non-deactivated element, it becomes
unreachable.

The element that got deactivated (and will be freed later) will
remain reachable in the set data structure, this can result in
a crash when such an element is retrieved during lookup (stale
pointer).

Add a check that the fully matching key does in fact map to the element
that we have marked as inactive in the deactivation step.
If not, we need to continue searching.

Add a bug/warn trap at the end of the function as well, the remove
function must not ever be called with an invisible/unreachable/non-existent
element.

v2: avoid uneeded temporary variable (Stefano)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26925 | netfilter: nf_tables: release mutex after nft_gc_seq_end from abort path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26925</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: release mutex after nft_gc_seq_end from abort path

The commit mutex should not be released during the critical section
between nft_gc_seq_begin() and nft_gc_seq_end(), otherwise, async GC
worker could collect expired objects and get the released commit lock
within the same GC sequence.

nf_tables_module_autoload() temporarily releases the mutex to load
module dependencies, then it goes back to replay the transaction again.
Move it at the end of the abort phase after nft_gc_seq_end() is called.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20248 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20248</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data in a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20249 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20249</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data in a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20313 | A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link><description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20295 | A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20295</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have read-only or higher privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20356 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20356</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges to perform command injection attacks on an affected system and elevate their privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient user input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the web-based management interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32879 | social-auth-app-django Improper Handling of Case Sensitivity vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32879</link><description>Python Social Auth is a social authentication/registration mechanism. Prior to version 5.4.1, due to default case-insensitive collation in MySQL or MariaDB databases, third-party authentication user IDs are not case-sensitive and could cause different IDs to match. This issue has been addressed by a fix released in version 5.4.1. An immediate workaround would be to change collation of the affected field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20358 | A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4126 | Tenda W15E SetSysTimeCfg formSetSysTime stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4126</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetSysTime of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument manualTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261869 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4127 | Tenda W15E guestWifiRuleRefresh stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4127</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function guestWifiRuleRefresh. The manipulation of the argument qosGuestDownstream leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-261870 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32876 | NewPipe has potential security vulnerability when importing settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32876</link><description>NewPipe is an Android app for video streaming written in Java. It supports exporting and importing backups, as a way to let users move their data to a new device effortlessly. However, in versions 0.13.4 through 0.26.1, importing a backup file from an untrusted source could have resulted in Arbitrary Code Execution. This is because backups are serialized/deserialized using Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol, which can allow constructing any class in the app, unless properly restricted.

To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to build a backup file containing the exploit, and then persuade a user into importing it. During the import process, the malicious code would be executed, possibly crashing the app, stealing user data from the NewPipe app, performing nasty actions through Android APIs, and attempting Android JVM/Sandbox escapes through vulnerabilities in the Android OS.

The attack can take place only if the user imports a malicious backup file, so an attacker would need to trick a user into importing a backup file from a source they can control. The implementation details of the malicious backup file can be independent of the attacked user or the device they are being run on, and do not require additional privileges.

All NewPipe versions from 0.13.4 to 0.26.1 are vulnerable. NewPipe version 0.27.0 fixes the issue by doing the following: Restrict the classes that can be deserialized when calling Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol, by adding a whitelist with only innocuous data-only classes that can't lead to Arbitrary Code Execution; deprecate backups serialized with Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol; use JSON serialization for all newly created backups (but still include an alternative file serialized with Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol in the backup zip for backwards compatibility); show a warning to the user when attempting to import a backup where the only available serialization mode is Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol (note that in the future this serialization mode will be removed completely).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4125 | Tenda W15E setStaticRoute formSetStaticRoute stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4125</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetStaticRoute of the file /goform/setStaticRoute. The manipulation of the argument staticRouteIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261868. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4141 | Out-of-bounds array write in Xpdf 4.05 due to incorrect bounds check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4141</link><description>Out-of-bounds array write in Xpdf 4.05 and earlier, triggered by an invalid character code in a Type 1 font. The root problem was a bounds check that was being optimized away by modern compilers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4123 | Tenda W15E SetPortMapping formSetPortMapping stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4123</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected by this issue is the function formSetPortMapping of the file /goform/SetPortMapping. The manipulation of the argument portMappingServer/portMappingProtocol/portMappingWan/porMappingtInternal/portMappingExternal leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4124 | Tenda W15E SetRemoteWebManage formSetRemoteWebManage stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4124</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. This affects the function formSetRemoteWebManage of the file /goform/SetRemoteWebManage. The manipulation of the argument remoteIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261867. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20353 | A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link><description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20359 | A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link><description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4121 | Tenda W15E formQOSRuleDel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4121</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected is the function formQOSRuleDel. The manipulation of the argument qosIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261864. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4122 | Tenda W15E setDebugCfg formSetDebugCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4122</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetDebugCfg of the file /goform/setDebugCfg. The manipulation of the argument enable/level/module leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261865 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4120 | Tenda W15E modifyIpMacBind formIPMacBindModify stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4120</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formIPMacBindModify of the file /goform/modifyIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindRuleId/IPMacBindRuleIp/IPMacBindRuleMac/IPMacBindRuleRemark leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261863. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0151 | Insufficient argument checking in Secure state Entry functions in software using Cortex-M Security Extensions (CMSE), that has been compiled...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0151</link><description>Insufficient argument checking in Secure state Entry functions in software using Cortex-M Security Extensions (CMSE), that has been compiled using toolchains that implement 'Arm v8-M Security Extensions Requirements on Development Tools' prior to version 1.4, allows an attacker to pass values to Secure state that are out of range for types smaller than 32-bits. Out of range values might lead to incorrect operations in secure state due.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4119 | Tenda W15E delIpMacBind formIPMacBindDel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4119</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formIPMacBindDel of the file /goform/delIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51477 | WordPress BuddyBoss Theme theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.60 - Unauth. Arbitrary WordPress Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51477</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in BUDDYBOSS DMCC BuddyBoss Theme allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects BuddyBoss Theme: from n/a through 2.4.60.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23228 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Locked Notes content may have b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23228</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Locked Notes content may have been unexpectedly unlocked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23271 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, Safari 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23271</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, Safari 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3. A malicious website may cause unexpected cross-origin behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27791 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, iOS 16.7.5 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27791</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, macOS Monterey 12.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51472 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.7 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51472</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3371 | Insufficient validation of external input in Compass may enable MITM attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3371</link><description>MongoDB Compass may accept and use insufficiently validated input from an untrusted external source. This may cause unintended application behavior, including data disclosure and enabling attackers to impersonate users. This issue affects MongoDB Compass versions 1.35.0 to 1.40.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51471 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51471</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4118 | Tenda W15E addIpMacBind formIPMacBindAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4118</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formIPMacBindAdd of the file /goform/addIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindRule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261861 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51425 | WordPress Rencontre plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.1 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51425</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Jacques Malgrange Rencontre – Dating Site allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Rencontre – Dating Site: from n/a through 3.10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47774 | WordPress Jetpack plugin &amp;lt; 12.7 - Auth. Iframe Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47774</link><description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Automattic Jetpack allows Clickjacking.This issue affects Jetpack: from n/a before 12.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48763 | WordPress JetFormBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48763</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS vulnerability in Crocoblock JetFormBuilder allows Code Injection.This issue affects JetFormBuilder: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51405 | WordPress BookingPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.74 - Booking Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51405</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Repute Infosystems BookingPress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects BookingPress: from n/a through 1.0.74.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4116 | Tenda W15E DelDhcpRule formDelDhcpRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formDelDhcpRule of the file /goform/DelDhcpRule. The manipulation of the argument delDhcpIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261859. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4117 | Tenda W15E DelPortMapping formDelPortMapping stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formDelPortMapping of the file /goform/DelPortMapping. The manipulation of the argument portMappingIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261860. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31090 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.60 - Unrestricted Zip Extraction vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31090</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.60.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32127 | WordPress Multi Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.6 - Unauth Arbitrary rating value change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32127</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Daniel Powney Multi Rating allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Multi Rating: from n/a through 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47504 | WordPress Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.16.4 - Auth. Arbitrary Attachment Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47504</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Elementor Elementor Website Builder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Elementor Website Builder: from n/a through 3.16.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25790 | WordPress WoodMart theme &amp;lt;= 7.0.4 - Unauth Arbitrary Shortcodes Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25790</link><description>Improper Authentication, Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in xtemos WoodMart allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects WoodMart: from n/a through 7.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32078 | WordPress FV Player plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.44.7212 - Unvalidated Redirects and Forwards vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32078</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Foliovision FV Flowplayer Video Player.This issue affects FV Flowplayer Video Player: from n/a through 7.5.44.7212.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32432 | WordPress Ovic Addon Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32432</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ovic Team Ovic Addon Toolkit.This issue affects Ovic Addon Toolkit: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4115 | Tenda W15E AddDnsForward formAddDnsForward stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4115</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected is the function formAddDnsForward of the file /goform/AddDnsForward. The manipulation of the argument DnsForwardRule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32675 | WordPress Order Limit for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32675</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xfinity Soft Order Limit for WooCommerce.This issue affects Order Limit for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32677 | WordPress LoginPress Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Unauth. License Activation/Deactivation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32677</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LoginPress LoginPress Pro.This issue affects LoginPress Pro: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32678 | WordPress TrackShip for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32678</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in TrackShip TrackShip for WooCommerce.This issue affects TrackShip for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32699 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Compare plugin &amp;lt;= 2.37.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32699</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Compare.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Compare: from n/a through 2.37.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32728 | WordPress Paid Membership Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32728</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions.This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through 2.11.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32773 | WordPress Royal Elementor Kit theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.116 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32773</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Kit.This issue affects Royal Elementor Kit: from n/a through 1.0.116.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4113 | Tenda TX9 SetSysTimeCfg sub_42D4DC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4113</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This vulnerability affects the function sub_42D4DC of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261856. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4114 | Tenda TX9 PowerSaveSet sub_42C014 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4114</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This issue affects the function sub_42C014 of the file /goform/PowerSaveSet. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261857 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32793 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32793</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro: from n/a through 2.12.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32794 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32794</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro: from n/a through 2.12.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32795 | WordPress WPCal.io  &amp;lt;= 0.9.5.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32795</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Revmakx WPCal.Io – Easy Meeting Scheduler.This issue affects WPCal.Io – Easy Meeting Scheduler: from n/a through 0.9.5.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32806 | WordPress Headline Analyzer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32806</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CoSchedule Headline Analyzer.This issue affects Headline Analyzer: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32872 | Umbraco Workflow&amp;#x27;s Backoffice users can execute arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32872</link><description>Umbraco workflow provides workflows for the Umbraco content management system. Prior to versions 10.3.9, 12.2.6, and 13.0.6, an Umbraco Backoffice user can modify requests to a particular API endpoint to include SQL, which will be executed by the server. Umbraco Workflow versions 10.3.9, 12.2.6, 13.0.6, as well as Umbraco Plumber version 10.1.2, contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32947 | WordPress WP ADA Compliance Check Basic plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32947</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AlumniOnline Web Services LLC WP ADA Compliance Check Basic.This issue affects WP ADA Compliance Check Basic: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32958 | WordPress Slash Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32958</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Giorgos Sarigiannidis Slash Admin allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Slash Admin: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23989 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9.2 - Content Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25785 | WordPress WP Post Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Vote Manipulation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25785</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shoaib Saleem WP Post Rating allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects WP Post Rating: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4112 | Tenda TX9 SetVirtualServerCfg sub_42CB94 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4112</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This affects the function sub_42CB94 of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261855. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4111 | Tenda TX9 SetLEDCfg sub_42BD7C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4111</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_42BD7C of the file /goform/SetLEDCfg. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261854 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28825 | Brute-force protection ineffective for some login methods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28825</link><description>Improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts on some authentication methods in Checkmk before 2.3.0b5 (beta), 2.2.0p26, 2.1.0p43, and in Checkmk 2.0.0 (EOL) facilitates password brute-forcing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23985 | WordPress Quiz Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.9.4 - Content Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23985</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quiz Maker team Quiz Maker.This issue affects Quiz Maker: from n/a through 6.3.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23976 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9.2 - Arbitrary Price Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23976</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45852 | WordPress WP-FormAssembly plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Auth. Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45852</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in FormAssembly / Drew Buschhorn WP-FormAssembly allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WP-FormAssembly: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32954 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32954</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters.This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32772 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.9 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32772</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32785 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32785</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32789 | WordPress Seers plugin &amp;lt;= 8.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32789</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Seers allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Seers: from n/a through 8.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32702 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Repute info systems ARForms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32707 | WordPress Image Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.125 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32707</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Image Slider Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Image Slider Widget: from n/a through 1.1.125.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32711 | WordPress myCred plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32711</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCred allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32808 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.9 - Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32808</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32823 | WordPress Rate My Post plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32823</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in FeedbackWP Rate my Post – WP Rating System.This issue affects Rate my Post – WP Rating System: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32721 | WordPress Jeg Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32721</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegtheme Jeg Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jeg Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32722 | WordPress Coupon &amp;amp; Discount Code Reveal Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32722</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coupon &amp; Discount Code Reveal Button allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Coupon &amp; Discount Code Reveal Button: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32723 | WordPress Advanced Floating Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32723</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Code Tides Advanced Floating Content allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Floating Content: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32791 | WordPress Premium Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32791</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32801 | WordPress Widget Post Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32801</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ShapedPlugin Widget Post Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Widget Post Slider: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32815 | WordPress All-in-one Like Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32815</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Peters All-in-one Like Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects All-in-one Like Widget: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32833 | WordPress List Custom Taxonomy Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32833</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nick Halsey List Custom Taxonomy Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects List Custom Taxonomy Widget: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32834 | WordPress WooCommerce Shipping Label plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebToffee WooCommerce Shipping Label allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Shipping Label: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32950 | WordPress WP Media Category Management plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DeBAAT WP Media Category Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Media Category Management: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32952 | WordPress Max Addons Pro for Bricks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BloomPixel Max Addons Pro for Bricks allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Max Addons Pro for Bricks: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32956 | WordPress RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32956</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rometheme RomethemeKit For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RomethemeKit For Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32706 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32706</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Repute info systems ARForms.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28976 | Dell Repository Manager, versions prior to 3.4.5, contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in API module. A local attacker with low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28976</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, versions prior to 3.4.5, contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in API module. A local attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized write access to the files stored on the server filesystem with the privileges of the running web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28977 | Dell Repository Manager, versions 3.4.2 through 3.4.4,contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in logger module. A local attacker with low pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28977</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, versions 3.4.2 through 3.4.4,contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in logger module. A local attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem with the privileges of the running web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32709 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32709</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Plechev Andrey WP-Recall.This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32710 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32710</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Plechev Andrey WP-Recall.This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32716 | WordPress StreamWeasels Twitch Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - API Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32716</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in StreamWeasels StreamWeasels Twitch Integration.This issue affects StreamWeasels Twitch Integration: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32726 | WordPress Frontend Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure on PII vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32726</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in vinoth06. Frontend Dashboard.This issue affects Frontend Dashboard: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28963 | Telemetry Dashboard v1.0.0.7 for Dell ThinOS 2402 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated user with lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28963</link><description>Telemetry Dashboard v1.0.0.7 for Dell ThinOS 2402 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated user with local access to the device could exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive proxy settings information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32780 | WordPress VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Invoices vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32780</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in E4J s.R.L. VikRentCar.This issue affects VikRentCar: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32781 | WordPress Email Customizer for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32781</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in ThemeHigh Email Customizer for WooCommerce.This issue affects Email Customizer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32782 | WordPress HT Mega plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32782</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HasThemes HT Mega.This issue affects HT Mega: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32788 | WordPress FG Joomla to Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.20.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32788</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Frédéric GILLES FG Joomla to WordPress.This issue affects FG Joomla to WordPress: from n/a through 4.20.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32796 | WordPress WP Fusion Lite  &amp;lt;= 3.42.10 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32796</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Very Good Plugins WP Fusion Lite.This issue affects WP Fusion Lite: from n/a through 3.42.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32816 | WordPress Combo Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.78 - Sensitive Data Exposure via API vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32816</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid.This issue affects Post Grid: from n/a through 2.2.78.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32825 | WordPress Simply Static plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32825</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Patrick Posner Simply Static.This issue affects Simply Static: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32953 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32953</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Newsletters.This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32817 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32817</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Import and export users and customers.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.26.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32835 | WordPress Export and Import Users and Customers plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32835</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WebToffee Import Export WordPress Users.This issue affects Import Export WordPress Users: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32718 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32718</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor.This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32836 | WordPress WP-Lister Lite for eBay plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.11 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32836</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WP Lab WP-Lister Lite for eBay.This issue affects WP-Lister Lite for eBay: from n/a through 3.5.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32775 | WordPress Embed Google Photos album plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32775</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Pavex Embed Google Photos album.This issue affects Embed Google Photos album: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32803 | WordPress SuperFaktura WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.40.3 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32803</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in 2day.Sk, Webikon SuperFaktura WooCommerce.This issue affects SuperFaktura WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.40.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32812 | WordPress Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.11 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32812</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Podlove Podlove Podcast Publisher.This issue affects Podlove Podcast Publisher: from n/a through 4.0.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32819 | WordPress Culqi plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.14 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32819</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Culqi.This issue affects Culqi: from n/a through 3.0.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32948 | WordPress ARMember – Membership Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.28 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32948</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Repute Infosystems ARMember.This issue affects ARMember: from n/a through 4.0.28.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32955 | WordPress FV Flowplayer Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.43.7212 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32955</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Foliovision FV Flowplayer Video Player.This issue affects FV Flowplayer Video Player: from n/a through 7.5.43.7212.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32951 | WordPress Max Addons Pro for Bricks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Reset vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32951</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BloomPixel Max Addons Pro for Bricks.This issue affects Max Addons Pro for Bricks: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31406 | Active debug code vulnerability exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31406</link><description>Active debug code vulnerability exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the device may perform unauthorized operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32051 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32051</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the device may obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33531 | cdbattags lua-resty-jwt 0.2.3 allows attackers to bypass all JWT-parsing signature checks by crafting a JWT with an enc header with the valu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33531</link><description>cdbattags lua-resty-jwt 0.2.3 allows attackers to bypass all JWT-parsing signature checks by crafting a JWT with an enc header with the value A256GCM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7253 | Import WP &amp;lt; 2.13.1 - Admin+ Server-side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7253</link><description>The Import WP  WordPress plugin before 2.13.1 does not prevent users with the administrator role from pinging conducting SSRF attacks, which may be a problem in multisite configurations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1743 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 29.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1743</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 29.8 does not sanitise and escape various parameters before outputting them back in pages and attributes, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1756 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 29.8 - Subscriber+ Email Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1756</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 29.8 does not have authorisation and CSRF in an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber, to call it and retrieve the list of customer email addresses along with their id, first name and last name</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2402 | Better Comments &amp;lt; 1.5.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2402</link><description>The Better Comments WordPress plugin before 1.5.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2404 | Better Comments &amp;lt; 1.5.6 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2404</link><description>The Better Comments WordPress plugin before 1.5.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow low privilege users such as Subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2972 | Floating Chat Widget &amp;lt; 3.1.9 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2972</link><description>The Floating Chat Widget: Contact Chat Icons, WhatsApp, Telegram Chat, Line Messenger, WeChat, Email, SMS, Call Button  WordPress plugin before 3.1.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3261 | Strong Testimonials &amp;lt; 3.1.12 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3261</link><description>The Strong Testimonials WordPress plugin before 3.1.12 does not validate and escape some of its Testimonial fields before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks. The attack requires a specific view to be performed</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28613 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PHP Task Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28613</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PHP Task Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the task_id parameter of the task-details.php, and edit-task.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 03:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4093 | SourceCodester Simple Subscription Website view_application.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4093</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Subscription Website 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_application.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 01:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4074 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website prodInfo.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4074</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file prodInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument prodId leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261800.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 23:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4075 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4075</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtAddress leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261801 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 23:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4072 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4072</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument txtSearch leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261798 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4073 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website prodList.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4073</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file prodList.php. The manipulation of the argument prodType leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261799.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30886 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the remotelink function of HadSky v7.6.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30886</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the remotelink function of HadSky v7.6.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the url parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4070 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website prodList.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4070</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file prodList.php. The manipulation of the argument prodType leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261796.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4071 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website prodInfo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4071</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file prodInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument prodId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261797 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31616 | An issue discovered in RG-RSR10-01G-T(W)-S and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S routers with firmware version RSR10-01G-T-S_RSR_3.0(1)B9P2, Release(0715...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31616</link><description>An issue discovered in RG-RSR10-01G-T(W)-S and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S routers with firmware version RSR10-01G-T-S_RSR_3.0(1)B9P2, Release(07150910) allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the common_quick_config.lua file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4069 | Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4069</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument txtSearch leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261795.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32866 | Conform contains Prototype Pollution Vulnerability in `parseWith...` function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32866</link><description>Conform, a type-safe form validation library, allows the parsing of nested objects in the form of `object.property`. Due to an improper implementation of this feature in versions prior to 1.1.1, an attacker can exploit the feature to trigger prototype pollution by passing a crafted input to `parseWith...` functions. Applications that use conform for server-side validation of form data or URL parameters are affected by this vulnerability. Version 1.1.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4066 | Tenda AC8 AdvSetMacMtuWan fromAdvSetMacMtuWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4066</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09. Affected is the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan of the file /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan. The manipulation of the argument wanMTU/wanSpeed/cloneType/mac/serviceName/serverName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261792. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32875 | Hugo doesn&amp;#x27;t escape markdown title in internal render hooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32875</link><description>Hugo is a static site generator. Starting in version 0.123.0 and prior to version 0.125.3, title arguments in Markdown for links and images not escaped in internal render hooks. Hugo users who are impacted are those who have these hooks enabled and do not trust their Markdown content files. The issue is patched in v0.125.3. As a workaround, replace the templates with user defined templates or disable the internal templates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32662 | FreeRDP rdp_redirection_read_base64_wchar out of bound read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32662</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. This occurs when `WCHAR` string is read with twice the size it has and converted to `UTF-8`, `base64` decoded. The string is only used to compare against the redirection server certificate. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32869 | Hono vulnerable to Restricted Directory Traversal in serveStatic with deno</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32869</link><description>Hono is a Web application framework that provides support for any JavaScript runtime. Prior to version 4.2.7, when using serveStatic with deno, it is possible to traverse the directory where `main.ts` is located. This can result in retrieval of unexpected files. Version 4.2.7 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32660 | FreeRDP zgfx_decompress out of memory vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32660</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to version 3.5.1, a malicious server can crash the FreeRDP client by sending invalid huge allocation size. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32661 | FreeRDP rdp_write_logon_info_v1 NULL access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32661</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to a possible `NULL` access and crash. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4064 | Tenda AC8 execCommand R7WebsSecurityHandler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function R7WebsSecurityHandler of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261790 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4065 | Tenda AC8 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.09. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261791. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32659 | freerdp_image_copy out of bound read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32659</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read if `((nWidth == 0) and (nHeight == 0))`. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4062 | Hualai Xiaofang iSC5 certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4062</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hualai Xiaofang iSC5 3.2.2_112 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to improper certificate validation. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4063 | EZVIZ CS-C6-21WFR-8 Davinci Application certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4063</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EZVIZ CS-C6-21WFR-8 5.2.7 Build 170628. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Davinci Application. The manipulation leads to improper certificate validation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The identifier VDB-261789 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32658 | FreeRDP ExtractRunLengthRegular* out of bound read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32658</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients prior to version 3.5.1 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Version 3.5.1 contains a patch for the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32482 | Tillitis TKey Signer possible RAM disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32482</link><description>The Tillitis TKey signer device application is an ed25519 signing tool. A vulnerability has been found that makes it possible to disclose portions of the TKey’s data in RAM over the USB interface. To exploit the vulnerability an attacker needs to use a custom client application and to touch the TKey. No secret is disclosed. All client applications integrating tkey-device-signer should upgrade to version 1.0.0 to receive a fix. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31208 | Synapse&amp;#x27;s V2 state resolution weakness allows DoS from remote room members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31208</link><description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver. A remote Matrix user with malicious intent, sharing a room with Synapse instances before 1.105.1, can dispatch specially crafted events to exploit a weakness in the V2 state resolution algorithm. This can induce high CPU consumption and accumulate excessive data in the database of such instances, resulting in a denial of service. Servers in private federations, or those that do not federate, are not affected. Server administrators should upgrade to 1.105.1 or later. Some workarounds are available. One can ban the malicious users or ACL block servers from the rooms and/or leave the room and purge the room using the admin API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21972 | An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21972</link><description>An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed shader to potentially achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21979 | An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21979</link><description>An out of bounds write vulnerability in the AMD Radeon™ user mode driver for DirectX® 11 could allow an attacker with access to a malformed shader to potentially achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32258 | The network server of fceux 2.7.0 has a path traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to overwrite any files on the server without authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32258</link><description>The network server of fceux 2.7.0 has a path traversal vulnerability, allowing attackers to overwrite any files on the server without authentication by fake ROM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31804 | An unquoted service path vulnerability in Terratec DMX_6Fire USB v.1.23.0.02 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Program....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31804</link><description>An unquoted service path vulnerability in Terratec DMX_6Fire USB v.1.23.0.02 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Program.exe component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33211 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter in ip/g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33211</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PPPOEPassword parameter in ip/goform/QuickIndex.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33212 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter in ip/gofor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33212</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the funcpara1 parameter in ip/goform/setcfm.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33213 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/go...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33213</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/RouteStatic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33214 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter in ip/goform/R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33214</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the entrys parameter in ip/goform/RouteStatic.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33215 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/go...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33215</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the mitInterface parameter in ip/goform/addressNat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33217 | Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter in ip/goform/add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33217</link><description>Tenda FH1206 V1.2.0.8(8155)_EN was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the page parameter in ip/goform/addressNat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28130 | An incorrect type conversion vulnerability exists in the DVPSSoftcopyVOI_PList::createFromImage functionality of OFFIS DCMTK 3.6.8. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28130</link><description>An incorrect type conversion vulnerability exists in the DVPSSoftcopyVOI_PList::createFromImage functionality of OFFIS DCMTK 3.6.8. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:57:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32679 | WordPress Shared Files plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32679</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shared Files PRO Shared Files.This issue affects Shared Files: from n/a through 1.7.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2477 | The wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Alternative Text' field of an uploaded image in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2477</link><description>The wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Alternative Text' field of an uploaded image in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28627 | An issue in Flipsnack v.18/03/2024 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reader.gz.js file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28627</link><description>An issue in Flipsnack v.18/03/2024 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the reader.gz.js file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26922 | drm/amdgpu: validate the parameters of bo mapping operations more clearly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26922</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: validate the parameters of bo mapping operations more clearly

Verify the parameters of
amdgpu_vm_bo_(map/replace_map/clearing_mappings) in one common place.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30800 | PX4 Autopilot v.1.14 allows an attacker to fly the drone into no-fly zones by breaching the geofence using flaws in the function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30800</link><description>PX4 Autopilot v.1.14 allows an attacker to fly the drone into no-fly zones by breaching the geofence using flaws in the function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47731 | IBM QRadar Suite Software cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47731</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite Software 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.19.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  272203.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3911 | Welotec: Clickjacking Vulnerability in WebUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3911</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can deceive users into performing unintended actions due to improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3491 | The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "How To" and "F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3491</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "How To" and "FAQ" Blocks in all versions up to, and including, 1.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3665 | The Rank Math SEO with AI SEO Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's HowTo and FAQ widgets...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3665</link><description>The Rank Math SEO with AI SEO Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's HowTo and FAQ widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.216 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3732 | The GeoDirectory – WordPress Business Directory Plugin, or Classified Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3732</link><description>The GeoDirectory – WordPress Business Directory Plugin, or Classified Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gd_single_tabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.48 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3185 | Rapid7 Insight Agent Sensitive Key Exposed To Local Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3185</link><description>A key used in logging.json does not follow the least privilege principle by default and is exposed to local users in the Rapid7 Platform.  This allows an attacker with local access to a machine with the logging.json file to use that key to authenticate to the platform with high privileges.  This was fixed in the Rapid7 platform starting 3 April 2024 via the introduction of a restricted role and the removal of automatic API key generation on installation of an agent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0900 | The Elespare – Build Your Blog, News &amp; Magazine Websites with Expert-Designed Template Kits. One Click Import: No Coding Skills Required! pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0900</link><description>The Elespare – Build Your Blog, News &amp; Magazine Websites with Expert-Designed Template Kits. One Click Import: No Coding Skills Required! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post creation due to a missing capability check on the elespare_create_post() function hooked via AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3664 | The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3664</link><description>The Quick Featured Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the set_thumbnail and delete_thumbnail functions in all versions up to, and including, 13.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to delete thumbnails and add thumbnails to posts they did not author.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48184 | QuickJS before 7414e5f has a quickjs.h JS_FreeValueRT use-after-free because of incorrect garbage collection of async functions with closure...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48184</link><description>QuickJS before 7414e5f has a quickjs.h JS_FreeValueRT use-after-free because of incorrect garbage collection of async functions with closures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48183 | QuickJS before c4cdd61 has a build_for_in_iterator NULL pointer dereference because of an erroneous lexical scope of "this" with eval.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48183</link><description>QuickJS before c4cdd61 has a build_for_in_iterator NULL pointer dereference because of an erroneous lexical scope of "this" with eval.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4031 | MEVO WEBCAM APP Windows Unquoted Service Path Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4031</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in Logitech MEVO WEBCAM APP on Windows allows Local Execution of Code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6833 | Information Exposure Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6833</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Administrator allows local users to gain sensitive information.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Administrator: before 11.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2493 | Session Hijacking Vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2493</link><description>Session Hijacking vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.1-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2798 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget container...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2798</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget containers in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.971 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2799 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Grid &amp; Advanced Tex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2799</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Grid &amp; Advanced Text widget HTML tags in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.96 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3889 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Accordi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3889</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.971 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes like 'accordion_title_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21511 | Versions of the package mysql2 before 3.9.7 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection due to improper sanitization of the timezone paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21511</link><description>Versions of the package mysql2 before 3.9.7 are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection due to improper sanitization of the timezone parameter in the readCodeFor function by calling a native MySQL Server date/time function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28890 | Forminator prior to 1.29.0 contains an unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28890</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.29.0 contains an unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain sensitive information by accessing files on the server, alter the site that uses the plugin, and cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31077 | Forminator prior to 1.29.3 contains a SQL injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote authenticated attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31077</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.29.3 contains a SQL injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote authenticated attacker with an administrative privilege may obtain and alter any information in the database and cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31857 | Forminator prior to 1.15.4 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31857</link><description>Forminator prior to 1.15.4 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote attacker may obtain user information etc. and alter the page contents on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1241 | Watchdog Antivirus v1.6.415 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1241</link><description>Watchdog Antivirus v1.6.415 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service vulnerability by triggering the 0x80002014 IOCTL code of the wsdk-driver.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2760 | Bkav Home v7816, build 2403161130 - Kernel Memory Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2760</link><description>Bkav Home v7816, build 2403161130 is vulnerable to a Memory Information Leak vulnerability by triggering the 0x222240 IOCTL code of the BkavSDFlt.sys driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3293 | The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the rtmedia_gallery shortcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3293</link><description>The rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the rtmedia_gallery shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.18 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 02:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3177 | Bypassing mountable secrets policy imposed by the ServiceAccount admission plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3177</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where users may be able to launch containers that bypass the mountable secrets policy enforced by the ServiceAccount admission plugin when using containers, init containers, and ephemeral containers with the envFrom field populated. The policy ensures pods running with a service account may only reference secrets specified in the service account’s secrets field. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if the ServiceAccount admission plugin and the kubernetes.io/enforce-mountable-secrets annotation are used together with containers, init containers, and ephemeral containers with the envFrom field populated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 23:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32657 | Hydra has persistent XSS vulnerability serving HTML build outputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32657</link><description>Hydra is a Continuous Integration service for Nix based projects. Attackers can execute arbitrary code in the browser context of Hydra and execute authenticated HTTP requests. The abused feature allows Nix builds to specify files that Hydra serves to clients. One use of this functionality is serving NixOS `.iso` files. The issue is only with html files served by Hydra. The issue has been patched on https://hydra.nixos.org around 2024-04-21 14:30 UTC. The nixpkgs package were fixed in unstable and 23.11. Users with custom Hydra packages can apply the fix commit to their local installations. The vulnerability is only triggered when opening HTML build artifacts, so not opening them until the vulnerability is fixed works around the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32480 | LibreNMS&amp;#x27;s Time-Based Blind SQL injection leads to database extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32480</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Versions prior to 24.4.0 are vulnerable to SQL injection. The `order` parameter is obtained from `$request`. After performing a string check, the value is directly incorporated into an SQL statement and concatenated, resulting in a SQL injection vulnerability. An attacker may extract a whole database this way. Version 24.4.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32653 | Insufficient input filtering of &amp;quot;package name&amp;quot; allows command execution in the device with shell privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32653</link><description>jadx is a  Dex to Java decompiler. Prior to version 1.5.0,  the package name is not filtered before concatenation. This can be exploited to inject arbitrary code into the package name. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute commands with shell privileges. Version 1.5.0 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32656 | Ant Media Server vulnerable to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32656</link><description>Ant Media Server is live streaming engine software. A local privilege escalation vulnerability in present in versions 2.6.0 through 2.8.2 allows any unprivileged operating system user account to escalate privileges to the root user account on the system. This vulnerability arises from Ant Media Server running with Java Management Extensions (JMX) enabled and authentication disabled on localhost on port 5599/TCP. This vulnerability is nearly identical to the local privilege escalation vulnerability CVE-2023-26269 identified in Apache James. Any unprivileged operating system user can connect to the JMX service running on port 5599/TCP on localhost and leverage the MLet Bean within JMX to load a remote MBean from an attacker-controlled server. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the Java process run by Ant Media Server and execute code within the context of the `antmedia` service account on the system. Version 2.9.0 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, one may remove certain parameters from the `antmedia.service` file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32479 | LibreNMS&amp;#x27;s Improper Sanitization on Service template name leads to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32479</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Prior to version 24.4.0, there is improper sanitization on the `Service` template name, which can lead to stored Cross-site Scripting. Version 24.4.0 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32461 | LibreNMS vulnerable to time-based SQL injection that leads to database extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32461</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. A SQL injection vulnerability in POST /search/search=packages in LibreNMS prior to version 24.4.0 allows a user with global read privileges to execute SQL commands via the package parameter. With this vulnerability, an attacker can exploit a SQL injection time based vulnerability to extract all data from the database, such as administrator credentials. Version 24.4.0 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32460 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in interleaved_decompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32460</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based based clients using `/bpp:32` legacy `GDI` drawing path with a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use modern drawing paths (e.g. `/rfx` or `/gfx` options). The workaround requires server side support.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31036 | A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the read_byte function in NanoMQ v.0.21.7 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via transmis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31036</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the read_byte function in NanoMQ v.0.21.7 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via transmission of crafted hexstreams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32459 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in ncrush_decompress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32459</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients and servers that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29368 | An issue discovered in moziloCMS v2.0 allows attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and run arbitrary code by changing the file extens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29368</link><description>An issue discovered in moziloCMS v2.0 allows attackers to bypass file upload restrictions and run arbitrary code by changing the file extension after upload via crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27574 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Trainme Academy version Ichin v.1.3.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27574</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Trainme Academy version Ichin v.1.3.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the informacion, idcurso, and tit parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32394 | An issue in ruijie.com/cn RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32394</link><description>An issue in ruijie.com/cn RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 and RG-RSR10-01G-T(WA)-S RSR_3.0(1)B9P2_RSR10-01G-TW-S_07150910 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32458 | FreeRDP Out-Of-Bounds Read in planar_skip_plane_rle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32458</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, use `/gfx` or `/rfx` modes (on by default, require server side support).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32040 | FreeRDP vulnerable to integer underflow in nsc_rle_decode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32040</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 and have connections to servers using the `NSC` codec are vulnerable to integer underflow. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use the NSC codec (e.g. use `-nsc`).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32041 | FreeRDP OutOfBound Read in zgfx_decompress_segment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32041</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients that use a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to out-of-bounds read. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, deactivate `/gfx` (on by default, set `/bpp` or `/rfx` options instead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32039 | FreeRDP Integer overflow &amp;amp; OutOfBound Write in clear_decompress_residual_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32039</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. FreeRDP based clients using a version of FreeRDP prior to 3.5.0 or 2.11.6 are vulnerable to integer overflow and out-of-bounds write. Versions 3.5.0 and 2.11.6 patch the issue. As a workaround, do not use `/gfx` options (e.g. deactivate with `/bpp:32` or `/rfx` as it is on by default).</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4040 | VFS Sandbox Escape in CrushFTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4040</link><description>VFS Sandbox Escape in CrushFTP in all versions before 10.7.1 and 11.1.0 on all platforms allows remote attackers with low privileges to read files from the filesystem outside of VFS Sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32238 | H3C ER8300G2-X is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The password for the router's management system can be accessed via the management...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32238</link><description>H3C ER8300G2-X is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The password for the router's management system can be accessed via the management system page login interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32399 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in RaidenMAILD Mail Server v.4.9.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32399</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in RaidenMAILD Mail Server v.4.9.4 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /webeditor/ component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32405 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32405</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted payload to the Answer field of InlineMultiQuestion parameter on Exam function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32407 | An issue in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Page Sandbox feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32407</link><description>An issue in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Page Sandbox feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29376 | Sylius 1.12.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "Province" field in Address Book.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29376</link><description>Sylius 1.12.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the "Province" field in Address Book.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31545 | Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/?page=user/manage_user&amp;id=6.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31545</link><description>Computer Laboratory Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "id" parameter of /admin/?page=user/manage_user&amp;amp;id=6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46897 | An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. The CapsuleIFWUSmm driver does not check the return value from a me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46897</link><description>An issue was discovered in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.5. The CapsuleIFWUSmm driver does not check the return value from a method or function. This can prevent it from detecting unexpected states and conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31666 | An issue in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the edit_addon_post.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31666</link><description>An issue in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the edit_addon_post.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 18:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28436 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in D-Link DAP products DAP-2230, DAP-2310, DAP-2330, DAP-2360, DAP-2553, DAP-2590, DAP-2690, DAP-2695, DA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28436</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in D-Link DAP products DAP-2230, DAP-2310, DAP-2330, DAP-2360, DAP-2553, DAP-2590, DAP-2690, DAP-2695, DAP-3520, DAP-3662 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the reload parameter in the session_login.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38290 | Certain software builds for the BLU View 2 and Sharp Rouvo V Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38290</link><description>Certain software builds for the BLU View 2 and Sharp Rouvo V Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.evenwell.fqc (versionCode='9020801', versionName='9.0208.01' ; versionCode='9020913', versionName='9.0209.13' ; versionCode='9021203', versionName='9.0212.03') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary shell commands in its context (system user) due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.evenwell.fqc app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The vulnerability allows local apps to access sensitive functionality that is generally restricted to pre-installed apps, such as programmatically performing the following actions: granting arbitrary permissions (which can be used to obtain sensitive user data), installing arbitrary apps, video recording the screen, wiping the device (removing the user's apps and data), injecting arbitrary input events, calling emergency phone numbers, disabling apps, accessing notifications, and much more. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: BLU View 2 (BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672046950:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1663816427:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1656476696:user/release-keys, BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1647856638:user/release-keys) and Sharp Rouvo V (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_460:user/release-keys and SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys). This malicious app starts an exported activity named com.evenwell.fqc/.activity.ClickTest, crashes the com.evenwell.fqc app by sending an empty Intent (i.e., having not extras) to the com.evenwell.fqc/.FQCBroadcastReceiver receiver component, and then it sends command arbitrary shell commands to the com.evenwell.fqc/.FQCService service component which executes them with "system" privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38291 | An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to ro.boot.wifimacaddr, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38291</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to ro.boot.wifimacaddr, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z and 10L) and Motorola devices (Moto G Pure and Moto G Power) leak the Wi-Fi MAC address to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys); TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:10/QKQ1.200329.002/3CJ0:user/release-keys and TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Pure (motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-2/74844:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-7/5cde8:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-10/d67faa:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-13/b4a29:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RH32.20-42-10/1c2540:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-13-2-1/6368dd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_a/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-50-2/20fec:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-138/103bd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-138-2/e5502:user/release-keys, and motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-10-14-2/5e0b0:user/release-keys); and Motorola Moto G Power (motorola/tonga_g/tonga:11/RRQ31.Q3-68-16-2/e5877:user/release-keys and motorola/tonga_g/tonga:12/S3RQS32.20-42-10-6/f876d3:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "ro.boot.wifimacaddr" system property to indirectly obtain the Wi-Fi MAC address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38292 | Certain software builds for the TCL 20XE Android device contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tct.gcs.hiddenmen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38292</link><description>Certain software builds for the TCL 20XE Android device contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy (versionCode='2', versionName='v11.0.1.0.0201.0') that allows local third-party apps to programmatically perform a factory reset due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable build are as follows: TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB7I-0:user/release-keys and TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB83-0:user/release-keys. This malicious app sends a broadcast intent to the exported com.tct.gcs.hiddenmenuproxy/.rtn.FactoryResetReceiver receiver component, which initiates a programmatic factory reset.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38293 | Certain software builds for the Nokia C200 and Nokia C100 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38293</link><description>Certain software builds for the Nokia C200 and Nokia C100 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app with a package name of com.tracfone.tfstatus (versionCode='31', versionName='12') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary AT commands in its context (radio user) via AT command injection due to inadequate access control and inadequate input filtering. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.tracfone.tfstatus app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: Nokia C200 (Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys and Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_040:user/release-keys) and Nokia C100 (Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_270:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_190:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_130:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_110:user/release-keys, Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys, and Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_050:user/release-keys). This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to the receiver component named com.tracfone.tfstatus/.TFStatus. This broadcast receiver extracts a string from the Intent and uses it as an extra when it starts the com.tracfone.tfstatus/.TFStatusActivity activity component which uses the externally controlled string as an input to execute an AT command. There are two different injection techniques to successfully inject arbitrary AT commands to execute.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38294 | Certain software builds for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo Android device contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.transsi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38294</link><description>Certain software builds for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo Android device contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.transsion.autotest.factory (versionCode='7', versionName='1.8.0(220310_1027)') that allows local third-party apps to execute arbitrary shell commands in its context (system user) due to inadequate access control. No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerability in the com.transsion.autotest.factory app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The vulnerability allows local apps to access sensitive functionality that is generally restricted to pre-installed apps, such as programmatically performing the following actions: granting arbitrary permissions (which can be used to obtain sensitive user data), installing arbitrary apps, video recording the screen, wiping the device (removing the user's apps and data), injecting arbitrary input events, calling emergency phone numbers, disabling apps, accessing notifications, and much more. The confirmed vulnerable software build fingerprints for the Itel Vision 3 Turbo device are as follows: Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V92-20230105:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V86-20221118:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V78-20221101:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V64-20220803:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V61-20220721:user/release-keys, Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V58-20220712:user/release-keys, and Itel/F6321/itel-S661LP:11/RP1A.201005.001/GL-V051-20220613:user/release-keys. This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to the receiver component named com.transsion.autotest.factory/.broadcast.CommandReceiver with the path to a shell script that it creates in its scoped storage directory. Then the com.transsion.autotest.factory app will execute the shell script with "system" privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38295 | Certain software builds for the TCL 30Z and TCL 10 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app that relies on a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38295</link><description>Certain software builds for the TCL 30Z and TCL 10 Android devices contain a vulnerable, pre-installed app that relies on a missing permission that provides no protection at runtime. The missing permission is required as an access permission by components in various pre-installed apps. On the TCL 30Z device, the vulnerable app has a package name of com.tcl.screenrecorder (versionCode='1221092802', versionName='v5.2120.02.12008.1.T' ; versionCode='1221092805', versionName='v5.2120.02.12008.2.T'). On the TCL 10L device, the vulnerable app has a package name of com.tcl.sos (versionCode='2020102827', versionName='v3.2014.12.1012.B'). When a third-party app declares and requests the missing permission, it can interact with certain service components in the aforementioned apps (that execute with "system" privileges) to perform arbitrary files reads/writes in its context. An app exploiting this vulnerability only needs to declare and request the single missing permission and no user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys) and TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys). This malicious app declares the missing permission named com.tct.smart.switchphone.permission.SWITCH_DATA as a normal permission, requests the missing permission, and uses it to interact with the com.tct.smart.switchdata.DataService service component that is declared in vulnerable apps that execute with "system" privileges to perform arbitrary file reads/writes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38296 | Various software builds for the following TCL 30Z and TCL A3X devices leak the ICCID to a system property that can be accessed by any local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38296</link><description>Various software builds for the following TCL 30Z and TCL A3X devices leak the ICCID to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys) and TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.tctPowerIccid" system property to indirectly obtain the ICCID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38297 | An issue was discovered in a third-party com.factory.mmigroup component, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Certain soft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38297</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party com.factory.mmigroup component, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Certain software builds for various Android devices contain a vulnerable pre-installed app with a package name of com.factory.mmigroup (versionCode='3', versionName='2.1) that allows local third-party apps to perform various actions, due to inadequate access control, in its context (system user), but the functionalities exposed depend on the specific device. The following capabilities are exposed to zero-permission, third-party apps on the following devices: arbitrary AT command execution via AT command injection (T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, and Boost Mobile Celero 5G); programmatic factory reset (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, Realme C25Y, and Lenovo Tab M8 HD), leaking IMEI (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y); leaking serial number (Samsung Galaxy A03s, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, Realme C25Y, and Lenovo Tab M8 HD); powering off the device (Realme C25Y, Samsung Galaxy A03S, and T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G); and programmatically enabling/disabling airplane mode (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y); and enabling Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, and GPS (Samsung Galaxy A03S, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G, Boost Mobile Celero, and Realme C25Y). No permissions or special privileges are necessary to exploit the vulnerabilities in the com.factory.mmigroup app. No user interaction is required beyond installing and running a third-party app. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: Boost Mobile Celero 5G (Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V067:user/release-keys, Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V064:user/release-keys, Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V061:user/release-keys, and Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V052:user/release-keys); Samsung Galaxy A03S (samsung/a03sutfn/a03su:13/TP1A.220624.014/S134DLUDU6CWB6:user/release-keys and samsung/a03sutfn/a03su:12/SP1A.210812.016/S134DLUDS5BWA1:user/release-keys); Lenovo Tab M8 HD (Lenovo/LenovoTB-8505F/8505F:10/QP1A.190711.020/S300637_220706_BMP:user/release-keys and Lenovo/LenovoTB-8505F/8505F:10/QP1A.190711.020/S300448_220114_BMP:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G (T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V070:user/release-keys and T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V066:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G (T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V077:user/release-keys and T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V060:user/release-keys); and Realme C25Y (realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1675861640000:user/release-keys, realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1664031768000:user/release-keys, realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1652814687000:user/release-keys, and realme/RMX3269/RED8F6:11/RP1A.201005.001/1635785712000:user/release-keys). This malicious app sends a broadcast Intent to com.factory.mmigroup/.MMIGroupReceiver. This causes the com.factory.mmigroup app to dynamically register for various action strings. The malicious app can then send these strings, allowing it to perform various behaviors that the com.factory.mmigroup app exposes. The actual behaviors exposed by the com.factory.mmigroup app depend on device model and chipset. The com.factory.mmigroup app executes as the "system" user, allowing it to interact with the baseband processor and perform various other sensitive actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38298 | Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z, A3X, 20XE, 10L) leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38298</link><description>Various software builds for the following TCL devices (30Z, A3X, 20XE, 10L) leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: TCL 30Z (TCL/4188R/Jetta_ATT:12/SP1A.210812.016/LV8E:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU5P:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU61:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU66:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU68:user/release-keys, TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6P:user/release-keys, and TCL/T602DL/Jetta_TF:12/SP1A.210812.016/vU6X:user/release-keys); TCL A3X (TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAAZ:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB3:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vAB7:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABA:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABM:user/release-keys, TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABP:user/release-keys, and TCL/A600DL/Delhi_TF:11/RKQ1.201202.002/vABS:user/release-keys); TCL 20XE (TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB7I-0:user/release-keys and TCL/5087Z_BO/Doha_TMO:11/RP1A.200720.011/PB83-0:user/release-keys); and TCL 10L (TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:10/QKQ1.200329.002/3CJ0:user/release-keys and TCL/T770B/T1_LITE:11/RKQ1.210107.001/8BIC:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "gsm.device.imei0" system property to indirectly obtain the device IMEI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38299 | Various software builds for the AT&amp;T Calypso, Nokia C100, Nokia C200, and BLU View 3 devices leak the device IMEI to a system property that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38299</link><description>Various software builds for the AT&amp;amp;T Calypso, Nokia C100, Nokia C200, and BLU View 3 devices leak the device IMEI to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: AT&amp;amp;T Calypso (ATT/U318AA/U318AA:10/QP1A.190711.020/1632369780:user/release-keys); Nokia C100 (Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_190:user/release-keys and Nokia/DrakeLite_02US/DKT:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_270:user/release-keys); Nokia C200 (Nokia/Drake_02US/DRK:12/SP1A.210812.016/02US_1_080:user/release-keys); and BLU View 3 (BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1628014629:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1632535579:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1637325978:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1650073052:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1657087912:user/release-keys, BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1666316280:user/release-keys, and BLU/B140DL/B140DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672371162:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.imei1" system property to indirectly obtain the device IMEI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38300 | A certain software build for the Orbic Maui device (Orbic/RC545L/RC545L:10/ORB545L_V1.4.2_BVZPP/230106:user/release-keys) leaks the IMEI and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38300</link><description>A certain software build for the Orbic Maui device (Orbic/RC545L/RC545L:10/ORB545L_V1.4.2_BVZPP/230106:user/release-keys) leaks the IMEI and the ICCID to system properties that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in this instance they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. This malicious app reads from the "persist.sys.verizon_test_plan_imei" system property to indirectly obtain the IMEI and reads the "persist.sys.verizon_test_plan_iccid" system property to obtain the ICCID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38301 | An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to vendor.gsm.serial, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Vari...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38301</link><description>An issue was discovered in a third-party component related to vendor.gsm.serial, shipped on devices from multiple device manufacturers. Various software builds for the BLU View 2, Boost Mobile Celero 5G, Sharp Rouvo V, Motorola Moto G Pure, Motorola Moto G Power, T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G, and T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G devices leak the device serial number to a system property that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in these instances they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. The software build fingerprints for each confirmed vulnerable device are as follows: BLU View 2 (BLU/B131DL/B130DL:11/RP1A.200720.011/1672046950:user/release-keys); Boost Mobile Celero 5G (Celero5G/Jupiter/Jupiter:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98119AA1_V067:user/release-keys); Sharp Rouvo V (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Pure (motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-2/74844:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-7/5cde8:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-10/d67faa:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-110-13/b4a29:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RH32.20-42-10/1c2540:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_trac/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-13-2-1/6368dd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_a/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-50-2/20fec:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRH31.Q3-46-138/103bd:user/release-keys, motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:11/RRHS31.Q3-46-138-2/e5502:user/release-keys, and motorola/ellis_vzw/ellis:12/S3RHS32.20-42-10-14-2/5e0b0:user/release-keys); Motorola Moto G Power (motorola/tonga_g/tonga:11/RRQ31.Q3-68-16-2/e5877:user/release-keys and motorola/tonga_g/tonga:12/S3RQS32.20-42-10-6/f876d3:user/release-keys); T-Mobile Revvl 6 Pro 5G (T-Mobile/Augusta/Augusta:12/SP1A.210812.016/SW_S98121AA1_V070:user/release-keys); and T-Mobile Revvl V+ 5G (T-Mobile/Sprout/Sprout:11/RP1A.200720.011/SW_S98115AA1_V077:user/release-keys). This malicious app reads from the "vendor.gsm.serial" system property to indirectly obtain the device serial number.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38302 | A certain software build for the Sharp Rouvo V device (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys) leak...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38302</link><description>A certain software build for the Sharp Rouvo V device (SHARP/VZW_STTM21VAPP/STTM21VAPP:12/SP1A.210812.016/1KN0_0_530:user/release-keys) leaks the Wi-Fi MAC address and the Bluetooth MAC address to system properties that can be accessed by any local app on the device without any permissions or special privileges. Google restricted third-party apps from directly obtaining non-resettable device identifiers in Android 10 and higher, but in this instance they are leaked by a high-privilege process and can be obtained indirectly. This malicious app reads from the "ro.boot.wifi_mac" system property to indirectly obtain the Wi-Fi MAC address and reads the "ro.boot.bt_mac" system property to obtain the Bluetooth MAC address.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-35503 | Improper verification of a user input in Open Source MANO v7-v12 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code within the LCM m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35503</link><description>Improper verification of a user input in Open Source MANO v7-v12 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code within the LCM module container via a Virtual Network Function (VNF) descriptor. An attacker may be able execute code to change the normal execution of the OSM components, retrieve confidential information, or gain access other parts of a Telco Operator infrastructure other than OSM itself.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28699 | A buffer overflow vulnerability in pdf2json v0.70 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the GString::copy() and ImgOutputDev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28699</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in pdf2json v0.70 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the GString::copy() and ImgOutputDev::ImgOutputDev function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34560 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34560</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the History parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34561 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34561</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the video description parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34562 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34562</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in PHPFox v4.8.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the status box.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27347 | Apache HugeGraph-Hubble: SSRF in Hubble connection page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27347</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Hubble.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Hubble: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27348 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: Command execution in gremlin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27348</link><description>RCE-Remote Command Execution vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0 in Java8 &amp; Java11

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0 with Java11 &amp; enable the Auth system, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27349 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: Bypass whitelist in Auth mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27349</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32368 | Insecure Permission vulnerability in Agasta Sanketlife 2.0 Pocket 12-Lead ECG Monitor FW Version 3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32368</link><description>Insecure Permission vulnerability in Agasta Sanketlife 2.0 Pocket 12-Lead ECG Monitor FW Version 3.0 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3645 | The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Counter widget in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3645</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Counter widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'title_html_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22813 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to overwrite the hardcoded IP address in the device memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22813</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to overwrite the hardcoded IP address in the device memory, disrupting network connectivity between the router and the controller.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22815 | An issue in the communication protocol of Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22815</link><description>An issue in the communication protocol of Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via crafted commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29661 | A File Upload vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29661</link><description>A File Upload vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22807 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to erase a critical sector of the flash memory, causing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22807</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to erase a critical sector of the flash memory, causing the machine to lose network connectivity and suffer from firmware corruption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22808 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22808</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the communication between the PathPilot controller and the CNC router via overwriting the card's name in the device memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22809 | Incorrect access control in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to access the G code's shared folder and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22809</link><description>Incorrect access control in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to access the G code's shared folder and view sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22811 | An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22811</link><description>An issue in Tormach xsTECH CNC Router, PathPilot Controller v2.9.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by disrupting the communication between the PathPilot controller and the CNC router via overwriting the Hostmot2 configuration cookie in the device memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4026 | Cross-Site Scripting in the Holded application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4026</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Holded application. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to store a JavaScript payload within all editable parameters within the 'General' and 'Team ID' functionalities, which could result in a session takeover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22856 | A SQL injection vulnerability via the Save Favorite Search function in Axefinance Axe Credit Portal &gt;= v.3.0 allows authenticated attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22856</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability via the Save Favorite Search function in Axefinance Axe Credit Portal &gt;= v.3.0 allows authenticated attackers to execute unintended queries and disclose sensitive information from DB tables via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28717 | An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28717</link><description>An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32681 | WordPress Prime Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32681</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 3.13.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32682 | WordPress Prime Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32682</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 3.13.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32684 | WordPress WP Ultimate Review plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - Broken Access Control on Review vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32684</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Wp Ultimate Review.This issue affects Wp Ultimate Review: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32687 | WordPress WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32687</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPClever WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce.This issue affects WPC Frequently Bought Together for WooCommerce: from n/a through 7.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32688 | WordPress MyRewards plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Long Watch Studio MyRewards.This issue affects MyRewards: from n/a through 5.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32691 | WordPress Active Products Tables for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32691</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in realmag777 Active Products Tables for WooCommerce.This issue affects Active Products Tables for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.6.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32693 | WordPress Automatic plugin &amp;lt; 3.93.0 - Multiple Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32693</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ValvePress Automatic.This issue affects Automatic: from n/a before 3.93.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32697 | WordPress HelloAsso plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HelloAsso allows Stored XSS.This issue affects HelloAsso: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32698 | WordPress Happy Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32698</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leevio Happy Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Happy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.10.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32694 | WordPress 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.62 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative interactive media 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 3.62.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32695 | WordPress Language Switcher for Transposh plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Marco Gasi Language Switcher for Transposh allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Language Switcher for Transposh: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32696 | WordPress AI Infographic Maker OpenAI plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in QuantumCloud Infographic Maker – iList allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Infographic Maker – iList: from n/a through 4.6.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32690 | WordPress RSS Feed Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32690</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood RSS Feed Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RSS Feed Widget: from n/a through 2.9.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7252 | Tickera &amp;lt; 3.5.2.5 - Ticket leakage through IDOR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7252</link><description>The Tickera  WordPress plugin before 3.5.2.5 does not prevent users from leaking other users' tickets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25101 | l2c2technologies Koha opac-MARCdetail.pl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25101</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in l2c2technologies Koha up to 20180108. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/koha/opac-MARCdetail.pl. The manipulation of the argument biblionumber with the input 2"&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier of the patch is 950fc8e101886821879066b33e389a47fb0a9782. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-261677 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28722 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Innovaphone myPBX v.14r1, v.13r3, v.12r2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the qu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28722</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Innovaphone myPBX v.14r1, v.13r3, v.12r2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the query parameter to the /CMD0/xml_modes.xml endpoint</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32418 | An issue in flusity CMS v2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_addon.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32418</link><description>An issue in flusity CMS v2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_addon.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30799 | An issue in PX4 Autopilot v1.14 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via the Breach R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30799</link><description>An issue in PX4 Autopilot v1.14 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via the Breach Return Point function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>