<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:39:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2022-4969 | bwoodsend rockhopper Binary Parser ragged_array.c count_rows buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4969</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in bwoodsend rockhopper up to 0.1.2. Affected by this issue is the function count_rows of the file rockhopper/src/ragged_array.c of the component Binary Parser. The manipulation of the argument raw leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. Upgrading to version 0.2.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 1a15fad5e06ae693eb9b8908363d2c8ef455104e. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266312.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35229 | ZKsync Era evaluation order of Yul function arguments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35229</link><description>ZKsync Era is a layer 2 rollup that uses zero-knowledge proofs to scale Ethereum. Prior to version 1.3.10, there is a very specific pattern `f(a(),b()); check_if_a_executed_last()` in Yul that exposes a bug in evaluation order of Yul function arguments. This vulnerability has been fixed in version 1.3.10. As a workaround, update and redeploy affected contracts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32978 | Kaminari Insecure File Permissions Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32978</link><description>Kaminari is a paginator for web app frameworks and object relational mappings. A security vulnerability involving insecure file permissions has been identified in the Kaminari pagination library for Ruby on Rails, concerning insecure file permissions. This vulnerability is of moderate severity due to the potential for unauthorized write access to particular Ruby files managed by the library. Such access could lead to the alteration of application behavior or data integrity issues. Users of affected versions are advised to update to Kaminari version 1.2.2 or later, where file permissions have been adjusted to enhance security. If upgrading is not feasible immediately, review and adjust the file permissions for particular Ruby files in Kaminari to ensure they are only accessible by authorized user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35219 | OpenAPI Generator Online - Arbitrary File Read/Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35219</link><description>OpenAPI Generator allows generation of API client libraries (SDK generation), server stubs, documentation and configuration automatically given an OpenAPI Spec. Prior to version 7.6.0, attackers can exploit a path traversal vulnerability to read and delete files and folders from an arbitrary, writable directory as anyone can set the output folder when submitting the request via the `outputFolder` option. The issue was fixed in version 7.6.0 by removing the usage of the `outputFolder` option. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0851 | SQLi in  Grup Arge Energy and Control Systems&amp;#x27;s Smartpower</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0851</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Grup Arge Energy and Control Systems Smartpower allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Smartpower: through V24.05.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:37:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34477 | configureNFS in lib/common/functions.sh in FOG through 1.5.10 allows local users to gain privileges by mounting a crafted NFS share (because...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34477</link><description>configureNFS in lib/common/functions.sh in FOG through 1.5.10 allows local users to gain privileges by mounting a crafted NFS share (because of no_root_squash and insecure). In order to exploit the vulnerability, someone needs to mount an NFS share in order to add an executable file as root. In addition, the SUID bit must be added to this file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50977 | In GNOME Shell through 45.2, unauthenticated remote code execution can be achieved by intercepting two DNS requests (GNOME Network Manager a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50977</link><description>In GNOME Shell through 45.2, unauthenticated remote code execution can be achieved by intercepting two DNS requests (GNOME Network Manager and GNOME Shell Portal Helper connectivity checks), and responding with attacker-specific IP addresses. This DNS hijacking causes GNOME Captive Portal to be launched via a WebKitGTK browser, by default, on the victim system; this can run JavaScript code inside a sandbox. NOTE: the vendor's position is that this is not a vulnerability because running JavaScript code inside a sandbox is the intended behavior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5407 | Code Injection vulnerability in RhinOS from SaltOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5407</link><description>A vulnerability in RhinOS 3.0-1190 could allow PHP code injection through the "search" parameter in /portal/search.htm. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to perform a reverse shell on the remote system, compromising the entire infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5408 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in RhinOS from SaltOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5408</link><description>Vulnerability in RhinOS 3.0-1190 consisting of an XSS through the "search" parameter of /portal/search.htm. This vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to steal details of a victim's user session by submitting a specially crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5409 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in RhinOS from SaltOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5409</link><description>RhinOS 3.0-1190 is vulnerable to an XSS via the "tamper" parameter in /admin/lib/phpthumb/phpthumb.php. An attacker could create a malicious URL and send it to a victim to obtain their session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5405 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WinNMP from Wtriple</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5405</link><description>A vulnerability had been discovered in WinNMP 19.02 consisting of an XSS attack via /tools/redis.php page in the k, hash, key and p parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to submit a specially crafted JavaScript payload for an authenticated user to retrieve their session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5406 | Multiple vulnerabilities in WinNMP from Wtriple</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5406</link><description>A vulnerability had been discovered in WinNMP 19.02 consisting of an XSS attack via index page in from, subject, text and hash parameters. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6349 | Heap overflow in libvpx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6349</link><description>A heap overflow vulnerability exists in libvpx - Encoding a frame that has larger dimensions than the originally configured size with VP9 may result in a heap overflow in libvpx.
We recommend upgrading to version 1.13.1 or above</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36383 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint SAML Authentication before 6.0.3. An attacker can place a crafted filename in the state field of a SAML ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36383</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint SAML Authentication before 6.0.3. An attacker can place a crafted filename in the state field of a SAML SSO-URL response, and the file corresponding to this filename will ultimately be deleted. This can lead to a SAML Authentication login outage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5035 | TP-Link Archer C5400X - RFTest Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5035</link><description>The affected device expose a network service called "rftest" that is vulnerable to unauthenticated command injection on ports TCP/8888, TCP/8889, and TCP/8890. By successfully exploiting this flaw, remote unauthenticated attacker can gain arbitrary command execution on the device with elevated privileges.This issue affects Archer C4500X: through 1_1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 07:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26289 | Remote Code Inclusion Vulnerability in Multiple PMB Versions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26289</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PMB Services PMB allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects PMB: from 7.5.1 before 7.5.6-2, from 7.4.1 before 7.4.9, from 7.3.1 before 7.3.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27314 | Stored XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27314</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus versions below 14730, ServiceDesk Plus MSP below 14720 and SupportCenter Plus below 14730 are vulnerable to stored XSS in the Custom Actions menu on the request details. This vulnerability can be exploited only by the SDAdmin role users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5403 | ASKEY 5G NR Small Cell - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5403</link><description>ASKEY 5G NR Small Cell fails to properly filter user input for certain functionality, allowing remote attackers with administrator privilege to execute arbitrary system commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 07:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3933 | Eclipse Open J9 With -Xgc:concurrentScavenge on IBM Z, could write/read outside of a buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3933</link><description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 release versions prior to 0.44.0 and after 0.13.0, when running with JVM option -Xgc:concurrentScavenge, the sequence generated for System.arrayCopy on the IBM Z platform with hardware and software support for guarded storage [1], could allow access to a buffer with an incorrect length value when executing an arraycopy sequence while the Concurrent Scavenge Garbage Collection cycle is active and the source and destination memory regions for arraycopy overlap. This allows read and write to addresses beyond the end of the array range.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3939 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.36 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3939</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.36 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4529 | Business Card &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Category Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4529</link><description>The Business Card WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions such as deleting card categories via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4530 | Business Card &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Category Edit via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4530</link><description>The Business Card WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions such as editing card categories via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4531 | Business Card &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Card Edit via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4531</link><description>The Business Card WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions such as editing cards via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4532 | Business Card &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary Card Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4532</link><description>The Business Card WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions such as deleting cards via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4533 | KKProgressbar2 Free &amp;lt;= 1.1.4.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4533</link><description>The KKProgressbar2 Free  WordPress plugin through 1.1.4.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admin users to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4534 | KKProgressbar2 Free &amp;lt;= 1.1.4.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4534</link><description>The KKProgressbar2 Free  WordPress plugin through 1.1.4.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4535 | KKProgressbar2 Free &amp;lt;= 1.1.4.2 - Progress Bar Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4535</link><description>The KKProgressbar2 Free  WordPress plugin through 1.1.4.2 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5400 | Openfind Mail2000 - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5400</link><description>Openfind Mail2000 does not properly filter parameters of specific CGI. Remote attackers with regular privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35291 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Splunk Config Explorer versions prior to 1.7.16. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35291</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Splunk Config Explorer versions prior to 1.7.16. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is using the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 04:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35297 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Booking versions prior to 2.4.5. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35297</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Booking versions prior to 2.4.5. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is accessing the web site using the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 04:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36384 | Pointsharp Cryptshare Server before 7.0.0 has an XSS issue that is related to notification messages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36384</link><description>Pointsharp Cryptshare Server before 7.0.0 has an XSS issue that is related to notification messages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5399 | Openfind Mail2000 - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5399</link><description>Openfind Mail2000 does not properly filter parameters of specific API. Remote attackers with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 03:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5397 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System instructorSubjects.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5397</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file instructorSubjects.php. The manipulation of the argument instructorId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266311.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 03:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5395 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System listofinstructor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5395</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file listofinstructor.php. The manipulation of the argument FullName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266309 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5396 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System newfaculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5396</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file newfaculty.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5394 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System newDept.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5394</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file newDept.php. The manipulation of the argument deptname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266308.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5393 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System listofcourse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5393</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file listofcourse.php. The manipulation of the argument idno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266307.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5392 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System editSubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5392</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editSubject.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266306 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5391 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System listofsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5391</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file listofsubject.php. The manipulation of the argument subjcode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266305 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5390 | itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System listofstudent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5390</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file listofstudent.php. The manipulation of the argument lname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266304.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5385 | oretnom23 Online Car Wash Booking System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5385</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in oretnom23 Online Car Wash Booking System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/?page=user/list. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name with the input  leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266303.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5384 | SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5384</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Facebook News Feed Like 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-266302 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5383 | lakernote EasyAdmin upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5383</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240324. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/file/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 9c8a836ace17a93c45e5ad52a2340788b7795030. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-266301 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36055 | Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily map physical memory with read/write acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36055</link><description>Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily map physical memory with read/write access via the MmMapIoSpace API (IOCTL 0x9c40a4f8, 0x9c40a4e8, 0x9c40a4c0, 0x9c40a4c4, 0x9c40a4ec, and seven others), leading to a denial of service (BSOD).</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36056 | Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily map physical memory via IOCTL 0x9c40649...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36056</link><description>Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily map physical memory via IOCTL 0x9c406490 (for IoAllocateMdl, MmBuildMdlForNonPagedPool, and MmMapLockedPages), leading to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36054 | Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily read kernel memory (and consequently ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36054</link><description>Hw64.sys in Marvin Test HW.exe before 5.0.5.0 allows unprivileged user-mode processes to arbitrarily read kernel memory (and consequently gain all privileges) via IOCTL 0x9c4064b8 (via MmMapIoSpace) and IOCTL 0x9c406490 (via ZwMapViewOfSection).</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5380 | jsy-1 short-url admin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5380</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in jsy-1 short-url 1.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 35c790897d6979392bc6f60707fc32da13a98b63. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266292.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5381 | itsourcecode Student Information Management System view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5381</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Student Information Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file view.php. The manipulation of the argument studentId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266293 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4286 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4286</link><description>Mintplex-Labs' anything-llm application is vulnerable to improper neutralization of special elements used in an expression language statement, identified in the commit id `57984fa85c31988b2eff429adfc654c46e0c342a`. The vulnerability arises from the application's handling of user modifications by managers or admins, allowing for the modification of all existing attributes of the `user` database entity without proper checks or sanitization. This flaw can be exploited to delete user threads, denying users access to their previously submitted data, or to inject fake threads and/or chat history for social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5379 | JFinalCMS template cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5379</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JFinalCMS up to 20240111. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/template. The manipulation of the argument directory leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266291.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34454 | Nintendo Wii U OS 5.5.5 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to forge SSL certificates as though they came from a Root CA, because there is a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34454</link><description>Nintendo Wii U OS 5.5.5 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to forge SSL certificates as though they came from a Root CA, because there is a secondary verification mechanism that only checks whether a CA is known and ignores the CA details and signature (and because * is accepted as a Common Name).</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 21:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5378 | SourceCodester School Intramurals Student Attendance Management System manage_sy.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5378</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Intramurals Student Attendance Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_sy.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266290 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5377 | SourceCodester Vehicle Management System newvehicle.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /newvehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266289 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5376 | Kashipara College Management System view_each_faculty.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5376</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file view_each_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266288.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 20:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5375 | Kashipara College Management System submit_student.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5375</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_student.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266287.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 20:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5374 | Kashipara College Management System submit_new_faculty.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5374</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file submit_new_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266286 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5373 | Kashipara College Management System submit_login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5373</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file submit_login.php. The manipulation of the argument usertype leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266285 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 19:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5372 | Kashipara College Management System submit_extracurricular_activity.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5372</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file submit_extracurricular_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_contact leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266284.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5371 | Kashipara College Management System submit_enroll_student.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5371</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file submit_enroll_student.php. The manipulation of the argument class_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266283.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5370 | Kashipara College Management System submit_enroll_staff.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file submit_enroll_staff.php. The manipulation of the argument class_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 17:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5369 | Kashipara College Management System submit_admin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266281 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5368 | Kashipara College Management System delete_faculty.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266280.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5367 | Kashipara College Management System each_extracurricula_activities.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file each_extracurricula_activities.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266279.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5366 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System edit-cate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5366</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file edit-cate.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 14:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29215 | Slash commands run in channel without channel membership via playbook task commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29215</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.1, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1, 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to enforce proper access control which allows a user to run a slash command in a channel they are not a member of via linking a playbook run to that channel and running a slash command as a playbook task command.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31859 | Member promoted to channel admin via playbooks run linking to channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31859</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to perform proper authorization checks which allows a member running a playbook in an existing channel to be promoted to a channel admin</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32045 | Playbook run link to private channel grants channel access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32045</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1, 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to enforce proper access controls for channel and team membership when linking a playbook run to a channel which allows  members to link their runs to private channels they were not members of.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34029 | AD/LDAP Group Members Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34029</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to perform a proper authorization check in the /api/v4/groups//channels//link endpoint which allows a user to learn the members of an AD/LDAP group that is linked to a team by adding the group to a channel, even if the user has no access to the team.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34152 | Playbook Run Metadata leak to Guest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34152</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to perform proper access control which allows a guest to get the metadata of a public playbook run that linked to the channel they are guest via sending an RHSRuns GraphQL query request to the server</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36241 | /playbook add slash command allows viewing arbitrary post contents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36241</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to enforce proper access controls which allows user to view arbitrary post contents via the /playbook add slash command</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36255 | Post actions can run playbook checklist task commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36255</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to perform proper input validation on post actions which allows an attacker to run a playbook checklist task command as another user via creating and sharing a deceptive post action that unexpectedly runs a slash command in some arbitrary channel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5270 | SAML to email switch possible when email signin is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5270</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.1, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to check if the email signup configuration option is enabled when a user requests to switch from SAML to Email. This allows the user to switch their authentication mail from SAML to email and possibly edit personal details that were otherwise non-editable and provided by the SAML provider.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5272 | Run Details leak to guest via webhook event &amp;quot;custom_playbooks_playbook_run_updated&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5272</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.3, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.1, 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.12 fail to restrict the audience of the "custom_playbooks_playbook_run_updated" webhook event, which allows a guest on a channel with a playbook run linked to see all the details of the playbook run when the run is marked by finished.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5365 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5365</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file manage_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266277 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5364 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System manage_tenant.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5364</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file manage_tenant.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266276.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5363 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5363</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266275.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5362 | SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System departmentDoctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5362</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file departmentDoctor.php. The manipulation of the argument deptid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5361 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System normal-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5361</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/normal-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266273 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5360 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5360</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/foreigner-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266272.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:36:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5359 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System foreigner-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5359</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/foreigner-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266271.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5358 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System normal-search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/normal-search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 09:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5357 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5357</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266269 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 08:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5356 | anji-plus AJ-Report testTransform;swagger-ui sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5356</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /dataSet/testTransform;swagger-ui. The manipulation of the argument dynSentence leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266268.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 07:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5355 | anji-plus AJ-Report IGroovyHandler command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5355</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. This issue affects the function IGroovyHandler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266267.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5354 | anji-plus AJ-Report detailByCode information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5354</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /reportShare/detailByCode. The manipulation of the argument shareToken leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 04:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5353 | anji-plus AJ-Report ZIP File decompress path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5353</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. This affects the function decompress of the component ZIP File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266265 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 04:26:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5352 | anji-plus AJ-Report validationRules deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5352</link><description>A vulnerability was found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function validationRules of the component com.anjiplus.template.gaea.business.modules.datasetparam.controller.DataSetParamController#verification. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266264.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5351 | anji-plus AJ-Report Javascript getValueFromJs deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5351</link><description>A vulnerability was found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getValueFromJs of the component Javascript Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266263.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5350 | anji-plus AJ-Report pageList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in anji-plus AJ-Report up to 1.4.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function pageList of the file /pageList. The manipulation of the argument p leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266262 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 22:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5340 | Ruijie RG-UAC sub_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240516. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/sub_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument key leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30056 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30056</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5339 | Ruijie RG-UAC online_check.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240516. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/online_check.php. The manipulation of the argument peernode leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266245 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5338 | Ruijie RG-UAC online.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240516. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/online.php. The manipulation of the argument peernode leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266244. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 15:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5337 | Ruijie RG-UAC user_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5337</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240516 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/systemConfig/sys_user/user_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument email2/user_name leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266243. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5336 | Ruijie RG-UAC vlan_add_commit.php addVlan os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5336</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240516 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function addVlan of the file /view/networkConfig/vlan/vlan_add_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument phyport leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266242 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4045 | Popup Builder by OptinMonster – WordPress Popups for Optins, Email Newsletters and Lead Generation &amp;lt;= 2.16.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4045</link><description>The Popup Builder by OptinMonster – WordPress Popups for Optins, Email Newsletters and Lead Generation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘campaign_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.16.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5218 | Reviews and Rating – Google Reviews &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5218</link><description>The Reviews and Rating – Google Reviews plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4858 | Testimonial Carousel For Elementor &amp;lt;= 10.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Limited Setting Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4858</link><description>The Testimonial Carousel For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_testimonials_option_callback' function in versions up to, and including, 10.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the OpenAI API key, disabling the feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 02:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5229 | Primary Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Pricing Table Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5229</link><description>The Primary Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 02:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5220 | ND Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 7.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5220</link><description>The ND Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 02:05:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>