<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-51246 | A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in GetSimple CMS 3.3.16 exists when using Source Code Mode as a backend user to add articles via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51246</link><description>A Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in GetSimple CMS 3.3.16 exists when using Source Code Mode as a backend user to add articles via the /admin/edit.php page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52206 | WordPress Page Builder: Live Composer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.25 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52206</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Live Composer Team Page Builder: Live Composer live-composer-page-builder.This issue affects Page Builder: Live Composer: from n/a through 1.5.25.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52213 | WordPress Rate Star Review Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52213</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VideoWhisper Rate Star Review – AJAX Reviews for Content, with Star Ratings allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Rate Star Review – AJAX Reviews for Content, with Star Ratings: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52216 | WordPress JS &amp;amp; CSS Script Optimizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52216</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yevhen Kotelnytskyi JS &amp; CSS Script Optimizer.This issue affects JS &amp; CSS Script Optimizer: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52200 | WordPress ARMember Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.22 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52200</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Repute Infosystems ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup.This issue affects ARMember – Membership Plugin, Content Restriction, Member Levels, User Profile &amp; User signup: n/a.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52205 | WordPress HTML5 SoundCloud Player Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52205</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in SVNLabs Softwares HTML5 SoundCloud Player with Playlist Free.This issue affects HTML5 SoundCloud Player with Playlist Free: from n/a through 2.8.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52207 | WordPress HTML5 MP3 Player with Playlist Free Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52207</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in SVNLabs Softwares HTML5 MP3 Player with Playlist Free.This issue affects HTML5 MP3 Player with Playlist Free: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25095 | Duplicator &amp;lt; 1.3.0 - Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25095</link><description>The Duplicator WordPress plugin before 1.3.0 does not properly escape values when its installer script replaces values in WordPress configuration files. If this installer script is left on the site after use, it could be use to run arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52190 | WordPress Coupon Referral Program Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52190</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in WP Swings Coupon Referral Program.This issue affects Coupon Referral Program: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5235 | Ovic Responsive WPBakery &amp;lt; 1.2.9 - Subscriber+ Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5235</link><description>The Ovic Responsive WPBakery WordPress plugin before 1.2.9 does not limit which options can be updated via some of its AJAX actions, which may allow attackers with a subscriber+ account to update blog options, such as 'users_can_register' and 'default_role'. It also unserializes user input in the process, which may lead to Object Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5911 | WP Custom Cursors &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5911</link><description>The WP Custom Cursors | WordPress Cursor Plugin WordPress plugin through 3.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5957 | Ni Purchase Order(PO) For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Admin+ File Upload to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5957</link><description>The Ni Purchase Order(PO) For WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not validate logo and signature image files uploaded in the settings, allowing high privileged user to upload arbitrary files to the web server, triggering an RCE vulnerability by uploading a web shell.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6042 | Getwid &amp;lt; 2.0.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending to Admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6042</link><description>Any unauthenticated user may send e-mail from the site with any title or content to the admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6139 | Essential Real Estate &amp;lt; 4.4.0 - Subscriber+ Denial of Service via Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6139</link><description>The Essential Real Estate WordPress plugin before 4.4.0 does not apply proper capability checks on its AJAX actions, which among other things, allow attackers with a subscriber account to conduct Denial of Service attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6140 | Essential Real Estate &amp;lt; 4.4 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6140</link><description>The Essential Real Estate WordPress plugin before 4.4.0 does not prevent users with limited privileges on the site, like subscribers, from momentarily uploading malicious PHP files disguised as ZIP archives, which may lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6141 | Essential Real Estate &amp;lt; 4.4.0 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6141</link><description>The Essential Real Estate WordPress plugin before 4.4.0 does not apply proper capability checks on its AJAX actions, which among other things, allow attackers with a subscriber account to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6161 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt; 2.1.9 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6161</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding WordPress plugin before 2.1.9 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6383 | Debug Log Manager &amp;lt; 2.3.0 - Sensitive Logs Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6383</link><description>The Debug Log Manager WordPress plugin before 2.3.0 contains a Directory listing vulnerability was discovered, which allows you to download the debug log without authorization and gain access to sensitive data</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6505 | Prime Mover &amp;lt; 1.9.3 - Directory Listing to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6505</link><description>The Migrate WordPress Website &amp; Backups WordPress plugin before 1.9.3 does not prevent directory listing in sensitive directories containing export files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6528 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt; 6.6.19 - Author+ Insecure Deserialization leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6528</link><description>The Slider Revolution WordPress plugin before 6.6.19 does not prevent users with at least the Author role from unserializing arbitrary content when importing sliders, potentially leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6529 | WP VR &amp;lt; 8.3.15 - Unauthenticated Plugin Downgrade leading to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6529</link><description>The WP VR WordPress plugin before 8.3.15 does not authorisation and CSRF in a function hooked to admin_init, allowing unauthenticated users to downgrade the plugin, thus leading to Reflected or Stored XSS, as previous versions have such vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6532 | WP Blogs&amp;#x27; Planetarium &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6532</link><description>The WP Blogs' Planetarium WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6555 | Email Subscription Popup &amp;lt; 1.2.20 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6555</link><description>The Email Subscription Popup WordPress plugin before 1.2.20 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6627 | WP Go Maps &amp;lt; 9.0.28 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6627</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) WordPress plugin before 9.0.28 does not properly protect most of its REST API routes, which attackers can abuse to store malicious HTML/Javascript on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6631 | Subnet Solutions Inc. PowerSYSTEM Center Unquoted Search Path or Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6631</link><description>PowerSYSTEM Center versions 2020 Update 16 and prior contain a vulnerability that may allow an authorized local user to insert arbitrary code into the unquoted service path and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6750 | Clone &amp;lt; 2.4.3 - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6750</link><description>The Clone WordPress plugin before 2.4.3 uses buffer files to store in-progress backup informations, which is stored at a publicly accessible, statically defined file path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6845 | CommentTweets  &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6845</link><description>The CommentTweets WordPress plugin through 0.6 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52208 | WordPress Constant Contact Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52208</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Constant Contact Constant Contact Forms.This issue affects Constant Contact Forms: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52222 | WordPress WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52222</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic WooCommerce.This issue affects WooCommerce: from n/a through 8.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-3600 | It was discovered that the eBPF implementation in the Linux kernel did not properly track bounds information for 32 bit registers when perfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3600</link><description>It was discovered that the eBPF implementation in the Linux kernel did not properly track bounds information for 32 bit registers when performing div and mod operations. A local attacker could use this to possibly execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1032 | The Linux kernel io_uring IORING_OP_SOCKET operation contained a double free in function __sys_socket_file() in file net/socket.c. This issu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1032</link><description>The Linux kernel io_uring IORING_OP_SOCKET operation contained a double free in function __sys_socket_file() in file net/socket.c. This issue was introduced in da214a475f8bd1d3e9e7a19ddfeb4d1617551bab and fixed in 649c15c7691e9b13cbe9bf6c65c365350e056067.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3328 | Race condition in snap-confine's must_mkdir_and_open_with_perms()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3328</link><description>Race condition in snap-confine's must_mkdir_and_open_with_perms()</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2602 | io_uring UAF, Unix SCM garbage collection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2602</link><description>io_uring UAF, Unix SCM garbage collection</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2588 | It was discovered that the cls_route filter implementation in the Linux kernel would not remove an old filter from the hashtable before free...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2588</link><description>It was discovered that the cls_route filter implementation in the Linux kernel would not remove an old filter from the hashtable before freeing it if its handle had the value 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2586 | It was discovered that a nft object or expression could reference a nft set on a different nft table, leading to a use-after-free once that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2586</link><description>It was discovered that a nft object or expression could reference a nft set on a different nft table, leading to a use-after-free once that table was deleted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2585 | It was discovered that when exec'ing from a non-leader thread, armed POSIX CPU timers would be left on a list but freed, leading to a use-af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2585</link><description>It was discovered that when exec'ing from a non-leader thread, armed POSIX CPU timers would be left on a list but freed, leading to a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52215 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager Plugin &amp;lt;=1.5.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52215</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in UkrSolution Simple Inventory Management – just scan barcode to manage products and orders. For WooCommerce.This issue affects Simple Inventory Management – just scan barcode to manage products and orders. For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52218 | WordPress WooCommerce Tranzila Gateway Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52218</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Anton Bond Woocommerce Tranzila Payment Gateway.This issue affects Woocommerce Tranzila Payment Gateway: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52219 | WordPress Gecka Terms Thumbnails Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52219</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Gecka Gecka Terms Thumbnails.This issue affects Gecka Terms Thumbnails: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52225 | WordPress Taggbox Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52225</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Tagbox Tagbox – UGC Galleries, Social Media Widgets, User Reviews &amp; Analytics.This issue affects Tagbox – UGC Galleries, Social Media Widgets, User Reviews &amp; Analytics: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21744 | WordPress Mapster WP Maps Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.38 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21744</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mapster Technology Inc. Mapster WP Maps allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mapster WP Maps: from n/a through 1.2.38.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21745 | WordPress Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21745</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Laybuy Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21747 | WordPress WP ERP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21747</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in weDevs WP ERP | Complete HR solution with recruitment &amp; job listings | WooCommerce CRM &amp; Accounting.This issue affects WP ERP | Complete HR solution with recruitment &amp; job listings | WooCommerce CRM &amp; Accounting: from n/a through 1.12.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 16:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21650 | XWiki Remote Code Execution vulnerability via user registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21650</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki is vulnerable to a remote code execution (RCE) attack through its user registration feature. This issue allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code by crafting malicious payloads in the "first name" or "last name" fields during user registration. This impacts all installations that have user registration enabled for guests. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.17, 15.5.3 and 15.8 RC1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32650 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the FST_BL_GEOM parsing maxhandle functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115, when compiled as a 32-bit bi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32650</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the FST_BL_GEOM parsing maxhandle functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115, when compiled as a 32-bit binary. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34087 | An improper array index validation vulnerability exists in the EVCD var len parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34087</link><description>An improper array index validation vulnerability exists in the EVCD var len parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .evcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34436 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the LXT2 num_time_table_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34436</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the LXT2 num_time_table_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35004 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the VZT longest_len value allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35004</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the VZT longest_len value allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35057 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_trace value elements allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35057</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_trace value elements allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35128 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 time_table tsec_nitems functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35128</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 time_table tsec_nitems functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35702 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35702</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the fstReaderVarint32 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35703 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35703</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the fstReaderVarint64 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35704 | Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35704</link><description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST LEB128 varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the fstReaderVarint32WithSkip function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35955 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35955</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the decompression function `LZ4_decompress_safe_partial`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35956 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35956</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the decompression function `fastlz_decompress`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35957 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35957</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the decompression function `uncompress`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35958 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35958</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 VCDATA parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the copy function `fstFread`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35959 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35959</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns `.ghw` decompression.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35960 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35960</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns legacy decompression in `vcd_main`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35961 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35961</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns decompression in `vcd_recorder_main`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35962 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35962</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns decompression in the `vcd2vzt` utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35963 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35963</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns decompression in the `vcd2lxt2` utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35964 | Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35964</link><description>Multiple OS command injection vulnerabilities exist in the decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted wave file can lead to arbitrary command execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns decompression in the `vcd2lxt` utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35969 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35969</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the chain_table of `FST_BL_VCDATA` and `FST_BL_VCDATA_DYN_ALIAS` section types.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35970 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35970</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the chain_table of the `FST_BL_VCDATA_DYN_ALIAS2` section type.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35989 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 zlib block allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35989</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 zlib block allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35992 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 vesc allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115, when compiled as ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35992</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 vesc allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115, when compiled as a 32-bit binary. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35994 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35994</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the tdelta initialization part.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35995 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35995</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the tdelta indexing when signal_lens is 1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35996 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35996</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the tdelta indexing when signal_lens is 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35997 | Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35997</link><description>Multiple improper array index validation vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 tdelta functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the tdelta indexing when signal_lens is 2 or more.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36746 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 fstWritex len functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36746</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 fstWritex len functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the handling of `len` in `fstWritex` when parsing the time table.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36747 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 fstWritex len functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36747</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 fstWritex len functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the handling of `len` in `fstWritex` when `beg_time` does not match the start of the time table.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36861 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the VZT LZMA_read_varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36861</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the VZT LZMA_read_varint functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36864 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 temp_signal_value_buf allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36864</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the fstReaderIterBlocks2 temp_signal_value_buf allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36915 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36915</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the allocation of the `chain_table` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36916 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36916</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the FST fstReaderIterBlocks2 chain_table allocation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .fst file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the allocation of the `chain_table_lengths` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37282 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the VZT LZMA_Read dmem extraction functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37282</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the VZT LZMA_Read dmem extraction functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37416 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37416</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the GUI's legacy VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37417 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37417</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the GUI's interactive VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37418 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37418</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2vzt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37419 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37419</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2lxt2 conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37420 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37420</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD parse_valuechange portdump functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2lxt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37442 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37442</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds read when triggered via the GUI's default VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37443 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37443</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds read when triggered via the GUI's legacy VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37444 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37444</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds read when triggered via the GUI's interactive VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37445 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37445</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2vzt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37446 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37446</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2lxt2 conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37447 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37447</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in the VCD var definition section functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when triggered via the vcd2lxt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37573 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37573</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the GUI's recoder (default) VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37574 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37574</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the GUI's legacy VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37575 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37575</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the GUI's interactive VCD parsing code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37576 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37576</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the vcd2vzt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37577 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37577</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the vcd2lxt2 conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37578 | Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37578</link><description>Multiple use-after-free vulnerabilities exist in the VCD get_vartoken realloc functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the use-after-free when triggered via the vcd2lxt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37921 | Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37921</link><description>Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the arbitrary write when triggered via the vcd2vzt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37922 | Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37922</link><description>Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the arbitrary write when triggered via the vcd2lxt2 conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37923 | Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37923</link><description>Multiple arbitrary write vulnerabilities exist in the VCD sorted bsearch functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vcd file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the arbitrary write when triggered via the vcd2lxt conversion utility.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38583 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_expand_integer_to_bits function of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38583</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_expand_integer_to_bits function of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38618 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38618</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `rows` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38619 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38619</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `msb` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38620 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38620</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `lsb` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38621 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38621</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `flags` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38622 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38622</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `len` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38623 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38623</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `vindex_offset` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38648 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_get_facname decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38648</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_get_facname decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write perfomed by the prefix copy loop.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38649 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_get_facname decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38649</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_get_facname decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write perfomed by the string copy loop.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38650 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode times parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38650</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode times parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when num_time_ticks is not zero.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38651 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode times parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38651</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode times parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when num_time_ticks is zero.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38652 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode dict parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38652</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode dict parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when num_time_ticks is not zero.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38653 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode dict parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38653</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_block_vch_decode dict parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when num_time_ticks is zero.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38657 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the LXT2 zlib block decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38657</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the LXT2 zlib block decompression functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39234 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_process_block autosort functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39234</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_process_block autosort functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when looping over `lt-&gt;numrealfacs`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39235 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_process_block autosort functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39235</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the VZT vzt_rd_process_block autosort functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .vzt file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write when looping over `lt-&gt;num_time_ticks`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39270 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39270</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `rows` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39271 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39271</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `msb` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39272 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39272</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `lsb` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39273 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39273</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `flags` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39274 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39274</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `len` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39275 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39275</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 facgeometry parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `value` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39316 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 num_dict_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39316</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 num_dict_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `string_pointers` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39317 | Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 num_dict_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39317</link><description>Multiple integer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 num_dict_entries functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer overflow when allocating the `string_lens` array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39413 | Multiple integer underflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_iter_radix shift operation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39413</link><description>Multiple integer underflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_iter_radix shift operation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer underflow when performing the left shift operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39414 | Multiple integer underflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_iter_radix shift operation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39414</link><description>Multiple integer underflow vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 lxt2_rd_iter_radix shift operation functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially crafted .lxt2 file can lead to memory corruption. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the integer underflow when performing the right shift operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39443 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .lxt2 file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39443</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write perfomed by the prefix copy loop.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39444 | Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .lxt2 file can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39444</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities exist in the LXT2 parsing functionality of GTKWave 3.3.115. A specially-crafted .lxt2 file can lead to arbitrary code execution. A victim would need to open a malicious file to trigger these vulnerabilities.This vulnerability concerns the out-of-bounds write perfomed by the string copy loop.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47211 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the uploadMib functionality of ManageEngine OpManager 12.7.258. A specially crafted HTTP reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47211</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the uploadMib functionality of ManageEngine OpManager 12.7.258. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to arbitrary file creation. An attacker can send a malicious MiB file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 14:53:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51701 | @fastify-reply-from JSON Content-Type parsing confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51701</link><description>fastify-reply-from is a Fastify plugin to forward the current HTTP request to another server. A reverse proxy server built with `@fastify/reply-from` could misinterpret the incoming body by passing an header `ContentType: application/json ; charset=utf-8`. This can lead to bypass of security checks. This vulnerability has been patched in '@fastify/reply-from` version 9.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7224 | OpenVPN Connect version 3.0 through 3.4.6 on macOS allows local users to execute code in external third party libraries using the DYLD_INSER...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7224</link><description>OpenVPN Connect version 3.0 through 3.4.6 on macOS allows local users to execute code in external third party libraries using the DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES environment variable</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21647 | HTTP Request/Response Smuggling in puma</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21647</link><description>Puma is a web server for Ruby/Rack applications built for parallelism. Prior to version 6.4.2, puma exhibited incorrect behavior when parsing chunked transfer encoding bodies in a way that allowed HTTP request smuggling. Fixed versions limits the size of chunk extensions. Without this limit, an attacker could cause unbounded resource (CPU, network bandwidth) consumption. This vulnerability has been fixed in versions 6.4.2 and 5.6.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21644 | pyLoad unauthenticated flask configuration leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21644</link><description>pyLoad is the free and open-source Download Manager written in pure Python. Any unauthenticated user can browse to a specific URL to expose the Flask config, including the `SECRET_KEY` variable. This issue has been patched in version 0.5.0b3.dev77.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21645 | pyLoad Log Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21645</link><description>pyLoad is the free and open-source Download Manager written in pure Python. A log injection vulnerability was identified in `pyload` allowing any unauthenticated actor to inject arbitrary messages into the logs gathered by `pyload`. Forged or otherwise, corrupted log files can be used to cover an attacker’s tracks or even to implicate another party in the commission of a malicious act. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.5.0b3.dev77.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 13:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0322 | Out-of-bounds Read in gpac/gpac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0322</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in GitHub repository gpac/gpac prior to 2.3-DEV.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:48:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6552 | Open redirect in TasmoAdmin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6552</link><description>Lack of "current" GET parameter validation during the action of changing a language leads to an open redirect vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0321 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in gpac/gpac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0321</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow in GitHub repository gpac/gpac prior to 2.3-DEV.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6921 | SQL Injection in PrestaShop Google Integrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6921</link><description>Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in PrestaShow Google Integrator (PrestaShop addon) allows for data extraction and modification. This attack is possible via command insertion in one of the cookies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0308 | Inis Proxy.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Inis up to 2.0.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file app/api/controller/default/Proxy.php. The manipulation of the argument p_url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249875.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 10:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0307 | Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System login_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0307</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249874 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5091 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5091</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory. This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r37p0 through r40p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29051 | User-defined OXMF templates could be used to access a limited part of the internal OX App Suite Java API. The existing switch to disable the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29051</link><description>User-defined OXMF templates could be used to access a limited part of the internal OX App Suite Java API. The existing switch to disable the feature by default was not effective in this case. Unauthorized users could discover and modify application state, including objects related to other users and contexts. We now make sure that the switch to disable user-generated templates by default works as intended and will remove the feature in future generations of the product. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29052 | Users were able to define disclaimer texts for an upsell shop dialog that would contain script code that was not sanitized correctly. Attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29052</link><description>Users were able to define disclaimer texts for an upsell shop dialog that would contain script code that was not sanitized correctly. Attackers could lure victims to user accounts with malicious script code and make them execute it in the context of a trusted domain. We added sanitization for this content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41710 | User-defined script code could be stored for a upsell related shop URL. This code was not correctly sanitized when adding it to DOM. Attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41710</link><description>User-defined script code could be stored for a upsell related shop URL. This code was not correctly sanitized when adding it to DOM. Attackers could lure victims to user accounts with malicious script code and make them execute it in the context of a trusted domain. We added sanitization for this content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0306 | Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System admin_login_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0306</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/admin_login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249873 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29048 | A component for parsing OXMF templates could be abused to execute arbitrary system commands that would be executed as the non-privileged run...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29048</link><description>A component for parsing OXMF templates could be abused to execute arbitrary system commands that would be executed as the non-privileged runtime user. Users and attackers could run system commands with limited privilege to gain unauthorized access to confidential information and potentially violate integrity by modifying resources. The template engine has been reconfigured to deny execution of harmful commands on a system level. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29049 | The "upsell" widget at the portal page could be abused to inject arbitrary script code. Attackers that manage to lure users to a compromised...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29049</link><description>The "upsell" widget at the portal page could be abused to inject arbitrary script code. Attackers that manage to lure users to a compromised account, or gain temporary access to a legitimate account, could inject script code to gain persistent code execution capabilities under a trusted domain. User input for this widget is now sanitized to avoid malicious content the be processed. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29050 | The optional "LDAP contacts provider" could be abused by privileged users to inject LDAP filter strings that allow to access content outside...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29050</link><description>The optional "LDAP contacts provider" could be abused by privileged users to inject LDAP filter strings that allow to access content outside of the intended hierarchy. Unauthorized users could break confidentiality of information in the directory and potentially cause high load on the directory server, leading to denial of service. Encoding has been added for user-provided fragments that are used when constructing the LDAP query. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0305 | Guangzhou Yingke Electronic Technology Ncast Guest Login IPSetup.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0305</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guangzhou Yingke Electronic Technology Ncast up to 2017 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage/IPSetup.php of the component Guest Login. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249872.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0304 | Youke365 collect.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0304</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Youke365 up to 1.5.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/api/controller/collect.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249871.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 08:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0303 | Youke365 Parameter caiji.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0303</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Youke365 up to 1.5.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /app/api/controller/caiji.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249870 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0302 | fhs-opensource iparking vueLogin deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0302</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in fhs-opensource iparking 1.5.22.RELEASE. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /vueLogin. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249869 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 07:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22216 | In default installations of Microchip maxView Storage Manager (for Adaptec Smart Storage Controllers) where Redfish server is configured for...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22216</link><description>In default installations of Microchip maxView Storage Manager (for Adaptec Smart Storage Controllers) where Redfish server is configured for remote system management, unauthorized access can occur, with data modification and information disclosure. This affects 3.00.23484 through 4.14.00.26064 (except for the patched versions 3.07.23980 and 4.07.00.25339).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0301 | fhs-opensource iparking PayTempOrderAction.java getData sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0301</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in fhs-opensource iparking 1.5.22.RELEASE. This vulnerability affects the function getData of the file src/main/java/com/xhb/pay/action/PayTempOrderAction.java. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249868.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0300 | Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform HTTP POST Request userattestation.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0300</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Baichuo Smart S150 Management Platform up to 20240101. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /useratte/userattestation.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument web_img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 06:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0299 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249865 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0298 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0298</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249864. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 05:04:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0297 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249863. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0296 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0296</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0295 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setWanCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0295</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. This affects the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249861 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0294 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setUssd os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0294</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this issue is the function setUssd of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ussd leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249860. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 03:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0293 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setUploadSetting os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0293</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setUploadSetting of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249859. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47140 | IBM CICS Transaction Gateway improper access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47140</link><description>IBM CICS Transaction Gateway 9.3 could allow a user to transfer or view files due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  270259.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50948 | IBM Storage Fusion HCI information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50948</link><description>IBM Storage Fusion HCI 2.1.0 through 2.6.1 contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.  IBM X-Force ID:  275671.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0292 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0292</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. Affected is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 02:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7215 | Chanzhaoyu chatgpt-web cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7215</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Chanzhaoyu chatgpt-web 2.11.1. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;image src onerror=prompt(document.domain)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249779.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0291 | Totolink LR1200GB cstecgi.cgi UploadFirmwareFile command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0291</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink LR1200GB 9.1.0u.6619_B20230130. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadFirmwareFile of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249857 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0290 | Kashipara Food Management System stock_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0290</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file stock_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_type leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249851.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0289 | Kashipara Food Management System stock_entry_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0289</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file stock_entry_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument itemype leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249850 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0288 | Kashipara Food Management System rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0288</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249849 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0287 | Kashipara Food Management System itemBillPdf.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0287</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file itemBillPdf.php. The manipulation of the argument printid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249848.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:03:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7214 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7214</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this issue is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v8 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249770 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 20:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47145 | IBM Db2 for Windows privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47145</link><description>IBM Db2 for Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges to the SYSTEM user using the MSI repair functionality.  IBM X-Force ID:  270402.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7213 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7213</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=1 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument v33 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249769 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0286 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System Contact Form index.php#contact_us cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0286</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php#contact_us of the component Contact Form. The manipulation of the argument Name/Email/Message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249843.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0284 | Kashipara Food Management System party_submit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0284</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249839.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7212 | DeDeCMS Backend file_class.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7212</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in DeDeCMS up to 5.7.112. Affected is an unknown function of the file file_class.php of the component Backend. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249768. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0283 | Kashipara Food Management System party_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0283</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_details.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249838 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0282 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterialsubmit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0282</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument tin leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249837 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0281 | Kashipara Food Management System loginCheck.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0281</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file loginCheck.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249836.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0280 | Kashipara Food Management System item_type_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0280</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file item_type_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument type_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249835.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0279 | Kashipara Food Management System item_list_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0279</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file item_list_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249834 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0278 | Kashipara Food Management System partylist_edit_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0278</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file partylist_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249833 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0277 | Kashipara Food Management System party_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0277</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249832.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0276 | Kashipara Food Management System rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0276</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249831.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0275 | Kashipara Food Management System item_edit_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0275</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file item_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249830 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0274 | Kashipara Food Management System billAjax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0274</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file billAjax.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249829 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0273 | Kashipara Food Management System addwaste_entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0273</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file addwaste_entry.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249828.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0272 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterialsubmit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0272</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument material_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249827.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7211 | Uniway Router Administrative Web Interface reliance on ip address for authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Uniway Router 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Administrative Web Interface. The manipulation leads to reliance on ip address for authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249766 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 10:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7210 | OneNav API improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OneNav up to 0.9.33. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?c=api of the component API. The manipulation of the argument X-Token leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249765 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 09:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7209 | Uniway Router Device Reset device_reset.cgi denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7209</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Uniway Router up to 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boaform/device_reset.cgi of the component Device Reset Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249758 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0271 | Kashipara Food Management System addmaterial_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0271</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file addmaterial_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249826 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0270 | Kashipara Food Management System item_list_submit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0270</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file item_list_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249825 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0268 | Kashipara Hospital Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file registration.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/pass/gender/age/city leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249824.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7208 | Totolink X2000R_V2 boa formTmultiAP buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7208</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink X2000R_V2 2.0.0-B20230727.10434. This vulnerability affects the function formTmultiAP of the file /bin/boa. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. VDB-249742 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0267 | Kashipara Hospital Management System Parameter login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0267</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249823.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:23:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0266 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System User Registration cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component User Registration. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 05:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0265 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System GET Parameter index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0265</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249821 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 05:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0264 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System LoginRegistration.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0264</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /LoginRegistration.php. The manipulation of the argument formToken leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249820.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 04:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0263 | ACME Ultra Mini HTTPd HTTP GET Request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0263</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ACME Ultra Mini HTTPd 1.21. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249819.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0262 | Online Job Portal Create News Page News.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0262</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Online Job Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/News.php of the component Create News Page. The manipulation of the argument News with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(0x00C57D)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249818 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0261 | Sentex FTPDMIN RNFR Command denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0261</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sentex FTPDMIN 0.96 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component RNFR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249817 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0260 | SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal Password Change change_password_teacher.php session expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0260</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file change_password_teacher.php of the component Password Change. The manipulation leads to session expiration. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249816.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:02:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51441 | Apache Axis 1.x (EOL) may allow SSRF when untrusted input is passed to the service admin HTTP API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51441</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Axis allowed users with access to the admin service to perform possible SSRF
This issue affects Apache Axis: through 1.3.

As Axis 1 has been EOL we recommend you migrate to a different SOAP engine, such as Apache Axis 2/Java. Alternatively you could use a build of Axis with the patch from  https://github.com/apache/axis-axis1-java/commit/685c309febc64aa393b2d64a05f90e7eb9f73e06  applied. The Apache Axis project does not expect to create an Axis 1.x release 
fixing this problem, though contributors that would like to work towards
 this are welcome.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 12:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6798 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6798</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized settings update due to a missing capability check when updating settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access or above to change the plugin's settings including proxy settings, which are also exposed to authors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6801 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6801</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50121 | Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50121</link><description>Autel EVO NANO drone flight control firmware version 1.6.5 is vulnerable to denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46953 | SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents modul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46953</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in ABO.CMS v.5.9.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the d parameter in the Documents module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39853 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39853</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Dzzoffice version 2.01, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the doobj and doevent parameters in the Network Disk backend module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50609 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50609</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AVA teaching video application service platform version 3.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to ajax.aspx.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 03:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50612 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50612</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in fit2cloud Cloud Explorer Lite version 1.4.1, allow local attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the cloud accounts parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 02:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>