<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:39:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-9686 | Portabilis i-Educar Listagem de áreas de conhecimento edit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9686</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /module/AreaConhecimento/edit of the component Listagem de áreas de conhecimento Page. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9685 | Portabilis i-Educar Listagem de áreas de conhecimento view sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9685</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /module/AreaConhecimento/view of the component Listagem de áreas de conhecimento Page. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9684 | Portabilis i-Educar Formula de Cálculo de Média edit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9684</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/FormulaMedia/edit of the component Formula de Cálculo de Média Page. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9683 | O2OA Personal Profile form cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /x_cms_assemble_control/jaxrs/form of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9682 | O2OA Personal Profile appdict cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9682</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /x_cms_assemble_control/jaxrs/design/appdict of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38677 | f2fs: fix to avoid out-of-boundary access in dnode page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38677</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: fix to avoid out-of-boundary access in dnode page

As Jiaming Zhang reported:

 
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x1c1/0x2a0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0x17e/0x800 mm/kasan/report.c:480
 kasan_report+0x147/0x180 mm/kasan/report.c:593
 data_blkaddr fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:3053 [inline]
 f2fs_data_blkaddr fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:3058 [inline]
 f2fs_get_dnode_of_data+0x1a09/0x1c40 fs/f2fs/node.c:855
 f2fs_reserve_block+0x53/0x310 fs/f2fs/data.c:1195
 prepare_write_begin fs/f2fs/data.c:3395 [inline]
 f2fs_write_begin+0xf39/0x2190 fs/f2fs/data.c:3594
 generic_perform_write+0x2c7/0x910 mm/filemap.c:4112
 f2fs_buffered_write_iter fs/f2fs/file.c:4988 [inline]
 f2fs_file_write_iter+0x1ec8/0x2410 fs/f2fs/file.c:5216
 new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
 vfs_write+0x546/0xa90 fs/read_write.c:686
 ksys_write+0x149/0x250 fs/read_write.c:738
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xf3/0x3d0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

The root cause is in the corrupted image, there is a dnode has the same
node id w/ its inode, so during f2fs_get_dnode_of_data(), it tries to
access block address in dnode at offset 934, however it parses the dnode
as inode node, so that get_dnode_addr() returns 360, then it tries to
access page address from 360 + 934 * 4 = 4096 w/ 4 bytes.

To fix this issue, let's add sanity check for node id of all direct nodes
during f2fs_get_dnode_of_data().</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9681 | O2OA Personal Profile agent cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9681</link><description>A flaw has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Affected is an unknown function of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/agent of the component Personal Profile Page. Executing manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9680 | O2OA Personal Profile page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9680</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This impacts an unknown function of the file /x_portal_assemble_designer/jaxrs/page of the component Personal Profile Page. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 07:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9679 | itsourcecode Student Information System course_edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9679</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Student Information System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /course_edit1.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9499 | Ocean Extra &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via oceanwp_library Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9499</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's oceanwp_library shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9500 | TablePress &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcode_debug Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9500</link><description>The TablePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘shortcode_debug’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54946 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54946</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54944 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54944</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to write malicious code in a specific file, which may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54945 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54945</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious file by controlling the destination file path.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54942 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54942</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to access deployment functionality without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54943 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54943</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability in SUNNET Corporate Training Management System before 10.11 allows remote attackers to perform unauthorized application deployment due to the absence of proper access control checks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4956 | WordPress Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4956</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in AA-Team Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Pro Bulk Watermark Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 02:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9618 | Related Posts Lite &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9618</link><description>The Related Posts Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.12. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the settings update functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 02:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34165 | NetSupport Manager &amp;lt; 14.12.0000 Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34165</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in NetSupport Manager 14.x versions prior to 14.12.0000 allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) or potentially leak a limited amount of memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34164 | NetSupport Manager &amp;lt; 14.12.0000 Heap-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34164</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in NetSupport Manager 14.x versions prior to 14.12.0000 allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) or potentially result in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58159 | WeGIA Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload Leading To Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58159</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. Prior to version 3.4.11, a remote code execution vulnerability was identified, caused by improper validation of uploaded files. The application allows an attacker to upload files with arbitrary filenames, including those with a .php extension. Because the uploaded file is written directly to disk without adequate sanitization or extension restrictions, a spreadsheet file followed by PHP code can be uploaded and executed on the server, leading to arbitrary code execution. This is due to insufficient mitigation of CVE-2025-22133. This issue has been patched in version 3.4.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57752 | Next.js Affected by Cache Key Confusion for Image Optimization API Routes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57752</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. In versions before 14.2.31 and from 15.0.0 to before 15.4.5, Next.js Image Optimization API routes are affected by cache key confusion. When images returned from API routes vary based on request headers (such as Cookie or Authorization), these responses could be incorrectly cached and served to unauthorized users due to a cache key confusion bug. This vulnerability has been fixed in Next.js versions 14.2.31 and 15.4.5. All users are encouraged to upgrade if they use API routes to serve images that depend on request headers and have image optimization enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55173 | Next.js Content Injection Vulnerability for Image Optimization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55173</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. In versions before 14.2.31 and from 15.0.0 to before 15.4.5, Next.js Image Optimization is vulnerable to content injection. The issue allowed attacker-controlled external image sources to trigger file downloads with arbitrary content and filenames under specific configurations. This behavior could be abused for phishing or malicious file delivery. This vulnerability has been fixed in Next.js versions 14.2.31 and 15.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58156 | Centurion ERP users can view hashed authentication tokens that belong to other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58156</link><description>Centurion ERP is an ERP with a focus on ITSM and automation. In versions starting from 1.12.0 to before 1.21.0, an authenticated user can view all authentication token details within the database. This includes the actual token, although only the hashed token. This does not include any un-hashed authentication token as viewable. This issue has been patched in version 1.21.0. A workaround for this is not deemed viable as it would involve disabling token authentication. Users are encouraged to remove any authentication token that was created by one of the effected versions of Centurion ERP. Webmasters can ensure this occurs by removing all authentication tokens from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57822 | Next.js Improper Middleware Redirect Handling Leads to SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57822</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. Prior to versions 14.2.32 and 17.4.7, when next() was used without explicitly passing the request object, it could lead to SSRF in self-hosted applications that incorrectly forwarded user-supplied headers. This vulnerability has been fixed in  Next.js Middleware versions 14.2.32 and 15.4.7. All users implementing custom middleware logic in self-hosted environments are strongly encouraged to upgrade and verify correct usage of the next() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9678 | Campcodes Online Loan Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9678</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Loan Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_borrower. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58160 | Tracing logging user input may result in poisoning logs with ANSI escape sequences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58160</link><description>tracing is a framework for instrumenting Rust programs to collect structured, event-based diagnostic information. Prior to version 0.3.20, tracing-subscriber was vulnerable to ANSI escape sequence injection attacks. Untrusted user input containing ANSI escape sequences could be injected into terminal output when logged, potentially allowing attackers to manipulate terminal title bars, clear screens or modify terminal display, and potentially mislead users through terminal manipulation. tracing-subscriber version 0.3.20 fixes this vulnerability by escaping ANSI control characters when writing events to destinations that may be printed to the terminal. A workaround involves avoiding printing logs to terminal emulators without escaping ANSI control sequences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58068 | Eventlet affected by HTTP request smuggling in unparsed trailers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58068</link><description>Eventlet is a concurrent networking library for Python. Prior to version 0.40.3, the Eventlet WSGI parser is vulnerable to HTTP Request Smuggling due to improper handling of HTTP trailer sections. This vulnerability could enable attackers to, bypass front-end security controls, launch targeted attacks against active site users, and poison web caches. This problem has been patched in Eventlet 0.40.3 by dropping trailers which is a breaking change if a backend behind eventlet.wsgi proxy requires trailers. A workaround involves not using eventlet.wsgi facing untrusted clients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58157 | gnark affected by denial of service when computing scalar multiplication using fake-GLV algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58157</link><description>gnark is a zero-knowledge proof system framework. In version 0.12.0, there is a potential denial of service vulnerability when computing scalar multiplication is using the fake-GLV algorithm. This is because the algorithm didn't converge quickly enough for some of the inputs. This issue has been patched in version 0.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58067 | Basecamp&amp;#x27;s Google Sign-In for Rails allowed redirects to protocol-relative URI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58067</link><description>Basecamp's Google Sign-In adds Google sign-in to Rails applications. Prior to version 1.3.1, it is possible to redirect a user to another origin if the "proceed_to" value in the session store is set to a protocol-relative URL. Normally the value of this URL is only written and read by the library or the calling application. However, it may be possible to set this session value from a malicious site with a form submission. Any Rails applications using the google_sign_in gem may be vulnerable, if this vector can be chained with another attack that is able to modify the OAuth2 request parameters. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.1. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9676 | NCSOFT Universe App com.ncsoft.universeapp AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9676</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in NCSOFT Universe App up to 1.3.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.ncsoft.universeapp. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9677 | Modo Legend of the Phoenix com.duige.hzw.multilingual AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9677</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Modo Legend of the Phoenix up to 1.0.5. The affected element is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.duige.hzw.multilingual. The manipulation results in improper export of android application components. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58066 | DoS Vulnerability in ntpd-rs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58066</link><description>nptd-rs is a tool for synchronizing your computer's clock, implementing the NTP and NTS protocols. In versions between 1.2.0 and 1.6.1 inclusive servers which allow non-NTS traffic are affected by a denial of service vulnerability, where an attacker can induce a message storm between two NTP servers running ntpd-rs. Client-only configurations are not affected. Affected users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.6.2 as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9674 | Transbyte Scooper News App com.hatsune.eagleee AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9674</link><description>A flaw has been found in Transbyte Scooper News App up to 1.2 on Android. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.hatsune.eagleee. This manipulation causes improper export of android application components. The attack requires local access. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9675 | Voice Changer App com.tuyangkeji.changevoice AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9675</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Voice Changer App up to 1.1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.tuyangkeji.changevoice. Executing manipulation can lead to improper export of android application components. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9672 | Rejseplanen App de.hafas.android.rejseplanen AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9672</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Rejseplanen App up to 8.2.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component de.hafas.android.rejseplanen. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9673 | Kakao 헤이카카오 Hey Kakao App com.kakao.i.connect AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9673</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Kakao 헤이카카오 Hey Kakao App up to 2.17.4 on Android. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.kakao.i.connect. The manipulation results in improper export of android application components. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56577 | An issue in Evope Core v.1.1.3.20 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the use of hard coded cryptographic keys.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56577</link><description>An issue in Evope Core v.1.1.3.20 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the use of hard coded cryptographic keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9671 | UAB Paytend App com.passport.cash AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9671</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UAB Paytend App up to 2.1.9 on Android. This impacts an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.passport.cash. Executing manipulation can lead to improper export of android application components. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46484 | TRENDnet TV-IP410 vA1.0R was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the /server/cgi-bin/testserv.cgi component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46484</link><description>TRENDnet TV-IP410 vA1.0R was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the /server/cgi-bin/testserv.cgi component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9669 | Jinher OA GetTreeDate.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9669</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Jinher OA 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file GetTreeDate.aspx. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9670 | mixmark-io turndown commonmark-rules.js redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9670</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in mixmark-io turndown up to 7.2.1. This affects an unknown function of the file src/commonmark-rules.js. Performing manipulation results in inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43773 | Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.1, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.14, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43773</link><description>Liferay Portal  7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q2.0 through 2025.Q2.1, 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.14, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.0 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13 and 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.18 has a security vulnerability that allowing for improper access through the expandoTableLocalService.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41471 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in copyparty v.1.9.1 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the WEEKE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41471</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in copyparty v.1.9.1 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the WEEKEND-PLANS function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9667 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel delete_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9667</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /delete_account.php of the component Admin Panel. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9666 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel delete_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9666</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /delete_student.php of the component Admin Panel. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58158 | Harness Affected by Arbitrary File Write in Gitness LFS server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58158</link><description>Harness Open Source is an end-to-end developer platform with Source Control Management, CI/CD Pipelines, Hosted Developer Environments, and Artifact Registries. Prior to version 3.3.0, Open Source Harness git LFS server (Gitness) exposes api to retrieve and upload files via git LFS. Implementation of upload git LFS file api is vulnerable to arbitrary file write. Due to improper sanitization for upload path, a malicious authenticated user who has access to Harness Gitness server api can use a crafted upload request to write arbitrary file to any location on file system, may even compromise the server. Users using git LFS are vulnerable. This issue has been patched in version 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9377 | Authenticated RCE via Parental Control command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9377</link><description>The authenticated remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability exists  in the Parental Control page on TP-Link Archer C7(EU) V2 and TL-WR841N/ND(MS) V9.

This issue affects Archer C7(EU) V2: before 241108 and TL-WR841N/ND(MS) V9: before 241108.

Both products have reached the status of EOL (end-of-life).
It's recommending to 

purchase the new 
product to ensure better performance and security. If replacement is not
 an option in the short term, please use the second reference link to 
download and install the patch(es).</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9665 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel edit_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9665</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit_student.php of the component Admin Panel. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29882 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29882</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29886 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29886</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29887 | QuRouter 2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29887</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuRouter 2.5.1. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuRouter 2.5.1.060 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29888 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29888</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29889 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29889</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29890 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29890</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29893 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29893</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29894 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29894</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29898 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29898</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29899 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29899</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29900 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29900</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30260 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30260</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30261 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30261</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to prevent other systems, applications, or processes from accessing the same type of resource.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 5.0.0.0 ( 2025/06/13 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30262 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30262</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 5.0.0.0 ( 2025/06/13 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30263 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30263</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 5.0.0.0 ( 2025/06/13 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30264 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30264</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30265 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30265</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to modify memory or crash processes.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30267 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30267</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30268 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30268</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30270 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30270</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30271 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30271</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30272 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30272</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If  can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30273 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30273</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to modify or corrupt memory.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30274 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30274</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If  can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30275 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30275</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30277 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30277</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30278 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30278</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33032 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33032</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QTS 5.2.5.3145 build 20250526 and later
QuTS hero h5.2.5.3138 build 20250519 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33033 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33033</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33036 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33036</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33037 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33037</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33038 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33038</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Qsync Central 4.5.0.7 ( 2025/04/23 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44015 | HybridDesk Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44015</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect HybridDesk Station. If an attacker gains local network access, they can then exploit the vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
HybridDesk Station 4.2.18 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44033 | SQL injection vulnerability in oa_system oasys v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the allDirector() method declara...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44033</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in oa_system oasys v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the allDirector() method declaration in src/main/java/cn/gson/oasys/mappers/AddressMapper.java</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52856 | VioStor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52856</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect VioStor. If a remote attacker, they can then exploit the vulnerability to compromise the security of the system.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
VioStor 5.1.6 build 20250621 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52861 | VioStor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52861</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect VioStor. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to read the contents of unexpected files or system data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
VioStor 5.1.6 build 20250621 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29874 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29874</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29875 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29875</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29878 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29878</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29879 | File Station 5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29879</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect File Station 5. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
File Station 5 5.5.6.4907 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12923 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12923</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If a remote attacker gains a user account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.5 ( 2025/01/02 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22483 | License Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22483</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If a remote attacker gains an administrator account, they can then exploit the vulnerability to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
License Center 1.8.51 and later
License Center 1.9.51 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9663 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel edit_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9663</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /edit_account.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9664 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel add_student_grade.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9664</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /add_student_grade.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument Add results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55763 | Buffer Overflow in the URI parser of CivetWeb 1.14 through 1.16 (latest) allows a remote attacker to achieve remote code execution via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55763</link><description>Buffer Overflow in the URI parser of CivetWeb 1.14 through 1.16 (latest) allows a remote attacker to achieve remote code execution via a crafted HTTP request. This vulnerability is triggered during request processing and may allow an attacker to corrupt heap memory, potentially leading to denial of service or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55579 | SolidInvoice 2.3.7 and fixed in v.2.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Tax Rate functionality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55579</link><description>SolidInvoice 2.3.7 and fixed in v.2.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Tax Rate functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55580 | SolidInvoice 2.3.7 and v.2.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the client's functionality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55580</link><description>SolidInvoice 2.3.7 and v.2.3.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the client's functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9660 | SourceCodester Bakeshop Online Ordering System passwordrecover.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9660</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Bakeshop Online Ordering System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /passwordrecover.php. Performing manipulation of the argument phonenumber results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9662 | code-projects Simple Grading System Admin Panel login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9662</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple Grading System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /login.php of the component Admin Panel. Executing manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9658 | O2OA Personal Profile dict cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9658</link><description>A flaw has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /x_portal_assemble_designer/jaxrs/dict/ of the component Personal Profile Page. This manipulation of the argument name/alias/description causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9659 | O2OA Personal Profile widget cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9659</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in O2OA up to 10.0-410. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /x_portal_assemble_designer/jaxrs/widget of the component Personal Profile Page. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46916 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite through 4.3.0 SR06 contains functionality that allows the removal of critical system files before the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46916</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite through 4.3.0 SR06 contains functionality that allows the removal of critical system files before the filesystem is properly mounted (e.g., leveraging a delete call in /etc/rc.d/init.d/mountfs to remove the /etc/fstab file). This can allow code execution and, in some versions, enable recovery of TPM Disk Encryption keys and decryption of the Windows system partition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46917 | Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite through 4.3.0 SR01 does not validate file attributes or the contents of /root during integrity valida...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46917</link><description>Diebold Nixdorf Vynamic Security Suite through 4.3.0 SR01 does not validate file attributes or the contents of /root during integrity validation. This allows code execution, recovery of TPM Disk Encryption keys, decryption of the Windows system partition, and full control of the Windows OS, e.g., through ~/.profile changes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47909 | Improper validation of TrustedOrigins allows CSRF attacks in github.com/gorilla/csrf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47909</link><description>Hosts listed in TrustedOrigins implicitly allow requests from the corresponding HTTP origins, allowing network MitMs to perform CSRF attacks. After the CVE-2025-24358 fix, a network attacker that places a form at http://example.com can't get it to submit to https://example.com because the Origin header is checked with sameOrigin against a synthetic URL. However, if a host is added to TrustedOrigins, both its HTTP and HTTPS origins will be allowed, because the schema of the synthetic URL is ignored and only the host is checked. For example, if an application is hosted on https://example.com and adds example.net to TrustedOrigins, a network attacker can serve a form at http://example.net to perform the attack. Applications should migrate to net/http.CrossOriginProtection, introduced in Go 1.25. If that is not an option, a backport is available as a module at filippo.io/csrf, and a drop-in replacement for the github.com/gorilla/csrf API is available at filippo.io/csrf/gorilla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55750 | Gitpod Classic Affected by Bitbucket OAuth Token Exposure via Redirect Fragment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55750</link><description>Gitpod is a developer platform for cloud development environments. In versions before main-gha.33628 for both Gitpod Classic and Gitpod Classic Enterprise, OAuth integration with Bitbucket in certain conditions allowed a crafted link to expose a valid Bitbucket access token via the URL fragment when clicked by an authenticated user. This resulted from how Bitbucket returned tokens and how Gitpod handled the redirect flow. The issue was limited to Bitbucket (GitHub and GitLab integrations were not affected), required user interaction, and has been mitigated through redirect handling and OAuth logic hardening. The issue was resolved in main-gha.33628 and later. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55177 | Incomplete authorization of linked device synchronization messages in WhatsApp for iOS prior to v2.25.21.73, WhatsApp Business for iOS v2.25...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55177</link><description>Incomplete authorization of linked device synchronization messages in WhatsApp for iOS prior to v2.25.21.73, WhatsApp Business for iOS v2.25.21.78, and WhatsApp for Mac v2.25.21.78 could have allowed an unrelated user to trigger processing of content from an arbitrary URL on a target’s device. We assess that this vulnerability, in combination with an OS-level vulnerability on Apple platforms (CVE-2025-43300), may have been exploited in a sophisticated attack against specific targeted users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55202 | Opencast has a partial path traversal vulnerability in UI config</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55202</link><description>Opencast is a free, open-source platform to support the management of educational audio and video content. In version 18.0 and versions before 17.7, the protections against path traversal attacks in the UI config module are insufficient, still partially allowing for attacks in very specific cases. The path is checked without checking for the file separator. This could allow attackers access to files within another folder which starts with the same path. This issue has been fixed in versions 17.7 and 18.1. To mitigate this issue, check for folders that start with the same path as the ui-config folder.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5808 | Authentication Bypass vulnerability discovered in the OpenText™ Self-Service Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5808</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in OpenText Self Service Password Reset allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Self Service Password Reset from before 4.8 patch 3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9656 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System add-directory.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9656</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-directory.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9657 | O2OA Personal Profile script cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9657</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /x_program_center/jaxrs/script of the component Personal Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument name/alias/description results in cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54877 | Tuleap&amp;#x27;s special and always there fields permissions are not verified in cross-tracker search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54877</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite created to facilitate management of software development and collaboration. In Tuleap Community Edition versions before 16.10.99.1754050155 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition versions before 16.9-8 and before 16.10-5, an attacker can access to the content of the special and always there fields of accessible artifacts even if the permissions associated with the underlying fields do not allow it. This issue has been fixed in Tuleap Community Edition version 16.10.99.1754050155 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition versions 16.9-8 and 16.10-5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55304 | Exiv2 has quadratic performance in ICC profile parsing in JpegBase::readMetadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55304</link><description>Exiv2 is a C++ library and a command-line utility to read, write, delete and modify Exif, IPTC, XMP and ICC image metadata. A denial-of-service was found in Exiv2 version 0.28.5: a quadratic algorithm in the ICC profile parsing code in jpegBase::readMetadata() can cause Exiv2 to run for a long time. The denial-of-service is triggered when Exiv2 is used to read the metadata of a crafted jpg image file. The bug is fixed in version 0.28.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9654 | AiondaDotCom mcp-ssh server-simple.mjs command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9654</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in AiondaDotCom mcp-ssh up to 1.0.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file server-simple.mjs. Performing manipulation results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.4 and 1.1.0 can resolve this issue. The patch is named cd2566a948b696501abfa6c6b03462cac5fb43d8. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9655 | O2OA Personal Profile person cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9655</link><description>A weakness has been identified in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This affects an unknown part of the file /x_organization_assemble_control/jaxrs/person/ of the component Personal Profile Page. Executing manipulation of the argument Description can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54080 | Exiv2 Segmentation Faults in Exiv2::EpsImage::writeMetadata() via crafted EPS file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54080</link><description>Exiv2 is a C++ library and a command-line utility to read, write, delete and modify Exif, IPTC, XMP and ICC image metadata. An out-of-bounds read was found in Exiv2 versions 0.28.5 and earlier. The out-of-bounds read is triggered when Exiv2 is used to write metadata into a crafted image file. An attacker could potentially exploit the vulnerability to cause a denial of service by crashing Exiv2, if they can trick the victim into running Exiv2 on a crafted image file. Note that this bug is only triggered when writing the metadata, which is a less frequently used Exiv2 operation than reading the metadata. The bug is fixed in version 0.28.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9652 | Portabilis i-Educar Cadastrar tipo de transferência educar_transferencia_tipo_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9652</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_transferencia_tipo_cad.php of the component Cadastrar tipo de transferência Page. This manipulation of the argument nm_tipo/desc_tipo causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9653 | Portabilis i-Educar Cadastrar projeto educar_projeto_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9653</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /intranet/educar_projeto_cad.php of the component Cadastrar projeto Page. Such manipulation of the argument nome/observacao leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9650 | yeqifu carRental AppFileUtils.java removeFileByPath path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9650</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yeqifu carRental up to 3fabb7eae93d209426638863980301d6f99866b3. This affects the function removeFileByPath of the file src/main/java/com/yeqifu/sys/utils/AppFileUtils.java. The manipulation of the argument carimg leads to path traversal. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9651 | shafhasan chatbox chat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in shafhasan chatbox up to 156a39cde62f78532c3265a70eda12c70907e56f. This impacts an unknown function of the file /chat.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9649 | appneta tcpreplay send_packets.c calc_sleep_time divide by zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9649</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in appneta tcpreplay 4.5.1. Impacted is the function calc_sleep_time of the file send_packets.c. Such manipulation leads to divide by zero. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.5.3-beta3 is recommended to address this issue. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component. The vendor confirms in a GitHub issue reply: "Was able to reproduce in 6fcbf03 but NOT 4.5.3-beta3."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9646 | O2OA calendarConfig cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9646</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in O2OA up to 10.0-410. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /x_organization_assemble_personal/jaxrs/definition/calendarConfig. The manipulation of the argument toMonthViewName results in cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor replied in the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "This issue will be fixed in the new version."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9647 | mtons mblog list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9647</link><description>A weakness has been identified in mtons mblog up to 3.5.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/role/list. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9644 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System bill_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9644</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /setting/bill_setup.php. Executing manipulation of the argument txtBillType can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9645 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System r_all_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9645</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /t_dashboard/r_all_info.php. The manipulation of the argument mid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:04:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9643 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System utility_bill_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9643</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setting/utility_bill_setup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument txtGasBill results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40708 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40708</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/event" petition, "name" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40709 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40709</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/person/” petition, "name" and "alias-0” parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40702 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40702</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/file" petition, "creator" and "license_holder" parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40703 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40703</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/group" petition, "name" and "alias-0” parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40704 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40704</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/edition" petition, "name" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40705 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40705</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/acquisition" petition, "name" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40706 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40706</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/source" petition, "name" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40707 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas by ACDH-CH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40707</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in OpenAtlas v8.9.0 from the Austrian Centre for Digital Humanities and Cultural Heritage (ACDH-CH), due to inadequate validation of user input when a POST request is sent. The vulnerabilities could allow a remote user to send specially crafted queries to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie details, via  the "/insert/place" petition, "name" and "alias-0” parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 11:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13342 | Booster for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.2.4 - Unauthenticated Double Extension Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13342</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'add_files_to_order' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files with double extensions on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This is only exploitable on select instances where the configuration will execute the first extension present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9217 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt;= 6.7.36 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read via &amp;#x27;used_svg&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;used_images&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9217</link><description>The Slider Revolution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.36 via the 'used_svg' and 'used_images' parameters. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4643 | Lack of JWT Expiration after Log Out in PayloadCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4643</link><description>Payload uses JSON Web Tokens (JWT) for authentication. After log out JWT is not invalidated, which allows an attacker who has stolen or intercepted token to freely reuse it until expiration date (which is by default set to 2 hours, but can be changed). 

This issue has been fixed in version 3.44.0 of Payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4644 | User Session Fixation after Account Removal in PayloadCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4644</link><description>A Session Fixation vulnerability existed in Payload's SQLite adapter due to identifier reuse during account creation. A malicious attacker could create a new account, save its JSON Web Token (JWT), and then delete the account, which did not invalidate the JWT. As a result, the next newly created user would receive the same identifier, allowing the attacker to reuse the JWT to authenticate and perform actions as that user.

This issue has been fixed in version 3.44.0 of Payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7071 | Timing side-channel vulnerability in AES-CBC decryption with PKCS#7 padding in ocrypto library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7071</link><description>Padding oracle attack vulnerability in Oberon microsystem AG’s ocrypto library in all versions since 3.1.0 and prior to 3.9.2 allows an attacker to recover plaintexts via timing measurements of AES-CBC PKCS#7 decrypt operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7383 | Timing side-channel vulnerability in AES-CBC decryption with PKCS#7 padding in Oberon PSA Crypto library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7383</link><description>Padding oracle attack vulnerability in Oberon microsystem AG’s Oberon PSA Crypto library in all versions since 1.0.0 and prior to 1.5.1 allows an attacker to recover plaintexts via timing measurements of AES-CBC PKCS#7 decrypt operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9071 | Insecure RSA-OAEP implementation with all-zero seed for padding in Oberon PSA Crypto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9071</link><description>Erroneously using an all-zero seed for RSA-OEAP padding instead of the generated random bytes, in Oberon microsystems AG’s Oberon PSA Crypto library in all versions up to 1.5.1, results in deterministic RSA and thus in a loss of confidentiality for guessable messages, recognition of repeated messages, and loss of security proofs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8150 | Events Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Typewriter and Countdown Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8150</link><description>The Events Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Typewriter and Countdown widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13987 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Synology RADIUS Server before 3.0.27-0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13987</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Synology RADIUS Server before 3.0.27-0139 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to read or write limited files in SRM and conduct limited denial-of-service via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54777 | Uncaught exception issue exists in Multiple products in bizhub series. If a malformed file is imported as an S/MIME Email certificate, it ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54777</link><description>Uncaught exception issue exists in Multiple products in bizhub series. If a malformed file is imported as an S/MIME Email certificate, it may cause a denial-of-service issue that disable the Web Connection feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8147 | LWSCache &amp;lt;= 2.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Activation via lwscache_activatePlugin Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8147</link><description>The LWSCache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to improper authorization on the lwscache_activatePlugin() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate arbitrary whitelisted LWS plugins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8290 | List Subpages &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8290</link><description>The List Subpages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8619 | OSM Map Widget for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8619</link><description>The OSM Map Widget for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Map Block URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9374 | Ultimate Tag Warrior Importer &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9374</link><description>The Ultimate Tag Warrior Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import tags granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9441 | iATS Online Forms &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9441</link><description>The iATS Online Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53507 | Multiple products provided by iND Co.,Ltd contain an insecure storage of sensitive information vulnerability. If exploited, configuration in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53507</link><description>Multiple products provided by iND Co.,Ltd contain an insecure storage of sensitive information vulnerability. If exploited, configuration information, such as admin password, may be disclosed. As for the details of affected product names and versions, refer to the information under [Product Status].</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53508 | Multiple products provided by iND Co.,Ltd contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53508</link><description>Multiple products provided by iND Co.,Ltd contain an OS command injection vulnerability. If exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed and sensitive information may be obtained. As for the details of affected product names and versions, refer to the information under [Product Status].</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9619 | E4 Sistemas Mercatus ERP id resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9619</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in E4 Sistemas Mercatus ERP 2.00.019. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /basico/webservice/imprimir-danfe/id/. Performing manipulation results in improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8857 | Changing｜Clinic Image System - Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8857</link><description>Clinic Image System developed by Changing contains hard-coded Credentials, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log into the system using administrator credentials embedded in the source code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8858 | Changing｜Clinic Image System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8858</link><description>Clinic Image System developed by Changing has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8861 | Changing｜TSA - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8861</link><description>TSA developed by Changing has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9609 | Portabilis i-Educar consulta improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9609</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /educacenso/consulta. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9610 | code-projects Online Event Judging System create_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9610</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Event Judging System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /create_account.php. This manipulation of the argument fname causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9639 | Ai3｜QbiCRMGateway - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9639</link><description>The QbiCRMGateway developed by Ai3 has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9607 | Portabilis i-Educar Tabelas de Arredondamento view sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9607</link><description>A flaw has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /module/TabelaArredondamento/view of the component Tabelas de Arredondamento Page. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9608 | Portabilis i-Educar Formula de Cálculo de Média view sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9608</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/FormulaMedia/view of the component Formula de Cálculo de Média Page. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9606 | Portabilis i-Educar agenda_preferencias.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9606</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /intranet/agenda_preferencias.php. Performing manipulation of the argument cod_agenda results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39245 | There is a CSV Injection Vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. This could allow an attacker to inject executable commands v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39245</link><description>There is a CSV Injection Vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. This could allow an attacker to inject executable commands via malicious CSV data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39246 | There is an Unquoted Service Path Vulnerability in some HikCentral FocSign versions. This could allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39246</link><description>There is an Unquoted Service Path Vulnerability in some HikCentral FocSign versions. This could allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39247 | There is an Access Control Vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain the ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39247</link><description>There is an Access Control Vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain the admin permission.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58323 | NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58323</link><description>NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitrary files due to improper privilege checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9605 | Tenda AC21/AC23 GetParentControlInfo stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9605</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC21 and AC23 16.03.08.16. Affected is the function GetParentControlInfo of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9601 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System employee_salary_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9601</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /setting/employee_salary_setup.php. The manipulation of the argument ddlEmpName results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9602 | Xinhu RockOA index.php publicsaveAjax improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9602</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Xinhu RockOA up to 2.6.9. Impacted is the function publicsaveAjax of the file /index.php. Performing manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9603 | Telesquare TLR-2005KSH internet.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9603</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Telesquare TLR-2005KSH 1.2.4. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/internet.cgi?Command=lanCfg. Executing manipulation of the argument Hostname can lead to command injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9604 | coze-studio aes.go hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9604</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in coze-studio up to 0.2.4. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file backend/domain/plugin/encrypt/aes.go. The manipulation of the argument AuthSecretKey/StateSecretKey/OAuthTokenSecretKey leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch. The vendor replied to the GitHub issue (translated from simplified Chinese): "For scenarios requiring encryption, we will implement user-defined key management through configuration and optimize the use of encryption tools, such as random salt."</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54142 | Akamai Ghost before 2025-07-21 allows HTTP Request Smuggling via an OPTIONS request that has an entity body, because there can be a subseque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54142</link><description>Akamai Ghost before 2025-07-21 allows HTTP Request Smuggling via an OPTIONS request that has an entity body, because there can be a subsequent request within the persistent connection between an Akamai proxy server and an origin server, if the origin server violates certain Internet standards.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44271 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to record the screen without an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44271</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. An app may be able to record the screen without an indicator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54554 | This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54554</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved handling of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54568 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54568</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.2. Parsing a maliciously crafted file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40927 | CGI::Simple versions 1.281 and earlier for Perl has a HTTP response splitting flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40927</link><description>CGI::Simple versions before 1.282 for Perl has a HTTP response splitting flaw
This vulnerability is a confirmed HTTP response splitting flaw in CGI::Simple that allows HTTP response header injection, which can be used for reflected XSS or open redirect under certain conditions.

Although some validation exists, it can be bypassed using URL-encoded values, allowing an attacker to inject untrusted content into the response via query parameters.



As a result, an attacker can inject a line break (e.g. %0A) into the parameter value, causing the server to split the HTTP response and inject arbitrary headers or even an HTML/JavaScript body, leading to reflected cross-site scripting (XSS), open redirect or other attacks.

The issue documented in CVE-2010-4410 https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-4410 is related but the fix was incomplete.

Impact

By injecting %0A (newline) into a query string parameter, an attacker can:

  *  Break the current HTTP header
  *  Inject a new header or entire body
  *  Deliver a script payload that is reflected in the server’s response
That can lead to the following attacks:

  *  reflected XSS
  *  open redirect
  *  cache poisoning
  *  header manipulation</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43187 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43187</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6. Running an hdiutil command may unexpectedly execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43255 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Ven...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43255</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43268 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A malicious app may be able to ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43268</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43284 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43284</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9599 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System month_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9599</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setting/month_setup.php. Executing manipulation of the argument txtMonthName can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9600 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System member_type_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9600</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /setting/member_type_setup.php. The manipulation of the argument txtMemberType leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9597 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System rented_all_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9597</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /o_dashboard/rented_all_info.php. Such manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9598 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System year_setup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9598</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /setting/year_setup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument txtXYear results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9595 | code-projects Student Information Management System login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9595</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Information Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uname results in cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9596 | itsourcecode Sports Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9596</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode Sports Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /login.php. This manipulation of the argument User causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48979 | An Improper Input Validation in UISP Application could allow a Command Injection by a malicious actor with High Privileges and local access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48979</link><description>An Improper Input Validation in UISP Application could allow a Command Injection by a malicious actor with High Privileges and local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9594 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System complain_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9594</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /report/complain_info.php. The manipulation of the argument vid leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9593 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System unit_status_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9593</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /report/unit_status_info.php. Executing manipulation of the argument usid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58062 | LSTM-Kirigaya&amp;#x27;s openmcp-client Vulnerable to RCE in MCP Authorization Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58062</link><description>LSTM-Kirigaya's openmcp-client is a vscode plugin for mcp developer. Prior to version 0.1.12, when users on a Windows platform connect to an attacker controlled MCP server, attackers could provision a malicious authorization server endpoint to silently achieve an OS command injection attack in the open() invocation, leading to client system compromise. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58061 | OpenEBS Local PV RawFile persistent volume data is world readable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58061</link><description>OpenEBS Local PV RawFile allows dynamic deployment of Stateful Persistent Node-Local Volumes &amp; Filesystems for Kubernetes. Prior to version 0.10.0, persistent volume data is world readable and that would allow non-privileged users to access sensitive data such as databases of k8s workload. The rawfile-localpv storage class creates persistent volume data under /var/csi/rawfile/ on Kubernetes hosts by default. However, the directory and data in it are world-readable. It allows non-privileged users to access the whole persistent volume data, and those can include sensitive information such as a whole database if the Kubernetes tenants are running MySQL or PostgreSQL in a container so it could lead to a database breach. This issue has been patched in version 0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9591 | ZrLog Theme Configuration Form config cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9591</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ZrLog up to 3.1.5. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/admin/template/config of the component Theme Configuration Form. Such manipulation of the argument footerLink leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9592 | itsourcecode Apartment Management System bill_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9592</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in itsourcecode Apartment Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /report/bill_info.php. Performing manipulation of the argument vid results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58058 | github.com/ulikunitz/xz leaks memory when decoding a corrupted multiple LZMA archives</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58058</link><description>xz is a pure golang package for reading and writing xz-compressed files. Prior to version 0.5.14, it is possible to put data in front of an LZMA-encoded byte stream without detecting the situation while reading the header. This can lead to increased memory consumption because the current implementation allocates the full decoding buffer directly after reading the header. The LZMA header doesn't include a magic number or has a checksum to detect such an issue according to the specification. Note that the code recognizes the issue later while reading the stream, but at this time the memory allocation has already been done. This issue has been patched in version 0.5.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9589 | Cudy WR1200EA shadow default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9589</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Cudy WR1200EA 2.3.7-20250113-121810. Affected is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow. Executing manipulation can lead to use of default password. The attack needs to be launched locally. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9590 | Weaver E-Mobile Mobile Management Platform cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9590</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Weaver E-Mobile Mobile Management Platform up to 20250813. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument gohome leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9586 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt wireless_device_dissoc command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9586</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. This vulnerability affects the function wireless_device_dissoc of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9585 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt wifilith_delete_pic_file command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9585</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. This affects the function wifilith_delete_pic_file of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. This manipulation of the argument portal_delete_picname causes command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9583 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt ping_config command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9583</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ping_config of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. The manipulation leads to command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9584 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt update_interface_png command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9584</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected by this issue is the function update_interface_png of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. The manipulation of the argument interface/display_name results in command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6203 | Vault unauthenticated denial of service through complex json payload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6203</link><description>A malicious user may submit a specially-crafted complex payload that otherwise meets the default request size limit which results in excessive memory and CPU consumption of Vault. This may lead to a timeout in Vault’s auditing subroutine, potentially resulting in the Vault server to become unresponsive. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-6203, is fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.3 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.3, 1.19.9, 1.18.14, and 1.16.25.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9582 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt ntp_timezone command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9582</link><description>A flaw has been found in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. Affected is the function ntp_timezone of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. Executing manipulation of the argument timestr can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9580 | LB-LINK BL-X26 HTTP set_blacklist os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9580</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LB-LINK BL-X26 1.2.8. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_blacklist of the component HTTP Handler. Such manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9581 | Comfast CF-N1 webmgnt multi_pppoe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9581</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Comfast CF-N1 2.6.0. This impacts the function multi_pppoe of the file /usr/bin/webmgnt. Performing manipulation of the argument phy_interface results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57215 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57215</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function get_parentControl_list_Info.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57220 | An input validation flaw in the 'ate' service of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 to escalate privileges to root via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57220</link><description>An input validation flaw in the 'ate' service of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 to escalate privileges to root via a crafted UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57219 | Incorrect access control in the endpoint /goform/ate of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 allows attackers to escalate privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57219</link><description>Incorrect access control in the endpoint /goform/ate of Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 allows attackers to escalate privileges or access sensitive components via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9577 | TOTOLINK X2000R Administrative shadow.sample default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9577</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in TOTOLINK X2000R up to 2.0.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow.sample of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation results in use of default credentials. Attacking locally is a requirement. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9579 | LB-LINK BL-X26 HTTP set_hidessid_cfg os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9579</link><description>A weakness has been identified in LB-LINK BL-X26 1.2.8. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_hidessid_cfg of the component HTTP Handler. This manipulation of the argument enable causes os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31971 | AIML Solutions for HCL SX is susceptible to a URL validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31971</link><description>AIML Solutions for HCL SX is vulnerable to a URL validation vulnerability.  The issue may allow attackers to launch a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack enabling unauthorized network calls from the system, potentially exposing internal services or sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9195 | Improper input validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local access to cause a Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9195</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with local access to cause a Denial of Service</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9575 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 upload.cgi cgiMain os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9575</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 1.0.013.001/1.0.04.001/1.0.04.002/1.1.05.003/1.2.07.001. This issue affects the function cgiMain of the file /cgi-bin/upload.cgi. Executing manipulation of the argument filename can lead to os command injection. The attack may be performed from a remote location. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9576 | seeedstudio ReSpeaker Administrative shadow default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9576</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in seeedstudio ReSpeaker LinkIt7688. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow of the component Administrative Interface. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. An attack has to be approached locally. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58059 | Valtimo scripting engine can be used to gain access to sensitive data or resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58059</link><description>Valtimo is a platform for Business Process Automation. In versions before 12.16.0.RELEASE, and from 13.0.0.RELEASE to before 13.1.2.RELEASE, any admin that can create or modify and execute process-definitions could gain access to sensitive data or resources. This includes but is not limited to: running executables on the application host, inspecting and extracting data from the host environment or application properties, spring beans (application context, database pooling). The following conditions have to be met in order to perform this attack: the user must be logged in, have the admin role, and must have some knowledge about running scripts via a the Camunda/Operator engine. Version 12.16.0 and 13.1.2 have been patched. It is strongly advised to upgrade. If no scripting is needed in any of the processes, it could be possible to disable it altogether via the ProcessEngineConfiguration. However, this workaround could lead to unexpected side-effects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58049 | XWiki PDF export jobs store sensitive cookies unencrypted in job statuses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58049</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions from 14.4.2 to before 16.4.8, 16.5.0-rc-1 to before 16.10.7, and 17.0.0-rc-1 to before 17.4.0-rc-1, the PDF export jobs store sensitive cookies unencrypted in job statuses. XWiki shouldn't store passwords in plain text, and it shouldn't be possible to gain access to plain text passwords by gaining access to, e.g., a backup of the data directory. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 16.4.8, 16.10.7, and 17.4.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57218 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the security_5g parameter in the function s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57218</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the security_5g parameter in the function sub_46284C.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58048 | Paymenter Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Public File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58048</link><description>Paymenter is a free and open-source webshop solution for hostings. Prior to version 1.2.11, the ticket attachments functionality in Paymenter allows a malicious authenticated user to upload arbitrary files. This could result in sensitive data extraction from the database, credentials being read from configuration files, and arbitrary system commands being run under the web server user context. This vulnerability was patched by commit 87c3db4 and was released under the version 1.2.11 tag without any other code modifications compared to version 1.2.10. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators can mitigate this vulnerability with one or more of the following measures: updating nginx config to download attachments instead of executing them or disallowing access to /storage/ fully using a WAF such as Cloudflare.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57217 | Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Password parameter in the function R7We...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57217</link><description>Tenda AC10 v4.0 firmware v16.03.10.09_multi_TDE01 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the Password parameter in the function R7WebsSecurityHandler.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58047 | Volto affected by possible DoS by invoking specific URL by anonymous user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58047</link><description>Volto is a React based frontend for the Plone Content Management System. In versions from 19.0.0-alpha.1 to before 19.0.0-alpha.4, 18.0.0 to before 18.24.0, 17.0.0 to before 17.22.1, and prior to 16.34.0, an anonymous user could cause the NodeJS server part of Volto to quit with an error when visiting a specific URL. The problem has been patched in versions 16.34.0, 17.22.1, 18.24.0, and 19.0.0-alpha.4. To mitigate downtime, have setup automatically restart processes that quit with an error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31977 | A cryptographic weakness has been identified in the HCL BigFix Service Management (SM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31977</link><description>HCL BigFix SM is affected by cryptographic weakness due to weak or outdated encryption algorithms.  An attacker with network access could exploit this weakness to decrypt or manipulate encrypted communications under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31979 | A File Upload Validation Bypass vulnerability has been identified in the HCL BigFix Service Management (SM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31979</link><description>A File Upload Validation Bypass vulnerability has been identified in the HCL BigFix SM, where the application fails to properly enforce file type restrictions during the upload process. An attacker may exploit this flaw to upload malicious or unauthorized files, such as scripts, executables, or web shells, by bypassing client-side or server-side validation mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31972 | HCL BigFix Service Management (SM) is affected by a Sensitive Information Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31972</link><description>HCL BigFix SM is affected by a Sensitive Information Exposure vulnerability where internal connections do not use TLS encryption which could allow an attacker unauthorized access to sensitive data transmitted between internal components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58334 | In JetBrains IDE Services before 2025.5.0.1086, 
2025.4.2.2164 users without appropriate permissions could assign high-privileged role for t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58334</link><description>In JetBrains IDE Services before 2025.5.0.1086, 
2025.4.2.2164 users without appropriate permissions could assign high-privileged role for themselves</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58335 | In JetBrains Junie before 252.284.66,
251.284.66,
243.284.66,
252.284.61,
251.284.61,
243.284.61,
252.284.50,
252.284.54,
251.284.54,
251.28...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58335</link><description>In JetBrains Junie before 252.284.66,
251.284.66,
243.284.66,
252.284.61,
251.284.61,
243.284.61,
252.284.50,
252.284.54,
251.284.54,
251.284.50,
243.284.54,
243.284.50 information disclosure was possible via search_project function</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57819 | FreePBX Affected by Authentication Bypass Leading to SQL Injection and RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57819</link><description>FreePBX is an open-source web-based graphical user interface. FreePBX 15, 16, and 17 endpoints are vulnerable due to insufficiently sanitized user-supplied data allowing unauthenticated access to FreePBX Administrator leading to arbitrary database manipulation and remote code execution. This issue has been patched in endpoint versions 15.0.66, 16.0.89, and 17.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57756 | Contao discloses sensitive information in the front end search index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57756</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 4.9.14 and prior to 4.13.56, 5.3.38, and 5.6.1, protected content elements that are rendered as fragments are indexed and become publicly available in the front end search. This issue has been patched in versions 4.13.56, 5.3.38, and 5.6.1. A workaround involves disabling the front end search.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57757 | Contao discloses information in the news module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57757</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.0.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, if a news feed contains protected news archives, their news items are not filtered and become publicly available in the RSS feed. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. A workaround involves not adding protected news archives to the news feed page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57758 | Contao has improper access control in the back end voters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57758</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.0.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, the table access voter in the back end doesn't check if a user is allowed to access the corresponding module. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. A workaround involves not relying solely on the voter and additionally to check USER_CAN_ACCESS_MODULE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57759 | Contao has improper privilege management for page and article fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57759</link><description>Contao is an Open Source CMS. In versions starting from 5.3.0 and prior to 5.3.38 and 5.6.1, under certain conditions, back end users may be able to edit fields of pages and articles without having the necessary permissions. This issue has been patched in versions 5.3.38 and 5.6.1. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51643 | Meitrack T366G-L GPS Tracker devices contain an SPI flash chip (Winbond 25Q64JVSIQ) that is accessible without authentication or tamper prot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51643</link><description>Meitrack T366G-L GPS Tracker devices contain an SPI flash chip (Winbond 25Q64JVSIQ) that is accessible without authentication or tamper protection. An attacker with physical access to the device can use a standard SPI programmer to extract the firmware using flashrom. This results in exposure of sensitive configuration data such as APN credentials, backend server information, and network parameter</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13986 | Nagios XI Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload Path Traversal RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13986</link><description>Nagios XI &lt; 2024R1.3.2 contains a remote code execution vulnerability by chaining two flaws: an arbitrary file upload and a path traversal in the Core Config Snapshots interface. The issue arises from insufficient validation of file paths and extensions during MIB upload and snapshot rename operations. Exploitation results in the placement of attacker-controlled PHP files in a web-accessible directory, executed as the www-data user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25010 | Kibana privilege escalation via reporting_user role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25010</link><description>Incorrect authorization in Kibana can lead to privilege escalation via the built-in reporting_user role which incorrectly has the ability to access all Kibana Spaces.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57767 | Asterisk can crash from a specifically malformed Authorization header in an incoming SIP request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57767</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 20.15.2, 21.10.2, and 22.5.2, if a SIP request is received with an Authorization header that contains a realm that wasn't in a previous 401 response's WWW-Authenticate header, or an Authorization header with an incorrect realm was received without a previous 401 response being sent, the get_authorization_header() function in res_pjsip_authenticator_digest will return a NULL. This wasn't being checked before attempting to get the digest algorithm from the header which causes a SEGV. This issue has been patched in versions 20.15.2, 21.10.2, and 22.5.2. There are no workarounds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29364 | spimsimulator spim v9.1.24 and before is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the READ_SYSCALL and WRITE_SYSCALL system calls. The application v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29364</link><description>spimsimulator spim v9.1.24 and before is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the READ_SYSCALL and WRITE_SYSCALL system calls. The application verifies the legitimacy of the starting and ending addresses for memory read/write operations. By configuring the starting and ending addresses for memory read/write to point to distinct memory segments within the virtual machine, it is possible to circumvent these checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54995 | Asterisk remotely exploitable leak of RTP UDP ports and internal resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54995</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. Prior to versions 18.26.4 and 18.9-cert17, RTP UDP ports and internal resources can leak due to a lack of session termination. This could result in leaks and resource exhaustion. This issue has been patched in versions 18.26.4 and 18.9-cert17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56236 | FormCms v0.5.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. Authenticated users can upload .html...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56236</link><description>FormCms v0.5.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the avatar upload feature. Authenticated users can upload .html files containing malicious JavaScript, which are accessible via a public URL. When a privileged user accesses the file, the script executes in their browser context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48908 | lychee-action vulnerable to arbitrary code injection in composite action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48908</link><description>lychee link checking action checks links in Markdown, HTML, and text files using lychee. Prior to version 2.0.2, there is a potential attack of arbitrary code injection vulnerability in lychee-setup of the composite action at action.yml. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8067 | Udisks: out-of-bounds read in udisks daemon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8067</link><description>A flaw was found in the Udisks daemon, where it allows unprivileged users to create loop devices using the D-BUS system. This is achieved via the loop device handler, which handles requests sent through the D-BUS interface. As two of the parameters of this handle, it receives the file descriptor list and index specifying the file where the loop device should be backed. The function itself validates the index value to ensure it isn't bigger than the maximum value allowed. However, it fails to validate the lower bound, allowing the index parameter to be a negative value. Under these circumstances, an attacker can cause the UDisks daemon to crash or perform a local privilege escalation by gaining access to files owned by privileged users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52054 | An issue was discovered in Tenda AC8 v4.0 AC1200 Dual-band Gigabit Wireless Router AC8v4.0 Firmware 16.03.33.05. The root password of the de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52054</link><description>An issue was discovered in Tenda AC8 v4.0 AC1200 Dual-band Gigabit Wireless Router AC8v4.0 Firmware 16.03.33.05. The root password of the device is calculated with a static string and the last two octets of the MAC address of the device. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to authenticate with network services on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55583 | D-Link DIR-868L B1 router firmware version FW2.05WWB02 contains an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability in the fileaccess.cgi ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55583</link><description>D-Link DIR-868L B1 router firmware version FW2.05WWB02 contains an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability in the fileaccess.cgi component. The endpoint /dws/api/UploadFile accepts a pre_api_arg parameter that is passed directly to system-level shell execution functions without sanitization or authentication. Remote attackers can exploit this to execute arbitrary commands as root via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49790 | IBM Watson Studio on Cloud Pak for Data cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49790</link><description>IBM Watson Studio on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0 and 5.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9578 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9578</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 40734.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51971 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in register.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. Unsanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51971</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in register.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. Unsanitized user input in the f_name parameter is reflected in the server response without proper HTML encoding or output escaping. This allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51972 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper sanitization of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51972</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login.php of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in the keyword POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51967 | A Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the themeSet.php file of ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51967</link><description>A Reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the themeSet.php file of ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System 1.0. The application fails to sanitize user-supplied input in the theme POST parameter, allowing an attacker to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51968 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php file of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. The application fails to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51968</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php file of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. The application fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the proId POST parameter, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary SQL expressions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51969 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the product.php page of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. This flaw is present in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51969</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the product.php page of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0. This flaw is present in the product_id GET parameter, which is not properly validated before being included in a SQL statement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58123 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin BGP Monitoring on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58123</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin BGP Monitoring allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58124 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin check-mk-api on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58124</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin check-mk-api allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58125 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin Freebox v6 agent on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58125</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin Freebox v6 agent allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58126 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin VMware vSAN on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58126</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin VMware vSAN allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58127 | Lack of TLS validation in plugin Dell Powerscale on Checkmk Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58127</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in Checkmk Exchange plugin Dell Powerscale allows attackers in MitM position to intercept traffic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48100 | WordPress bidorbuy Store Integrator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48100</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in extremeidea bidorbuy Store Integrator allows Remote Code Inclusion. This issue affects bidorbuy Store Integrator: from n/a through 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48109 | WordPress XM-Backup plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48109</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Xavier Media XM-Backup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects XM-Backup: from n/a through 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48110 | WordPress Link View plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48110</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mibuthu Link View allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Link View: from n/a through 0.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48304 | WordPress Google XML News Sitemap plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.02 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48304</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Gary Illyes Google XML News Sitemap plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google XML News Sitemap plugin: from n/a through 0.02.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48305 | WordPress Goal Tracker for Patreon plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vikingjs Goal Tracker for Patreon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Goal Tracker for Patreon: from n/a through 0.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48306 | WordPress Savyour Affiliate Partner plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48306</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in developers savyour Savyour Affiliate Partner allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Savyour Affiliate Partner: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48307 | WordPress SEO For Images plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48307</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kasonzhao SEO For Images allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SEO For Images: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48308 | WordPress Newsletter subscription optin module plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48308</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nonletter Newsletter subscription optin module allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Newsletter subscription optin module: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48309 | WordPress BetPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 Lite - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48309</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in web-able BetPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BetPress: from n/a through 1.0.1 Lite.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48310 | WordPress Table Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48310</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wptableeditor Table Editor allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Table Editor: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48311 | WordPress Invisible Optin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48311</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OffClicks Invisible Optin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Invisible Optin: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48312 | WordPress WPAvatar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 文派翻译（WP Chinese Translation） WPAvatar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPAvatar: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48313 | WordPress Tripadvisor Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48313</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kevin heath Tripadvisor Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tripadvisor Shortcode: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48314 | WordPress Add Code To Head plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48314</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in salubrio Add Code To Head allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Add Code To Head: from n/a through 1.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48315 | WordPress WordPress HTML plugin &amp;lt;= 0.51 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48315</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in stanton119 WordPress HTML allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WordPress HTML: from n/a through 0.51.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48316 | WordPress Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48316</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ItayXD Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Responsive Mobile-Friendly Tooltip: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48318 | WordPress 多说社会化评论框 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48318</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shen2 多说社会化评论框 allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects 多说社会化评论框: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48319 | WordPress Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48319</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gslauraspeck Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mesa Mesa Reservation Widget: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48320 | WordPress 百度分享按钮 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48320</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in cuckoohello 百度分享按钮 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects 百度分享按钮: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48321 | WordPress Ultimate twitter profile widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48321</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dyiosah Ultimate twitter profile widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultimate twitter profile widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48322 | WordPress Statify Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Finn Dohrn Statify Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Statify Widget: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48323 | WordPress Advance Food Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48323</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Md Abunaser Khan Advance Food Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advance Food Menu: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48324 | WordPress tli.tl auto Twitter poster plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in khashabawy tli.tl auto Twitter poster allows Stored XSS. This issue affects tli.tl auto Twitter poster: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48325 | WordPress WP Admin Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48325</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shmish111 WP Admin Theme allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Admin Theme: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48327 | WordPress WP Mailgun SMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48327</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in inkthemes WP Mailgun SMTP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WP Mailgun SMTP: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48343 | WordPress WPMU Ldap Authentication plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48343</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aaron Axelsen WPMU Ldap Authentication allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPMU Ldap Authentication: from n/a through 5.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48347 | WordPress bxSlider integration for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48347</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vincent Mimoun-Prat bxSlider integration for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects bxSlider integration for WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48348 | WordPress Site Offline plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48348</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in chandrashekharsahu Site Offline allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Site Offline: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48349 | WordPress Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in origincode Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Gallery – Vimeo and YouTube Gallery: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48350 | WordPress AutoWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48350</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Neuralabz LTD AutoWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects AutoWP: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48351 | WordPress Kento Splash Screen plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48351</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PluginsPoint Kento Splash Screen allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Kento Splash Screen: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48352 | WordPress Yandex Site search pinger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sitesearch-yandex Yandex Site search pinger allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Yandex Site search pinger: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48353 | WordPress Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48353</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dactum Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront) allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Clickbank WordPress Plugin (Niche Storefront): from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48354 | WordPress Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48354</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Smart Widgets Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Better Post &amp;amp; Filter Widgets for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48356 | WordPress Kanpress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1   - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48356</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Isra Kanpress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Kanpress: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48357 | WordPress Century ToolKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Arbitrary Plugin Activation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48357</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Theme Century Century ToolKit allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Century ToolKit: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48358 | WordPress Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) – WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48358</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in everythingwp Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) &amp;#8211; WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Risk Free Cash On Delivery (COD) &amp;#8211; WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48359 | WordPress ATT YouTube Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48359</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in thaihavnn07 ATT YouTube Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ATT YouTube Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48360 | WordPress Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48360</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Razvan Stanga Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Varnish/Nginx Proxy Caching: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48361 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48361</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Saeed Sattar Beglou Hesabfa Accounting allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48362 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48362</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saeed Sattar Beglou Hesabfa Accounting allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48363 | WordPress Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48363</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Metin Saraç Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Popup for CF7 with Sweet Alert: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48364 | WordPress rajce plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48364</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in vEnCa-X rajce allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects rajce: from n/a through 0.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48365 | WordPress Custom Comment plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48365</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in imaprogrammer Custom Comment allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Comment: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49383 | WordPress Neresa Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49383</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CocoBasic Neresa allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Neresa: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49387 | WordPress Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49387</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in add-ons.org Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Drag and Drop File Upload for Elementor Forms: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49388 | WordPress Miraculous Core Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49388</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in kamleshyadav Miraculous Core Plugin allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Miraculous Core Plugin: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49402 | WordPress Houzez CRM Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49402</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in favethemes Houzez CRM allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Houzez CRM: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49404 | WordPress Listeo-Core Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.32 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49404</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in purethemes Listeo-Core allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Listeo-Core: from n/a through 1.9.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49405 | WordPress Houzez Theme &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49405</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49407 | WordPress Houzez Theme &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in favethemes Houzez allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Houzez: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52761 | WordPress WP Funnel Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52761</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in manfcarlo WP Funnel Manager allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Funnel Manager: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53215 | WordPress Yahoo! WebPlayer Plugin &amp;lt;=  2.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53215</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8bitkid Yahoo! WebPlayer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Yahoo! WebPlayer: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53216 | WordPress Glamer Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53216</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ThemeUniver Glamer allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Glamer: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53220 | WordPress XmasB Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53220</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in XmasB XmasB Quotes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XmasB Quotes: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53223 | WordPress Theme Switcher Reloaded Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53223</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in undoIT Theme Switcher Reloaded allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Switcher Reloaded: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53224 | WordPress NextGEN Gallery Search Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Koen Schuit NextGEN Gallery Search allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NextGEN Gallery Search: from n/a through 2.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53225 | WordPress e-Boekhouden.nl Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in eboekhouden e-Boekhouden.nl allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects e-Boekhouden.nl: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53227 | WordPress Magazine Saga Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53227</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine Saga allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine Saga: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53230 | WordPress Page Manager for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53230</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in honzat Page Manager for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Page Manager for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53243 | WordPress Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53243</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress allows Object Injection. This issue affects Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp;amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53244 | WordPress Magazine Elite Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53244</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine Elite allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine Elite: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53247 | WordPress BlogMarks Theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53247</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPInterface BlogMarks allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BlogMarks: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53248 | WordPress Magazine Theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53248</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Unfoldwp Magazine allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Magazine: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53250 | WordPress Chartbeat Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53250</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Chartbeat Chartbeat allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Chartbeat: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53289 | WordPress Theme Blvd Widget Areas Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53289</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason Theme Blvd Widget Areas allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Theme Blvd Widget Areas: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53326 | WordPress Gutenify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53326</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in CodeYatri Gutenify allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Gutenify: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53328 | WordPress Poll, Survey &amp;amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage Plugin &amp;lt;= 19.11.0 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53328</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Assaf Parag Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Poll, Survey &amp; Quiz Maker Plugin by Opinion Stage: from n/a through 19.11.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53334 | WordPress Jannah Theme &amp;lt;= 7.4.1 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53334</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in TieLabs Jannah allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Jannah: from n/a through 7.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53337 | WordPress LifePress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53337</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ashan Perera LifePress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects LifePress: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53572 | WordPress WP Easy Contact Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53572</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design WP Easy Contact allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Easy Contact: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53576 | WordPress Ovatheme Events Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53576</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ovatheme Ovatheme Events allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ovatheme Events: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53578 | WordPress Kipso Theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53578</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in gavias Kipso allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Kipso: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53579 | WordPress Captcha.eu Plugin &amp;lt; 1.0.61 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in captcha.eu Captcha.eu allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Captcha.eu: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53583 | WordPress Employee Spotlight Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53583</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design Employee Spotlight allows Object Injection. This issue affects Employee Spotlight: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53584 | WordPress WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp;amp; Support Ticket System Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53584</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in emarket-design WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System allows Object Injection. This issue affects WP Ticket Customer Service Software &amp; Support Ticket System: from n/a through 6.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53588 | WordPress UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53588</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Dmitry V. (CEO of "UKR Solution") UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator allows Path Traversal. This issue affects UPC/EAN/GTIN Code Generator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54029 | WordPress WooCommerce csv import export Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54029</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in extendons WooCommerce csv import export allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WooCommerce csv import export: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54710 | WordPress Tiktok Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54710</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Tiktok Feed allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Tiktok Feed: from n/a through 1.0.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54714 | WordPress Zephyr Project Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.201 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54714</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dylan James Zephyr Project Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Zephyr Project Manager: from n/a through 3.3.201.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54716 | WordPress Ireca Theme &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54716</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ovatheme Ireca allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Ireca: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54720 | WordPress Nest Addons Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54720</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SteelThemes Nest Addons allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Nest Addons: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54724 | WordPress Golo Theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54724</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uxper Golo allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Golo: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54725 | WordPress Golo Theme &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54725</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in uxper Golo allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Golo: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54731 | WordPress YouTube Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54731</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in emarket-design YouTube Showcase allows Object Injection. This issue affects YouTube Showcase: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54733 | WordPress All Bootstrap Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.28 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54733</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Miles All Bootstrap Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects All Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54734 | WordPress B Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.30 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54734</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins B Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects B Slider: from n/a through 1.1.30.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54738 | WordPress Jobmonster Theme &amp;lt;= 4.7.9 - Broken Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54738</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in NooTheme Jobmonster allows Authentication Abuse. This issue affects Jobmonster: from n/a through 4.7.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54742 | WordPress WpEvently Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.8 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54742</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently allows Object Injection. This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through 4.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39496 | WordPress WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro plugin &amp;lt; 2.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39496</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WBW WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WooBeWoo Product Filter Pro: from n/a before 2.9.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9376 | Block Bad Bots and Stop Bad Bots Crawlers and Spiders and Anti Spam Protection &amp;lt;= 11.58 - Insufficient Authorization to Unauthenticated Blocklist Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9376</link><description>The Block Bad Bots and Stop Bad Bots Crawlers and Spiders and Anti Spam Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an insufficient capability check on the 'stopbadbots_check_wordpress_logged_in_cookie' function in all versions up to, and including, 11.58. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass blocklists, rate limits, and other plugin functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54540 | Reflected XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54540</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via sSort parameter in admin's panel functionality. A malicious attacker can craft a specially crafted URL that, when opened, results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim's browser.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54541 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54541</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in page deletion functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special website, which when visited by the admin, will automatically send a POST request deleting an article.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54542 | Sending Password in GET Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54542</link><description>QuickCMS sends password and login via GET Request. This allows a local attacker with access to the victim's browser history to obtain the necessary credentials to log in as the user.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54543 | Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54543</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS via sDescriptionMeta parameter in page editor SEO functionality. Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54544 | Stored XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54544</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Stored XSS via aDirFilesDescriptions parameter in files editor functionality. Malicious attacker with admin privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when visiting edited page. By default admin user is not able to add JavaScript into the website.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55175 | Reflected XSS in QuickCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55175</link><description>QuickCMS is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via sLangEdit parameter in admin's panel functionality. A malicious attacker can craft a specially crafted URL that, when opened, results in arbitrary JavaScript execution in the victim's browser.

The vendor was notified early about this vulnerability, but didn't respond with the details of vulnerability or vulnerable version range. Only version 6.8 was tested and confirmed as vulnerable, other versions were not tested and might also be vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48963 | Local privilege escalation due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48963</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to improper soft link handling. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 40296.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58240 | tls: separate no-async decryption request handling from async</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58240</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: separate no-async decryption request handling from async

If we're not doing async, the handling is much simpler. There's no
reference counting, we just need to wait for the completion to wake us
up and return its result.

We should preferably also use a separate crypto_wait. I'm not seeing a
UAF as I did in the past, I think aec7961916f3 ("tls: fix race between
async notify and socket close") took care of it.

This will make the next fix easier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46409 | Inadequate encryption strength issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46409</link><description>Inadequate encryption strength issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, a function that requires authentication may be accessed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52460 | Files or directories accessible to external parties issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52460</link><description>Files or directories accessible to external parties issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If exploited, uploaded files and SS1 configuration files may be accessed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53396 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier), whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53396</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier), which may allow users who can log in to a client terminal to obtain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53970 | SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53970</link><description>SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and execute OS commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54762 | SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54762</link><description>SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files and execute OS commands with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54819 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54819</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, legitimate files may be overwritten by a remote authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58072 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58072</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') issue exists in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier). If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary files may be viewed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58081 | Use of hard-coded password issue/vulnerability in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58081</link><description>Use of hard-coded password issue/vulnerability in SS1 Ver.16.0.0.10 and earlier (Media version:16.0.0a and earlier) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to view arbitrary files with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58322 | NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58322</link><description>NAVER MYBOX Explorer for Windows before 3.0.8.133 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM by executing arbitrary commands due to improper privilege checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6255 | Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via className Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6255</link><description>The Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘className’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8073 | Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8073</link><description>The Dynamic AJAX Product Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13807 | Xagio SEO &amp;lt;= 7.1.0.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure via Unprotected Back-Up Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13807</link><description>The Xagio SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0.5 via the backup functionality due to weak filename structure and lack of protection in the directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from backups which can include the entire database and site's files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7955 | RingCentral Communications 1.5 - 1.6.8 - Missing Server‑Side Verification to Authentication Bypass via ringcentral_admin_login_2fa_verify Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7955</link><description>The RingCentral Communications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper validation within the ringcentral_admin_login_2fa_verify() function in versions 1.5 to 1.6.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user simply by supplying identical bogus codes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7956 | Ajax Search Lite &amp;lt;= 4.13.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Basic Information Exposure via ASL_Query in AJAX Search Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7956</link><description>The Ajax Search Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Basic Information Exposure due to missing authorization in its AJAX search handler in all versions up to, and including, 4.13.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to issue repeated AJAX requests to leak the content of any protected post in rolling 100‑character windows.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8977 | Simple Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 3.9.33 - Simple Download Monitor &amp;lt;= 3.9.33 – Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via order parameter in Log Export functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8977</link><description>The Simple Download Monitor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the order parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.33 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, and permissions granted by an Administrator, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9648 | WP ULike Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Unauthenticated Limited Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9648</link><description>The WP ULike Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the WP_Ulike_Pro_File_Uploader class in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload limited arbitrary files like .php2, .php6, .php7, .phps, .pht, .phtm, .pgif, .shtml, .phar, .inc, .hphp, .ctp, .module, .html, .svg on the affected site's server which may make make other attacks like Cross-Site Scripting possible. Only versions up to 1.8.7 were confirmed vulnerable, however, the earliest tested version for a patch we have access to is 1.9.4, so we are considering 1.9.4 the patched version.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0951 | LiquidThemes Themes &amp;lt;= Various Versions - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) All Plugins Deactivated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0951</link><description>Multiple plugins and/or themes for WordPress by LiquidThemes are vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the liquid_reset_wordpress_before AJAX in various versions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to deactivate all of a site's plugins. While we escalated this to Envato after not being able to establish contact, it appears the developer added a nonce check, however that is not sufficient protection as the nonce is exposed to all users with access to the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8603 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.148 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8603</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.148 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9345 | File Manager, Code Editor, and Backup by Managefy &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9345</link><description>The File Manager, Code Editor, and Backup by Managefy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.8 via the ajax_downloadfile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions on files outside of the originally intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9346 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.14.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9346</link><description>The Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via settings in all versions up to, and including, 10.14.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36003 | IBM Security Verify Governance Identity Manager information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36003</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance Identity Manager 10.0.2 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when detailed technical error messages are returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7812 | Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7812</link><description>The Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the adminExport() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and execute remote code when the Server command execution setting is enabled via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8897 | Beaver Builder Plugin (Lite Version) &amp;lt;= 2.9.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8897</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘'fl_builder' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9344 | UsersWP &amp;lt;= 1.2.42 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9344</link><description>The UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp; Members Directory plugin for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'uwp_profile' and 'uwp_profile_header' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.42 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9352 | Pronamic Google Maps &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9352</link><description>The Pronamic Google Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the description field in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>