<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 05:34:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-21408 | beat-access for Windows version 3.0.3 and prior contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21408</link><description>beat-access for Windows version 3.0.3 and prior contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 05:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1361 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1361</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24479 | HUSTOJ has Arbitrary File Write (Zip Slip) in Problem Import Modules that leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24479</link><description>HUSTOF is an open source online judge based on PHP/C++/MySQL/Linux for ACM/ICPC and NOIP training. Prior to version 26.01.24, the problem_import_qduoj.php and problem_import_hoj.php modules fail to properly sanitize filenames within uploaded ZIP archives. Attackers can craft a malicious ZIP file containing files with path traversal sequences (e.g., ../../shell.php). When extracted by the server, this allows writing files to arbitrary locations in the web root, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). Version 26.01.24 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24480 | QGIS had validated RCE and Repository Takeover via GitHub Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24480</link><description>QGIS is a free, open source, cross platform geographical information system (GIS) The repository contains a GitHub Actions workflow called "pre-commit checks" that, before commit 76a693cd91650f9b4e83edac525e5e4f90d954e9, was vulnerable to remote code execution and repository compromise because it used the `pull_request_target` trigger and then checked out and executed untrusted pull request code in a privileged context. Workflows triggered by `pull_request_target` ran with the base repository's credentials and access to secrets. If these workflows then checked out and executed code from the head of an external pull request (which could have been attacker controlled), the attacker could have executed arbitrary commands with elevated privileges. This insecure pattern has been documented as a security risk by GitHub and security researchers. Commit 76a693cd91650f9b4e83edac525e5e4f90d954e9 removed the vulnerable code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24486 | Python-Multipart has Arbitrary File Write via Non-Default Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24486</link><description>Python-Multipart is a streaming multipart parser for Python. Prior to version 0.0.22, a Path Traversal vulnerability exists when using non-default configuration options `UPLOAD_DIR` and `UPLOAD_KEEP_FILENAME=True`. An attacker can write uploaded files to arbitrary locations on the filesystem by crafting a malicious filename. Users should upgrade to version 0.0.22 to receive a patch or, as a workaround, avoid using `UPLOAD_KEEP_FILENAME=True` in project configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24489 | Gakido vulnerable to HTTP Header Injection (CRLF Injection)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24489</link><description>Gakido is a Python HTTP client focused on browser impersonation and anti-bot evasion. A vulnerability was discovered in Gakido prior to version 0.1.1 that allowed HTTP header injection through CRLF (Carriage Return Line Feed) sequences in user-supplied header values and names. When making HTTP requests with user-controlled header values containing `\r\n` (CRLF), `\n` (LF), or `\x00` (null byte) characters, an attacker could inject arbitrary HTTP headers into the request. The fix in version 0.1.1 adds a `_sanitize_header()` function that strips `\r`, `\n`, and `\x00` characters from both header names and values before they are included in HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24490 | MobSF has Stored XSS via Manifest Analysis - Dialer Code Host Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24490</link><description>MobSF is a mobile application security testing tool used. Prior to version 4.4.5, a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in MobSF's Android manifest analysis allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a victim's browser session by uploading a malicious APK. The `android:host` attribute from `` elements is rendered in HTML reports without sanitization, enabling session hijacking and account takeover. Version 4.4.5 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24686 | go-tuf Path Traversal in TAP 4 Multirepo Client Allows Arbitrary File Write via Malicious Repository Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24686</link><description>go-tuf is a Go implementation of The Update Framework (TUF). go-tuf's TAP 4 Multirepo Client uses the map file repository name string (`repoName`) as a filesystem path component when selecting the local metadata cache directory. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 2.4.1, if an application accepts a map file from an untrusted source, an attacker can supply a `repoName` containing traversal (e.g., `../escaped-repo`) and cause go-tuf to create directories and write the root metadata file outside the intended `LocalMetadataDir` cache base, within the running process's filesystem permissions. Version 2.4.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23683 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Fiori App (Intercompany Balance Reconciliation)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23683</link><description>SAP Fiori App Intercompany Balance Reconciliation does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This has low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1448 | D-Link DIR-615 Web Management wiz_policy_3_machine.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1448</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-615 up to 4.10. This impacts an unknown function of the file /wiz_policy_3_machine.php of the component Web Management Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument ipaddr results in os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1449 | Hisense TransTech Smart Bus Management System TireMng.aspx Page_Load sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1449</link><description>A flaw has been found in Hisense TransTech Smart Bus Management System up to 20260113. Affected is the function Page_Load of the file YZSoft/Forms/XForm/BM/BusComManagement/TireMng.aspx. Executing a manipulation of the argument key can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24478 | AnythingLLM vulnerable to Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24478</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns pieces of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. Prior to version 1.10.0, a critical Path Traversal vulnerability in the DrupalWiki integration allows a malicious admin (or an attacker who can convince an admin to configure a malicious DrupalWiki URL) to write arbitrary files to the server. This can lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) by overwriting configuration files or writing executable scripts. Version 1.10.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24477 | AnythingLLM has key leak in `systemSettings.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24477</link><description>AnythingLLM is an application that turns pieces of content into context that any LLM can use as references during chatting. If AnythingLLM prior to version 1.10.0 is configured to use Qdrant as the vector database with an API key, this QdrantApiKey could be exposed in plain text to unauthenticated users via the `/api/setup-complete` endpoint. Leakage of QdrantApiKey allows an unauthenticated attacker full read/write access to the Qdrant vector database instance used by AnythingLLM. Since Qdrant often stores the core knowledge base for RAG in AnythingLLM, this can lead to complete compromise of the semantic search / retrieval functionality and indirect leakage of confidential uploaded documents. Version 1.10.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30248 | DLL hijacking in the WD Discovery Installer in Western Digital WD Discovery 5.2.730 on Windows allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30248</link><description>DLL hijacking in the WD Discovery Installer in Western Digital WD Discovery 5.2.730 on Windows allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via placement of a crafted dll in the installer's search path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24470 | Skipper Ingress Controller Allows Unauthorized Access to Internal Services via ExternalName</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24470</link><description>Skipper is an HTTP router and reverse proxy for service composition. Prior to version 0.24.0, when running Skipper as an Ingress controller, users with permissions to create an Ingress and a Service of type ExternalName can create routes that enable them to use Skipper's network access to reach internal services. Version 0.24.0 disables Kubernetes ExternalName by default. As a workaround, developers can allow list targets of an ExternalName and allow list via regular expressions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24476 | Shaarli vulnerable to stored XSS via Suggested Tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24476</link><description>Shaarli is a personal bookmarking service. Prior to version 0.16.0, crafting a malicious tag which starting with `"` prematurely ends the `&lt;input /&gt;` tag on the start page and allows an attacker to add arbitrary html leading to a possible XSS attack. Version 0.16.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24123 | BentoML has a Path Traversal via Bentofile Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24123</link><description>BentoML is a Python library for building online serving systems optimized for AI apps and model inference. Prior to version 1.4.34, BentoML's `bentofile.yaml` configuration allows path traversal attacks through multiple file path fields (`description`, `docker.setup_script`, `docker.dockerfile_template`, `conda.environment_yml`). An attacker can craft a malicious bentofile that, when built by a victim, exfiltrates arbitrary files from the filesystem into the bento archive. This enables supply chain attacks where sensitive files (SSH keys, credentials, environment variables) are silently embedded in bentos and exposed when pushed to registries or deployed. Version 1.4.34 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24400 | AssertJ has XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability when parsing untrusted XML via isXmlEqualTo assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24400</link><description>AssertJ provides Fluent testing assertions for Java and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Starting in version 1.4.0 and prior to version 3.27.7, an XML External Entity (XXE) vulnerability exists in `org.assertj.core.util.xml.XmlStringPrettyFormatter`: the `toXmlDocument(String)` method initializes `DocumentBuilderFactory` with default settings, without disabling DTDs or external entities. This formatter is used by the `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` assertion for `CharSequence` values. An application is vulnerable only when it uses untrusted XML input with either `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` from `org.assertj.core.api.AbstractCharSequenceAssert` or `xmlPrettyFormat(String)` from `org.assertj.core.util.xml.XmlStringPrettyFormatter`. If untrusted XML input is processed by tone of these methods, an attacker couldnread arbitrary local files via `file://` URIs (e.g., `/etc/passwd`, application configuration files); perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via HTTP/HTTPS URIs, and/or cause Denial of Service via "Billion Laughs" entity expansion attacks. `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` has been deprecated in favor of XMLUnit in version 3.18.0 and will be removed in version 4.0. Users of affected versions should, in order of preference: replace `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` with XMLUnit, upgrade to version 3.27.7, or avoid using `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` or `XmlStringPrettyFormatter` with untrusted input. `XmlStringPrettyFormatter` has historically been considered a utility for `isXmlEqualTo(CharSequence)` rather than a feature for AssertJ users, so it is deprecated in version 3.27.7 and removed in version 4.0, with no replacement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24408 | sigstore has CSRF possibility in OIDC authentication during signing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24408</link><description>sigstore-python is a Python tool for generating and verifying Sigstore signatures. Prior to version 4.2.0, the sigstore-python OAuth authentication flow is susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery. `_OAuthSession` creates a unique "state" and sends it as a parameter in the authentication request but the "state" in the server response seems not not be cross-checked with this value. Version 4.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1445 | iJason-Liu Books_Manager upload_bookCover.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1445</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iJason-Liu Books_Manager up to 298ba736387ca37810466349af13a0fdf828e99c. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file controllers/books_center/upload_bookCover.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument book_cover results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24003 | EvseV2G has sequence state validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24003</link><description>EVerest is an EV charging software stack. In versions up to and including 2025.12.1, it is possible to bypass the sequence state verification including authentication, and send requests that transition to forbidden states relative to the current one, thereby updating the current context with illegitimate data.cThanks to the modular design of EVerest, authorization is handled in a separate module and EVSEManager Charger internal state machine cannot transition out of the `WaitingForAuthentication` state through ISO 15118-2 communication. From this state, it was however possible through ISO 15118-2 messages which are published to the MQTT server to trick it into preparing to charge, and even to prepare to send current. The final requirement to actually send current to the EV was the closure of the contactors, which does not appear to be possible without leaving the `WaitingForAuthentication` state and leveraging ISO 15118-2 messages. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24131 | pnpm has Path Traversal via arbitrary file permission modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24131</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.2, when pnpm processes a package's `directories.bin` field, it uses `path.join()` without validating the result stays within the package root. A malicious npm package can specify `"directories": {"bin": "../../../../tmp"}` to escape the package directory, causing pnpm to chmod 755 files at arbitrary locations. This issue only affects Unix/Linux/macOS. Windows is not affected (`fixBin` gated by `EXECUTABLE_SHEBANG_SUPPORTED`). Version 10.28.2 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24056 | pnpm has symlink traversal in file:/git dependencies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24056</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.2, when pnpm installs a `file:` (directory) or `git:` dependency, it follows symlinks and reads their target contents without constraining them to the package root. A malicious package containing a symlink to an absolute path (e.g., `/etc/passwd`, `~/.ssh/id_rsa`) causes pnpm to copy that file's contents into `node_modules`, leaking local data. The vulnerability only affects `file:` and `git:` dependencies. Registry packages (npm) have symlinks stripped during publish and are NOT affected. The issue impacts developers installing local/file dependencies andCI/CD pipelines installing git dependencies. It can lead to credential theft via symlinks to `~/.aws/credentials`, `~/.npmrc`, `~/.ssh/id_rsa`. Version 10.28.2 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23889 | pnpm has Windows-specific tarball Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23889</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's tarball extraction allows malicious packages to write files outside the package directory on Windows. The path normalization only checks for `./` but not `.\`. On Windows, backslashes are directory separators, enabling path traversal. This vulnerability is Windows-only. This issue impacts Windows pnpm users, Windows CI/CD pipelines (GitHub Actions Windows runners, Azure DevOps), and those who can overwrite `.npmrc`, build configs, or other files. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23890 | pnpm scoped bin name Path Traversal allows arbitrary file creation outside node_modules/.bin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23890</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's bin linking allows malicious npm packages to create executable shims or symlinks outside of `node_modules/.bin`. Bin names starting with `@` bypass validation, and after scope normalization, path traversal sequences like `../../` remain intact. This issue affects all pnpm users who install npm packages, CI/CD pipelines using pnpm, and those who can overwrite config files, scripts, or other sensitive files. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59471 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in self-hosted Next.js applications that have `remotePatterns` configured for the Image Optimizer. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59471</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in self-hosted Next.js applications that have `remotePatterns` configured for the Image Optimizer. The image optimization endpoint (`/_next/image`) loads external images entirely into memory without enforcing a maximum size limit, allowing an attacker to cause out-of-memory conditions by requesting optimization of arbitrarily large images. This vulnerability requires that `remotePatterns` is configured to allow image optimization from external domains and that the attacker can serve or control a large image on an allowed domain.

Strongly consider upgrading to 15.5.10 or 16.1.5 to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in Next applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59472 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in Next.js versions with Partial Prerendering (PPR) enabled when running in minimal mode. The PPR r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59472</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in Next.js versions with Partial Prerendering (PPR) enabled when running in minimal mode. The PPR resume endpoint accepts unauthenticated POST requests with the `Next-Resume: 1` header and processes attacker-controlled postponed state data. Two closely related vulnerabilities allow an attacker to crash the server process through memory exhaustion:

1. **Unbounded request body buffering**: The server buffers the entire POST request body into memory using `Buffer.concat()` without enforcing any size limit, allowing arbitrarily large payloads to exhaust available memory.

2. **Unbounded decompression (zipbomb)**: The resume data cache is decompressed using `inflateSync()` without limiting the decompressed output size. A small compressed payload can expand to hundreds of megabytes or gigabytes, causing memory exhaustion.

Both attack vectors result in a fatal V8 out-of-memory error (`FATAL ERROR: Reached heap limit Allocation failed - JavaScript heap out of memory`) causing the Node.js process to terminate. The zipbomb variant is particularly dangerous as it can bypass reverse proxy request size limits while still causing large memory allocation on the server.

To be affected you must have an application running with `experimental.ppr: true` or `cacheComponents: true` configured along with the NEXT_PRIVATE_MINIMAL_MODE=1 environment variable.

Strongly consider upgrading to 15.6.0-canary.61 or 16.1.5 to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in Next applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59473 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the Structure for Admin authenticated user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59473</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the Structure for Admin authenticated user</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23888 | pnpm: Binary ZIP extraction allows arbitrary file write via path traversal (Zip Slip)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23888</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.28.1, a path traversal vulnerability in pnpm's binary fetcher allows malicious packages to write files outside the intended extraction directory. The vulnerability has two attack vectors: (1) Malicious ZIP entries containing `../` or absolute paths that escape the extraction root via AdmZip's `extractAllTo`, and (2) The `BinaryResolution.prefix` field is concatenated into the extraction path without validation, allowing a crafted prefix like `../../evil` to redirect extracted files outside `targetDir`. The issue impacts all pnpm users who install packages with binary assets, users who configure custom Node.js binary locations, CI/CD pipelines that auto-install binary dependencies, and those who can overwrite config files, scripts, or other sensitive files leading to RCE. Version 10.28.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1444 | iJason-Liu Books_Manager add_book_check.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1444</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iJason-Liu Books_Manager up to 298ba736387ca37810466349af13a0fdf828e99c. This affects an unknown part of the file controllers/books_center/add_book_check.php. Such manipulation of the argument mark leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22696 | dcap-qvl has Missing Verification for QE Identity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22696</link><description>dcap-qvl implements the quote verification logic for DCAP (Data Center Attestation Primitives). A vulnerability present in versions prior to 0.3.9 involves a critical gap in the cryptographic verification process within the dcap-qvl. The library fetches QE Identity collateral (including qe_identity, qe_identity_signature, and qe_identity_issuer_chain) from the PCCS. However, it skips to verify the QE Identity signature against its certificate chain and does not enforce policy constraints on the QE Report. An attacker can forge the QE Identity data to whitelist a malicious or non-Intel Quoting Enclave. This allows the attacker to forge the QE and sign untrusted quotes that the verifier will accept as valid. Effectively, this bypasses the entire remote attestation security model, as the verifier can no longer trust the entity responsible for signing the quotes. All deployments utilizing the dcap-qvl library for SGX or TDX quote verification are affected. The vulnerability has been patched in dcap-qvl version 0.3.9. The fix implements the missing cryptographic verification for the QE Identity signature and enforces the required checks for MRSIGNER, ISVPRODID, and ISVSVN against the QE Report. Users of the `@phala/dcap-qvl-node` and `@phala/dcap-qvl-web` packages should switch to the pure JavaScript implementation, `@phala/dcap-qvl`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. Users must upgrade to the patched version to ensure that QE Identity collateral is properly verified.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22709 | vm2 has a Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22709</link><description>vm2 is an open source vm/sandbox for Node.js. In vm2 prior to version 3.10.2, `Promise.prototype.then` `Promise.prototype.catch` callback sanitization can be bypassed. This allows attackers to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code. In lib/setup-sandbox.js, the callback function of `localPromise.prototype.then` is sanitized, but `globalPromise.prototype.then` is not sanitized. The return value of async functions is `globalPromise` object. Version 3.10.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1443 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminDeleteUser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1443</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminDeleteUser.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9615 | Networkmanager: networkmanager file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9615</link><description>A flaw was found in NetworkManager. The NetworkManager package allows access to files that may belong to other users. NetworkManager allows non-root users to configure the system's network. The daemon runs with root privileges and can access files owned by users different from the one who added the connection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9820 | Gnutls: stack-based buffer overflow in gnutls_pkcs11_token_init() function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9820</link><description>A flaw was found in the GnuTLS library, specifically in the gnutls_pkcs11_token_init() function that handles PKCS#11 token initialization. When a token label longer than expected is processed, the function writes past the end of a fixed-size stack buffer. This programming error can cause the application using GnuTLS to crash or, in certain conditions, be exploited for code execution. As a result, systems or applications relying on GnuTLS may be vulnerable to a denial of service or local privilege escalation attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11065 | Github.com/go-viper/mapstructure/v2: go-viper&amp;#x27;s mapstructure may leak sensitive information in logs in github.com/go-viper/mapstructure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11065</link><description>A flaw was found in github.com/go-viper/mapstructure/v2, in the field processing component using mapstructure.WeakDecode. This vulnerability allows information disclosure through detailed error messages that may leak sensitive input values via malformed user-supplied data processed in security-critical contexts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11687 | Gi-docgen: reflected dom xss in gi-docgen</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11687</link><description>A flaw was found in the gi-docgen. This vulnerability allows arbitrary JavaScript execution in the context of the page — enabling DOM access, session cookie theft and other client-side attacks — via a crafted URL that supplies a malicious value to the q GET parameter (reflected DOM XSS).</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14459 | Virt-cdi-controller: unauthorized pvc cloning via dataimportcron</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14459</link><description>A flaw was found in KubeVirt Containerized Data Importer (CDI). This vulnerability allows a user to clone PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs) from unauthorized namespaces, resulting in unauthorized access to data via the DataImportCron PVC source mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14525 | Kubevirt: kubevirt: vm administration denial of service via guest agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14525</link><description>A flaw was found in kubevirt. A user within a virtual machine (VM), if the guest agent is active, can exploit this by causing the agent to report an excessive number of network interfaces. This action can overwhelm the system's ability to store VM configuration updates, effectively blocking changes to the Virtual Machine Instance (VMI). This allows the VM user to restrict the VM administrator's ability to manage the VM, leading to a denial of service for administrative operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14969 | Hibernate-reactive-core: hibernate reactive: denial of service due to connection leak on http client disconnect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14969</link><description>A flaw was found in Hibernate Reactive. When an HTTP endpoint is exposed to perform database operations, a remote client can prematurely close the HTTP connection. This action may lead to leaking connections from the database connection pool, potentially causing a Denial of Service (DoS) by exhausting available database connections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9520 | IDOR Leading to Owner Account Hijacking in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9520</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability exists in Omada Controllers that allows an attacker with Administrator permissions to manipulate requests and potentially hijack the Owner account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9521 | Password Confirmation Bypass in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9521</link><description>Password Confirmation Bypass vulnerability in Omada Controllers, allowing an attacker with a valid session token to bypass secondary verification, and change the user’s password without proper confirmation, leading to weakened account security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9522 | Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Omada Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9522</link><description>Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Omada Controllers through webhook functionality, enabling crafted requests to internal services, which may lead to enumeration of information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0810 | Gix-date: gix-date: undefined behavior due to invalid string generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0810</link><description>A flaw was found in gix-date. The `gix_date::parse::TimeBuf::as_str` function can generate strings containing invalid non-UTF8 characters. This issue violates the internal safety invariants of the `TimeBuf` component, leading to undefined behavior when these malformed strings are subsequently processed. This could potentially result in application instability or other unforeseen consequences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1190 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-services: keycloak saml brokering: response delay due to unchecked notonorafter in subjectconfirmationdata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1190</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak's SAML brokering functionality. When Keycloak is configured as a client in a Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) setup, it fails to validate the `NotOnOrAfter` timestamp within the `SubjectConfirmationData`. This allows an attacker to delay the expiration of SAML responses, potentially extending the time a response is considered valid and leading to unexpected session durations or resource consumption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23864 | Multiple denial of service vulnerabilities exist in React Server Components, affecting the following packages: react-server-dom-parcel, reac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23864</link><description>Multiple denial of service vulnerabilities exist in React Server Components, affecting the following packages: react-server-dom-parcel, react-server-dom-turbopack, react-server-dom-webpack.

The vulnerabilities are triggered by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to Server Function endpoints, and could lead to server crashes, out-of-memory exceptions or excessive CPU usage; depending on the vulnerable code path being exercised, the application configuration and application code.

Strongly consider upgrading to the latest package versions to reduce risk and prevent availability issues in applications using React Server Components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70368 | Worklenz version 2.1.5 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Updates feature. An attacker can submit a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70368</link><description>Worklenz version 2.1.5 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Updates feature. An attacker can submit a malicious payload in the Updates text field which is then rendered in the reporting view without proper sanitization. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim's browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14756 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in Archer MR600</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14756</link><description>Command injection vulnerability was found in the admin interface component of TP-Link Archer MR600 v5 firmware, allowing authenticated attackers to execute system commands with a limited character length via crafted input in the browser developer console, possibly leading to service disruption or full compromise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57784 | Tomahawk authentication timing attack due to usage of &amp;#x27;strcmp&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57784</link><description>Tomahawk auth timing attack due to usage of `strcmp` has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows a local attacker to access the management client.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57785 | Double free in XSLT in &amp;#x27;show_index&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57785</link><description>A Double Free in XSLT `show_index` has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows an unauthenticated attacker to corrupt data which may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71178 | Crucial Storage Executive &amp;lt; 11.08.082025.00 Installer DLL Preloading LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71178</link><description>Crucial Storage Executive installer versions prior to 11.08.082025.00 contain a DLL preloading vulnerability. During installation, the installer runs with elevated privileges and loads Windows DLLs using an uncontrolled search path, which can cause a malicious DLL placed alongside the installer to be loaded instead of the intended system library. A local attacker who can convince a victim to run the installer from a directory containing the attacker-supplied DLL can achieve arbitrary code execution with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0925 | Tanium addressed an improper input validation vulnerability in Discover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0925</link><description>Tanium addressed an improper input validation vulnerability in Discover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24432 | Tenda W30E V2 Missing CSRF Protections for Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24432</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) lack cross-site request forgery (CSRF) protections on administrative endpoints, including those used to change administrator account credentials. As a result, an attacker can craft malicious requests that, when triggered by an authenticated user’s browser, modify administrative passwords and other configuration settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24435 | Tenda W30E V2 Permissive CORS Allows Cross-origin Data Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24435</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) implement an insecure Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) policy on authenticated administrative endpoints. The device sets Access-Control-Allow-Origin: * in combination with Access-Control-Allow-Credentials: true, allowing attacker-controlled origins to issue credentialed cross-origin requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24439 | Tenda W30E V2 Lacks X-Content-Type-Options Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24439</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) fail to include the X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff response header on web management interfaces. As a result, browsers that perform MIME sniffing may incorrectly interpret attacker-influenced responses as executable script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36953 | MiniTool ShadowMaker 3.2 - &amp;#x27;MTAgentService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36953</link><description>MiniTool ShadowMaker 3.2 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the MTAgentService that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\MiniTool ShadowMaker\AgentService.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36954 | Xeroneit Library Management System 3.1 - &amp;quot;Add Book Category &amp;quot; Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36954</link><description>Xeroneit Library Management System 3.1 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Book Category feature that allows administrators to inject malicious scripts. Attackers can insert a payload in the Category Name field to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when the page is loaded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36955 | Grav CMS 1.6.30 Admin Plugin 1.9.18 - &amp;#x27;Page Title&amp;#x27; Persistent Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36955</link><description>Grav CMS 1.6.30 with Admin Plugin 1.9.18 contains a persistent cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious scripts through the page title field. Attackers can create a new page with a malicious script in the title, which will be executed when the page is viewed in the admin panel or on the site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36956 | Openfire 4.6.0 - &amp;#x27;path&amp;#x27; Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36956</link><description>Openfire 4.6.0 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the nodejs plugin that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts through the 'path' parameter. Attackers can craft a payload with script tags to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of administrative users viewing the nodejs configuration page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36957 | PDF Complete 3.5.310.2002 - &amp;#x27;pdfsvc.exe&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36957</link><description>PDF Complete 3.5.310.2002 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its pdfsvc.exe service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to inject and execute malicious code with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36958 | Kite 1.2020.1119.0 - &amp;#x27;KiteService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36958</link><description>Kite 1.2020.1119.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the KiteService Windows service that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in 'C:\Program Files\Kite\KiteService.exe' to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36959 | IDT PC Audio 1.0.6499.0 - &amp;#x27;STacSV&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36959</link><description>IDT PC Audio 1.0.6499.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the STacSV service to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem account permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36960 | Forma LMS 2.3 - &amp;#x27;First &amp;amp; Last Name&amp;#x27; Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36960</link><description>Forma LMS 2.3 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into user profile first and last name fields. Attackers can craft scripts like '' to execute arbitrary JavaScript when the profile is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57783 | Improper header parsing may lead to request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57783</link><description>Improper header parsing may lead to request smuggling has been identified in Hiawatha webserver version 11.7 which allows an unauthenticated attacker to access restricted resources managed by Hiawatha webserver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1224 | Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Discover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1224</link><description>Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Discover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24428 | Tenda W30E V2 Incorrect Authorization Allows Administrator Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24428</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) contain an authorization flaw in the user management API that allows a low-privileged authenticated user to change the administrator account password. By sending a crafted request directly to the backend endpoint, an attacker can bypass role-based restrictions enforced by the web interface and obtain full administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24429 | Tenda W30E V2 Hardcoded Default Password for Built-in Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24429</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) ship with a predefined default password for a built-in authentication account that is not required to be changed during initial configuration. An attacker can leverage these default credentials to gain authenticated access to the management interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24430 | Tenda W30E V2 HTTP Responses Expose Plaintext Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24430</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) disclose sensitive account credentials in cleartext within HTTP responses generated by the maintenance interface. Because the management interface is accessible over unencrypted HTTP by default, credentials may be exposed to network-based interception.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24431 | Tenda W30E V2 Web UI Reveals Passwords in Cleartext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24431</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) display stored user account passwords in plaintext within the administrative web interface. Any user with access to the affected management pages can directly view credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24433 | Tenda W30E V2 Stored XSS via Username Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24433</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the user creation functionality. Insufficient input validation allows attacker-controlled script content to be stored and later executed when administrative users access the affected management pages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24436 | Tenda W30E V2 Lacks Rate Limiting on Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24436</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) do not enforce rate limiting or account lockout mechanisms on authentication endpoints. This allows attackers to perform unrestricted brute-force attempts against administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24437 | Tenda W30E V2 Missing Cache Controls for Credential-bearing Pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24437</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) serve sensitive administrative content without appropriate cache-control directives. As a result, browsers may store credential-bearing responses locally, exposing them to subsequent unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24440 | Tenda W30E V2 Allows Password Changes Without Verifying Current Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24440</link><description>Shenzhen Tenda W30E V2 firmware versions up to and including V16.01.0.19(5037) allow account passwords to be changed through the maintenance interface without requiring verification of the existing password. This enables unauthorized password changes when access to the affected endpoint is obtained.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1446 | There is a Cross Site Scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Pro versions 3.6.0 and earlier. A local attacker could supply malicious strings into Ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1446</link><description>There is a Cross Site Scripting issue in Esri ArcGIS Pro versions 3.6.0 and earlier. A local attacker could supply malicious strings into ArcGIS Pro which may execute when a specific dialog is opened.  This issue is fixed in ArcGIS Pro 3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21509 | Microsoft Office Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21509</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70982 | Incorrect access control in the importUser function of SpringBlade v4.5.0 allows attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily import s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70982</link><description>Incorrect access control in the importUser function of SpringBlade v4.5.0 allows attackers with low-level privileges to arbitrarily import sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67274 | An issue in continuous.software aangine v.2025.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the excel-integration-service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67274</link><description>An issue in continuous.software aangine v.2025.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the excel-integration-service template download module, integration-persistence-service job listing module, portfolio-item-service data retrieval module endpoints</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:18:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36952 | IObit Uninstaller 10 Pro - Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36952</link><description>IObit Uninstaller 10 Pro contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated system privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted service path in the IObit Uninstaller Service to insert malicious code that would execute with SYSTEM-level permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50537 | Stack overflow vulnerability in eslint before 9.26.0 when serializing objects with circular references in eslint/lib/shared/serialization.js...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50537</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in eslint before 9.26.0 when serializing objects with circular references in eslint/lib/shared/serialization.js. The exploit is triggered via the RuleTester.run() method, which validates test cases and checks for duplicates. During validation, the internal function checkDuplicateTestCase() is called, which in turn uses the isSerializable() function for serialization checks. When a circular reference object is passed in, isSerializable() enters infinite recursion, ultimately causing a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1283 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1283</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1284 | Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1284</link><description>An Out-Of-Bounds Write vulnerability affecting the EPRT file reading procedure in SOLIDWORKS eDrawings from Release SOLIDWORKS 2025 through Release SOLIDWORKS 2026 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code while opening a specially crafted EPRT file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15057 | Apache Continuum: Command injection leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15057</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in Apache Continuum.

This issue affects Apache Continuum: all versions.

Attackers with access to the installations REST API can use this to invoke arbitrary commands on the server.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59090 | Unauthenticated SOAP API in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59090</link><description>On the exos 9300 server, a SOAP API is reachable on port 8002. This API does not require any authentication prior to sending requests. Therefore, network access to the exos server allows e.g. the creation of arbitrary access log events as well as querying the 2FA PINs associated with the enrolled chip cards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59091 | Hardcoded Legacy Accounts Allowing Control Over Access Managers in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59091</link><description>Multiple hardcoded credentials have been identified, which are allowed to sign-in to the exos 9300 datapoint server running on port 1004 and 1005. This server is used for relaying status information from and to the Access Managers. This information, among other things, is used to graphically visualize open doors and alerts. However, controlling the Access Managers via this interface is also possible.

To send and receive status information, authentication is necessary. The Kaba exos 9300 application contains hard-coded credentials for four different users, which are allowed to login to the datapoint server and receive as well as send information, including commands to open arbitrary doors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59092 | Unauthenticated RPC Service in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59092</link><description>An RPC service, which is part of exos 9300, is reachable on port 4000, run by the process FSMobilePhoneInterface.exe. This service is used for interprocess communication between services and the Kaba exos 9300 GUI, containing status information about the Access Managers. Interacting with the service does not require any authentication. Therefore, it is possible to send arbitrary status information about door contacts etc. without prior authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59093 | Insecure Password Derivation Function for Database Administrator in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59093</link><description>Exos 9300 instances are using a randomly generated database password to connect to the configured MSSQL server. The password is derived from static random values, which are concatenated to the hostname and a random string that can be read by every user from the registry. This allows an attacker to derive the database password and get authenticated access to the central exos 9300 database as the user Exos9300Common. The user has the roles ExosDialog and ExosDialogDotNet assigned, which are able to read most tables of the database as well as update and insert into many tables.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59094 | Local Privilege Escalation in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300 System management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59094</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability has been identified in the Kaba exos 9300 System management application (d9sysdef.exe). Within this application it is possible to specify an arbitrary executable as well as the weekday and start time, when the specified executable should be run with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59095 | Hard-coded Key for PIN Encryption in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59095</link><description>The program libraries (DLL) and binaries used by exos 9300 contain multiple hard-coded secrets. One notable example is the function "EncryptAndDecrypt" in the library Kaba.EXOS.common.dll. This algorithm uses a simple XOR encryption technique combined with a cryptographic key (cryptoKey) to transform each character of the input string. However, it's important to note that this implementation does not provide strong encryption and should not be considered secure for sensitive data. It's more of a custom encryption approach rather than a common algorithm used in cryptographic applications. The key itself is static and based on the founder's name of the company. The functionality is for example used to encrypt the user PINs before storing them in the MSSQL database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59096 | Weak Default Password in dormakaba Kaba exos 9300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59096</link><description>The default password for the extended admin user mode in the application U9ExosAdmin.exe ("Kaba 9300 Administration") is hard-coded in multiple locations as well as documented in the locally stored user documentation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59097 | Unauthenticated SOAP API in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59097</link><description>The exos 9300 application can be used to configure Access Managers (e.g. 92xx, 9230 and 9290). The configuration is done in a graphical user interface on the dormakaba exos server. As soon as the save button is clicked in exos 9300, the whole configuration is sent to the selected Access Manager via SOAP. The SOAP request is sent without any prior authentication or authorization by default. Though authentication and authorization can be configured using IPsec for 92xx-K5 devices and mTLS for 92xx-K7 devices, it is not enabled by default and must therefore be activated with additional steps.

This insecure default allows an attacker with network level access to completely control the whole environment. An attacker is for example easily able to conduct the following tasks without prior authentication:
- Re-configure Access Managers (e.g. remove alarming system requirements)
- Freely re-configure the inputs and outputs
- Open all connected doors permanently
- Open all doors for a defined time interval
- Change the admin password
- and many more

Network level access can be gained due to an insufficient network segmentation as well as missing LAN firewalls. Devices with an insecure configuration have been identified to be directly exposed to the internet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59098 | Trace Functionality Leaking Sensitive Data in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59098</link><description>The Access Manager is offering a trace functionality to debug errors and issues with the device. The trace functionality is implemented as a simple TCP socket. A tool called TraceClient.exe, provided by dormakaba via the Access Manager web interface, is used to connect to the socket and receive debug information. The data is permanently broadcasted on the TCP socket. The socket can be accessed without any authentication or encryption. 

The transmitted data is based on the set verbosity level. The verbosity level can be set using the http(s) endpoint with the service interface password or with the guessable identifier of the device via the SOAP interface.

The transmitted data contains sensitive data like the Card ID as well as all button presses on Registration units. This allows an attacker with network level access to retrieve all entered PINs on a registration unit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59099 | Unauthenticated Path Traversal in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59099</link><description>The Access Manager is using the open source web server CompactWebServer written in C#. This web server is affected by a path traversal vulnerability, which allows an attacker to directly access files via simple GET requests without prior authentication. 

Hence, it is possible to retrieve all files stored on the file system, including the SQLite database Database.sq3, containing badge information and the corresponding PIN codes. Additionally, when trying to access certain files, the web server crashes and becomes unreachable for about 60 seconds. This can be abused to continuously send the request and cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59100 | Unauthenticated Access to the SQLite Database in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59100</link><description>The web interface offers a functionality to export the internal SQLite database. After executing the database export, an automatic download is started and the device reboots. After rebooting, the exported database is deleted and cannot be accessed anymore. However, it was noticed that sometimes the device does not reboot and therefore the exported database is not deleted, or the device reboots and the export is not deleted for unknown reasons. The path where the database export is located can be accessed without prior authentication. This leads to the fact that an attacker might be able to get access to the exported database without prior authentication. 
The database includes sensitive data like passwords, card pins, encrypted Mifare sitekeys and much more.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59101 | Insufficient Session Management in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59101</link><description>Instead of typical session tokens or cookies, it is verified on a per-request basis if the originating IP address has once successfully logged in. As soon as an authentication request from a certain source IP is successful, the IP address is handled as authenticated. No other session information is stored. Therefore, it is possible to spoof the IP address of a logged-in user to gain access to the Access Manager web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59102 | Secrets Stored in Plaintext in Database in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59102</link><description>The web server of the Access Manager offers a functionality to download a backup of the local database stored on the device. This database contains the whole configuration. This includes encrypted MIFARE keys, card data, user PINs and much more. The PINs are even stored unencrypted. Combined with the fact that an attacker can easily get access to the backup functionality by abusing the session management issue (CVE-2025-59101), or by exploiting the weak default password (CVE-2025-59108), or by simply setting a new password without prior authentication via the SOAP API (CVE-2025-59097), it is easily possible to access the sensitive data on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59103 | Weak Default Passwords for SSH Access in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59103</link><description>The Access Manager 92xx in hardware revision K7 is based on Linux instead of Windows CE embedded in older hardware revisions. In this new hardware revision it was noticed that an SSH service is exposed on port 22. By analyzing the firmware of the devices, it was noticed that there are two users with hardcoded and weak passwords that can be used to access the devices via SSH. The passwords can be also guessed very easily. The password of at least one user is set to a random value after the first deployment, with the restriction that the password is only randomized if the configured date is prior to 2022. Therefore, under certain circumstances, the passwords are not randomized. For example, if the clock is never set on the device, the battery of the clock module has been changed, the Access Manager has been factory reset and has not received a time yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59104 | Unlocked Bootloader in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59104</link><description>With physical access to the device and enough time an attacker is able to solder test leads to the debug footprint (or use the 6-Pin tag-connect cable). Thus, the attacker gains access to the bootloader, where the kernel command line can be changed. An attacker is able to gain a root shell through this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59105 | Unencrypted Flash Storage in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59105</link><description>With physical access to the device and enough time an attacker can desolder the flash memory, modify it and then reinstall it because of missing encryption. Thus, essential files, such as "/etc/passwd", as well as stored certificates, cryptographic keys, stored PINs and so on can be modified and read, in order to gain SSH root access on the Linux-based K7 model. On the Windows CE based K5 model, the password for the Access Manager can additionally be read in plain text from the stored SQLite database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59106 | Web Server Running with Root Privileges in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59106</link><description>The binary serving the web server and executing basically all actions launched from the Web UI is running with root privileges. This is against the least privilege principle. If an attacker is able to execute code on the system via other vulnerabilities it is possible to directly execute commands with highest privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59107 | Static Firmware Encryption Password in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59107</link><description>Dormakaba provides the software FWServiceTool to update the firmware version of the Access Managers via the network. The firmware in some instances is provided in an encrypted ZIP file. Within this tool, the password used to decrypt the ZIP and extract the firmware is set statically and can be extracted. This password was valid for multiple observed firmware versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59108 | Weak Default Passwords in dormakaba access manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59108</link><description>By default, the password for the Access Manager's web interface, is set to 'admin'. In the tested version changing the password was not enforced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59109 | UART Leaking Sensitive Data in dormakaba registration unit 9002</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59109</link><description>The dormakaba registration units 9002 (PIN Pad Units) have an exposed UART header on the backside. The PIN pad is sending every button press to the UART interface. An attacker can use the interface to exfiltrate PINs. As the devices are explicitly built as Plug-and-Play to be easily replaced, an attacker is easily able to remove the device, install a hardware implant which connects to the UART and exfiltrates the data exposed via UART to another system (e.g. via WiFi).</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27821 | HDFS native client: Out of bounds write in URI parser of native HDFS client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27821</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Hadoop HDFS native client.

This issue affects Apache Hadoop: from 3.2.0 before 3.4.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.4.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41083 | Improper Neutralization in Altitude Communication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41083</link><description>Vulnerability in Altitude Authentication Service and Altitude Communication Server v8.5.3290.0 by Altitude, where manipulation of Host header in HTTP requests allows redirection to an arbitrary URL or modification of the base URL to trick the victim into sending login credentials to a malicious website. This behavior can be used to redirect clients to endpoints controlled by the attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24656 | Apache Karaf: Decanter log-socket collector has deserialization vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24656</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Karaf Decanter.


The Decanter log socket collector exposes the port 4560, without authentication. If the collector exposes allowed classes property, this configuration can be bypassed.
It means that the log socket collector is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted data, eventually causing DoS.


NB: Decanter log socket collector is not installed by default. Users who have not installed Decanter log socket are not impacted by this issue.

This issue affects Apache Karaf Decanter before 2.12.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.12.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41082 | HTTP Request/Response Smuggling in Altitude Communication Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41082</link><description>Illegal HTTP request traffic vulnerability (CL.0) in Altitude Communication Server, caused by inconsistent analysis of multiple HTTP requests over a single Keep-Alive connection using  Content-Length headers. This can cause a desynchronization of requests between frontend and backend servers, which could allow request hiding, cache poisoning or security bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1428 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1428</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1429 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1429</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1427 | WellChoose｜Single Sign-On Portal System -  OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1427</link><description>Single Sign-On Portal System developed by WellChoose has a OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1425 | pymumu SmartDNS SVBC Record dns.c _dns_decode_SVCB_HTTPS stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1425</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in pymumu SmartDNS up to 47.1. This vulnerability affects the function _dns_decode_rr_head/_dns_decode_SVCB_HTTPS of the file src/dns.c of the component SVBC Record Parser. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The patch is identified as 2d57c4b4e1add9b4537aeb403f794a084727e1c8. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1424 | PHPGurukul News Portal Profile Pic unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1424</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in PHPGurukul News Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Profile Pic Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1423 | code-projects Online Examination System admin_pic.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1423</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin_pic.php. Executing a manipulation can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14316 | AhaChat Messenger Marketing &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14316</link><description>The AhaChat Messenger Marketing WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14973 | Recipe Card Blocks &amp;lt; 3.4.13 - Contributor+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14973</link><description>The Recipe Card Blocks Lite WordPress plugin before 3.4.13 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing contributors and above to perform SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1422 | code-projects Online Examination System Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Login Page. Performing a manipulation of the argument User results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1421 | code-projects Online Examination System Add Pages cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1421</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Add Pages. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1420 | Tenda AC23 WifiExtraSet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1420</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. This manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1419 | D-Link DCS700l Web Form setDayNightMode command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1419</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DCS700l 1.03.09. Affected is an unknown function of the file /setDayNightMode of the component Web Form Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument LightSensorControl can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1418 | GPAC SRT Subtitle Import text_to_bifs.c gf_text_import_srt_bifs out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1418</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in GPAC up to 2.4.0. This affects the function gf_text_import_srt_bifs of the file src/scene_manager/text_to_bifs.c of the component SRT Subtitle Import. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds write. The attack needs to be performed locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The name of the patch is 10c73b82cf0e367383d091db38566a0e4fe71772. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1416 | GPAC filedump.c DumpMovieInfo null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1416</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function DumpMovieInfo of the file applications/mp4box/filedump.c. The manipulation results in null pointer dereference. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The patch is identified as d45c264c20addf0c1cc05124ede33f8ffa800e68. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1417 | GPAC filedump.c dump_isom_rtp null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1417</link><description>A weakness has been identified in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected by this issue is the function dump_isom_rtp of the file applications/mp4box/filedump.c. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. Patch name: f96bd57c3ccdcde4335a0be28cd3e8fe296993de. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1414 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request get_Information getInformation command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1414</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. This impacts the function getInformation of the file /equipment/get_Information of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Executing a manipulation of the argument fortEquipmentIp can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1415 | GPAC media_export.c gf_media_export_webvtt_metadata null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in GPAC up to 2.4.0. Affected is the function gf_media_export_webvtt_metadata of the file src/media_tools/media_export.c. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to null pointer dereference. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is af951b892dfbaaa38336ba2eba6d6a42c25810fd. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1413 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request port_validate portValidate command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1413</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. This affects the function portValidate of the file /fort/ip_and_port/port_validate of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument port results in command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1412 | Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System HTTP POST Request get_clip_img command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1412</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Sangfor Operation and Maintenance Security Management System up to 3.0.12. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /fort/audit/get_clip_img of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument frame/dirno leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1410 | Beetel 777VR1 UART missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1410</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. Impacted is an unknown function of the component UART Interface. The manipulation results in missing authentication. An attack on the physical device is feasible. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1411 | Beetel 777VR1 UART access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1411</link><description>A flaw has been found in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. The affected element is an unknown function of the component UART Interface. This manipulation causes improper access controls. It is feasible to perform the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1409 | Beetel 777VR1 UART excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1409</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component UART Interface. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 23:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1408 | Beetel 777VR1 UART weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1408</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component UART Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to weak password requirements. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. The attack requires a high level of complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 23:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1407 | Beetel 777VR1 UART information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1407</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Beetel 777VR1 up to 01.00.09/01.00.09_55. This affects an unknown part of the component UART Interface. Performing a manipulation results in information disclosure. The attack may be carried out on the physical device. The attack is considered to have high complexity. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 22:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71162 | dmaengine: tegra-adma: Fix use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71162</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: tegra-adma: Fix use-after-free

A use-after-free bug exists in the Tegra ADMA driver when audio streams
are terminated, particularly during XRUN conditions. The issue occurs
when the DMA buffer is freed by tegra_adma_terminate_all() before the
vchan completion tasklet finishes accessing it.

The race condition follows this sequence:

  1. DMA transfer completes, triggering an interrupt that schedules the
     completion tasklet (tasklet has not executed yet)
  2. Audio playback stops, calling tegra_adma_terminate_all() which
     frees the DMA buffer memory via kfree()
  3. The scheduled tasklet finally executes, calling vchan_complete()
     which attempts to access the already-freed memory

Since tasklets can execute at any time after being scheduled, there is
no guarantee that the buffer will remain valid when vchan_complete()
runs.

Fix this by properly synchronizing the virtual channel completion:
 - Calling vchan_terminate_vdesc() in tegra_adma_stop() to mark the
   descriptors as terminated instead of freeing the descriptor.
 - Add the callback tegra_adma_synchronize() that calls
   vchan_synchronize() which kills any pending tasklets and frees any
   terminated descriptors.

Crash logs:
[  337.427523] BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in vchan_complete+0x124/0x3b0
[  337.427544] Read of size 8 at addr ffff000132055428 by task swapper/0/0

[  337.427562] Call trace:
[  337.427564]  dump_backtrace+0x0/0x320
[  337.427571]  show_stack+0x20/0x30
[  337.427575]  dump_stack_lvl+0x68/0x84
[  337.427584]  print_address_description.constprop.0+0x74/0x2b8
[  337.427590]  kasan_report+0x1f4/0x210
[  337.427598]  __asan_load8+0xa0/0xd0
[  337.427603]  vchan_complete+0x124/0x3b0
[  337.427609]  tasklet_action_common.constprop.0+0x190/0x1d0
[  337.427617]  tasklet_action+0x30/0x40
[  337.427623]  __do_softirq+0x1a0/0x5c4
[  337.427628]  irq_exit+0x110/0x140
[  337.427633]  handle_domain_irq+0xa4/0xe0
[  337.427640]  gic_handle_irq+0x64/0x160
[  337.427644]  call_on_irq_stack+0x20/0x4c
[  337.427649]  do_interrupt_handler+0x7c/0x90
[  337.427654]  el1_interrupt+0x30/0x80
[  337.427659]  el1h_64_irq_handler+0x18/0x30
[  337.427663]  el1h_64_irq+0x7c/0x80
[  337.427667]  cpuidle_enter_state+0xe4/0x540
[  337.427674]  cpuidle_enter+0x54/0x80
[  337.427679]  do_idle+0x2e0/0x380
[  337.427685]  cpu_startup_entry+0x2c/0x70
[  337.427690]  rest_init+0x114/0x130
[  337.427695]  arch_call_rest_init+0x18/0x24
[  337.427702]  start_kernel+0x380/0x3b4
[  337.427706]  __primary_switched+0xc0/0xc8</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-71163 | dmaengine: idxd: fix device leaks on compat bind and unbind</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-71163</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: idxd: fix device leaks on compat bind and unbind

Make sure to drop the reference taken when looking up the idxd device as
part of the compat bind and unbind sysfs interface.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22996 | net/mlx5e: Don&amp;#x27;t store mlx5e_priv in mlx5e_dev devlink priv</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22996</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5e: Don't store mlx5e_priv in mlx5e_dev devlink priv

mlx5e_priv is an unstable structure that can be memset(0) if profile
attaching fails, mlx5e_priv in mlx5e_dev devlink private is used to
reference the netdev and mdev associated with that struct. Instead,
store netdev directly into mlx5e_dev and get mdev from the containing
mlx5_adev aux device structure.

This fixes a kernel oops in mlx5e_remove when switchdev mode fails due
to change profile failure.

$ devlink dev eswitch set pci/0000:00:03.0 mode switchdev
Error: mlx5_core: Failed setting eswitch to offloads.
dmesg:
workqueue: Failed to create a rescuer kthread for wq "mlx5e": -EINTR
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1: mlx5e_netdev_init_profile:6214:(pid 37199): mlx5e_priv_init failed, err=-12
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1 gpu3rdma1: mlx5e_netdev_change_profile: new profile init failed, -12
workqueue: Failed to create a rescuer kthread for wq "mlx5e": -EINTR
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1: mlx5e_netdev_init_profile:6214:(pid 37199): mlx5e_priv_init failed, err=-12
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1 gpu3rdma1: mlx5e_netdev_change_profile: failed to rollback to orig profile, -12

$ devlink dev reload pci/0000:00:03.0 ==&gt; oops

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000520
 #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
 #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
PGD 0 P4D 0
Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] SMP NOPTI
CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 521 Comm: devlink Not tainted 6.18.0-rc5+ #117 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:mlx5e_remove+0x68/0x130
RSP: 0018:ffffc900034838f0 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: ffff88810283c380 RBX: ffff888101874400 RCX: ffffffff826ffc45
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000001 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffff888102d789c0 R08: ffff8881007137f0 R09: ffff888100264e10
R10: ffffc90003483898 R11: ffffc900034838a0 R12: ffff888100d261a0
R13: ffff888100d261a0 R14: ffff8881018749a0 R15: ffff888101874400
FS:  00007f8565fea740(0000) GS:ffff88856a759000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000000000000520 CR3: 000000010b11a004 CR4: 0000000000370ef0
Call Trace:
 
 device_release_driver_internal+0x19c/0x200
 bus_remove_device+0xc6/0x130
 device_del+0x160/0x3d0
 ? devl_param_driverinit_value_get+0x2d/0x90
 mlx5_detach_device+0x89/0xe0
 mlx5_unload_one_devl_locked+0x3a/0x70
 mlx5_devlink_reload_down+0xc8/0x220
 devlink_reload+0x7d/0x260
 devlink_nl_reload_doit+0x45b/0x5a0
 genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0xe8/0x140</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22997 | net: can: j1939: j1939_xtp_rx_rts_session_active(): deactivate session upon receiving the second rts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22997</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: can: j1939: j1939_xtp_rx_rts_session_active(): deactivate session upon receiving the second rts

Since j1939_session_deactivate_activate_next() in j1939_tp_rxtimer() is
called only when the timer is enabled, we need to call
j1939_session_deactivate_activate_next() if we cancelled the timer.
Otherwise, refcount for j1939_session leaks, which will later appear as

| unregister_netdevice: waiting for vcan0 to become free. Usage count = 2.

problem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22998 | nvme-tcp: fix NULL pointer dereferences in nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22998</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme-tcp: fix NULL pointer dereferences in nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec

Commit efa56305908b ("nvmet-tcp: Fix a kernel panic when host sends an invalid H2C PDU length")
added ttag bounds checking and data_offset
validation in nvmet_tcp_handle_h2c_data_pdu(), but it did not validate
whether the command's data structures (cmd-&gt;req.sg and cmd-&gt;iov) have
been properly initialized before processing H2C_DATA PDUs.

The nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec() function dereferences these pointers
without NULL checks. This can be triggered by sending H2C_DATA PDU
immediately after the ICREQ/ICRESP handshake, before
sending a CONNECT command or NVMe write command.

Attack vectors that trigger NULL pointer dereferences:
1. H2C_DATA PDU sent before CONNECT → both pointers NULL
2. H2C_DATA PDU for READ command → cmd-&gt;req.sg allocated, cmd-&gt;iov NULL
3. H2C_DATA PDU for uninitialized command slot → both pointers NULL

The fix validates both cmd-&gt;req.sg and cmd-&gt;iov before calling
nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec(). Both checks are required because:
- Uninitialized commands: both NULL
- READ commands: cmd-&gt;req.sg allocated, cmd-&gt;iov NULL
- WRITE commands: both allocated</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22999 | net/sched: sch_qfq: do not free existing class in qfq_change_class()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22999</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: sch_qfq: do not free existing class in qfq_change_class()

Fixes qfq_change_class() error case.

cl-&gt;qdisc and cl should only be freed if a new class and qdisc
were allocated, or we risk various UAF.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23000 | net/mlx5e: Fix crash on profile change rollback failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23000</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5e: Fix crash on profile change rollback failure

mlx5e_netdev_change_profile can fail to attach a new profile and can
fail to rollback to old profile, in such case, we could end up with a
dangling netdev with a fully reset netdev_priv. A retry to change
profile, e.g. another attempt to call mlx5e_netdev_change_profile via
switchdev mode change, will crash trying to access the now NULL
priv-&gt;mdev.

This fix allows mlx5e_netdev_change_profile() to handle previous
failures and an empty priv, by not assuming priv is valid.

Pass netdev and mdev to all flows requiring
mlx5e_netdev_change_profile() and avoid passing priv.
In mlx5e_netdev_change_profile() check if current priv is valid, and if
not, just attach the new profile without trying to access the old one.

This fixes the following oops, when enabling switchdev mode for the 2nd
time after first time failure:

 ## Enabling switchdev mode first time:

mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1: E-Switch: Supported tc chains and prios offload
workqueue: Failed to create a rescuer kthread for wq "mlx5e": -EINTR
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1: mlx5e_netdev_init_profile:6214:(pid 37199): mlx5e_priv_init failed, err=-12
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1 gpu3rdma1: mlx5e_netdev_change_profile: new profile init failed, -12
workqueue: Failed to create a rescuer kthread for wq "mlx5e": -EINTR
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1: mlx5e_netdev_init_profile:6214:(pid 37199): mlx5e_priv_init failed, err=-12
mlx5_core 0012:03:00.1 gpu3rdma1: mlx5e_netdev_change_profile: failed to rollback to orig profile, -12
                                                                         ^^^^^^^^
mlx5_core 0000:00:03.0: E-Switch: Disable: mode(LEGACY), nvfs(0), necvfs(0), active vports(0)

 ## retry: Enabling switchdev mode 2nd time:

mlx5_core 0000:00:03.0: E-Switch: Supported tc chains and prios offload
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000038
 #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
 #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
PGD 0 P4D 0
Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] SMP NOPTI
CPU: 13 UID: 0 PID: 520 Comm: devlink Not tainted 6.18.0-rc4+ #91 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:mlx5e_detach_netdev+0x3c/0x90
Code: 50 00 00 f0 80 4f 78 02 48 8b bf e8 07 00 00 48 85 ff 74 16 48 8b 73 78 48 d1 ee 83 e6 01 83 f6 01 40 0f b6 f6 e8 c4 42 00 00 &lt;48&gt; 8b 45 38 48 85 c0 74 08 48 89 df e8 cc 47 40 1e 48 8b bb f0 07
RSP: 0018:ffffc90000673890 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff8881036a89c0 RCX: 0000000000000000
RDX: ffff888113f63800 RSI: ffffffff822fe720 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000002dcd R09: 0000000000000000
R10: ffffc900006738e8 R11: 00000000ffffffff R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 0000000000000000 R14: ffff8881036a89c0 R15: 0000000000000000
FS:  00007fdfb8384740(0000) GS:ffff88856a9d6000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000000000000038 CR3: 0000000112ae0005 CR4: 0000000000370ef0
Call Trace:
 
 mlx5e_netdev_change_profile+0x45/0xb0
 mlx5e_vport_rep_load+0x27b/0x2d0
 mlx5_esw_offloads_rep_load+0x72/0xf0
 esw_offloads_enable+0x5d0/0x970
 mlx5_eswitch_enable_locked+0x349/0x430
 ? is_mp_supported+0x57/0xb0
 mlx5_devlink_eswitch_mode_set+0x26b/0x430
 devlink_nl_eswitch_set_doit+0x6f/0xf0
 genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0xe8/0x140
 genl_rcv_msg+0x18b/0x290
 ? __pfx_devlink_nl_pre_doit+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_devlink_nl_eswitch_set_doit+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_devlink_nl_post_doit+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_genl_rcv_msg+0x10/0x10
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x52/0x100
 genl_rcv+0x28/0x40
 netlink_unicast+0x282/0x3e0
 ? __alloc_skb+0xd6/0x190
 netlink_sendmsg+0x1f7/0x430
 __sys_sendto+0x213/0x220
 ? __sys_recvmsg+0x6a/0xd0
 __x64_sys_sendto+0x24/0x30
 do_syscall_64+0x50/0x1f0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e
RIP: 0033:0x7fdfb8495047</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23001 | macvlan: fix possible UAF in macvlan_forward_source()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23001</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

macvlan: fix possible UAF in macvlan_forward_source()

Add RCU protection on (struct macvlan_source_entry)-&gt;vlan.

Whenever macvlan_hash_del_source() is called, we must clear
entry-&gt;vlan pointer before RCU grace period starts.

This allows macvlan_forward_source() to skip over
entries queued for freeing.

Note that macvlan_dev are already RCU protected, as they
are embedded in a standard netdev (netdev_priv(ndev)).

https: //lore.kernel.org/netdev/695fb1e8.050a0220.1c677c.039f.GAE@google.com/T/#u</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23002 | lib/buildid: use __kernel_read() for sleepable context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23002</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

lib/buildid: use __kernel_read() for sleepable context

Prevent a "BUG: unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference in
filemap_read_folio".

For the sleepable context, convert freader to use __kernel_read() instead
of direct page cache access via read_cache_folio().  This simplifies the
faultable code path by using the standard kernel file reading interface
which handles all the complexity of reading file data.

At the moment we are not changing the code for non-sleepable context which
uses filemap_get_folio() and only succeeds if the target folios are
already in memory and up-to-date.  The reason is to keep the patch simple
and easier to backport to stable kernels.

Syzbot repro does not crash the kernel anymore and the selftests run
successfully.

In the follow up we will make __kernel_read() with IOCB_NOWAIT work for
non-sleepable contexts.  In addition, I would like to replace the
secretmem check with a more generic approach and will add fstest for the
buildid code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23003 | ip6_tunnel: use skb_vlan_inet_prepare() in __ip6_tnl_rcv()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23003</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ip6_tunnel: use skb_vlan_inet_prepare() in __ip6_tnl_rcv()

Blamed commit did not take care of VLAN encapsulations
as spotted by syzbot [1].

Use skb_vlan_inet_prepare() instead of pskb_inet_may_pull().

[1]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in __INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:253 [inline]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:275 [inline]
 BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in IP6_ECN_decapsulate+0x7a8/0x1fa0 include/net/inet_ecn.h:321
  __INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:253 [inline]
  INET_ECN_decapsulate include/net/inet_ecn.h:275 [inline]
  IP6_ECN_decapsulate+0x7a8/0x1fa0 include/net/inet_ecn.h:321
  ip6ip6_dscp_ecn_decapsulate+0x16f/0x1b0 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:729
  __ip6_tnl_rcv+0xed9/0x1b50 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:860
  ip6_tnl_rcv+0xc3/0x100 net/ipv6/ip6_tunnel.c:903
 gre_rcv+0x1529/0x1b90 net/ipv6/ip6_gre.c:-1
  ip6_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x1c89/0x2c60 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:438
  ip6_input_finish+0x1f4/0x4a0 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:489
  NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:318 [inline]
  ip6_input+0x9c/0x330 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:500
  ip6_mc_input+0x7ca/0xc10 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:590
  dst_input include/net/dst.h:474 [inline]
  ip6_rcv_finish+0x958/0x990 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:79
  NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:318 [inline]
  ipv6_rcv+0xf1/0x3c0 net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:311
  __netif_receive_skb_one_core net/core/dev.c:6139 [inline]
  __netif_receive_skb+0x1df/0xac0 net/core/dev.c:6252
  netif_receive_skb_internal net/core/dev.c:6338 [inline]
  netif_receive_skb+0x57/0x630 net/core/dev.c:6397
  tun_rx_batched+0x1df/0x980 drivers/net/tun.c:1485
  tun_get_user+0x5c0e/0x6c60 drivers/net/tun.c:1953
  tun_chr_write_iter+0x3e9/0x5c0 drivers/net/tun.c:1999
  new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
  vfs_write+0xbe2/0x15d0 fs/read_write.c:686
  ksys_write fs/read_write.c:738 [inline]
  __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:749 [inline]
  __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:746 [inline]
  __x64_sys_write+0x1fb/0x4d0 fs/read_write.c:746
  x64_sys_call+0x30ab/0x3e70 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:2
  do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
  do_syscall_64+0xd3/0xf80 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Uninit was created at:
  slab_post_alloc_hook mm/slub.c:4960 [inline]
  slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:5263 [inline]
  kmem_cache_alloc_node_noprof+0x9e7/0x17a0 mm/slub.c:5315
  kmalloc_reserve+0x13c/0x4b0 net/core/skbuff.c:586
  __alloc_skb+0x805/0x1040 net/core/skbuff.c:690
  alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:1383 [inline]
  alloc_skb_with_frags+0xc5/0xa60 net/core/skbuff.c:6712
  sock_alloc_send_pskb+0xacc/0xc60 net/core/sock.c:2995
  tun_alloc_skb drivers/net/tun.c:1461 [inline]
  tun_get_user+0x1142/0x6c60 drivers/net/tun.c:1794
  tun_chr_write_iter+0x3e9/0x5c0 drivers/net/tun.c:1999
  new_sync_write fs/read_write.c:593 [inline]
  vfs_write+0xbe2/0x15d0 fs/read_write.c:686
  ksys_write fs/read_write.c:738 [inline]
  __do_sys_write fs/read_write.c:749 [inline]
  __se_sys_write fs/read_write.c:746 [inline]
  __x64_sys_write+0x1fb/0x4d0 fs/read_write.c:746
  x64_sys_call+0x30ab/0x3e70 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:2
  do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
  do_syscall_64+0xd3/0xf80 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 6465 Comm: syz.0.17 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(none)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/25/2025</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23004 | dst: fix races in rt6_uncached_list_del() and rt_del_uncached_list()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23004</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dst: fix races in rt6_uncached_list_del() and rt_del_uncached_list()

syzbot was able to crash the kernel in rt6_uncached_list_flush_dev()
in an interesting way [1]

Crash happens in list_del_init()/INIT_LIST_HEAD() while writing
list-&gt;prev, while the prior write on list-&gt;next went well.

static inline void INIT_LIST_HEAD(struct list_head *list)
{
	WRITE_ONCE(list-&gt;next, list); // This went well
	WRITE_ONCE(list-&gt;prev, list); // Crash, @list has been freed.
}

Issue here is that rt6_uncached_list_del() did not attempt to lock
ul-&gt;lock, as list_empty(&amp;amp;rt-&gt;dst.rt_uncached) returned
true because the WRITE_ONCE(list-&gt;next, list) happened on the other CPU.

We might use list_del_init_careful() and list_empty_careful(),
or make sure rt6_uncached_list_del() always grabs the spinlock
whenever rt-&gt;dst.rt_uncached_list has been set.

A similar fix is neeed for IPv4.

[1]

 BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in INIT_LIST_HEAD include/linux/list.h:46 [inline]
 BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in list_del_init include/linux/list.h:296 [inline]
 BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in rt6_uncached_list_flush_dev net/ipv6/route.c:191 [inline]
 BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in rt6_disable_ip+0x633/0x730 net/ipv6/route.c:5020
Write of size 8 at addr ffff8880294cfa78 by task kworker/u8:14/3450

CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 3450 Comm: kworker/u8:14 Tainted: G             L      syzkaller #0 PREEMPT_{RT,(full)}
Tainted: [L]=SOFTLOCKUP
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/25/2025
Workqueue: netns cleanup_net
Call Trace:
 
  dump_stack_lvl+0xe8/0x150 lib/dump_stack.c:120
  print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
  print_report+0xca/0x240 mm/kasan/report.c:482
  kasan_report+0x118/0x150 mm/kasan/report.c:595
  INIT_LIST_HEAD include/linux/list.h:46 [inline]
  list_del_init include/linux/list.h:296 [inline]
  rt6_uncached_list_flush_dev net/ipv6/route.c:191 [inline]
  rt6_disable_ip+0x633/0x730 net/ipv6/route.c:5020
  addrconf_ifdown+0x143/0x18a0 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3853
 addrconf_notify+0x1bc/0x1050 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:-1
  notifier_call_chain+0x19d/0x3a0 kernel/notifier.c:85
  call_netdevice_notifiers_extack net/core/dev.c:2268 [inline]
  call_netdevice_notifiers net/core/dev.c:2282 [inline]
  netif_close_many+0x29c/0x410 net/core/dev.c:1785
  unregister_netdevice_many_notify+0xb50/0x2330 net/core/dev.c:12353
  ops_exit_rtnl_list net/core/net_namespace.c:187 [inline]
  ops_undo_list+0x3dc/0x990 net/core/net_namespace.c:248
  cleanup_net+0x4de/0x7b0 net/core/net_namespace.c:696
  process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3257 [inline]
  process_scheduled_works+0xad1/0x1770 kernel/workqueue.c:3340
  worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3421
  kthread+0x711/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:463
  ret_from_fork+0x510/0xa50 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:158
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:246
 

Allocated by task 803:
  kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:57 [inline]
  kasan_save_track+0x3e/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:78
  unpoison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:340 [inline]
  __kasan_slab_alloc+0x6c/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:366
  kasan_slab_alloc include/linux/kasan.h:253 [inline]
  slab_post_alloc_hook mm/slub.c:4953 [inline]
  slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:5263 [inline]
  kmem_cache_alloc_noprof+0x18d/0x6c0 mm/slub.c:5270
  dst_alloc+0x105/0x170 net/core/dst.c:89
  ip6_dst_alloc net/ipv6/route.c:342 [inline]
  icmp6_dst_alloc+0x75/0x460 net/ipv6/route.c:3333
  mld_sendpack+0x683/0xe60 net/ipv6/mcast.c:1844
  mld_send_cr net/ipv6/mcast.c:2154 [inline]
  mld_ifc_work+0x83e/0xd60 net/ipv6/mcast.c:2693
  process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3257 [inline]
  process_scheduled_works+0xad1/0x1770 kernel/workqueue.c:3340
  worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3421
  kthread+0x711/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:463
  ret_from_fork+0x510/0xa50 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:158
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entr
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23005 | x86/fpu: Clear XSTATE_BV[i] in guest XSAVE state whenever XFD[i]=1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23005</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/fpu: Clear XSTATE_BV[i] in guest XSAVE state whenever XFD[i]=1

When loading guest XSAVE state via KVM_SET_XSAVE, and when updating XFD in
response to a guest WRMSR, clear XFD-disabled features in the saved (or to
be restored) XSTATE_BV to ensure KVM doesn't attempt to load state for
features that are disabled via the guest's XFD.  Because the kernel
executes XRSTOR with the guest's XFD, saving XSTATE_BV[i]=1 with XFD[i]=1
will cause XRSTOR to #NM and panic the kernel.

E.g. if fpu_update_guest_xfd() sets XFD without clearing XSTATE_BV:

  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  WARNING: arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:1524 at exc_device_not_available+0x101/0x110, CPU#29: amx_test/848
  Modules linked in: kvm_intel kvm irqbypass
  CPU: 29 UID: 1000 PID: 848 Comm: amx_test Not tainted 6.19.0-rc2-ffa07f7fd437-x86_amx_nm_xfd_non_init-vm #171 NONE
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 0.0.0 02/06/2015
  RIP: 0010:exc_device_not_available+0x101/0x110
  Call Trace:
   
   asm_exc_device_not_available+0x1a/0x20
  RIP: 0010:restore_fpregs_from_fpstate+0x36/0x90
   switch_fpu_return+0x4a/0xb0
   kvm_arch_vcpu_ioctl_run+0x1245/0x1e40 [kvm]
   kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x2c3/0x8f0 [kvm]
   __x64_sys_ioctl+0x8f/0xd0
   do_syscall_64+0x62/0x940
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53
   
  ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

This can happen if the guest executes WRMSR(MSR_IA32_XFD) to set XFD[18] = 1,
and a host IRQ triggers kernel_fpu_begin() prior to the vmexit handler's
call to fpu_update_guest_xfd().

and if userspace stuffs XSTATE_BV[i]=1 via KVM_SET_XSAVE:

  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  WARNING: arch/x86/kernel/traps.c:1524 at exc_device_not_available+0x101/0x110, CPU#14: amx_test/867
  Modules linked in: kvm_intel kvm irqbypass
  CPU: 14 UID: 1000 PID: 867 Comm: amx_test Not tainted 6.19.0-rc2-2dace9faccd6-x86_amx_nm_xfd_non_init-vm #168 NONE
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 0.0.0 02/06/2015
  RIP: 0010:exc_device_not_available+0x101/0x110
  Call Trace:
   
   asm_exc_device_not_available+0x1a/0x20
  RIP: 0010:restore_fpregs_from_fpstate+0x36/0x90
   fpu_swap_kvm_fpstate+0x6b/0x120
   kvm_load_guest_fpu+0x30/0x80 [kvm]
   kvm_arch_vcpu_ioctl_run+0x85/0x1e40 [kvm]
   kvm_vcpu_ioctl+0x2c3/0x8f0 [kvm]
   __x64_sys_ioctl+0x8f/0xd0
   do_syscall_64+0x62/0x940
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53
   
  ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

The new behavior is consistent with the AMX architecture.  Per Intel's SDM,
XSAVE saves XSTATE_BV as '0' for components that are disabled via XFD
(and non-compacted XSAVE saves the initial configuration of the state
component):

  If XSAVE, XSAVEC, XSAVEOPT, or XSAVES is saving the state component i,
  the instruction does not generate #NM when XCR0[i] = IA32_XFD[i] = 1;
  instead, it operates as if XINUSE[i] = 0 (and the state component was
  in its initial state): it saves bit i of XSTATE_BV field of the XSAVE
  header as 0; in addition, XSAVE saves the initial configuration of the
  state component (the other instructions do not save state component i).

Alternatively, KVM could always do XRSTOR with XFD=0, e.g. by using
a constant XFD based on the set of enabled features when XSAVEing for
a struct fpu_guest.  However, having XSTATE_BV[i]=1 for XFD-disabled
features can only happen in the above interrupt case, or in similar
scenarios involving preemption on preemptible kernels, because
fpu_swap_kvm_fpstate()'s call to save_fpregs_to_fpstate() saves the
outgoing FPU state with the current XFD; and that is (on all but the
first WRMSR to XFD) the guest XFD.

Therefore, XFD can only go out of sync with XSTATE_BV in the above
interrupt case, or in similar scenarios involving preemption on
preemptible kernels, and it we can consider it (de facto) part of KVM
ABI that KVM_GET_XSAVE returns XSTATE_BV[i]=0 for XFD-disabled features.

[Move clea
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23006 | ASoC: tlv320adcx140: fix null pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23006</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: tlv320adcx140: fix null pointer

The "snd_soc_component" in "adcx140_priv" was only used once but never
set. It was only used for reaching "dev" which is already present in
"adcx140_priv".</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23007 | block: zero non-PI portion of auto integrity buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23007</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

block: zero non-PI portion of auto integrity buffer

The auto-generated integrity buffer for writes needs to be fully
initialized before being passed to the underlying block device,
otherwise the uninitialized memory can be read back by userspace or
anyone with physical access to the storage device. If protection
information is generated, that portion of the integrity buffer is
already initialized. The integrity data is also zeroed if PI generation
is disabled via sysfs or the PI tuple size is 0. However, this misses
the case where PI is generated and the PI tuple size is nonzero, but the
metadata size is larger than the PI tuple. In this case, the remainder
("opaque") of the metadata is left uninitialized.
Generalize the BLK_INTEGRITY_CSUM_NONE check to cover any case when the
metadata is larger than just the PI tuple.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23008 | drm/vmwgfx: Fix KMS with 3D on HW version 10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23008</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/vmwgfx: Fix KMS with 3D on HW version 10

HW version 10 does not have GB Surfaces so there is no backing buffer for
surface backed FBs. This would result in a nullptr dereference and crash
the driver causing a black screen.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23009 | xhci: sideband: don&amp;#x27;t dereference freed ring when removing sideband endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23009</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xhci: sideband: don't dereference freed ring when removing sideband endpoint

xhci_sideband_remove_endpoint() incorrecly assumes that the endpoint is
running and has a valid transfer ring.

Lianqin reported a crash during suspend/wake-up stress testing, and
found the cause to be dereferencing a non-existing transfer ring
'ep-&gt;ring' during xhci_sideband_remove_endpoint().

The endpoint and its ring may be in unknown state if this function
is called after xHCI was reinitialized in resume (lost power), or if
device is being re-enumerated, disconnected or endpoint already dropped.

Fix this by both removing unnecessary ring access, and by checking
ep-&gt;ring exists before dereferencing it. Also make sure endpoint is
running before attempting to stop it.

Remove the xhci_initialize_ring_info() call during sideband endpoint
removal as is it only initializes ring structure enqueue, dequeue and
cycle state values to their starting values without changing actual
hardware enqueue, dequeue and cycle state. Leaving them out of sync
is worse than leaving it as it is. The endpoint will get freed in after
this in most usecases.

If the (audio) class driver want's to reuse the endpoint after offload
then it is up to the class driver to ensure endpoint is properly set up.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23010 | ipv6: Fix use-after-free in inet6_addr_del().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23010</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: Fix use-after-free in inet6_addr_del().

syzbot reported use-after-free of inet6_ifaddr in
inet6_addr_del(). [0]

The cited commit accidentally moved ipv6_del_addr() for
mngtmpaddr before reading its ifp-&gt;flags for temporary
addresses in inet6_addr_del().

Let's move ipv6_del_addr() down to fix the UAF.

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in inet6_addr_del.constprop.0+0x67a/0x6b0 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3117
Read of size 4 at addr ffff88807b89c86c by task syz.3.1618/9593

CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 9593 Comm: syz.3.1618 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/25/2025
Call Trace:
 
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x116/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xcd/0x630 mm/kasan/report.c:482
 kasan_report+0xe0/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:595
 inet6_addr_del.constprop.0+0x67a/0x6b0 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3117
 addrconf_del_ifaddr+0x11e/0x190 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3181
 inet6_ioctl+0x1e5/0x2b0 net/ipv6/af_inet6.c:582
 sock_do_ioctl+0x118/0x280 net/socket.c:1254
 sock_ioctl+0x227/0x6b0 net/socket.c:1375
 vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
 __se_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:583 [inline]
 __x64_sys_ioctl+0x18e/0x210 fs/ioctl.c:583
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xcd/0xf80 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
RIP: 0033:0x7f164cf8f749
Code: ff ff c3 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 40 00 48 89 f8 48 89 f7 48 89 d6 48 89 ca 4d 89 c2 4d 89 c8 4c 8b 4c 24 08 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 c7 c1 a8 ff ff ff f7 d8 64 89 01 48
RSP: 002b:00007f164de64038 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000010
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007f164d1e5fa0 RCX: 00007f164cf8f749
RDX: 0000200000000000 RSI: 0000000000008936 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00007f164d013f91 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 00007f164d1e6038 R14: 00007f164d1e5fa0 R15: 00007ffde15c8288
 

Allocated by task 9593:
 kasan_save_stack+0x33/0x60 mm/kasan/common.c:56
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30 mm/kasan/common.c:77
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:397 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0xaa/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:414
 kmalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:957 [inline]
 kzalloc_noprof include/linux/slab.h:1094 [inline]
 ipv6_add_addr+0x4e3/0x2010 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:1120
 inet6_addr_add+0x256/0x9b0 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3050
 addrconf_add_ifaddr+0x1fc/0x450 net/ipv6/addrconf.c:3160
 inet6_ioctl+0x103/0x2b0 net/ipv6/af_inet6.c:580
 sock_do_ioctl+0x118/0x280 net/socket.c:1254
 sock_ioctl+0x227/0x6b0 net/socket.c:1375
 vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
 __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:597 [inline]
 __se_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:583 [inline]
 __x64_sys_ioctl+0x18e/0x210 fs/ioctl.c:583
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xcd/0xf80 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Freed by task 6099:
 kasan_save_stack+0x33/0x60 mm/kasan/common.c:56
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30 mm/kasan/common.c:77
 kasan_save_free_info+0x3b/0x60 mm/kasan/generic.c:584
 poison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:252 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_free+0x5f/0x80 mm/kasan/common.c:284
 kasan_slab_free include/linux/kasan.h:234 [inline]
 slab_free_hook mm/slub.c:2540 [inline]
 slab_free_freelist_hook mm/slub.c:2569 [inline]
 slab_free_bulk mm/slub.c:6696 [inline]
 kmem_cache_free_bulk mm/slub.c:7383 [inline]
 kmem_cache_free_bulk+0x2bf/0x680 mm/slub.c:7362
 kfree_bulk include/linux/slab.h:830 [inline]
 kvfree_rcu_bulk+0x1b7/0x1e0 mm/slab_common.c:1523
 kvfree_rcu_drain_ready mm/slab_common.c:1728 [inline]
 kfree_rcu_monitor+0x1d0/0x2f0 mm/slab_common.c:1801
 process_one_work+0x9ba/0x1b20 kernel/workqueue.c:3257
 process_scheduled_works kernel/workqu
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23011 | ipv4: ip_gre: make ipgre_header() robust</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23011</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv4: ip_gre: make ipgre_header() robust

Analog to commit db5b4e39c4e6 ("ip6_gre: make ip6gre_header() robust")

Over the years, syzbot found many ways to crash the kernel
in ipgre_header() [1].

This involves team or bonding drivers ability to dynamically
change their dev-&gt;needed_headroom and/or dev-&gt;hard_header_len

In this particular crash mld_newpack() allocated an skb
with a too small reserve/headroom, and by the time mld_sendpack()
was called, syzbot managed to attach an ipgre device.

[1]
skbuff: skb_under_panic: text:ffffffff89ea3cb7 len:2030915468 put:2030915372 head:ffff888058b43000 data:ffff887fdfa6e194 tail:0x120 end:0x6c0 dev:team0
 kernel BUG at net/core/skbuff.c:213 !
Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN PTI
CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 1322 Comm: kworker/1:9 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 10/25/2025
Workqueue: mld mld_ifc_work
 RIP: 0010:skb_panic+0x157/0x160 net/core/skbuff.c:213
Call Trace:
 
  skb_under_panic net/core/skbuff.c:223 [inline]
  skb_push+0xc3/0xe0 net/core/skbuff.c:2641
  ipgre_header+0x67/0x290 net/ipv4/ip_gre.c:897
  dev_hard_header include/linux/netdevice.h:3436 [inline]
  neigh_connected_output+0x286/0x460 net/core/neighbour.c:1618
  NF_HOOK_COND include/linux/netfilter.h:307 [inline]
  ip6_output+0x340/0x550 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:247
  NF_HOOK+0x9e/0x380 include/linux/netfilter.h:318
  mld_sendpack+0x8d4/0xe60 net/ipv6/mcast.c:1855
  mld_send_cr net/ipv6/mcast.c:2154 [inline]
  mld_ifc_work+0x83e/0xd60 net/ipv6/mcast.c:2693
  process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3257 [inline]
  process_scheduled_works+0xad1/0x1770 kernel/workqueue.c:3340
  worker_thread+0x8a0/0xda0 kernel/workqueue.c:3421
  kthread+0x711/0x8a0 kernel/kthread.c:463
  ret_from_fork+0x510/0xa50 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:158
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:246</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23012 | mm/damon/core: remove call_control in inactive contexts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23012</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/damon/core: remove call_control in inactive contexts

If damon_call() is executed against a DAMON context that is not running,
the function returns error while keeping the damon_call_control object
linked to the context's call_controls list.  Let's suppose the object is
deallocated after the damon_call(), and yet another damon_call() is
executed against the same context.  The function tries to add the new
damon_call_control object to the call_controls list, which still has the
pointer to the previous damon_call_control object, which is deallocated. 
As a result, use-after-free happens.

This can actually be triggered using the DAMON sysfs interface.  It is not
easily exploitable since it requires the sysfs write permission and making
a definitely weird file writes, though.  Please refer to the report for
more details about the issue reproduction steps.

Fix the issue by making two changes.  Firstly, move the final
kdamond_call() for cancelling all existing damon_call() requests from
terminating DAMON context to be done before the ctx-&gt;kdamond reset.  This
makes any code that sees NULL ctx-&gt;kdamond can safely assume the context
may not access damon_call() requests anymore.  Secondly, let damon_call()
to cleanup the damon_call_control objects that were added to the
already-terminated DAMON context, before returning the error.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23013 | net: octeon_ep_vf: fix free_irq dev_id mismatch in IRQ rollback</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23013</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: octeon_ep_vf: fix free_irq dev_id mismatch in IRQ rollback

octep_vf_request_irqs() requests MSI-X queue IRQs with dev_id set to
ioq_vector. If request_irq() fails part-way, the rollback loop calls
free_irq() with dev_id set to 'oct', which does not match the original
dev_id and may leave the irqaction registered.

This can keep IRQ handlers alive while ioq_vector is later freed during
unwind/teardown, leading to a use-after-free or crash when an interrupt
fires.

Fix the error path to free IRQs with the same ioq_vector dev_id used
during request_irq().</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36933 | IPTInstaller 4.0.9 - &amp;#x27;PassThru Service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36933</link><description>HTC IPTInstaller 4.0.9 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the PassThru Service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path to inject and execute malicious code with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36934 | Deep Instinct Windows Agent 1.2.24.0 - &amp;#x27;DeepNetworkService&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36934</link><description>Deep Instinct Windows Agent 1.2.24.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the DeepNetworkService that allows local users to potentially execute code with elevated privileges. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in C:\Program Files\HP Sure Sense\DeepNetworkService.exe to inject malicious code that would execute with LocalSystem permissions during service startup.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36935 | KMSpico 17.1.0.0 - &amp;#x27;Service KMSELDI&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36935</link><description>KMSpico 17.1.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the Service KMSELDI configuration that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path in C:\Program Files\KMSpico\Service_KMS.exe to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36936 | Magic Mouse 2 utilities  2.20 - &amp;#x27;magicmouse2service&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36936</link><description>Magic Mouse 2 Utilities 2.20 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in its Windows service configuration. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path to inject malicious executables and gain elevated system privileges by placing a malicious file in the service path.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36937 | MEMU PLAY 3.7.0 - &amp;#x27;MEmusvc&amp;#x27; Unquoted Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36937</link><description>Microvirt MEMU Play 3.7.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the MEmusvc Windows service that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted binary path to inject malicious executables that will be run with elevated LocalSystem privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36932 | Seacms 11.1 - &amp;#x27;checkuser&amp;#x27; Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36932</link><description>SeaCMS 11.1 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the checkuser parameter of the admin settings page. Attackers can inject malicious JavaScript payloads that will execute in users' browsers when the page is loaded.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36931 | Click2Magic 1.1.5 - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36931</link><description>Click2Magic 1.1.5 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious scripts in the chat name input. Attackers can craft a malicious payload in the chat name to capture administrator cookies when the admin processes user requests.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:07:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1406 | lcg0124 BootDo Host Header AccessControlFilter.java redirectToLogin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1406</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in lcg0124 BootDo up to 5ccd963c74058036b466e038cff37de4056c1600. Affected by this vulnerability is the function redirectToLogin of the file AccessControlFilter.java of the component Host Header Handler. This manipulation of the argument Hostname causes open redirect. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6461 | CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Unauthenticated Post Disclosure in class-cubewp-search-ajax-hooks.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6461</link><description>The CubeWP – All-in-One Dynamic Content Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.27 via the search feature in class-cubewp-search-ajax-hooks.php due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>