<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6518 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6518</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6520 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6520</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5614 | Piotnet Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5614</link><description>The Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 via the 'pafe_posts_list' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including titles and excerpts of future, draft, and pending blog posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6521 | fluentform &amp;lt;= 5.1.19 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6521</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6627 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via PDF View Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6627</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's PDF View widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6897 | aThemes Starter Sites &amp;lt;= 1.0.53 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6897</link><description>The aThemes Starter Sites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.53 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 11:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6458 | WooCommerce Product Table Lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Missing Authorization to (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6458</link><description>The WooCommerce Product Table Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post title modification due to a missing capability check on the wcpt_presets__duplicate_preset_to_table function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber access and above to change titles of arbitrary posts. Missing sanitization can lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting when viewed by an admin via the WooCommerce Product Table.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 08:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6569 | Campaign Monitor for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6569</link><description>The Campaign Monitor for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15. This is due the plugin not properly restricting direct access to /forms/views/admin/create.php and display_errors being enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 08:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5969 | AIomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5969</link><description>The AIomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary email sending vulnerability in versions up to, and including, 2.0.5. This is due to insufficient limitations on the email recipient and the content in the 'aiomatic_send_email' function which are reachable via AJAX. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails with any content to any recipient.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 07:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42029 | xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland (aka an XDG Desktop Portal backend for Hyprland) before 1.3.3 allows OS command execution, e.g., because single ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42029</link><description>xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland (aka an XDG Desktop Portal backend for Hyprland) before 1.3.3 allows OS command execution, e.g., because single quotes are not used when sending a list of app IDs and titles via the environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 04:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1798 | Tutor LMS – Migration Tool &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization in tutor_lp_export_xml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1798</link><description>The Tutor LMS – Migration Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the tutor_lp_export_xml function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export courses, including private and password protected courses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1804 | Tutor LMS – Migration Tool &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization in tutor_import_from_xml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1804</link><description>The Tutor LMS – Migration Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the tutor_import_from_xml function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to import courses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4410 | IgnitionDeck Crowdfunding Platform &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4410</link><description>The IgnitionDeck Crowdfunding Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This is due to missing capability checks on various functions called via AJAX actions in the ~/classes/class-idf-wizard.php file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to execute various AJAX actions. This includes actions to change the permalink structure, plugin settings and others.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6152 | Flipbox Builder &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6152</link><description>The Flipbox Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the flipbox_builder_Flipbox_ShortCode function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6431 | Media.net Ads Manager &amp;lt;= 2.10.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6431</link><description>The Media.net Ads Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation and missing capability check in the 'sendMail' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level and above permissions, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The vulnerability is only exploitable if anyone has ever logged in through the API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6545 | Admin Trim Interface &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6545</link><description>The Admin Trim Interface plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6546 | One Click Close Comments &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6546</link><description>The One Click Close Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6547 | Add Admin CSS &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6547</link><description>The Add Admin CSS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1.  This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6548 | Add Admin JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6548</link><description>The Add Admin JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6549 | Admin Post Navigation &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6549</link><description>The Admin Post Navigation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1. This is due to the plugin utilizing bootstrap and leaving test files with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6566 | Aramex Shipping WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.21 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6566</link><description>The Aramex Shipping WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.21. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the composer-setup.php file which also has display_errors enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6573 | Intelligence &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6573</link><description>The Intelligence plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This is due the plugin not preventing direct access to the /vendor/levelten/intel/realtime/index.php file and display_errors being enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6591 | Ultimate WordPress Auction Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Email Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6591</link><description>The Ultimate WordPress Auction Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email creation and sending due to a missing capability check on the 'send_auction_email_callback' and 'resend_auction_email_callback' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to craft emails that include links and send to any email address.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6634 | Master Currency WP &amp;lt;= 1.1.61 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Currency Converter Form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6634</link><description>The Master Currency WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's currencyconverterform shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.61 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6661 | ParityPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6661</link><description>The ParityPress – Parity Pricing with Discount Rules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via  'Discount Text' in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 02:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37034 | An issue was discovered in Couchbase Server before 7.2.5 and 7.6.0 before 7.6.1. It does not ensure that credentials are negotiated with the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37034</link><description>An issue was discovered in Couchbase Server before 7.2.5 and 7.6.0 before 7.6.1. It does not ensure that credentials are negotiated with the Key-Value (KV) service using SCRAM-SHA when remote link encryption is configured for Half-Secure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:30:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40433 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Tencent wechat v.8.0.37 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the web-view component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40433</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Tencent wechat v.8.0.37 allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the web-view component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41815 | Starship vulnerable to shell injection via undocumented, unpredictable shell expansion in custom commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41815</link><description>Starship is a cross-shell prompt. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 1.20.0, undocumented and unpredictable shell expansion and/or quoting rules make it easily to accidentally cause shell injection when using custom commands with starship in bash. This issue only affects users with custom commands, so the scope is limited, and without knowledge of others' commands, it could be hard to successfully target someone. Version 1.20.0 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41118 | streamlit-geospatial blind SSRF in pages/7_📦_Web_Map_Service.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41118</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `url` variable on line 47 of `pages/7_📦_Web_Map_Service.py` takes user input, which is passed to `get_layers` function, in which `url` is used with `get_wms_layer` method. `get_wms_layer` method creates a request to arbitrary destinations, leading to blind server-side request forgery. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41119 | streamlit-geospatial remote code execution in pages/8_🏜️_Raster_Data_Visualization.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41119</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `vis_params` variable on line 80 in `8_🏜️_Raster_Data_Visualization.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 86, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41120 | streamlit-geospatial blind SSRF in pages/9_🔲_Vector_Data_Visualization.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41120</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `url` variable on line 63 of `pages/9_🔲_Vector_Data_Visualization.py` takes user input, which is later passed to the `gpd.read_file` method. `gpd.read_file` method creates a request to arbitrary destinations, leading to blind server-side request forgery. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41117 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/10_🌍_Earth_Engine_Datasets.py</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41117</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `vis_params` variable on line 115 in `pages/10_🌍_Earth_Engine_Datasets.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 126, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41628 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Severalnines Cluster Control 2.1.0-9780 and before allows a remote attacker to include and display file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41628</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Severalnines Cluster Control 2.1.0-9780 and before allows a remote attacker to include and display file content in an HTTP request via the CMON API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41114 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py MODIS Gap filled Land Surface Temperature Daily option</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41114</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `palette` variable on line 430 in `pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 435, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41115 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py MODIS Ocean Color SMI option palette</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41115</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `palette` variable on line 488 in `pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 493, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41116 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py MODIS Ocean Color SMI option vis_params</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41116</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `vis_params` variable on line 1254 in `pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 1345, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41112 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py Any Earth Engine ImageCollection option palette</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41112</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the palette variable in `pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 380, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41113 | Remote code execution in streamlit geospatial in pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py Any Earth Engine ImageCollection option vis_params</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41113</link><description>streamlit-geospatial is a streamlit multipage app for geospatial applications. Prior to commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489, the `vis_params` variable on line 383 or line 390 in `pages/1_📷_Timelapse.py` takes user input, which is later used in the `eval()` function on line 395, leading to remote code execution. Commit c4f81d9616d40c60584e36abb15300853a66e489 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38508 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in the web interface or SSH captive command shell interface of XCC that could allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38508</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in the web interface or SSH captive command shell interface of XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38509 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38509</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted IPMI command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38510 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in the SSH captive command shell interface that could allow an authenticated XCC user wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38510</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in the SSH captive command shell interface that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via specially crafted file uploads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38511 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in an upload processing functionality of XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38511</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in an upload processing functionality of XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via specially crafted file uploads.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38512 | A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38512</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was discovered in XCC that could allow an authenticated XCC user with elevated privileges to perform command injection via specially crafted IPMI commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4786 | An improper validation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Tab K10 that could allow a specially crafted application to keep the device ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4786</link><description>An improper validation vulnerability was reported in the Lenovo Tab K10 that could allow a specially crafted application to keep the device on.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40116 | An issue in Solar-Log 1000 before v2.8.2 and build 52-23.04.2013 was discovered to store plaintext passwords in the export.html, email.html,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40116</link><description>An issue in Solar-Log 1000 before v2.8.2 and build 52-23.04.2013 was discovered to store plaintext passwords in the export.html, email.html, and sms.html files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40117 | Incorrect access control in Solar-Log 1000 before v2.8.2 and build 52- 23.04.2013 allows attackers to obtain Administrative privileges via c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40117</link><description>Incorrect access control in Solar-Log 1000 before v2.8.2 and build 52- 23.04.2013 allows attackers to obtain Administrative privileges via connecting to the web administration server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42007 | SPX (aka php-spx) through 0.4.15 allows SPX_UI_URI Directory Traversal to read arbitrary files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42007</link><description>SPX (aka php-spx) through 0.4.15 allows SPX_UI_URI Directory Traversal to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38872 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38872</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5717 and below are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in the monitoring module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39304 | ChurchCRM SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39304</link><description>ChurchCRM is an open-source church management system. Versions of the application prior to 5.9.2 are vulnerable to an authenticated SQL injection due to an improper sanitization of user input. Authentication is required, but no elevated privileges are necessary. This allows attackers to inject SQL statements directly into the database query due to inadequate sanitization of the EID parameter in in a GET request to `/GetText.php`. Version 5.9.2 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38871 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38871</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5717 and below are vulnerable to the authenticated SQL injection in the reports module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50700 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Deepin dde-file-manager 6.0.54 and earlier allows privileged operations to be called by unprivileged u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50700</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Deepin dde-file-manager 6.0.54 and earlier allows privileged operations to be called by unprivileged users via the D-Bus method.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41812 | txtdot SSRF vulnerability in /get</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41812</link><description>txtdot is an HTTP proxy that parses only text, links, and pictures from pages, removing ads and heavy scripts. Prior to version 1.7.0, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `/get` route of txtdot allows remote attackers to use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and retrieve information in the internal network. Version 1.7.0 prevents displaying the response of forged requests, but the requests can still be sent. For complete mitigation, a firewall between txtdot and other internal network resources should be set.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41813 | txtdot SSRF vulnerability in /proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41813</link><description>txtdot is an HTTP proxy that parses only text, links, and pictures from pages, removing ads and heavy scripts. Starting in version 1.4.0 and prior to version 1.6.1, a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `/proxy` route of txtdot allows remote attackers to use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and retrieve information in the internal network. Version 1.6.1 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27357 | An issue was discovered in WithSecure Elements Agent through 23.x for macOS, WithSecure Elements Client Security through 23.x for macOS, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27357</link><description>An issue was discovered in WithSecure Elements Agent through 23.x for macOS, WithSecure Elements Client Security through 23.x for macOS, and WithSecure MDR through 23.x for macOS. Local Privilege Escalation can occur during installations or updates by admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27358 | An issue was discovered in WithSecure Elements Agent through 23.x for macOS and WithSecure Elements Client Security through 23.x for macOS. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27358</link><description>An issue was discovered in WithSecure Elements Agent through 23.x for macOS and WithSecure Elements Client Security through 23.x for macOS. Local users can block an admin from completing an installation, aka a Denial-of-Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24257 | An issue in skteco.com Central Control Attendance Machine web management platform v.3.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24257</link><description>An issue in skteco.com Central Control Attendance Machine web management platform v.3.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the csl/user component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26520 | An issue in Hangzhou Xiongwei Technology Development Co., Ltd. Restaurant Digital Comprehensive Management platform v1 allows an attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26520</link><description>An issue in Hangzhou Xiongwei Technology Development Co., Ltd. Restaurant Digital Comprehensive Management platform v1 allows an attacker to bypass authentication and perform arbitrary password resets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41373 | ICEcoder 8.1 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability via lib/backup-versions-preview-loader.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41373</link><description>ICEcoder 8.1 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability via lib/backup-versions-preview-loader.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41374 | ICEcoder 8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via lib/settings-screen.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41374</link><description>ICEcoder 8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via lib/settings-screen.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41375 | ICEcoder 8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via lib/terminal-xhr.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41375</link><description>ICEcoder 8.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via lib/terminal-xhr.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41353 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\groups\edit-group.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41353</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\groups\edit-group.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41354 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/admin/widgets/edit.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41354</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/admin/widgets/edit.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41355 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/tools/request-ip/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41355</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/tools/request-ip/index.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41356 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\firewall-zones\zones-edit-network.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41356</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via app\admin\firewall-zones\zones-edit-network.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41357 | phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/admin/powerDNS/record-edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41357</link><description>phpipam 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /app/admin/powerDNS/record-edit.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7050 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services may allow Multi-factor Authentication Bypass in particular sce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7050</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in OpenText OpenText Directory Services may allow Multi-factor Authentication Bypass in particular scenarios.This issue affects OpenText Directory Services: 24.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41670 | PayPal Official Module for PrestaShop has Improperly Implemented Security Check for Standard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41670</link><description>In the module "PayPal Official" for PrestaShop 7+ releases prior to version 6.4.2 and for PrestaShop 1.6 releases prior to version 3.18.1, a malicious customer can confirm an order even if payment is finally declined by PayPal. A logical weakness during the capture of a payment in case of disabled webhooks can be exploited to create an accepted order. This could allow a threat actor to confirm an order with a fraudulent payment support. Versions 6.4.2 and 3.18.1 contain a patch for the issue. Additionally, users enable webhooks and check they are callable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41805 | Tracks vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41805</link><description>Tracks, a Getting Things Done (GTD) web application, is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting in versions prior to 2.7.1. Reflected cross-site scripting enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of a user’s browser if that user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft. Tracks version 2.7.1 is patched. No known complete workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6922 | Server-Side Request Forgery in Automation 360</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6922</link><description>Automation Anywhere Automation 360 v21-v32 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in a web API component. An attacker with unauthenticated access to the Automation 360 Control Room HTTPS service (port 443) or HTTP service (port 80) can trigger arbitrary web requests from the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40689 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40689</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify, or delete information in the back-end database.  IBM X-Force ID:  297719.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7128 | Openshift-console: unauthenticated data exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7128</link><description>A flaw was found in the Openshift console. Several endpoints in the application use the authHandler() and authHandlerWithUser() middleware functions. When the default authentication provider ("openShiftAuth") is set, these functions do not perform any authentication checks, relying instead on the targeted service to handle authentication and authorization. This issue leads to various degrees of data exposure due to a lack of proper credential verification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41692 | Incorrect Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41692</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to presence of root terminal access on a serial interface without proper access control. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by accessing the root shell on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41690 | Default Credential Storage in Plaintext Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41690</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to storing of default username and password credentials in plaintext within the router's firmware/ database. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and reverse engineer the binary data to access the plaintext default credentials on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41691 | Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41691</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to storing of FTP credentials in plaintext within the SquashFS-root filesystem associated with the router's firmware. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and reverse engineer the binary data to access the plaintext FTP credentials from the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the FTP server associated with the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41688 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41688</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due lack of encryption in storing of usernames and passwords within the router's firmware/ database. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and reverse engineer the binary data to access the plaintext credentials on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41689 | Hard-coded Credentials Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41689</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to unencrypted storing of WPA/ WPS credentials within the router's firmware/ database. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and reverse engineer the binary data to access the plaintext WPA/ WPS credentials on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass WPA/ WPS and gain access to the Wi-Fi network of the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 12:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41686 | Password Policy Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41686</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to improper implementation of password policies. A local attacker could exploit this by creating password that do not adhere to the defined security standards/policy on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to expose the router to potential security threats.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41687 | Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41687</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to transmission of password in plain text. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting transmission within an HTTP session on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to gain unauthorized access to the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41685 | Cookie Without HTTPOnly Flag Set Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41685</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to missing HTTPOnly flag for the session cookies associated with the router's web management interface. An attacker with remote access could exploit this by intercepting transmission within an HTTP session on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to capture cookies and obtain sensitive information on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41684 | Cookie Without Secure Flag Set Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41684</link><description>This vulnerability exists in SyroTech SY-GPON-1110-WDONT Router due to missing secure flag for the session cookies associated with the router's web management interface. An attacker with remote access could exploit this by intercepting transmission within an HTTP session on the vulnerable system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to capture cookies and compromise the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7062 | Local Privilege Escalation in Nimble Commander &amp;lt;= v1.6.0, Build 4087</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7062</link><description>Nimble Commander suffers from a privilege escalation vulnerability due to the server (info.filesmanager.Files.PrivilegedIOHelperV2) performing improper/insufficient validation of a client’s authorization before executing an operation. Consequently, it is possible to execute system-level commands as the root user, such as changing permissions and ownership, obtaining a handle (file descriptor) of an arbitrary file, and terminating processes, among other operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38522 | Apache Traffic Server: Incomplete field name check allows request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38522</link><description>Apache Traffic Server accepts characters that are not allowed for HTTP field names and forwards malformed requests to origin servers. This can be utilized for request smuggling and may also lead cache poisoning if the origin servers are vulnerable.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35161 | Apache Traffic Server: Incomplete check for chunked trailer section allows request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35161</link><description>Apache Traffic Server forwards malformed HTTP chunked trailer section to origin servers. This can be utilized for request smuggling and may also lead cache poisoning if the origin servers are vulnerable.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users can set a new setting (proxy.config.http.drop_chunked_trailers) not to forward chunked trailer section.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35296 | Apache Traffic Server: Invalid Accept-Encoding can force forwarding requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35296</link><description>Invalid Accept-Encoding header can cause Apache Traffic Server to fail cache lookup and force forwarding requests.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25090 | Apache Roller: Insufficient input validation for some user profile and bookmark fields when Roller in untested-users mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25090</link><description>Insufficient input validation and sanitation in Profile name &amp; screenname, Bookmark name &amp; description and blogroll name features in all versions of Apache Roller on all platforms allows an authenticated user to perform an XSS attack. Mitigation: if you do not have Roller configured for untrusted users, then you need to do nothing because you trust your users to author raw HTML and other web content. If you are running with untrusted users then you should upgrade to Roller 6.1.3.

This issue affects Apache Roller: from 5.0.0 before 6.1.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40897 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in orcparse.c of ORC versions prior to 0.4.39. If a developer is tricked to process a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40897</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in orcparse.c of ORC versions prior to 0.4.39. If a developer is tricked to process a specially crafted file with the affected ORC compiler, an arbitrary code may be executed on the developer's build environment. This may lead to compromise of developer machines or CI build environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6490 | Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider &amp;lt;= 3.9.10 - CSRF to slider deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6490</link><description>During testing of the Master Slider  WordPress plugin through 3.9.10, a CSRF vulnerability was found, which allows an unauthorized user to manipulate requests on behalf of the victim and thereby delete all of the sliders inside Master Slider  WordPress plugin through 3.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49921 | An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby Watcher search input logged the search query results on DEBUG log level. This could lead to raw c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49921</link><description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby Watcher search input logged the search query results on DEBUG log level. This could lead to raw contents of documents stored in Elasticsearch to be printed in logs. Elastic has released 8.11.2 and 7.17.16 that resolves this issue by removing this excessive logging. This issue only affects users that use Watcher and have a Watch defined that uses the search input and additionally have set the search input’s logger to DEBUG or finer, for example using: org.elasticsearch.xpack.watcher.input.search, org.elasticsearch.xpack.watcher.input, org.elasticsearch.xpack.watcher, or wider, since the loggers are hierarchical.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 05:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7120 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_base_config.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7120</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. This affects an unknown part of the file list_base_config.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272451.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 05:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7119 | MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System employee_viewmore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7119</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System up to 20230911. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /employee_viewmore.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. VDB-272450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7118 | MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System department_viewmore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7118</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System up to 20230911. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /department_viewmore.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier VDB-272449 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 04:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7117 | MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System shift_viewmore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7117</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System up to 20230911. Affected is an unknown function of the file /shift_viewmore.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272448. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7116 | MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System branch_viewmore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7116</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System up to 20230911. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /branch_viewmore.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272447. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4447 | In the System → Maintenance tool, the Logged Users tab surfaces sessionId data for all users via the Direct Web Remoting API (UserSessionAja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4447</link><description>In the System → Maintenance tool, the Logged Users tab surfaces sessionId data for all users via the Direct Web Remoting API (UserSessionAjax.getSessionList.dwr) calls. While this is information that would and should be available to admins who possess "Sign In As" powers, admins who otherwise lack this privilege would still be able to utilize the session IDs to imitate other users.


While this is a very small attack vector that requires very high permissions to execute, its danger lies principally in obfuscating attribution; all Sign In As operations are attributed appropriately in the log files, and a malicious administrator could use this information to render their dealings untraceable — including those admins who have not been granted this ability — such as by using a session ID to generate an API token.

Fixed in: 24.07.12 / 23.01.20 LTS / 23.10.24v13 LTS / 24.04.24v5 LTS</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7115 | MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System designation_viewmore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7115</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MD-MAFUJUL-HASAN Online-Payroll-Management-System up to 20230911. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /designation_viewmore.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. VDB-272446 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7114 | Tianchoy Blog so.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7114</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tianchoy Blog up to 1.8.8. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /so.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272445 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41468 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmdinput parameter at /goform/exeCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41468</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the cmdinput parameter at /goform/exeCommand</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41473 | Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the mac parameter at ip/goform/WriteFacMac</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41473</link><description>Tenda FH1201 v1.2.0.14 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the mac parameter at ip/goform/WriteFacMac</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24621 | Softaculous Webuzo Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24621</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains an authentication bypass vulnerability through the password reset functionality. Remote, anonymous attackers can exploit this vulnerability to gain full server access as the root user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24622 | Softaculous Webuzo Password Reset Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24622</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection in the password reset functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24623 | Softaculous Webuzo FTP Management Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24623</link><description>Softaculous Webuzo contains a command injection vulnerability in the FTP management functionality. A remote, authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to gain code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38103 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38103</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3938 | The "reset password" login page accepted an HTML injection via URL parameters.

This has already been rectified via patch, and as such it ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3938</link><description>The "reset password" login page accepted an HTML injection via URL parameters.

This has already been rectified via patch, and as such it cannot be demonstrated via Demo site link. Those interested to see the vulnerability may spin up a  http://localhost:8082/dotAdmin/#/public/login?resetEmailSent=true&amp;amp;resetEmail=%3Ch1%3E%3Ca%20href%3D%22https:%2F%2Fgoogle.com%22%3ECLICK%20ME%3C%2Fa%3E%3C%2Fh1%3E 

This will result in a view along these lines:





  *  OWASP Top 10 - A03: Injection
  *  CVSS Score: 5.4
  *   AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator 
  *   https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator?vector=AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N&amp;... https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7106 | Spina CMS media_folders cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7106</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Spina CMS 2.18.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/media_folders. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272431. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7105 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX Lista Ura Page detalheIdUra sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7105</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file /detalheIdUra of the component Lista Ura Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272430 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41809 | OpenObserve Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in `openobserve/web/src/views/MemberSubscription.vue`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41809</link><description>OpenObserve is an open-source observability platform. Starting in version 0.4.4 and prior to version 0.10.0, OpenObserve contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in line 32 of `openobserve/web/src/views/MemberSubscription.vue`. Version 0.10.0 sanitizes incoming html.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41808 | OpenObserve stored XSS vulnerability may lead to complete account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41808</link><description>The OpenObserve open-source observability platform provides the ability to filter logs in a dashboard by the values uploaded in a given log. However, all versions of the platform through 0.9.1 do not sanitize user input in the filter selection menu, which may result in complete account takeover. It has been noted that the front-end uses `DOMPurify` or Vue templating to escape cross-site scripting (XSS) extensively, however certain areas of the front end lack this XSS protection. When combining the missing protection with the insecure authentication handling that the front-end uses, a malicious user may be able to take over any victim's account provided they meet the exploitation steps. As of time of publication, no patched version is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6558 | HMS Industrial Networks Anybus-CompactCom 30 Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6558</link><description>HMS Industrial Networks

Anybus-CompactCom 30 products are vulnerable to a XSS attack caused by the lack of input sanitation checks. As a consequence, it is possible to insert HTML code into input fields and store the HTML code. The stored HTML code will be embedded in the page and executed by host browser the next time the page is loaded, enabling social engineering attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29069 | snapd will follow archived symlinks when unpacking a filesystem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29069</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, snapd failed to properly check the
destination of symbolic links when extracting a snap. The snap format 
is a squashfs file-system image and so can contain symbolic links and
other file types. Various file entries within the snap squashfs image
(such as icons and desktop files etc) are directly read by snapd when
it is extracted. An attacker who could convince a user to install a
malicious snap which contained symbolic links at these paths could then 
cause snapd to write out the contents of the symbolic link destination
into a world-readable directory. This in-turn could allow an unprivileged
user to gain access to privileged information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38287 | The password-reset mechanism in the Forgot Password functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38287</link><description>The password-reset mechanism in the Forgot Password functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers to force the application into resetting the administrator's password to a random insecure 8-digit value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38288 | A command-injection issue in the Certificate Signing Request (CSR) functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows authenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38288</link><description>A command-injection issue in the Certificate Signing Request (CSR) functionality in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows authenticated attackers with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying server as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38289 | A boolean-based SQL injection issue in the Virtual Meeting Password (VMP) endpoint in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38289</link><description>A boolean-based SQL injection issue in the Virtual Meeting Password (VMP) endpoint in R-HUB TurboMeeting through 8.x allows unauthenticated remote attackers to extract hashed passwords from the database, and authenticate to the application, via crafted SQL input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40324 | A CRLF injection vulnerability in E-Staff v5.1 allows attackers to insert Carriage Return (CR) and Line Feed (LF) characters into input fiel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40324</link><description>A CRLF injection vulnerability in E-Staff v5.1 allows attackers to insert Carriage Return (CR) and Line Feed (LF) characters into input fields, leading to HTTP response splitting and header manipulation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29068 | snapd non-regular file indefinite blocking read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29068</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, snapd failed to properly check the file
type when extracting a snap. The snap format is a squashfs file-system
image and so can contain files that are non-regular files (such as pipes 
or sockets etc). Various file entries within the snap squashfs image
(such as icons etc) are directly read by snapd when it is extracted. An 
attacker who could convince a user to install a malicious snap which
contained non-regular files at these paths could then cause snapd to block
indefinitely trying to read from such files and cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1724 | snapd allows $HOME/bin symlink</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1724</link><description>In snapd versions prior to 2.62, when using AppArmor for enforcement of 
sandbox permissions, snapd failed to restrict writes to the $HOME/bin
path. In Ubuntu, when this path exists, it is automatically added to
the users PATH. An attacker who could convince a user to install a
malicious snap which used the 'home' plug could use this vulnerability
to install arbitrary scripts into the users PATH which may then be run
by the user outside of the expected snap sandbox and hence allow them
to escape confinement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40318 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Webkul Qloapps v1.6.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40318</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Webkul Qloapps v1.6.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28772 | IBM Security Directory Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28772</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  285645.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40873 | XSS in Secure Access administrative console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40873</link><description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure
Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.07.
Attackers with system administrator permissions can interfere with another
system administrator’s use of the publishing UI when the administrators are
editing the same management object. The scope is unchanged, there is no loss of
confidentiality. Impact to system availability is none, impact to system
integrity is high.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32759 | IBM Security Directory Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32759</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 uses insufficient session expiration which could allow an unauthorized user to obtain sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  228565.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40872 | Elevation of privilege in Absolute Secure Access clients and servers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40872</link><description>There is an elevation of privilege vulnerability in server
and client components of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.07.
Attackers with local access and valid desktop user credentials can elevate
their privilege to system level by passing invalid address data to the vulnerable
component. This could be used to
manipulate process tokens to elevate the privilege of a normal process to
System. The scope is changed, the impact to system confidentiality and
integrity is high, the impact to the availability of the effected component is
none.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41801 | OpenProject packaged installation has Open Redirect Vulnerability in Sign-In in default configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41801</link><description>OpenProject is open source project management software. Prior to version 14.3.0, using a forged HOST header in the default configuration of packaged installations and using the "Login required" setting, an attacker could redirect to a remote host to initiate a phishing attack against an OpenProject user's account. This vulnerability affects default packaged installation of OpenProject without any additional configuration or modules on Apache (such as mod_security, manually setting a host name, having a fallthrough VirtualHost). It might also affect other installations that did not take care to fix the HOST/X-Forwarded-Host headers. Version 14.3.0 includes stronger protections for the hostname from within the application using the HostAuthorization middleware of Rails to reject any requests with a host name that does not match the configured one. Also, all generated links by the application are now ensured to use the built-in hostname. Users who aren't able to upgrade immediately may use mod_security for Apache2 or manually fix the Host and X-Forwarded-Host headers in their proxying application before reaching the application server of OpenProject. Alternatively, they can manually apply the patch to opt-in to host header protections in previous versions of OpenProject.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36542 | Insecure permissions in kuma v2.7.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's tok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36542</link><description>Insecure permissions in kuma v2.7.0 allows attackers to access sensitive data and escalate privileges by obtaining the service account's token.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7007 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel in Positron Broadcast Signal Processor TRA7005</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7007</link><description>Positron Broadcast Signal Processor TRA7005 v1.20 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass exploit that could allow an attacker to have unauthorized access to protected areas of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41800 | Craft CMS Allows TOTP Token To Stay Valid After Use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41800</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). Craft CMS 5 allows reuse of TOTP tokens multiple times within the validity period. An attacker is able to re-submit a valid TOTP token to establish an authenticated session. This requires that the attacker has knowledge of the victim's credentials. This has been patched in Craft 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7101 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX Authentication Form login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7101</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login of the component Authentication Form. The manipulation of the argument usuario leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272423. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41806 | Open edX Platform&amp;#x27;s instructor upload CSV for cohort creation not Private by Default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41806</link><description>The Open edX Platform is a learning management platform. Instructors can upload csv files containing learner information to create cohorts in the instructor dashboard. These files are uploaded using the django default storage. With certain storage backends, uploads may become publicly available when the uploader uses versions master, palm, olive, nutmeg, maple, lilac, koa, or juniper. The patch in commit cb729a3ced0404736dfa0ae768526c82b608657b ensures that cohorts data uploaded to AWS S3 buckets is written with a private ACL. Beyond patching, deployers should also ensure that existing cohorts uploads have a private ACL, or that other precautions are taken to avoid public access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36111 | KubePi&amp;#x27;s JWT token validation has a defect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36111</link><description>KubePi is a K8s panel. Starting in version 1.6.3 and prior to version 1.8.0, there is a defect in the KubePi JWT token verification. The JWT key in the default configuration file is empty. Although a random 32-bit string will be generated to overwrite the key in the configuration file when the key is detected to be empty in the configuration file reading logic, the key is empty during actual verification. Using an empty key to generate a JWT token can bypass the login verification and directly take over the back end. Version 1.8.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39671 | Access control vulnerability in the security verification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39671</link><description>Access control vulnerability in the security verification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39672 | Memory request logic vulnerability in the memory module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and ava...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39672</link><description>Memory request logic vulnerability in the memory module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7271 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the NMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7271</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the NMS module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39670 | Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account synchronisation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39670</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the account synchronisation module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39673 | Vulnerability of serialisation/deserialisation mismatch in the iAware module. Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39673</link><description>Vulnerability of serialisation/deserialisation mismatch in the iAware module. Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39674 | Plaintext vulnerability in the Gallery search module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39674</link><description>Plaintext vulnerability in the Gallery search module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6589 | LearnPress &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6589</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.8.2 via the 'render_content_block_template' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37084 | CVE-2024-37084: Remote code execution in Spring Cloud Data Flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37084</link><description>In Spring Cloud Data Flow versions prior to 2.11.4,  a malicious user who has access to the Skipper server api can use a crafted upload request to write an arbitrary file to any location on the file system which could lead to compromising the server</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41705 | A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6.8 before 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially expl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41705</link><description>A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6.8 before 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.14.P4 (6.14.0.4) and 6.13 P4 (6.13.0.4) are also fixed releases. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-30639.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41706 | A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before version 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41706</link><description>A stored XSS issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before version 2024.06. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.14 P4 (6.14.0.4) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41707 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.06. Authenticated users can achieve HTML content injection. A remote authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41707</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.06. Authenticated users can achieve HTML content injection. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this to store malicious HTML code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6972 | In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain circumstances it is possible for sensitive variables to be printed in the task log in c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6972</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain circumstances it is possible for sensitive variables to be printed in the task log in clear-text.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4811 | In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain conditions, a user with specific role assignments can access restricted project artifac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4811</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server under certain conditions, a user with specific role assignments can access restricted project artifacts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 05:07:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7047 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7047</link><description>A cross site scripting vulnerability exists in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.6 prior to 17.0.5, 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary scripts under the context of the current logged in user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:03:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7057 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7057</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 prior to 17.0.5, starting from 17.1 prior to 17.1.3, and starting from 17.2 prior to 17.2.1 where job artifacts can be inappropriately exposed to users lacking the proper authorization level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>