<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:40:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-3160 | Intelbras HDCVI 1016 HTTP GET Request cap.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3160</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Intelbras MHDX 1004, MHDX 1008, MHDX 1016, MHDX 5016, HDCVI 1008 and HDCVI 1016 up to 20240401. This affects an unknown part of the file /cap.js of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier VDB-258933 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor explains that they do not classify the information shown as sensitive and therefore there is no vulnerability which is about to harm the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3148 | DedeCMS makehtml_archives_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3148</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.112. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file dede/makehtml_archives_action.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258923. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3146 | DedeCMS makehtml_rss_action.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3146</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/makehtml_rss_action.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258921 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3147 | DedeCMS makehtml_map.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3147</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/makehtml_map.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3144 | DedeCMS makehtml_spec.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3144</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/makehtml_spec.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258919. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3145 | DedeCMS makehtml_js_action.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3145</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/makehtml_js_action.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258920. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3137 | Improper Privilege Management in uvdesk/community-skeleton</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3137</link><description>Improper Privilege Management in uvdesk/community-skeleton</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3142 | Clavister E10/E80 Setting cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Clavister E10 and E80 up to 20240323 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258917 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3143 | DedeCMS member_rank.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3143</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/member_rank.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258918 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27334 | Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27334</link><description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21978.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27333 | Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27333</link><description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21976.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3140 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3140</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument middlename leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258915.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3141 | Clavister E10/E80 Misc Settings Page MiscSettings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3141</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Clavister E10 and E80 up to 20240323 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /?Page=Node&amp;OBJ=/System/AdvancedSettings/DeviceSettings/MiscSettings of the component Misc Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument WatchdogTimerTime/BufFloodRebootTime/MaxPipeUsers/AVCache Lifetime/HTTPipeliningMaxReq/Reassembly MaxConnections/Reassembly MaxProcessingMem/ScrSaveTime leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258916. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3139 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System save_users improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3139</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function save_users of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258914 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 22:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3138 | francoisjacquet RosarioSIS Add Portal Note cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3138</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability was found in francoisjacquet RosarioSIS 11.5.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Add Portal Note. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258911. NOTE: The vendor explains that the PDF is opened by the browser app in a sandbox, so no data from the website should be accessible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 22:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27327 | PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27327</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27328 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27328</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22280.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27329 | PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27329</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22285.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27330 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27330</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22286.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27331 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27331</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22287.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27332 | PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27332</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22288.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0637 | Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0637</link><description>Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateDirectory function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22294.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1179 | TP-Link Omada ER605 DHCPv6 Client Options Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1179</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 DHCPv6 Client Options Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DHCP options. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1863 | Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1863</link><description>Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HTTP requests on port 3000. When parsing the token parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21539.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23115 | Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23115</link><description>Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateGroups function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22295.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23116 | Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23116</link><description>Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateLCARelation function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22296.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23117 | Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23117</link><description>Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactServiceCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22297.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23118 | Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23118</link><description>Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactHostCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22298.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23119 | Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23119</link><description>Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the insertGraphTemplate function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22339.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27323 | PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27323</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27324 | PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27324</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22270.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27325 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27325</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22275.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27326 | PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27326</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22276.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3165 | Database Credential Exposure in the Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3165</link><description>System-&gt;Maintenance-&gt; Log Files in dotCMS dashboard is providing the username/password for database connections in the log output. Nevertheless, this is a moderate issue as it requires a backend admin as well as that dbs are locked down by environment.  

OWASP Top 10 - A05) Insecure Design

OWASP Top 10 - A05) Security Misconfiguration

OWASP Top 10 - A09) Security Logging and Monitoring Failure</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3164 | In dotCMS dashboard, the Tools and Log Files tabs under System → Maintenance Portlet, which is and always has been an Admin portlet, is acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3164</link><description>In dotCMS dashboard, the Tools and Log Files tabs under System → Maintenance Portlet, which is and always has been an Admin portlet, is accessible to anyone with that portlet and not just to CMS Admins. Users that get site admin but not a system admin, should not have access to the System Maintenance → Tools portlet. This would share database username and password under Log Files and download DB Dump and other dotCMS Content under Tools. Nothing in the System → Maintenance should be displayed for users with site admin role. Only system admins must have access to System Maintenance.

OWASP Top 10 - A01) Broken Access Control

OWASP Top 10 - A04) Insecure Design</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51570 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51570</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the RMI interface, which listens on TCP port 41009 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21012.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51571 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro SocketService Missing Authentication Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51571</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro SocketService Missing Authentication Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SocketService module, which listens on UDP port 41222 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21162.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51572 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro getMacAddressByIp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51572</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro getMacAddressByIp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getMacAddressByIP function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21163.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51573 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro updateManagerPassword Exposed Dangerous Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51573</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro updateManagerPassword Exposed Dangerous Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateManagerPassword function. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21203.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29433 | A deserialization vulnerability in the FASTJSON component of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29433</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability in the FASTJSON component of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying crafted data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29435 | An issue discovered in Alldata v0.4.6 allows attacker to run arbitrary commands via the processId parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29435</link><description>An issue discovered in Alldata v0.4.6 allows attacker to run arbitrary commands via the processId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48906 | Stack Overflow vulnerability in Btstack 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted input to the char_for_nibb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48906</link><description>Stack Overflow vulnerability in Btstack 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted input to the char_for_nibble function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3135 | Cross Site Request Forgery to denial of service or credit loss in LocalAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3135</link><description>The web server lacked CSRF tokens allowing an attacker to host malicious JavaScript on a host that when visited by a LocalAI user, could allow the attacker to fill disk space to deny service or abuse credits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 18:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28232 | Username Enumeration in CasaOS via bypass of CVE-2024-24766</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28232</link><description>Go package IceWhaleTech/CasaOS-UserService provides user management functionalities to CasaOS. The Casa OS Login page has disclosed the username enumeration vulnerability in the login page which was patched in version 0.4.7. This issue in CVE-2024-28232 has been patched in version 0.4.8 but that version has not yet been uploaded to Go's package manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3131 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258874 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25574 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25574</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability exists in GetDIAE_usListParameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3129 | SourceCodester Image Accordion Gallery App add-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Image Accordion Gallery App 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-image.php. The manipulation of the argument image_name leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258873 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30858 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_fire_wall.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30858</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_fire_wall.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30859 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupSSLCert.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30859</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupSSLCert.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30861 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/configguide/ipsec_guide_1.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30861</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/configguide/ipsec_guide_1.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30860 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/export_excel_user.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30860</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/export_excel_user.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30862 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30862</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/index.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30863 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/history.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30863</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/history.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30867 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_virtual_site_info.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30867</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_virtual_site_info.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28547 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in SPS Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28547</link><description>Memory corruption in SPS Application while requesting for public key in sorter TA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33023 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in SPS-Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33023</link><description>Memory corruption while processing finish_sign command to pass a rsp buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33099 | Improper Input Validation in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33099</link><description>Transient DOS while processing SMS container of non-standard size received in DL NAS transport in NR.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33100 | Improper input validation in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33100</link><description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message when message ID is not defined in the 3GPP specification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33101 | Incorrect Type Conversion or Cast in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33101</link><description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS TRANSPORT message with payload length 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33111 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33111</link><description>Information disclosure when VI calibration state set by ADSP is greater than MAX_FBSP_STATE in the response payload to AFE calibration command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33115 | Buffer Over-read in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33115</link><description>Memory corruption while processing buffer initialization, when trusted report for certain report types are generated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43515 | Buffer copy without checking size of input (Classic buffer overflow) in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43515</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running kernel address sanitizers (syzkaller) on tmecom with DEBUG_FS enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21452 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21452</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding an ASN.1 OER message containing a SEQUENCE of unknown extensions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21453 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21453</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding message of size that exceeds the available system memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21454 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21454</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding the ToBeSignedMessage in Automotive Telematics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21463 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21463</link><description>Memory corruption while processing Codec2 during v13k decoder pitch synthesis.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21468 | Use After Free in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21468</link><description>Memory corruption when there is failed unmap operation in GPU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21470 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Graphics Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21470</link><description>Memory corruption while allocating memory for graphics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21472 | Use After Free in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21472</link><description>Memory corruption in Kernel while handling GPU operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21473 | Improper Input Validation in WIN SON</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21473</link><description>Memory corruption while redirecting log file to any file location with any file name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30864 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupTimePolicy.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30864</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupTimePolicy.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30865 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_user_login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30865</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_user_login.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30866 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30866</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/menu.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26655 | Fix memory leak in posix_clock_open()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26655</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Fix memory leak in posix_clock_open()

If the clk ops.open() function returns an error, we don't release the
pccontext we allocated for this clock.

Re-organize the code slightly to make it all more obvious.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3128 | Replify-Messenger Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3128</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Replify-Messenger 1.0 on Android. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258869 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early and responded very quickly. He does not intend to maintain the app anymore and will revoke the availability in the Google Play Store.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31099 | WordPress Phlox Core Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme.This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.15.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3125 | Zebra ZTC GK420d Alert Setup Page settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3125</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Zebra ZTC GK420d 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /settings of the component Alert Setup Page. The manipulation of the argument Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258868. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30868 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/add_getlogin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30868</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/add_getlogin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30870 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/address_interpret.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30870</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/address_interpret.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30871 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/applyhardware.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30871</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/applyhardware.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30872 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /include/authrp.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30872</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /include/authrp.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3124 | fridgecow smartalarm Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3124</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in fridgecow smartalarm 1.8.1 on Android. This affects an unknown part of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258867.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4966 | sequentech admin-console Election Description cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in sequentech admin-console up to 6.1.7 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Election Description Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 7.0.0-beta.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 0043a6b1e6e0f5abc9557e73f9ffc524fc5d609d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-258782 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6154 | Local privilege escalation in Bitdefender Total Security (VA-11168)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6154</link><description>A configuration setting issue in seccenter.exe as used in Bitdefender Total Security, Bitdefender Internet Security, Bitdefender Antivirus Plus, Bitdefender Antivirus Free allows an attacker to change the product's expected behavior and potentially load a third-party library upon execution. This issue affects Total Security: 27.0.25.114; Internet Security: 27.0.25.114; Antivirus Plus: 27.0.25.114; Antivirus Free: 27.0.25.114.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3130 |  Insecure Data Storage leading to sensitive Information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3130</link><description>Hard-coded Credentials in CoolKit eWeLlink app are before 5.4.x on Android and IOS allows local attacker to unauthorized access to sensitive data via Decryption algorithm and key obtained after decompiling app</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25080 | WebMail in Axigen 10.x before 10.3.3.62 allows XSS via the image attachment viewer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25080</link><description>WebMail in Axigen 10.x before 10.3.3.62 allows XSS via the image attachment viewer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26653 | usb: misc: ljca: Fix double free in error handling path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26653</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: misc: ljca: Fix double free in error handling path

When auxiliary_device_add() returns error and then calls
auxiliary_device_uninit(), callback function ljca_auxdev_release
calls kfree(auxdev-&gt;dev.platform_data) to free the parameter data
of the function ljca_new_client_device. The callers of
ljca_new_client_device shouldn't call kfree() again
in the error handling path to free the platform data.

Fix this by cleaning up the redundant kfree() in all callers and
adding kfree() the passed in platform_data on errors which happen
before auxiliary_device_init() succeeds .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26654 | ALSA: sh: aica: reorder cleanup operations to avoid UAF bugs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26654</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: sh: aica: reorder cleanup operations to avoid UAF bugs

The dreamcastcard-&gt;timer could schedule the spu_dma_work and the
spu_dma_work could also arm the dreamcastcard-&gt;timer.

When the snd_pcm_substream is closing, the aica_channel will be
deallocated. But it could still be dereferenced in the worker
thread. The reason is that del_timer() will return directly
regardless of whether the timer handler is running or not and
the worker could be rescheduled in the timer handler. As a result,
the UAF bug will happen. The racy situation is shown below:

      (Thread 1)                 |      (Thread 2)
snd_aicapcm_pcm_close()          |
 ...                             |  run_spu_dma() //worker
                                 |    mod_timer()
  flush_work()                   |
  del_timer()                    |  aica_period_elapsed() //timer
  kfree(dreamcastcard-&gt;channel)  |    schedule_work()
                                 |  run_spu_dma() //worker
  ...                            |    dreamcastcard-&gt;channel-&gt; //USE

In order to mitigate this bug and other possible corner cases,
call mod_timer() conditionally in run_spu_dma(), then implement
PCM sync_stop op to cancel both the timer and worker. The sync_stop
op will be called from PCM core appropriately when needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15038 | NUUO NVRmini 2 deletefile.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15038</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in NUUO NVRmini 2 up to 3.0.8. Affected is an unknown function of the file /deletefile.php. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258780.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1526 | Hubbub Lite &amp;lt; 1.33.1 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Posts Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1526</link><description>The Hubbub Lite  WordPress plugin before 1.33.1 does not ensure that user have access to password protected post before displaying its content in a meta tag.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2262 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Filter Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2262</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not have CSRF check in its bulk action, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete arbitrary filters via CSRF attack, granted they know the related filter slugs</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2263 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2263</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2278 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2278</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its Filters settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20039 | In modem protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20039</link><description>In modem protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01240012; Issue ID: MSV-1215.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20040 | In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20040</link><description>In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08360153 (for MT6XXX chipsets) / WCNCR00363530 (for MT79XX chipsets); Issue ID: MSV-979.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20041 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20041</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541746; Issue ID: ALPS08541746.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20042 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20042</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541780; Issue ID: ALPS08541780.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20043 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20043</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541781; Issue ID: ALPS08541781.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20044 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20044</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541784; Issue ID: ALPS08541784.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20045 | In audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect calculation of buffer size. This could lead to local information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20045</link><description>In audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect calculation of buffer size. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08024748; Issue ID: ALPS08029526.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20046 | In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20046</link><description>In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08485622; Issue ID: ALPS08485622.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20047 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20047</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08587865; Issue ID: ALPS08486807.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20048 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20048</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541769; Issue ID: ALPS08541769.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20049 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20049</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541765; Issue ID: ALPS08541765.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20050 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20050</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541757.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20051 | In flashc, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20051</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20052 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20052</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541761.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20053 | In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20053</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541764.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20054 | In gnss, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20054</link><description>In gnss, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08580200; Issue ID: ALPS08580200.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20055 | In imgsys, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20055</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS08518692; Issue ID: MSV-1012.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31033 | JJWT (aka Java JWT) through 0.12.5 ignores certain characters and thus a user might falsely conclude that they have a strong key. The impact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31033</link><description>JJWT (aka Java JWT) through 0.12.5 ignores certain characters and thus a user might falsely conclude that they have a strong key. The impacted code is the setSigningKey() method within the DefaultJwtParser class and the signWith() method within the DefaultJwtBuilder class.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28895 | 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for Android v2.3.1 to v3.161.1 and 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for iOS v3.2.2 to v4.109.0 contain a cross-site scripting vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28895</link><description>'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for Android v2.3.1 to v3.161.1 and 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for iOS v3.2.2 to v4.109.0 contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the WebView of 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App via other app installed on the user's device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27609 | Bonita before 2023.2-u2 allows stored XSS via a UI screen in the administration panel.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27609</link><description>Bonita before 2023.2-u2 allows stored XSS via a UI screen in the administration panel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51803 | LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.5.7 does not prevent use of icons that have non-image data such as the "&lt;?php ?&gt;" substring.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51803</link><description>LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.5.7 does not prevent use of icons that have non-image data such as the "&lt;?php ?&gt;" substring.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125110 | wp-file-upload Plugin wfu_ajaxactions.php wfu_ajax_action_callback cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125110</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wp-file-upload Plugin up to 2.4.3 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function wfu_ajax_action_callback of the file lib/wfu_ajaxactions.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.4.4 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is c846327df030a0a97da036a2f07c769ab9284ddb. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-258781 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30524 | WordPress PDF Viewer for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30524</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RedLettuce Plugins PDF Viewer for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PDF Viewer for Elementor: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30530 | WordPress MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp;amp; Podcast by Sonaar plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30530</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sonaar Music MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar: from n/a through 5.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30548 | WordPress underConstruction plugin &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Noah Kagan underConstruction allows Stored XSS.This issue affects underConstruction: from n/a through 1.21.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30549 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30549</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cimatti Consulting Contact Forms by Cimatti allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Forms by Cimatti: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30550 | WordPress Gallery – Image and Video Gallery with Thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30550</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdevart Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30551 | WordPress Sticky Anything plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Toast Plugins Sticky Anything.This issue affects Sticky Anything: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 20:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30552 | WordPress Responsive flipbook plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30552</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wppdf.Org Responsive flipbook allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive flipbook: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30553 | WordPress WP Twitter Mega Fan Box Widget  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joby Joseph WP Twitter Mega Fan Box Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Twitter Mega Fan Box Widget : from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30554 | WordPress DD Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wouter Dijkstra DD Rating allows Stored XSS.This issue affects DD Rating: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30555 | WordPress Ultimate Social Comments plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30555</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sayan Datta Ultimate Social Comments – Email Notification &amp; Lazy Load allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultimate Social Comments – Email Notification &amp; Lazy Load: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30556 | WordPress Mighty Classic Pros And Cons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30556</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MightyThemes Mighty Classic Pros And Cons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mighty Classic Pros And Cons: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30557 | WordPress Aesop Story Engine plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aesopinteractive Aesop Story Engine allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Aesop Story Engine: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:44:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30558 | WordPress Add Shortcodes Actions And Filters plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Simpson Add Shortcodes Actions And Filters allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Add Shortcodes Actions And Filters: from n/a through 2.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30559 | WordPress Spin 360 deg and 3D Model Viewer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maurice Spin 360 deg and 3D Model Viewer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Spin 360 deg and 3D Model Viewer: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30561 | WordPress Appointment Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scientech It Solution Appointment Calendar allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Appointment Calendar: from n/a through 2.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31084 | WordPress Weekly Class Schedule plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31084</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pulsar Web Design Weekly Class Schedule allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Weekly Class Schedule: from n/a through 3.19.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31085 | WordPress Post-Plugin Library plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31085</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rob Marsh, SJ Post-Plugin Library allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Post-Plugin Library: from n/a through 2.6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31087 | WordPress pageMash plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31087</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joel Starnes pageMash &gt; Page Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects pageMash &gt; Page Management: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31089 | WordPress Platinum SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31089</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Techblissonline.Com (Rajesh) Platinum SEO allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Platinum SEO: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31090 | WordPress Hacklog Down As PDF plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31090</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 荒野无灯 Hacklog Down As PDF allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Hacklog Down As PDF: from n/a through 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31091 | WordPress Custom Field Bulk Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SparkWeb Interactive, Inc. Custom Field Bulk Editor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Custom Field Bulk Editor: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31092 | WordPress Comic Easel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.15 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Philip M. Hofer (Frumph) Comic Easel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Comic Easel: from n/a through 1.15.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31097 | WordPress SEO Title Tag plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31097</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stephan Spencer SEO Title Tag allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SEO Title Tag: from n/a through 3.5.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31101 | WordPress AI Twitter Feeds (Twitter widget &amp;amp; shortcode) plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31101</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in August Infotech AI Twitter Feeds (Twitter widget &amp; shortcode) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects AI Twitter Feeds (Twitter widget &amp; shortcode): from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31102 | WordPress Prenotazioni plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31102</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scimone Ignazio Prenotazioni allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Prenotazioni: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31103 | WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.21 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31103</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kanban for WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kanban Boards for WordPress: from n/a through 2.5.21.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31104 | WordPress GetResponse for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.33 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31104</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GetResponse GetResponse for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GetResponse for WordPress: from n/a through 5.5.33.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31106 | WordPress Yoo Slider – Image Slider &amp;amp; Video Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31106</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yooslider Yoo Slider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Yoo Slider: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31107 | WordPress OpenID plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31107</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DiSo Development Team OpenID allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects OpenID: from n/a through 3.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31108 | WordPress iFlyChat plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31108</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in iFlyChat Team iFlyChat – WordPress Chat iflychat allows Stored XSS.This issue affects iFlyChat – WordPress Chat: from n/a through 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31110 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31110</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Katz Web Services, Inc. Contact Form 7 Newsletter allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Newsletter: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:05:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31112 | WordPress Convert Post Types plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31112</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stephanie Leary Convert Post Types allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Convert Post Types: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31117 | WordPress WooCommerce Bookings Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.36 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31117</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moises Heberle WooCommerce Bookings Calendar.This issue affects WooCommerce Bookings Calendar: from n/a through 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31120 | WordPress Gallery – Image and Video Gallery with Thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31120</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdevart Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31121 | WordPress HeartThis plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31121</link><description>Contributor Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in HeartThis &lt;= 0.1.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31122 | WordPress User Rights Access Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prism IT Systems User Rights Access Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects User Rights Access Manager: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31123 | WordPress SpiderFAQ plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31123</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebDorado SpiderFAQ allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SpiderFAQ: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30526 | WordPress Easy Social Feed – Social Photos Gallery – Post Feed – Like Box plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30526</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Easy Social Feed.This issue affects Easy Social Feed: from n/a through 6.5.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30536 | WordPress Slugs Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30536</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WPFactory Slugs Manager.This issue affects Slugs Manager: from n/a through 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30541 | WordPress LWS Optimize plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30541</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in LWS LWS Optimize.This issue affects LWS Optimize: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31096 | WordPress Nictitate theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31096</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kopatheme Nictitate.This issue affects Nictitate: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31100 | WordPress Popup Cart Lite for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31100</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Festi-Team Popup Cart Lite for WooCommerce.This issue affects Popup Cart Lite for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30489 | WordPress WP Cost Estimation &amp;amp; Payment Forms Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1.75 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30489</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in loopus WP Cost Estimation &amp; Payment Forms Builder.This issue affects WP Cost Estimation &amp; Payment Forms Builder: from n/a through 10.1.75.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30543 | WordPress Whizzy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.18 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30543</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in UPQODE Whizz.This issue affects Whizzy: from n/a through 1.1.18.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31095 | WordPress Thumbs Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31095</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Ricard Torres Thumbs Rating.This issue affects Thumbs Rating: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30523 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro – Mailchimp Add On plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30523</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro Paid Memberships Pro – Mailchimp Add On pmpro-mailchimp.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro – Mailchimp Add On: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30533 | WordPress Layouts for Elementor plugin &amp;lt; 1.8 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30533</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Techeshta Layouts for Elementor.This issue affects Layouts for Elementor: from n/a before 1.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30535 | WordPress Easy Form Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30535</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WhiteStudio Easy Form Builder.This issue affects Easy Form Builder: from n/a through 3.7.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31116 | WordPress 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.74 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31116</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in 10Web 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps.This issue affects 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps: from n/a through 1.0.74.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31094 | WordPress Filter Custom Fields &amp;amp; Taxonomies Light plugin &amp;lt;= 1.05 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31094</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Filter Custom Fields &amp; Taxonomies Light.This issue affects Filter Custom Fields &amp; Taxonomies Light: from n/a through 1.05.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31114 | WordPress Shortcode Addons &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31114</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in biplob018 Shortcode Addons.This issue affects Shortcode Addons: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31115 | WordPress Chauffeur Taxi Booking System for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.9 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31115</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in QuanticaLabs Chauffeur Taxi Booking System for WordPress.This issue affects Chauffeur Taxi Booking System for WordPress: from n/a through 6.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50311 | IBM CICS Transaction Gateway for Multiplatforms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50311</link><description>IBM CICS Transaction Gateway for Multiplatforms 9.2 and 9.3 transmits or stores authentication credentials, but it uses an insecure method that is susceptible to unauthorized interception and/or retrieval.  IBM X-Force ID:  273612.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50959 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50959</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2,19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3,20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1,2 2.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 may allow end users to query more documents than expected from a connected Enterprise Content Management system when configured to use a system account.  IBM X-Force ID:  275938.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22353 | IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22353</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.3 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially crafted request. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  280400.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 11:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25027 | IBM Security Verify Access Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25027</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.6 could disclose sensitive snapshot information due to missing encryption.  IBM X-Force ID:  281607.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 11:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36828 | DiscuzX install_function.php show_next_step cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36828</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DiscuzX up to 3.4-20200818. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function show_next_step of the file upload/install/include/install_function.php. The manipulation of the argument uchidden leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.4-20210119 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 4a9673624f46f7609486778ded9653733020c567. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258612.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20191 | Zimbra zm-admin-ajax Form Textbox Field Error XFormItem.js XFormItem.prototype.setError cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Zimbra zm-admin-ajax up to 8.8.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function XFormItem.prototype.setError of the file WebRoot/js/ajax/dwt/xforms/XFormItem.js of the component Form Textbox Field Error Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.8.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is bb240ce0c71c01caabaa43eed30c78ba8d7d3591. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-258621 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 08:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10131 | chrisy TFO Graphviz Plugin tfo-graphviz-admin.php admin_page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chrisy TFO Graphviz Plugin up to 1.9 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function admin_page_load/admin_page of the file tfo-graphviz-admin.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.10 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 594c953a345f79e26003772093b0caafc14b92c2. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258620.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3118 | Dreamer CMS Attachment permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3118</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation leads to permission issues. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258779. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 04:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41724 | A command injection vulnerability in Ivanti Sentry prior to 9.19.0 allows unauthenticated threat actor to execute arbitrary commands on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41724</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in Ivanti Sentry prior to 9.19.0 allows unauthenticated threat actor to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the appliance within the same physical or logical network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 02:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46808 | An file upload vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM before 2023.4, allows an authenticated remote user to perform file writes to the server. Success...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46808</link><description>An file upload vulnerability in Ivanti ITSM before 2023.4, allows an authenticated remote user to perform file writes to the server. Successful exploitation may lead to execution of commands in the context of non-root user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 02:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3117 | YouDianCMS ChannelAction.class.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3117</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in YouDianCMS up to 9.5.12. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file App\Lib\Action\Admin\ChannelAction.class.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258778 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 02:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>