<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 11:09:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1814 | Tenda AC6 WifiExtraSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1814</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC6 15.03.05.16. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/WifiExtraSet. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 11:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1813 | zj1983 zz cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1813</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-08. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1812 | zj1983 zz SuperZ.java GetUserOrg sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1812</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in zj1983 zz up to 2024-08. Affected is the function GetUserOrg of the file com/futvan/z/framework/core/SuperZ.java. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 09:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1811 | AT Software Solutions ATSVD Login Endpoint login.aspx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AT Software Solutions ATSVD up to 3.4.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.aspx of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.4.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 08:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1810 | Pixsoft Vivaz Login Endpoint servlet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1810</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pixsoft Vivaz 6.0.11. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /servlet?act=login&amp;amp;submit=1&amp;amp;evento=0&amp;amp;pixrnd=0125021817031859360231 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument sistema leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 07:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1809 | Pixsoft Sol Login Endpoint servlet sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1809</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pixsoft Sol up to 7.6.6c and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pix_projetos/servlet?act=login&amp;amp;submit=1&amp;amp;evento=0&amp;amp;pixrnd=0125021816444195731041 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25724 | list_item_verbose in tar/util.c in libarchive through 3.7.7 does not check an strftime return value, which can lead to a denial of service o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25724</link><description>list_item_verbose in tar/util.c in libarchive through 3.7.7 does not check an strftime return value, which can lead to a denial of service or unspecified other impact via a crafted TAR archive that is read with a verbose value of 2. For example, the 100-byte buffer may not be sufficient for a custom locale.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 02:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1808 | Pixsoft E-Saphira Login Endpoint servlet sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1808</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Pixsoft E-Saphira 1.7.24 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /servlet?act=login&amp;amp;tipo=1 of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument txtUsuario leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 01:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1807 | Eastnets PaymentSafe Edit Manual Reply directRouter.rfc cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1807</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /directRouter.rfc of the component Edit Manual Reply Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 01:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1806 | Eastnets PaymentSafe URL Default.aspx improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1806</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Default.aspx of the component URL Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 23:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1804 | Blizzard Battle.Net profapi.dll uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1804</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Blizzard Battle.Net up to 2.39.0.15212 on Windows and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1800 | D-Link DAR-7000 HTTP POST Request sxh_vpnlic.php get_ip_addr_details command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1800</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 3.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_ip_addr_details of the file /view/vpn/sxh_vpn/sxh_vpnlic.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ethname leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 18:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1799 | Zorlan SkyCaiji Tool.php previewAction server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1799</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Zorlan SkyCaiji 2.9. This affects the function previewAction of the file vendor/skycaiji/app/admin/controller/Tool.php. The manipulation of the argument data leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 17:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1797 | Hunan Zhonghe Baiyi Information Technology Baiyiyun Asset Management and Operations System anyUserBoundHouse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1797</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hunan Zhonghe Baiyi Information Technology Baiyiyun Asset Management and Operations System up to 20250217. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /wuser/anyUserBoundHouse.php. The manipulation of the argument huid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 14:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41778 | IBM Controller information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41778</link><description>IBM Controller 11.0.0 through 11.0.1 and 11.1.0 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1791 | Zorlan SkyCaiji Tool.php fileAction unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1791</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Zorlan SkyCaiji 2.9 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function fileAction of the file vendor/skycaiji/app/admin/controller/Tool.php. The manipulation of the argument save_data leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 13:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1788 | rizinorg rizin utf8.c rz_utf8_encode heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1788</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in rizinorg rizin up to 0.8.0. This affects the function rz_utf8_encode in the library /librz/util/utf8.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1491 | WP Posts Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via auto_play_timeout Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1491</link><description>The WP Posts Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘auto_play_timeout’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 12:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13833 | Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Object Injection via Gallery Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13833</link><description>The Album Gallery – WordPress Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 via deserialization of untrusted input from gallery meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 11:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1404 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 4.4.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated User Email Retrieval via ays_sccp_reports_user_search Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1404</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_sccp_reports_user_search() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a list of registered user emails.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 11:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1786 | rizinorg rizin pdb.c msf_stream_directory_free buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1786</link><description>A vulnerability was found in rizinorg rizin up to 0.7.4. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function msf_stream_directory_free in the library /librz/bin/pdb/pdb.c. The manipulation of the argument -P leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.8.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 10:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13546 | GenerateBlocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via &amp;#x27;get_image_description&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13546</link><description>The GenerateBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.1 via the 'get_image_description' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of private, draft, and scheduled posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13611 | Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13611</link><description>The Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 via the 'bp-better-messages' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/bp-better-messages directory which can contain file attachments included in chat messages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13697 | Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Unauthenticated Limited Server-Side Request Forgery in nice_links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13697</link><description>The Better Messages – Live Chat for WordPress, BuddyPress, PeepSo, Ultimate Member, BuddyBoss plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 via the 'nice_links'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. Successful exploitation requires the "Enable link previews" to be enabled (default).</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13910 | Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 &amp;lt;= 2.36 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13910</link><description>The Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'database_backup_ajax_delete' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.35. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.36.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1291 | Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;icon&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1291</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘icon’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12544 | SurveyJS: Drag &amp;amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder to create, style and embed multiple forms of any complexity &amp;lt;= 1.12.17 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via SurveyJS_DeleteFile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12544</link><description>The SurveyJS: Drag &amp; Drop WordPress Form Builder to create, style and embed multiple forms of any complexity plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to a missing capability check on the callback function of the SurveyJS_DeleteFile class in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.17. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php). This function is still vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery as of 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13806 | Authors List &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13806</link><description>The The Authors List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13911 | Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 &amp;lt;= 2.35 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13911</link><description>The Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.35 via the /dashboard/backup.php file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including full database credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1564 | SetSail Membership &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1564</link><description>The SetSail Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to  in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity through the social login. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators and take over access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1638 | Alloggio Membership &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authentication Bypass via Social Login Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1638</link><description>The Alloggio Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity through the alloggio_membership_init_rest_api_facebook_login and alloggio_membership_init_rest_api_google_login functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators, without knowing a password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1671 | Academist Membership &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authentication Bypass via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1671</link><description>The Academist Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This is due to the academist_membership_check_facebook_user() function not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including site administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 07:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12824 | Nokri – Job Board WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12824</link><description>The Nokri – Job Board WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to the plugin not properly checking for an empty token value prior updating their details like password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's password, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13373 | Exertio Framework &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13373</link><description>The Exertio Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the fl_forgot_pass_new() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1459 | Page Builder by SiteOrigin &amp;lt;= 2.31.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1459</link><description>The Page Builder by SiteOrigin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Embedded Video(PB) widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.31.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1502 | IP2Location Redirection &amp;lt;= 1.33.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Settings Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1502</link><description>The IP2Location Redirection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'download_ip2location_redirection_backup' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.33.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1730 | Simple Download Counter &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1730</link><description>The Simple Download Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 via the 'simple_download_counter_download_handler'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including any local file on the server, such as wp-config.php or /etc/passwd.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27554 | ToDesktop before 2024-10-03, as used by Cursor before 2024-10-03 and other applications, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27554</link><description>ToDesktop before 2024-10-03, as used by Cursor before 2024-10-03 and other applications, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the build server (e.g., read secrets from the desktopify config.prod.json file), and consequently deploy updates to any app, via a postinstall script in package.json. No exploitation occurred.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13901 | Counter Box: Add Engaging Countdowns, Timers &amp;amp; Counters to Your WordPress Site &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13901</link><description>The Counter Box: Add Engaging Countdowns, Timers &amp; Counters to Your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13518 | Simple:Press &amp;lt;= 6.10.11 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Unauthorized Post Editing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13518</link><description>The Simple:Press Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.10.11. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'sp_save_edited_post' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify a forum post via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13559 | TemplatesNext ToolKit &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13559</link><description>The TemplatesNext ToolKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tx_woo_wishlist_table' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13568 | Fluent Support – Helpdesk &amp;amp; Customer Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13568</link><description>The Fluent Support – Helpdesk &amp; Customer Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the 'fluent-support' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/fluent-support directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13746 | Booking Calendar and Notification &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Missing Authorization via wpcb_all_bookings, wpcb_update_booking_post, and wpcb_delete_posts Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13746</link><description>The Booking Calendar and Notification plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to missing capability checks on the wpcb_all_bookings(), wpcb_update_booking_post(), and wpcb_delete_posts() functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data, create or update bookings, or  delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13750 | Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.27 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13750</link><description>The Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.27 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9212 | SKU Generator for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9212</link><description>The SKU Generator for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9217 | Currency Switcher for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.16.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9217</link><description>The Currency Switcher for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0820 | Clicface Trombi &amp;lt;= 2.08 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via nom Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0820</link><description>The Clicface Trombi plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘nom’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.08 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 04:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13358 | BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages &amp;lt;= 3.4.24 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13358</link><description>The BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wc4bp_delete_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins page setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1780 | BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages &amp;lt;= 3.4.25 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1780</link><description>The BuddyPress WooCommerce My Account Integration. Create WooCommerce Member Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wc4bp_delete_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.25. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugins page setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23115 | A Use After Free vulnerability on UniFi Protect Cameras could allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23115</link><description>A Use After Free vulnerability on UniFi Protect Cameras could allow a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras management network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23116 | An Authentication Bypass vulnerability on UniFi Protect Application with Auto-Adopt Bridge Devices enabled could allow a malicious actor wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23116</link><description>An Authentication Bypass vulnerability on UniFi Protect Application with Auto-Adopt Bridge Devices enabled could allow a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to take control of UniFi Protect Cameras.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23117 | An Insufficient Firmware Update Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23117</link><description>An Insufficient Firmware Update Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to make unsupported changes to the camera system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23118 | An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23118</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability could allow an authenticated malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network to make unsupported changes to the camera system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23119 | An Improper Neutralization of Escape Sequences vulnerability could allow an Authentication Bypass with a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23119</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Escape Sequences vulnerability could allow an Authentication Bypass with a Remote Code Execution (RCE) by a malicious actor with access to UniFi Protect Cameras adjacent network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 03:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27416 | Asking For Scratch Username And Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27416</link><description>Scratch-Coding-Hut.github.io is the website for Coding Hut. The website as of 28 February 2025 contained a sign in with scratch username and password form. Any user who used the sign in page would be susceptible to any other user signing into their account. As of time of publication, a fix is not available but work on a fix is underway. As a workaround, users should avoid signing in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25723 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GPAC version 2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25723</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GPAC version 2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25379 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in 07FLYCMS v.1.3.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25379</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in 07FLYCMS v.1.3.9 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter of the del.html component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25476 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SysPass 3.2.x allows a malicious user with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary Jav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25476</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SysPass 3.2.x allows a malicious user with elevated privileges to execute arbitrary Javascript code by specifying a malicious XSS payload as a notification type or notification component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25478 | The account file upload functionality in Syspass 3.2.x fails to properly handle special characters in filenames. This mismanagement leads to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25478</link><description>The account file upload functionality in Syspass 3.2.x fails to properly handle special characters in filenames. This mismanagement leads to the disclosure of the web application s source code, exposing sensitive information such as the database password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1509 | Brocade ASCG 3.2.0 web interface does not enforce HSTS, as defined by RFC 6797 for ports 8030 and 8100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1509</link><description>Brocade ASCG before 3.2.0 Web Interface  is not 
enforcing HSTS, as defined by RFC 6797. HSTS is an optional response 
header that can be configured on the server to instruct the browser to 
only communicate via HTTPS. The lack of HSTS allows downgrade attacks, 
SSL-stripping man-in-the-middle attacks, and weakens cookie-hijacking 
protections.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26466 | Openssh: denial-of-service in openssh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26466</link><description>A flaw was found in the OpenSSH package. For each ping packet the SSH server receives, a pong packet is allocated in a memory buffer and stored in a queue of packages. It is only freed when the server/client key exchange has finished. A malicious client may keep sending such packages, leading to an uncontrolled increase in memory consumption on the server side. Consequently, the server may become unavailable, resulting in a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27414 | MinIO SFTP authentication bypass due to improperly trusted SSH key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27414</link><description>MinIO is a high performance object storage. Starting in RELEASE.2024-06-06T09-36-42Z and prior to 
RELEASE.2025-02-28T09-55-16Z, a bug in evaluating the trust of the SSH key used in an SFTP connection to MinIO allows authentication bypass and unauthorized data access. On a MinIO server with SFTP access configured and using LDAP as an external identity provider, MinIO supports SSH key based authentication for SFTP connections when the user has the `sshPublicKey` attribute set in their LDAP server. The server trusts the client's key only when the public key is the same as the `sshPublicKey` attribute. Due to the bug, when the user has no `sshPublicKey` property in LDAP, the server ends up trusting the key allowing the client to perform any FTP operations allowed by the MinIO access policies associated with the LDAP user (or any of their groups). Three requirements must be met in order to exploit the vulnerability. First, the MinIO server must be configured to allow SFTP access and use LDAP as an external identity provider. Second, the attacker must have knowledge of an LDAP username that does not have the `sshPublicKey` property set. Third, such an LDAP username or one of their groups must also have some MinIO access policy configured. When this bug is successfully exploited, the attacker can perform any FTP operations (i.e. reading, writing, deleting and listing objects) allowed by the access policy associated with the LDAP user account (and their groups). Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27410 | PwnDoc Arbitrary File Write to RCE using Path Traversal in backup restore as admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27410</link><description>PwnDoc is a penetration test reporting application. Prior to version 1.2.0, the backup restore functionality is vulnerable to path traversal in the TAR entry's name, allowing an attacker to overwrite any file on the system with their content. By overwriting an included `.js` file and restarting the container, this allows for Remote Code Execution as an administrator. The remote code execution occurs because any user with the `backups:create` and `backups:update` (only administrators by default) is able to overwrite any file on the system. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27413 | PwnDoc Arbitrary File Write to RCE using Path Traversal in template update from backup templates.json</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27413</link><description>PwnDoc is a penetration test reporting application. Prior to version 1.2.0, the backup restore functionality allows an administrator to import raw data into the database, including Path Traversal (`../`) sequences. This is problematic for the template update functionality as it uses the path from the database to write arbitrary content to, potentially overwriting source code to achieve Remote Code Execution. Any user with the `backups:create`, `backups:update` and `templates:update` permissions (only administrators by default) can write arbitrary content to anywhere on the filesystem. By overwriting source code, it is possible to achieve Remote Code Execution. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0769 | PixelYourSite 10.1.1.1 - Insecure deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0769</link><description>PixelYourSite - Your smart PIXEL (TAG) and API Manager 10.1.1.1 was found to be vulnerable. Unvalidated user input is used directly in an unserialize function in myapp/modules/facebook/facebook-server-a sync-task.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0159 | IBM FlashSystem authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0159</link><description>IBM FlashSystem (IBM Storage Virtualize (8.5.0.0 through 8.5.0.13, 8.5.1.0, 8.5.2.0 through 8.5.2.3, 8.5.3.0 through 8.5.3.1, 8.5.4.0, 8.6.0.0 through 8.6.0.5, 8.6.1.0, 8.6.2.0 through 8.6.2.1, 8.6.3.0, 8.7.0.0 through 8.7.0.2, 8.7.1.0, 8.7.2.0 through 8.7.2.1) could allow a remote attacker to bypass RPCAdapter endpoint authentication by sending a specifically crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0160 | IBM FlashSystem code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0160</link><description>IBM FlashSystem (IBM Storage Virtualize (8.5.0.0 through 8.5.0.13, 8.5.1.0, 8.5.2.0 through 8.5.2.3, 8.5.3.0 through 8.5.3.1, 8.5.4.0, 8.6.0.0 through 8.6.0.5, 8.6.1.0, 8.6.2.0 through 8.6.2.1, 8.6.3.0, 8.7.0.0 through 8.7.0.2, 8.7.1.0, 8.7.2.0 through 8.7.2.1)  could allow a remote attacker with access to the system to execute arbitrary Java code due to improper restrictions in the RPCAdapter service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1795 | Mishandling of comma during folding and unicode-encoding of email headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1795</link><description>During an address list folding when a separating comma ends up on a folded line and that line is to be unicode-encoded then the separator itself is also unicode-encoded. Expected behavior is that the separating comma remains a plan comma. This can result in the address header being misinterpreted by some mail servers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25609 | TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25609</link><description>TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation of the static_ipv6 parameter in the formIpv6Setup interface of /bin/boa</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25610 | TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25610</link><description>TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation of the static_gw parameter in the formIpv6Setup interface of /bin/boa.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 19:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25635 | TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25635</link><description>TOTOlink A3002R V1.1.1-B20200824.0128 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper input validation of the pppoe_dns1 parameter in the formIpv6Setup interface of /bin/boa.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25428 | TRENDnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25428</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25429 | Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the r_name variable inside the have_same_name fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25429</link><description>Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the r_name variable inside the have_same_name function on the /addschedule.htm page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25430 | Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the configname parameter on the /cbi_addcert.htm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25430</link><description>Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the configname parameter on the /cbi_addcert.htm page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25431 | Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the The ssid key of wifi_data parameter on the /...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25431</link><description>Trendnet TEW-929DRU 1.0.0.10 contains a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the The ssid key of wifi_data parameter on the /captive_portal.htm page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27408 | Manifest Uses a One-Way Hash without a Salt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27408</link><description>Manifest offers users a one-file micro back end. Prior to version 4.9.1, Manifest employs a weak password hashing implementation that uses SHA3 without a salt. This exposes user passwords to a higher risk of being cracked if an attacker gains access to the database. Without the use of a salt, identical passwords across multiple users will result in the same hash, making it easier for attackers to identify and exploit patterns, thereby accelerating the cracking process. Version 4.9.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24316 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24316</link><description>The Dario Health Internet-based server infrastructure is vulnerable due to exposure of development environment details, which could lead to unsafe functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24318 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Sensitive Cookie Without &amp;#x27;HttpOnly&amp;#x27; Flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24318</link><description>Cookie policy is observable via built-in browser tools. In the presence of XSS, this could lead to full session compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20049 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20049</link><description>The Dario Health portal service application is vulnerable to XSS, which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24849 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24849</link><description>Lack of encryption in transit for cloud infrastructure facilitating potential for sensitive data manipulation or exposure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23405 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Improper Output Neutralization For Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23405</link><description>Unauthenticated log effects metrics gathering incident response efforts and potentially exposes risk of injection attacks (ex log injection).</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24843 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Storage of Sensitive Data in a Mechanism without Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24843</link><description>Insecure file retrieval process that facilitates potential for file manipulation to affect product stability and confidentiality, integrity, authenticity, and attestation of stored data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 17:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20060 | Dario Health USB-C Blood Glucose Monitoring System Starter Kit Android Application Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20060</link><description>An attacker could expose cross-user personal identifiable information (PII) and personal health information transmitted to the Android device via the Dario Health application database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54175 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54175</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD 

could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to an improper check for unusual or exceptional conditions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0985 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0985</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD 

stores potentially sensitive information in environment variables that could be obtained by a local user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26047 | Loggrove v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the read.py file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26047</link><description>Loggrove v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the read.py file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26263 | GeoVision ASManager Windows desktop application with the version 6.1.2.0 or less, is vulnerable to credentials disclosure due to improper me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26263</link><description>GeoVision ASManager Windows desktop application with the version 6.1.2.0 or less, is vulnerable to credentials disclosure due to improper memory handling in the ASManagerService.exe process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44754 | Cryptographic key extraction from internal flash in Minut M2 with firmware version #15142 allows physically proximate attackers to inject mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44754</link><description>Cryptographic key extraction from internal flash in Minut M2 with firmware version #15142 allows physically proximate attackers to inject modified firmware into any other Minut M2 product via USB.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27400 | Magento vulnerable to stored XSS in theme config fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27400</link><description>Magento Long Term Support (LTS) is an unofficial, community-driven project provides an alternative to the Magento Community Edition e-commerce platform with a high level of backward compatibility. Versions prior to 20.12.3 and 20.13.1 contain a vulnerability that allows script execution in the admin panel which could lead to cross-site scripting against authenticated admin users. The attack requires an admin user with configuration access, so in practicality it is not very likely to be useful given that a user with this level of access is probably already a full admin. Versions 20.12.3 and 20.13.1 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25461 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SeedDMS 6.0.29. A user or rogue admin with the "Add Category" permission can inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25461</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in SeedDMS 6.0.29. A user or rogue admin with the "Add Category" permission can inject a malicious XSS payload into the category name field. When a document is subsequently associated with this category, the payload is stored on the server and rendered without proper sanitization or output encoding. This results in the XSS payload executing in the browser of any user who views the document.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25916 | wuzhicms v4.1.0 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in del function in \coreframe\app\member\admin\group.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25916</link><description>wuzhicms v4.1.0 has a Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in del function in \coreframe\app\member\admin\group.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26326 | A vulnerability in the remote connection complements of the NVDA (Nonvisual Desktop Access) 2024.4.1 and 2024.4.2 was identified, which allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26326</link><description>A vulnerability in the remote connection complements of the NVDA (Nonvisual Desktop Access) 2024.4.1 and 2024.4.2 was identified, which allows an attacker to obtain total control of the remote system when guessing a weak password. The problem occurs because the complements accept any password typed by the user and do not have an additional authentication or checking mechanism by the computer that will be accessed. Tests indicate that over 1,000 systems use easy to guess passwords, many with less than 4 to 6 characters, including common sequences. This enables brute strength or attempt and error attacks on the part of malicious invaders. Vulnerability can be explored by a remote striker who knows or can guess the password used in the connection. As a result, the invader gets complete access to the affected system and can run commands, modify files and compromise user security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 15:10:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1747 | HTML injection vulnerability in OpenCart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1747</link><description>HTML injection vulnerabilities in OpenCart versions prior to 4.1.0. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to modify the HTML of the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL and modifying the parameter name in /account/login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1748 | HTML injection vulnerability in OpenCart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1748</link><description>HTML injection vulnerabilities in OpenCart versions prior to 4.1.0. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to modify the HTML of the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL and modifying the parameter name in /account/register.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1749 | HTML injection vulnerability in OpenCart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1749</link><description>HTML injection vulnerabilities in OpenCart versions prior to 4.1.0. These vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to modify the HTML of the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL and modifying the parameter name in /account/voucher.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1776 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Soteshop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1776</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Soteshop, versions prior to 8.3.4, which could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the ‘query’ parameter in /app-google-custom-search/searchResults. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1746 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in OpenCart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1746</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in OpenCart versions prior to 4.1.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the search in the /product/search endpoint. This vulnerability could be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1300 | Open redirect in CodeChecker web server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1300</link><description>CodeChecker is an analyzer tooling, defect database and viewer extension for the Clang Static Analyzer and Clang Tidy. 

The CodeChecker web server contains an open redirect vulnerability due to missing protections against multiple slashes after the product name in the URL. This results in bypassing the protections against CVE-2021-28861, leading to the same open redirect pathway.

This issue affects CodeChecker: through 6.24.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1319 | Site Mailer &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1319</link><description>The Site Mailer – SMTP Replacement, Email API Deliverability &amp; Email Log plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22270 | Stored XSS in CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22270</link><description>An attacker with access to the Administration panel, specifically the "Role Management"
tab, can
inject code by adding a new role in the "name" field. It should be noted, however, that the risk of exploiting vulnerability is reduced due to the
required additional error that allows bypassing the Content-Security-Policy policy, which
mitigates JS code execution while still allowing HTML injection.


This issue affects CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager in SaaS version 24.7.1. The status of other versions is unknown. After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22271 | IP Spoofing in CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22271</link><description>The application or its infrastructure allows for IP address spoofing by providing its own value in the "X-Forwarded-For" header. Thus, the action logging mechanism in the application loses accountability


This issue affects CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager in SaaS version 24.7.1. The status of other versions is unknown. After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22272 | Self Reflected XSS in CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22272</link><description>In the "/EPMUI/ModalDlgHandler.ashx?value=showReadonlyDlg" endpoint, it is possible to inject code in the "modalDlgMsgInternal" parameter via POST, which is then executed in the browser. The risk of exploiting vulnerability is reduced due to the required additional bypassing the Content-Security-Policy policy


This issue affects CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager in SaaS version 24.7.1. The status of other versions is unknown. After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22273 | Lack of rate-limiting in password change mechanism in CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22273</link><description>Application does not limit the number or frequency of user interactions, such as the number of incoming requests. At the "/EPMUI/VfManager.asmx/ChangePassword" endpoint it is possible to perform a brute force attack on the current password in use.


This issue affects CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager in SaaS version 24.7.1. The status of other versions is unknown. After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22274 | HTML injection in CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22274</link><description>It is possible to inject HTML code into the page content using the "content" field in the "Application definition" page.


This issue affects CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager in SaaS version 24.7.1. The status of other versions is unknown. After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 13:04:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10860 | NextMove Lite – Thank You Page for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.19.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Deactivation Reason Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10860</link><description>The NextMove Lite – Thank You Page for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized submission of data due to a missing capability check on the _submit_uninstall_reason_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to submit a deactivation reason on behalf of a site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 09:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22492 | Insecure storage of connection strings in FRS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22492</link><description>The connection string visible to users with access to FRSCore database on Foreseer Reporting Software (FRS) VM, this
string can be used for gaining administrative access to the 4crXref database. This vulnerability has been resolved in the latest version 1.5.100 of FRS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13469 | Pricing Table by PickPlugins &amp;lt;= 1.12.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13469</link><description>The Pricing Table by PickPlugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Button Link in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13638 | Order Attachments for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13638</link><description>The Order Attachments for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.1 via the 'uploads' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads directory which can contain file attachments added to orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13716 | Forex Calculators &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13716</link><description>The Forex Calculators plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_settings_callback() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13831 | Tabs for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authentiated (Shop Manager+) PHP Object Injection in product_has_custom_tabs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13831</link><description>The Tabs for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'product_has_custom_tabs' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13832 | Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Restricted Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13832</link><description>The Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 via the 'ut_elementor' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13851 | Modal Portfolio &amp;lt;= 1.7.4.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13851</link><description>The Modal Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8420 | DHVC Form &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8420</link><description>The DHVC Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.7. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to supply the 'role' field when registering. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as an administrator on sites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8425 | WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8425</link><description>The WooCommerce Ultimate Gift Card plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'mwb_wgm_preview_mail' and 'mwb_wgm_woocommerce_add_cart_item_data' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9019 | SecuPress Free — WordPress Security &amp;lt;= 2.2.5.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via secupress_check_ban_ips_form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9019</link><description>The SecuPress Free — WordPress Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's secupress_check_ban_ips_form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9193 | WHMpress &amp;lt;= 6.3-revision-0 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9193</link><description>The WHMpress - WHMCS WordPress Integration Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 6.3-revision-0 via the whmpress_domain_search_ajax_extended_results() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. Utilizing the /admin/services.php file, this can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9195 | WHMPress - WHMCS Client Area &amp;lt;= 4.3-revision-3- Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9195</link><description>The WHMPress - WHMCS Client Area plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the update_settings case in the /admin/ajax.php file in all versions up to, and including, 4.3-revision-3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1413 | Dylib Hijacking in DaVinci Resolve</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1413</link><description>DaVinci Resolve on MacOS was found to be installed with incorrect file permissions (rwxrwxrwx). This is inconsistent with standard macOS security practices, where applications should have drwxr-xr-x permissions. Incorrect permissions allow for Dylib Hijacking. Guest account, other users and applications can exploit this vulnerability for privilege escalation. This issue affects DaVinci Resolve on MacOS in versions before 19.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1560 | WOW Entrance Effects (WEE!) &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1560</link><description>The WOW Entrance Effects (WEE!) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wee' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1570 | Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.1 - Privilege Escalation and Account Takeover via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1570</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 8.1. This is due to the directorist_generate_password_reset_pin_code() and reset_user_password() functions not having enough controls to prevent a successful brute force attack of the OTP to change a password, or verify that a password reset request came from an authorized user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force an OTP that makes it possible to change any users passwords, including an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1662 | URL Media Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery via DNS Rebinding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1662</link><description>The URL Media Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 via the 'url_media_uploader_url_upload' action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22491 | Improper Input Validation in Foreseer Reporting Software (FRS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22491</link><description>The user input was not sanitized on Reporting Hierarchy Management page of Foreseer Reporting Software (FRS) application which could lead into execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a browser context
for all the interacting users. This security issue has been patched in the latest version 1.5.100 of the FRS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 08:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1572 | KiviCare – Clinic &amp;amp; Patient Management System (EHR) &amp;lt;= 3.6.7 - Authenticated (Doctor+) SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;u_id&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1572</link><description>The KiviCare – Clinic &amp; Patient Management System (EHR) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘u_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with doctor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0764 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read in update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0764</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read due to insufficient input validation in the 'update' method of the 'Members' class in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level privileges or higher, to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1405 | Product Catalog Simple &amp;lt;= 1.7.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via show_products Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1405</link><description>The Product Catalog Simple plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's show_products shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1571 | Exclusive Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Animated Text and Image Comparison Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1571</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Animated Text and Image Comparison Widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 07:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12820 | MK Google Directions &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12820</link><description>The MK Google Directions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'MKGD' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1506 | Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1506</link><description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the counter_access_key_setup() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update social login provider settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1511 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1511</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1513 | Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal, Social Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 26.0.0.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1513</link><description>The Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal or Stripe, Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Name and Comment field when commenting on photo gallery entries in all versions up to, and including, 26.0.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 05:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13796 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Unauthenticated User Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13796</link><description>The Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.6 via the /wp-json/post-grid/v2/get_users REST API This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including including emails and other user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0801 | RateMyAgent Official &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to API Key Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0801</link><description>The RateMyAgent Official plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'rma-settings-wizard'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's API key via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1505 | Advanced AJAX Product Filters &amp;lt;= 1.6.8.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1505</link><description>The Advanced AJAX Product Filters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'nonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1757 | WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1757</link><description>The WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'pfhub_portfolio' and 'pfhub_portfolio_portfolio' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1744 | Out-of-bounds Write in radare2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1744</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in radareorg radare2 allows 

heap-based buffer over-read or buffer overflow.This issue affects radare2: before &lt;5.9.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54173 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54173</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD reveals potentially sensitive information in trace files that could be read by a local user when webconsole trace is enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:03:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56340 | IBM MQ path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56340</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 FP5 is vulnerable to local file inclusion vulnerability, allowing an attacker to access sensitive files by inserting path traversal payloads inside the deficon parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0823 | IBM MQ path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0823</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 FP5 and 12.0.0 through 12.0.4 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0975 | IBM MQ code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0975</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD console could allow an authenticated user to execute code due to improper neutralization of escape characters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:03:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23225 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23225</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to the improper handling of invalid headers sent to the queue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 03:03:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>