<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-39624 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39624</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39630 | WordPress Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.13 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39630</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MotoPress Timetable and Event Schedule allows Object Injection.This issue affects Timetable and Event Schedule: from n/a through 2.4.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39633 | WordPress PowerPack for Beaver Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33.0 - Contributor+ Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39633</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in IdeaBox PowerPack for Beaver Builder allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects PowerPack for Beaver Builder: from n/a through 2.33.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39634 | WordPress PowerPack Pro for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.14 - Contributor+ Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39634</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in IdeaBox PowerPack Pro for Elementor allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects PowerPack Pro for Elementor: from n/a through 2.10.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41259 | Use of insecure hashing algorithm in the Gravatar's service in Navidrome v0.52.3 allows attackers to manipulate a user's account information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41259</link><description>Use of insecure hashing algorithm in the Gravatar's service in Navidrome v0.52.3 allows attackers to manipulate a user's account information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7366 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System Login ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273345 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7365 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_establishment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_establishment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273344.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7364 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_records.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7364</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_records.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273343.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7363 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_person.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7363</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_person.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273342 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7362 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7362</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273341 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4353 | Concrete CMS version 9 Generate Dashboard Name input Field Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4353</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 through 9.3.2 are affected by a stored XSS vulnerability in the generate dashboard board
instance functionality. The Name input field does not check the input sufficiently letting a rogue administrator hav the capability to inject malicious
JavaScript code. The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability a CVSS v3.1 score of 3.1 with a vector of  AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator  and a CVSS v4 score of 1.8 with a vector of CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:H/AT:N/PR:H/UI:A/VC:L/VI:L/VA:N/SC:N/SI:N/SA:N Thanks fhAnso for reporting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6990 | Uninitialized Use in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6990</link><description>Uninitialized Use in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Critical)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7255 | Out of bounds read in WebTransport in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7255</link><description>Out of bounds read in WebTransport in Google Chrome prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7256 | Insufficient data validation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7256</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Dawn in Google Chrome on Android prior to 127.0.6533.88 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7361 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7361</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273340.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7360 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7360</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273339.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23600 | PingIDM OpenIDM Query Filter Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23600</link><description>Improper Input Validation of query search results for private field data in PingIDM OPENIDM (Query Filter module) allows for a potentially efficient brute forcing approach leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7211 | Vulnerable Identity Server on 1E Platform may permit URL redirections to untrusted sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7211</link><description>The Identity Server used by 1E Platform could enable URL redirection to untrusted sites. 

Note: The Identity Server on 1E Platform has been updated with the necessary patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41962 | Bostr Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41962</link><description>Bostr is an nostr relay aggregator proxy that acts like a regular nostr relay. bostr let everyone in even having authorized_keys being set when noscraper is set to true. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7359 | SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7359</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273338 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41265 | A TLS certificate verification issue discovered in cortex v0.42.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the makeOperatorReque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41265</link><description>A TLS certificate verification issue discovered in cortex v0.42.1 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the makeOperatorRequest function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6873 | Specially crafted request could caused undefined behaviour which may lead to Remote Code Execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6873</link><description>It is possible to crash or redirect the execution flow of the ClickHouse server process from an unauthenticated vector by sending a specially crafted request to the ClickHouse server native interface. This redirection is limited to what is available within a 256-byte range of memory at the time of execution, and no known remote code execution (RCE) code has been produced or exploited.

 Fixes have been merged to all currently supported version of ClickHouse. If you are maintaining your own forked version of ClickHouse or using an older version and cannot upgrade, the fix for this vulnerability can be found in this commit  https://github.com/ClickHouse/ClickHouse/pull/64024 .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41264 | An issue discovered in casdoor v1.636.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() method.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41264</link><description>An issue discovered in casdoor v1.636.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() method.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6040 | Missing client_id in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6040</link><description>In parisneo/lollms-webui version v9.8, the lollms_binding_infos is missing the client_id parameter, which leads to multiple security vulnerabilities. Specifically, the endpoints /reload_binding, /install_binding, /reinstall_binding, /unInstall_binding, /set_active_binding_settings, and /update_binding_settings are susceptible to CSRF attacks and local attacks. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform unauthorized actions on the victim's machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41260 | A static initialization vector (IV) in the encrypt function of netbird v0.28.4 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41260</link><description>A static initialization vector (IV) in the encrypt function of netbird v0.28.4 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6242 | Rockwell Automation Chassis Restrictions Bypass Vulnerability in Select Logix Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:27:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41961 | Elektra vulnerable to remote code execution in universal search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41961</link><description>Elektra is an opinionated Openstack Dashboard for Operators and Consumers of Openstack Services. A code injection vulnerability was found in the live search functionality of the Ruby on Rails based Elektra web application. An authenticated user can craft a search term containing Ruby code, which later flows into an `eval` sink which executes the code. Fixed in commit 8bce00be93b95a6512ff68fe86bf9554e486bc02.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29977 | Malicious remote can create arbitrary reactions on arbitrary posts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29977</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to properly validate synced reactions, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to create arbitrary reactions on arbitrary posts</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36492 | Existing local user overwritten by malicious remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36492</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow the modification of local users when syncing users in shared channels. which allows a malicious remote to overwrite an existing local user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39274 | Malicious remote can add users to arbitrary teams and channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39274</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly validate that the channel that comes from the sync message is a shared channel, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to add users to arbitrary teams and channels</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39777 | Malicious remote can invite itself to an arbitrary local channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39777</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow unsolicited invites to expose access to local channels, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to send an invite with the ID of an existing local channel, and that local channel will then become shared without the consent of the local admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39832 | Permanently local data deletion by malicious remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39832</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly safeguard an error handling which allows a malicious remote to permanently delete local data by abusing dangerous error handling, when share channels were enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39837 | Malicious remote can create arbitrary channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39837</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to properly restrict channel creation which allows a malicious remote to create arbitrary channels, when shared channels were enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39839 | Remote username set to an arbitrary string by remote user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39839</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow users to set their own remote username, when shared channels were enabled, which allows a user on a remote to set their remote username prop to an arbitrary string, which would be then synced to the local server as long as the user hadn't been synced before.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41123 | REXML DoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41123</link><description>REXML is an XML toolkit for Ruby. The REXML gem before 3.3.2 has some DoS vulnerabilities when it parses an XML that has many specific characters such as whitespace character, `&gt;]` and `]&gt;`. The REXML gem 3.3.3 or later include the patches to fix these vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41144 | Malicious remote can create/update/delete arbitrary posts in arbitrary channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41144</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5, 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to properly validate synced posts, when shared channels are enabled,  which allows a malicious remote to create/update/delete arbitrary posts in arbitrary channels</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41162 | Malicious remote can make an arbitrary local channel read-only</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41162</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6, 9.7.x &lt;= 9.7.5 and 9.8.x &lt;= 9.8.1 fail to disallow the modification of local channels by a remote, when shared channels are enabled, which allows a malicious remote to make an arbitrary local channel read-only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41926 | Malicious remote can claim that a user was synced from another remote</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41926</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.9.x &lt;= 9.9.0 and 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.6 fail to validate the source of sync messages and only allow the correct remote IDs, which allows a malicious remote to set arbitrary RemoteId values for synced users and therefore claim that a user was synced from another remote.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41946 | REXML DoS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41946</link><description>REXML is an XML toolkit for Ruby. The REXML gem 3.3.2 has a DoS vulnerability when it parses an XML that has many entity expansions with SAX2 or pull parser API. The REXML gem 3.3.3 or later include the patch to fix the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6923 | Email header injection due to unquoted newlines</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6923</link><description>There is a MEDIUM severity vulnerability affecting CPython.

The 
email module didn’t properly quote newlines for email headers when 
serializing an email message allowing for header injection when an email
 is serialized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7358 | Point B Ltd Getscreen Agent Installation getscreen.msi temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Point B Ltd Getscreen Agent 2.19.6 on Windows. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file getscreen.msi of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to creation of temporary file with insecure permissions. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273337 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but was not able to provide a technical response in time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7357 | D-Link DIR-600 soap.cgi soapcgi_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7357</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.18. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function soapcgi_main of the file /soap.cgi. The manipulation of the argument service leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273329 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2455 | Element Pack - Addon for Elementor Page Builder WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.9.0 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Wrapper Link URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2455</link><description>The Element Pack - Addon for Elementor Page Builder WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the widget wrapper link URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6346 | Post Grid, Form Maker, Popup Maker, WooCommerce Blocks, Post Blocks, Post Carousel – Combo Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.2.85a - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via redirectURL Parameter of Date Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6346</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the redirectURL parameter of the Date Countdown widget, in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.85a due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28972 | Dell InsightIQ, Verion 5.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28972</link><description>Dell InsightIQ, Verion 5.0.0, contains a use of a broken or risky cryptographic algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38481 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38481</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25948 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25948</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38489 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior contains Out of bound write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38489</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior contains Out of bound write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service (partial) event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38490 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38490</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain a Out of bound Write Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25947 | Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain an Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25947</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module version 5.3.0.0 and prior, contain an Out of bound Read Vulnerability. A privileged local attacker could execute arbitrary code potentially resulting in a denial of service event.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5678 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5678</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 170900 and below are vulnerable to the authenticated admin-only SQL Injection in the Create Monitor feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5330 | Breakdance &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5330</link><description>The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the breakdance_css_file_paths_cache parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5331 | Breakdance &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5331</link><description>The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to export form submissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7302 | Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp;amp; Scheduler &amp;lt;= 7.5.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7302</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 3gp2 file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 7.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the 3gp2 file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1747 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.2 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1747</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.2 does not have authorisation and CSRF in various AJAX actions, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber, to call them and update/delete/create customer metadata, also leading to Stored Cross-Site Scripting due to the lack of escaping of said metadata values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2843 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.1 - User Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2843</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin users delete users via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2872 | Swift Framework &amp;lt; 2024.04.30 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2872</link><description>The socialdriver-framework WordPress plugin before 2024.04.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3983 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 30.1 - Bulk Action via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3983</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 30.1 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting customers via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4090 | My Sticky Bar &amp;lt; 2.7.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4090</link><description>The Floating Notification Bar, Sticky Menu on Scroll, Announcement Banner, and Sticky Header for Any   WordPress plugin before 2.7.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6496 | Light Poll &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Polls Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6496</link><description>The Light Poll WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF checks when deleting polls, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6529 | Ultimate Classified Listings &amp;lt; 1.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6529</link><description>The Ultimate Classified Listings WordPress plugin before 1.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7343 | Baidu UEditor cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7343</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baidu UEditor 1.4.2. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ueditor142/php/controller.php?action=catchimage. The manipulation of the argument source[] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 05:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2090 | Remote Content Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2090</link><description>The Remote Content Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 via the remote_content shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7342 | Baidu UEditor unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7342</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Baidu UEditor 1.4.3.3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /ueditor/php/controller.php?action=uploadfile&amp;amp;encode=utf-8. The manipulation of the argument upfile leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273273 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7339 | TVT DVR TD-2104TS-CL queryDevInfo information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7339</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TVT DVR TD-2104TS-CL, DVR TD-2108TS-HP, Provision-ISR DVR SH-4050A5-5L(MM) and AVISION DVR AV108T and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /queryDevInfo. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273262 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1715 | AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp;amp; Ads.txt &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Ad Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1715</link><description>The AdFoxly – Ad Manager, AdSense Ads &amp; Ads.txt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the adfoxly_ad_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable ads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6698 | FundEngine – Donation and Crowdfunding Platform &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6698</link><description>The FundEngine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying user meta updated through the update_user_meta function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta which can be leveraged to update their capabilities to gain administrator access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7338 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7338</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. This affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7337 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. Affected by this issue is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7336 | TOTOLINK EX200 cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected by this vulnerability is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6687 | CTT Expresso para WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.2.12 - Information Exposure via Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6687</link><description>The CTT Expresso para WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information exposure in all versions up to and including 3.2.12 via the /wp-content/uploads/cepw directory. The generated .pdf and log files are publicly accessible and contain sensitive information such as sender and receiver names, phone numbers, physical addresses, and email addresses</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7335 | TOTOLINK EX200 getSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK EX200 4.0.3c.7646_B20201211. Affected is the function getSaveConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=save&amp;amp;setting. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34021 | Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted file may be uploade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34021</link><description>Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted file may be uploaded to the affected product by a logged-in user with an administrative privilege, resulting in an arbitrary OS command execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39607 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted request may be sent to the affected product by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39607</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. A specially crafted request may be sent to the affected product by a logged-in user with an administrative privilege to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40883 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. Viewing a malicious page while logging in to the affected pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40883</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in ELECOM wireless LAN routers. Viewing a malicious page while logging in to the affected product with an administrative privilege, the user may be directed to perform unintended operations such as changing the login ID, login password, etc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7333 | TOTOLINK N350RT cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7333</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument week/sTime/eTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7334 | TOTOLINK EX1200L cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1200L 9.3.5u.6146_B20201023. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7332 | TOTOLINK CP450 Telnet Service product.ini hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_cste/cgi-bin/product.ini of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7331 | TOTOLINK A3300R cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A3300R 17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7330 | YouDianCMS ydLib.php curl_exec server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7330</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in YouDianCMS 7 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function curl_exec of the file /App/Core/Extend/Function/ydLib.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273253 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38182 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38182</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7329 | YouDianCMS image_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7329</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in YouDianCMS 7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Public/ckeditor/plugins/multiimage/dialogs/image_upload.php. The manipulation of the argument files leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273252. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7328 | YouDianCMS information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7328</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in YouDianCMS 7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /t.php?action=phpinfo. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273251. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7327 | Xinhu RockOA openmodhetongAction.php dataAction sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7327</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Xinhu RockOA 2.6.2. This vulnerability affects the function dataAction of the file /webmain/task/openapi/openmodhetongAction.php. The manipulation of the argument nickName leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273250 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41262 | mmudb v1.9.3 was discovered to use the HTTP protocol in the ShowMetricsRaw and ShowMetricsAsText functions, possibly allowing attackers to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41262</link><description>mmudb v1.9.3 was discovered to use the HTTP protocol in the ShowMetricsRaw and ShowMetricsAsText functions, possibly allowing attackers to intercept communications via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41258 | An issue was discovered in filestash v0.4. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41258</link><description>An issue was discovered in filestash v0.4. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing attackers to obtain sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41256 | Default configurations in the ShareProofVerifier function of filestash v0.4 causes the application to skip the TLS certificate verification ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41256</link><description>Default configurations in the ShareProofVerifier function of filestash v0.4 causes the application to skip the TLS certificate verification process when sending out email verification codes, possibly allowing attackers to access sensitive data via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41254 | An issue was discovered in litestream v0.3.13. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41254</link><description>An issue was discovered in litestream v0.3.13. The usage of the ssh.InsecureIgnoreHostKey() disables host key verification, possibly allowing attackers to obtain sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-3772 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager versions prior to 2.6.40.3154 that could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3772</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager versions prior to 2.6.40.3154 that could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6197 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6197</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-6198 | A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6198</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager prior to version 2.8.90.11211 that could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4001 | An authentication bypass vulnerability could allow an attacker to access API functions without authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4001</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability could allow an attacker to access API functions without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4002 | A command injection vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to execute operating system commands as root via a specially crafted API...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4002</link><description>A command injection vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to execute operating system commands as root via a specially crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4003 | A denial-of-service vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to trigger an internal service restart via a specially crafted API reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4003</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability could allow an authenticated user to trigger an internal service restart via a specially crafted API request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1577 | A path hijacking vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Driver Manager prior to version 3.1.1307.1308 that could allow a local user to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1577</link><description>A path hijacking vulnerability was reported in Lenovo Driver Manager prior to version 3.1.1307.1308 that could allow a local user to execute code with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41255 | filestash v0.4 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification when using the FTPS protocol, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41255</link><description>filestash v0.4 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification when using the FTPS protocol, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the Init function of index.go.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7326 | IObit DualSafe Password Manager BPL RTL120.BPL uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7326</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in IObit DualSafe Password Manager 1.4.0.3. This affects an unknown part in the library RTL120.BPL of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The identifier VDB-273249 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41253 | goframe v2.7.2 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41253</link><description>goframe v2.7.2 is configured to skip TLS certificate verification, possibly allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via the gclient component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4187 | Stored XSS vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Filr. The vulnerability could cause users to not be warned when clicking links to external sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4187</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Filr product, affecting versions 24.1.1 and 24.2. The vulnerability could cause users to not be warned when clicking links to external sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40464 | An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendMail function located in beego/core/logs/sm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40464</link><description>An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the sendMail function located in beego/core/logs/smtp.go file</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40465 | An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getCacheFileName function in file.go file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40465</link><description>An issue in beego v.2.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getCacheFileName function in file.go file</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41660 | slpd-lite unauthenticated memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41660</link><description>slpd-lite is a unicast SLP UDP server. Any OpenBMC system that includes the slpd-lite package is impacted. Installing this package is the default when building OpenBMC. Nefarious users can send slp packets to the BMC using UDP port 427 to cause memory overflow issues within the slpd-lite daemon on the BMC. Patches will be available in the latest openbmc/slpd-lite repository.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7325 | IObit Driver Booster BPL VCL120.BPL uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7325</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Driver Booster 11.0.0.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality in the library VCL120.BPL of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273248. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41951 | PheonixAppAPI has visible Encoding Maps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41951</link><description>Pheonix App is a Python application designed to streamline various tasks, from managing files to playing mini-games. The issue is that the map of encoding/decoding languages are visible in code. The Problem was patched in 0.2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41954 | FOG Weak file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41954</link><description>FOG is a cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. The application stores plaintext service account credentials in the "/opt/fog/.fogsettings" file. This file is by default readable by all users on the host. By exploiting these credentials, a malicious user could create new accounts for the web application and much more. The vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41955 | Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) has an Open Redirect in Login Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41955</link><description>Mobile Security Framework (MobSF) is a security research platform for mobile applications in Android, iOS and Windows Mobile. An open redirect vulnerability exist in MobSF authentication view. Update to MobSF v4.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41108 | FOG Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41108</link><description>FOG is a free open-source cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. The hostinfo page has missing/improper access control since only the host's mac address is required to obtain the configuration information. This data can only be retrieved if a task is pending on that host. Otherwise, an error message containing "Invalid tasking!" will be returned. The domainpassword in the hostinfo dump is hidden even to authenticated users, as it is displayed as a row of asterisks when navigating to the host's Active Directory settings.  This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40645 | FOG Authenticated File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40645</link><description>FOG is a cloning/imaging/rescue suite/inventory management system. An improperly restricted file upload feature allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary code on the fogproject server. The Rebranding feature has a check on the client banner image requiring it to be 650 pixels wide and 120 pixels high. Apart from that, there are no checks on things like file extensions. This can be abused by appending a PHP webshell to the end of the image and changing the extension to anything the PHP web server will parse. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.10.41.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41630 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC18 V15.03.3.10_EN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41630</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Tenda AC18 V15.03.3.10_EN allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ssid parameter at ip/goform/fast_setting_wifi_set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28149 | An issue was discovered in the IhisiServiceSmm module in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.42, 5.3 before 05.37.42, 5.4 before 0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28149</link><description>An issue was discovered in the IhisiServiceSmm module in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.2 before 05.28.42, 5.3 before 05.37.42, 5.4 before 05.45.39, 5.5 before 05.53.39, and 5.6 before 05.60.39 that could allow an attacker to modify UEFI variables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23444 | Elasticsearch elasticsearch-certutil csr fails to encrypt private key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23444</link><description>It was discovered by Elastic engineering that when elasticsearch-certutil CLI tool is used with the csr option in order to create a new Certificate Signing Requests, the associated private key that is generated is stored on disk unencrypted even if the --pass parameter is passed in the command invocation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7324 | IObit iTop Data Recovery Pro BPL madbasic_.bpl uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7324</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit iTop Data Recovery Pro 4.4.0.687. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library madbasic_.bpl of the component BPL Handler. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Local access is required to approach this attack. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273247. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6973 | Remote Code Execution in Cato Windows SDP client via crafted URLs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6973</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Windows SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6974 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local Privilege Escalation via self-upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6974</link><description>Untrusted Search Path, Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6975 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local Privilege Escalation via openssl configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6975</link><description>Untrusted Search Path vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6977 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Sensitive data in trace logs can lead to account takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6977</link><description>A vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows the insertion of sensitive information into the log file, which can lead to an account takeover. However, the attack requires bypassing protections on modifying the tunnel token on a the attacker's system.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.34.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6978 | Cato Networks Windows SDP Client Local root certificates can be installed by low-privileged users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6978</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Cato Networks SDP Client on Windows allows Command Injection.This issue affects SDP Client: before 5.10.28.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41953 | Zitadel improperly sanitizes HTML in emails and Console UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41953</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management system. ZITADEL uses HTML for emails and renders certain information such as usernames dynamically. That information can be entered by users or administrators. Due to a missing output sanitization, these emails could include malicious code. This may potentially lead to a threat where an attacker, without privileges, could send out altered notifications that are part of the registration processes. An attacker could create a malicious link, where the injected code would be rendered as part of the email. On the user's detail page, the username was also not sanitized and would also render HTML, giving an attacker the same vulnerability. While it was possible to inject HTML including javascript, the execution of such scripts would be prevented by most email clients and the Content Security Policy in Console UI. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.58.1, 2.57.1, 2.56.2, 2.55.5, 2.54.8 2.53.9, and 2.52.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41952 | Zitadel has an &amp;quot;Ignoring unknown usernames&amp;quot; vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41952</link><description>Zitadel is an open source identity management system. ZITADEL administrators can enable a setting called "Ignoring unknown usernames" which helps mitigate attacks that try to guess/enumerate usernames. If enabled, ZITADEL will show the password prompt even if the user doesn't exist and report "Username or Password invalid". Due to a implementation change to prevent deadlocks calling the database, the flag would not be correctly respected in all cases and an attacker would gain information if an account exist within ZITADEL, since the error message shows "object not found" instead of the generic error message. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.58.1, 2.57.1, 2.56.2, 2.55.5, 2.54.8, and 2.53.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41950 | Insecure Jinja2 templates rendered in Haystack Components can lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41950</link><description>Haystack is an end-to-end LLM framework that allows you to build applications powered by LLMs, Transformer models, vector search and more. Haystack clients that let their users create and run Pipelines from scratch are vulnerable to remote code executions. Certain Components in Haystack use Jinja2 templates, if anyone can create and render that template on the client machine they run any code. The vulnerability has been fixed with Haystack `2.3.1`.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39694 | Duende IdentityServer Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39694</link><description>Duende IdentityServer is an OpenID Connect and OAuth 2.x framework for ASP.NET Core. It is possible for an attacker to craft malicious Urls that certain functions in IdentityServer will incorrectly treat as local and trusted. If such a Url is returned as a redirect, some browsers will follow it to a third-party, untrusted site. Note: by itself, this vulnerability does **not** allow an attacker to obtain user credentials, authorization codes, access tokens, refresh tokens, or identity tokens. An attacker could however exploit this vulnerability as part of a phishing attack designed to steal user credentials. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.6, 6.3.10, 6.2.5, 6.1.8, and 6.0.5. Duende.IdentityServer 5.1 and earlier and all versions of IdentityServer4 are no longer supported and will not be receiving updates. If upgrading is not possible, use `IUrlHelper.IsLocalUrl` from ASP.NET Core to validate return Urls in user interface code in the IdentityServer host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39318 | Ibexa Admin UI vulnerable to DOM-based Cross-site Scripting in file upload widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39318</link><description>The Ibexa Admin UI Bundle contains all the necessary parts to run the Ibexa DXP Back Office interface. The file upload widget is vulnerable to XSS payloads in filenames. Access permission to upload files is required. As such, in most cases only authenticated editors and administrators will have the required permission. It is not persistent, i.e. the payload is only executed during the upload. In effect, an attacker will have to trick an editor/administrator into uploading a strangely named file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41947 | XWiki Platform XSS through conflict resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41947</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. By creating a conflict when another user with more rights is currently editing a page, it is possible to execute JavaScript snippets on the side of the other user, which compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.8 and 16.3.0RC1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37898 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to document deletion and overwrite from edit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37898</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When a user has view but not edit right on a page in XWiki, that user can delete the page and replace it by a page with new content without having delete right. The previous version of the page is moved into the recycle bin and can be restored from there by an admin. As the user is recorded as deleter, the user would in theory also be able to view the deleted content, but this is not directly possible as rights of the previous version are transferred to the new page and thus the user still doesn't have view right on the page. It therefore doesn't seem to be possible to exploit this to gain any rights. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.6 by cancelling save operations by users when a new document shall be saved despite the document's existing already.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37900 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting through attachment filename in uploader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37900</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. When uploading an attachment with a malicious filename, malicious JavaScript code could be executed. This requires a social engineering attack to get the victim into uploading a file with a malicious name. The malicious code is solely executed during the upload and affects only the user uploading the attachment. While this allows performing actions in the name of that user, it seems unlikely that a user wouldn't notice the malicious filename while uploading the attachment. This has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5, 15.10.6 and 16.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37901 | XWiki Platform vulnerable to remote code execution from account via SearchSuggestConfigSheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37901</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Any user with edit right on any page can perform arbitrary remote code execution by adding instances of `XWiki.SearchSuggestConfig` and `XWiki.SearchSuggestSourceClass` to their user profile or any other page. This compromises the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.21, 15.5.5 and 15.10.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7340 | W&amp;amp;B Weave server remote arbitrary file leak and privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7340</link><description>The Weave server API allows remote users to fetch files from a specific directory, but due to a lack of input validation, it is possible to traverse and leak arbitrary files remotely. In various common scenarios, this allows a low-privileged user to assume the role of the server admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37135 | DM5500 5.16.0.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A local attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37135</link><description>DM5500 5.16.0.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A local attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31199 | A “CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')” allows malicious users to permanently injec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31199</link><description>A “CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')” allows malicious users to permanently inject arbitrary Javascript code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31200 | A “CWE-201: Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31200</link><description>A “CWE-201: Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to retrieve the password in cleartext when an administrative session is open in the browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31201 | A “CWE-428: Unquoted Search Path or Element” affects the ThermoscanIP_Scrutation service. Such misconfiguration could be abused in scenarios...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31201</link><description>A “CWE-428: Unquoted Search Path or Element” affects the ThermoscanIP_Scrutation service. Such misconfiguration could be abused in scenarios where incorrect permissions were assigned to the C:\ path to attempt a privilege escalation on the local machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31202 | A “CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource” in the ThermoscanIP installation folder allows a local attacker to perfor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31202</link><description>A “CWE-732: Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource” in the ThermoscanIP installation folder allows a local attacker to perform a Local Privilege Escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31203 | A “CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow” in the wd210std.dll dynamic library packaged with the ThermoscanIP installer allows a local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31203</link><description>A “CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow” in the wd210std.dll dynamic library packaged with the ThermoscanIP installer allows a local attacker to possibly trigger a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition on the target component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3082 | A “CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3082</link><description>A “CWE-256: Plaintext Storage of a Password” affecting the administrative account allows an attacker with physical access to the machine to retrieve the password in cleartext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3083 | A “CWE-352: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)” can be exploited by remote attackers to perform state-changing operations with administrative...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3083</link><description>A “CWE-352: Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF)” can be exploited by remote attackers to perform state-changing operations with administrative privileges by luring authenticated victims into visiting a malicious web page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39379 | T5 Acrobat Vulnerability - JP2KTile::ReadHdrAndInit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39379</link><description>Acrobat for Edge versions 126.0.2592.81 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read access. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to read contents from a location in memory past the buffer boundary, potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6208 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.97 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6208</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdm_all_packages' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.97 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'cols' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 12:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7321 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System User Registration signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file signup.php of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument user leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273232.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7320 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System Admin Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7320</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/index.php of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273231.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6725 | Formidable Forms &amp;lt;= 6.11.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6725</link><description>The Formidable Forms – Contact Form Plugin, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘html’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with form editing permissions and Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7135 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 0.21.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7135</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.21.7. The function is also vulnerable to directory traversal. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7311 | code-projects Online Bus Reservation Site register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7311</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Bus Reservation Site 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file register.php. The manipulation of the argument Email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273203.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7310 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7310</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file sort_user.php. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273202 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7309 | SourceCodester Record Management System entry.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7309</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file entry.php. The manipulation of the argument school leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273201 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7308 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System view_bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7308</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view_bill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273200.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37129 | Dell Inventory Collector, versions prior to 12.3.0.6 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user could pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37129</link><description>Dell Inventory Collector, versions prior to 12.3.0.6 contains a Path Traversal vulnerability. A local authenticated malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32857 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability.  An attacker could potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32857</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability.  An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2508 | WP Mobile Menu &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.4 - Missing Authorization to _mobmenu_icon Post Meta Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2508</link><description>The WP Mobile Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_menu_item_icon function in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add the '_mobmenu_icon' post meta to arbitrary posts with an arbitrary (but sanitized) value. NOTE: Version 2.8.4.4 contains a partial fix for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37127 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37127</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7307 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_billing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7307</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manage_billing.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273199.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37142 | Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37142</link><description>Dell Peripheral Manager, versions prior to 1.7.6, contain an uncontrolled search path element vulnerability. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability through preloading malicious DLL or symbolic link exploitation, leading to arbitrary code execution and escalation of privilege</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7264 | ASN.1 date parser overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7264</link><description>libcurl's ASN1 parser code has the `GTime2str()` function, used for parsing an
ASN.1 Generalized Time field. If given an syntactically incorrect field, the
parser might end up using -1 for the length of the *time fraction*, leading to
a `strlen()` getting performed on a pointer to a heap buffer area that is not
(purposely) null terminated.

This flaw most likely leads to a crash, but can also lead to heap contents
getting returned to the application when
[CURLINFO_CERTINFO](https://curl.se/libcurl/c/CURLINFO_CERTINFO.html) is used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28074 | Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition 4.1.5 and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions 4.0 through 4.6.1 and version 5.0 contain a buffer over...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28074</link><description>Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition 4.1.5 and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions 4.0 through 4.6.1 and version 5.0 contain a buffer over-read vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7306 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_block.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7306</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_block.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7303 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System Send Blood Request Page request.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7303</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /request.php of the component Send Blood Request Page. The manipulation of the argument Address/bloodgroup leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273185 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6980 | Verbose error handling issue in GravityZone Update Server proxy service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6980</link><description>A verbose error handling issue in the proxy service implemented in the GravityZone Update Server allows an attacker to cause a server-side request forgery. This issue only affects GravityZone Console versions before 6.38.1-5 running only on premise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7300 | Bolt CMS Showcase Creation showcases cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7300</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Bolt CMS 3.7.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /bolt/editcontent/showcases of the component Showcase Creation Handler. The manipulation of the argument textarea leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273168. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7299 | Bolt CMS Entry Preview page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7299</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Bolt CMS 3.7.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /preview/page of the component Entry Preview Handler. The manipulation of the argument body leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273167. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6165 | WANotifier &amp;lt; 2.6.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6165</link><description>The WANotifier  WordPress plugin before 2.6.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6272 | SpiderContacts &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6272</link><description>The SpiderContacts WordPress plugin through 1.1.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6408 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.57 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6408</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.57 does not sanitise and escape its Slider Title, which could allow high privilege users such as editors and above to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6412 | HTML Forms – Simple WordPress Forms Plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.34 - Bulk Delete via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6412</link><description>The HTML Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.3.34 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6695 | profile-builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.8 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6695</link><description>it's possible for an attacker to gain administrative access without having any kind of account on the targeted site and perform unauthorized actions. This is due to improper logic flow on the user registration process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7290 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_tenant.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7290</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /manage_tenant.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273159.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7205 | sharing unnecessary device-sensitive information allows Secondary user able to take over devices as primary user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7205</link><description>When the device is shared, the homepage module are before 2.19.0  in eWeLink Cloud Service allows Secondary user to take over devices as primary user via sharing unnecessary device-sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42381 | os/linux/elf.rb in Homebrew brew before 4.2.20 uses ldd to load ELF files obtained from untrusted sources, which allows attackers to achieve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42381</link><description>os/linux/elf.rb in Homebrew brew before 4.2.20 uses ldd to load ELF files obtained from untrusted sources, which allows attackers to achieve code execution via an ELF file with a custom .interp section. NOTE: this code execution would occur during an un-sandboxed binary relocation phase, which occurs before a user would expect execution of downloaded package content. (237d1e783f7ee261beaba7d3f6bde22da7148b0a was the tested vulnerable version.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7289 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7289</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /manage_payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273158 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6770 | Lifetime free Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress VForm &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6770</link><description>The Lifetime free Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress VForm plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7288 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7288</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_block. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273157 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7287 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7287</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273156.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7286 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System Login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7286</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273155.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39948 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39948</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39949 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39949</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39950 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39950</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products. Attackers can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities to initiate device initialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7285 | SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7285</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39944 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.Attackers
can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities,
ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39944</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.Attackers
can send carefully crafted data packets to the interface with vulnerabilities,
causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39945 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.  After
obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a
carefu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39945</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.  After
obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a
carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing
the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39946 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a carefull...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39946</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the administrator's username and password, the attacker can send a carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing device initialization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39947 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the ordinary user's username and password, the attacker can send a carefull...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39947</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.After obtaining the ordinary user's username and password, the attacker can send a carefully crafted data packet to the interface with vulnerabilities, causing the device to crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7284 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7284</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument about leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273153 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7283 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7283</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273152.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7282 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System manage_model.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7282</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_model.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273151.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7281 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7281</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php?page=manage_lot. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273150 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 01:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7280 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System view_reserved.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/view_reserved.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273149 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7279 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273148.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6255 | Arbitrary File Deletion via Directory Traversal in gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6255</link><description>A vulnerability in the JSON file handling of gaizhenbiao/chuanhuchatgpt version 20240410 allows any user to delete any JSON file on the server, including critical configuration files such as `config.json` and `ds_config_chatbot.json`. This issue arises due to improper validation of file paths, enabling directory traversal attacks. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to disrupt the functioning of the system, manipulate settings, or potentially cause data loss or corruption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7278 | itsourcecode Alton Management System team_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7278</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/team_save.php. The manipulation of the argument team leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273147.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7277 | itsourcecode Alton Management System Add a Menu menu.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7277</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/menu.php of the component Add a Menu. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273146 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 23:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7276 | itsourcecode Alton Management System member_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7276</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/member_save.php. The manipulation of the argument last/first leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273145 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 23:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7275 | itsourcecode Alton Management System category_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7275</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/category_save.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 22:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37281 | Kibana Denial of Service issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37281</link><description>An issue was discovered in Kibana where a user with Viewer role could cause a Kibana instance to crash by sending a large number of maliciously crafted requests to a specific endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 21:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7274 | itsourcecode Alton Management System reservation_status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7274</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /reservation_status.php. The manipulation of the argument rcode leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273143.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 21:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5901 | SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle &amp;lt;= 1.62.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Image Grid widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5901</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.62.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7273 | itsourcecode Alton Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7273</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Alton Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument rcode leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273142 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38983 | Prototype Pollution in alykoshin mini-deep-assign v0.0.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38983</link><description>Prototype Pollution in alykoshin mini-deep-assign v0.0.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and cause other impacts via the _assign() method at (/lib/index.js:91)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39010 | chase-moskal snapstate v0.0.9 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function attemptNestedProperty. This vulnerability all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39010</link><description>chase-moskal snapstate v0.0.9 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function attemptNestedProperty. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39011 | Prototype Pollution in chargeover redoc v2.0.9-rc.69 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39011</link><description>Prototype Pollution in chargeover redoc v2.0.9-rc.69 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and cause other impacts via the function mergeObjects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39012 | ais-ltd strategyen v0.4.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeObjects. This vulnerability allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39012</link><description>ais-ltd strategyen v0.4.0 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function mergeObjects. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38984 | Prototype Pollution in lukebond json-override 0.2.0 allows attackers to to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38984</link><description>Prototype Pollution in lukebond json-override 0.2.0 allows attackers to to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via the __proto__ property.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:58:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38986 | Prototype Pollution in 75lb deep-merge 1.1.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and cause other i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38986</link><description>Prototype Pollution in 75lb deep-merge 1.1.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) and cause other impacts via merge methods of lodash to merge objects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41945 | The fuels-ts typescript SDK has no awareness of to-be-spent transactions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41945</link><description>fuels-ts is a library for interacting with Fuel v2.  The typescript SDK has no awareness of to-be-spent transactions causing some transactions to fail or silently get pruned as they are funded with already used UTXOs. The problem occurs, because the `fund` function in `fuels-ts/packages/account/src/account.ts` gets the needed ressources statelessly with the function `getResourcesToSpend` without taking into consideration already used UTXOs. This issue will lead to unexpected SDK behaviour, such as a transaction not getting included in the `txpool` / in a block or a previous transaction silently getting removed from the `txpool` and replaced with a new one.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33976 | TensorFlow segfault in array_ops.upper_bound</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33976</link><description>TensorFlow is an end-to-end open source platform for machine learning. `array_ops.upper_bound` causes a segfault when not given a rank 2 tensor. The fix will be included in TensorFlow 2.13 and will also cherrypick this commit on TensorFlow 2.12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36572 | Prototype pollution in allpro form-manager 0.7.4 allows attackers to run arbitrary code and cause other impacts via the functions setDefault...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36572</link><description>Prototype pollution in allpro form-manager 0.7.4 allows attackers to run arbitrary code and cause other impacts via the functions setDefaults, mergeBranch, and Object.setObjectValue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41610 | D-Link DIR-820LW REVB FIRMWARE PATCH 2.03.B01_TC contains hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service, enabling attackers to log in remotely...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41610</link><description>D-Link DIR-820LW REVB FIRMWARE PATCH 2.03.B01_TC contains hardcoded credentials in the Telnet service, enabling attackers to log in remotely to the Telnet service and perform arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41611 | In D-Link DIR-860L REVA FIRMWARE PATCH 1.10..B04, the Telnet service contains hardcoded credentials, enabling attackers to log in remotely t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41611</link><description>In D-Link DIR-860L REVA FIRMWARE PATCH 1.10..B04, the Telnet service contains hardcoded credentials, enabling attackers to log in remotely to the Telnet service and perform arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41437 | A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_unfilter() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41437</link><description>A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_unfilter() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41438 | A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_stored() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41438</link><description>A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_stored() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41439 | A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_block() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41439</link><description>A heap buffer overflow in the function cp_block() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41440 | A heap buffer overflow in the function png_quantize() of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PN...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41440</link><description>A heap buffer overflow in the function png_quantize() of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41443 | A stack overflow in the function cp_dynamic() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41443</link><description>A stack overflow in the function cp_dynamic() (/vendor/cute_png.h) of hicolor v0.5.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted PNG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3930 | XML External Entity in Akana</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3930</link><description>In versions of Akana API Platform prior to 2024.1.0 a flaw resulting in XML External Entity (XXE) was discovered.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5250 | Overly Verbose Errors in SAML Integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5250</link><description>In versions of Akana API Platform prior to 2024.1.0 overly verbose errors can be found in SAML integrations</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5249 | SAML Replay in Akana</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5249</link><description>In versions of Akana API Platform prior to 2024.1.0, SAML tokens can be replayed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41304 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uploadFileAction() function of WonderCMS v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41304</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the uploadFileAction() function of WonderCMS v3.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41305 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the Plugins Page of WonderCMS v3.4.3 allows attackers to force the application to make arbitrary req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41305</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the Plugins Page of WonderCMS v3.4.3 allows attackers to force the application to make arbitrary requests via injection of crafted URLs into the pluginThemeUrl parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41943 | I, Librarian Stored XSS vulnerability in Item Summary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41943</link><description>I, Librarian is an open-source version of a PDF managing SaaS. PDF notes are displayed on the Item Summary page without any form of validation or sanitation. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by inserting a payload in the PDF notes that contains malicious code or script. This code will then be executed when the page is loaded in the browser. The vulnerability was fixed in version 5.11.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33167 | IBM Security Directory Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33167</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 and IBM Security Verify Directory Integrator 10.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to set the HTTPOnly flag. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information from the cookie.  IBM X-Force ID:  228587.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41915 | Authenticated SQL Injection Vulnerability in ClearPass Policy Manager Web-based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41915</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of ClearPass Policy Manager could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks against the ClearPass Policy Manager instance. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain and modify sensitive information in the underlying database potentially leading to complete compromise of the ClearPass Policy Manager cluster.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41916 | Authenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure in ClearPass Policy Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41916</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ClearPass Policy Manager that allows for an attacker with administrative privileges to access sensitive information in a cleartext format. A successful exploit allows an attacker to retrieve information which could be used to potentially gain further access to network services supported by ClearPass Policy Manager.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5486 | Authenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure in ClearPass Policy Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5486</link><description>A vulnerability exists in ClearPass Policy Manager that allows for an attacker with administrative privileges to access sensitive information in a cleartext format. A successful exploit allows an attacker to retrieve information which could be used to potentially gain further access to network services supported by ClearPass Policy Manager</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7208 | CVE-2024-7208</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7208</link><description>Hosted services do not verify the sender of an email against authenticated users, allowing an attacker to spoof the identify of another user's email address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26288 | IBM Aspera Orchestrator session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26288</link><description>IBM Aspera Orchestrator 4.0.1 does not invalidate session after a password change which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  248477.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38001 | IBM Aspera Orchestrator cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38001</link><description>IBM Aspera Orchestrator 4.0.1 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.  IBM X-Force ID:  260206.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7209 | CVE-2024-7209</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7209</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the use of shared SPF records in multi-tenant hosting providers, allowing attackers to use network authorization to be abused to spoof the email identify of the sender.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26289 | IBM Aspera Orchestrator HTTP header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26289</link><description>IBM Aspera Orchestrator 4.0.1 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  248478.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41944 | Sensitive Information Disclosure abusing SQL Injection in Xibo CMS proof of play report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41944</link><description>Xibo is a content management system (CMS). An SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in the `report/data/proofofplayReport` API route inside the CMS. This allows an authenticated user to to obtain and modify arbitrary data from the Xibo database by injecting specially crafted values in to the `sortBy` parameter. Users should upgrade to version 3.3.12 or 4.0.14 which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7297 | Langflow Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7297</link><description>Langflow versions prior to 1.0.13 suffer from a Privilege Escalation vulnerability, allowing a remote and low privileged attacker to gain super admin privileges by performing a mass assignment request on the '/api/v1/users' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41802 | Xibo allows Sensitive Information Disclosure abusing SQL Injection in Xibo CMS DataSet Data Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41802</link><description>Xibo is a content management system (CMS). An SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in the API routes inside the CMS responsible for Filtering DataSets. This allows an authenticated user to to obtain and modify arbitrary data from the Xibo database by injecting specially crafted values in to the APIs for importing JSON and importing a Layout containing DataSet data.
Users should upgrade to version 3.3.12 or 4.0.14 which fix this issue</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41803 | Xibo allows Sensitive Information Disclosure abusing SQL Injection in Xibo CMS DataSet Filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41803</link><description>Xibo is a content management system (CMS). An SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in the API routes inside the CMS responsible for Filtering DataSets. This allows an authenticated user to to obtain arbitrary data from the Xibo database by injecting specially crafted values in to the API for viewing DataSet data. Users should upgrade to version 3.3.12 or 4.0.14 which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41804 | Xibo allows Sensitive Information Disclosure abusing SQL Injection in Xibo CMS DataSet Column Formula</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41804</link><description>Xibo is a content management system (CMS). An SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in the API route inside the CMS responsible for Adding/Editing DataSet Column Formulas. This allows an authenticated user to to obtain and modify arbitrary data from the Xibo database by injecting specially crafted values in to the `formula` parameter. Users should upgrade to version 3.3.12 or 4.0.14 which fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41109 | Pimcore vulnerable to disclosure of system and database information behind /admin firewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41109</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend user interface for Pimcore. Navigating to `/admin/index/statistics` with a logged in Pimcore user exposes information about the Pimcore installation, PHP version, MYSQL version, installed bundles and all database tables and their row count in the system.  This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.2, 1.4.6, and 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39320 | Discourse allows iframe injection though default site setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39320</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to 3.2.5 and 3.3.0.beta5, the vulnerability allows an attacker to inject iframes from any domain, bypassing the intended restrictions enforced by the allowed_iframes setting. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.5 and 3.3.0.beta5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4188 | Security vulnerability exists in Documentum server cloud releases that could allow access to sensitive information which can impact system Operation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4188</link><description>Unprotected Transport of Credentials vulnerability in OpenText™ Documentum™ Server could allow Credential Stuffing.This issue affects Documentum™ Server: from 16.7 through 23.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37299 | Discourse vulnerable to DoS via Tag Group</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37299</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to 3.2.5 and 3.3.0.beta5, crafting requests to submit very long tag group names can reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.5 and 3.3.0.beta5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37165 | Discourse has an XSS via Onebox system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37165</link><description>Discourse is an open source discussion platform. Prior to 3.2.3 and 3.3.0.beta3, improperly sanitized Onebox data could lead to an XSS vulnerability in some situations. This vulnerability only affects Discourse instances which have disabled the default Content Security Policy. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.3 and 3.3.0.beta3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23091 | Weak password hashing using MD5 in funzioni.php in HotelDruid before 1.32 allows an attacker to obtain plaintext passwords from hash values.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23091</link><description>Weak password hashing using MD5 in funzioni.php in HotelDruid before 1.32 allows an attacker to obtain plaintext passwords from hash values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38909 | Studio 42 elFinder 2.1.64 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Copying files with an unauthorized extension between server directories...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38909</link><description>Studio 42 elFinder 2.1.64 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Copying files with an unauthorized extension between server directories allows an arbitrary attacker to expose secrets, perform RCE, etc.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6699 | SQLi in Mikafon Electronic&amp;#x27;s Mikafon MA7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6699</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mikafon Electronic Inc. Mikafon MA7 allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Mikafon MA7: from v3.0 before v3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 12:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7127 | XSS in Stackposts - Social Marketing Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability in Stackposts Social Marketing Tool allows Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack. By submitting the payload in the username during registration, it can be executed later in the application panel. This could lead to the unauthorised acquisition of information (e.g. cookies from a logged-in user). After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer. Our team has confirmed the existence of this vulnerability. We suppose this issue affects Social Marketing Tool in all versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41701 | AccuPOS – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41701</link><description>AccuPOS - CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41702 | SiberianCMS – CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41702</link><description>SiberianCMS - CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41694 | Cybonet – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41694</link><description>Cybonet - CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41695 | Cybonet - CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41695</link><description>Cybonet - CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41696 | Priority PRI WEB Portal Add-On for Priority ERP on prem – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41696</link><description>Priority 

PRI WEB Portal Add-On for Priority ERP on prem

- CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7226 | SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System Password Change cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Medicine Tracker System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save_user of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272806 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38429 | Matrix -  CWE-552: Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38429</link><description>Matrix -  CWE-552: Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38430 | Matrix - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38430</link><description>Matrix - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38431 | Matrix Tafnit v8 - CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38431</link><description>Matrix Tafnit v8

 - 

CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38432 | Matrix – Tafnit v8 CWE-646: Reliance on File Name or Extension of Externally-Supplied File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38432</link><description>Matrix Tafnit v8

 - 



CWE-646: Reliance on File Name or Extension of Externally-Supplied File</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41141 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in EC-CUBE Web API Plugin. When there are multiple users using OAuth Management feature and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41141</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in EC-CUBE Web API Plugin. When there are multiple users using OAuth Management feature and one of them inputs some crafted value on the OAuth Management page, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the other user who accessed the management page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41924 | Acceptance of extraneous untrusted data with trusted data vulnerability exists in EC-CUBE 4 series. If this vulnerability is exploited, an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41924</link><description>Acceptance of extraneous untrusted data with trusted data vulnerability exists in EC-CUBE 4 series. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker who obtained the administrative privilege may install an arbitrary PHP package. If the obsolete versions of PHP packages are installed, the product may be affected by some known vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40895 | FFRI AMC versions 3.4.0 to 3.5.3 and some OEM products that implement/bundle FFRI AMC versions 3.4.0 to 3.5.3 allow a remote unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40895</link><description>FFRI AMC versions 3.4.0 to 3.5.3 and some OEM products that implement/bundle FFRI AMC versions 3.4.0 to 3.5.3 allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands when certain conditions are met in an environment where the notification program setting is enabled and the executable file path is set to a batch file (.bat) or command file (.cmd) extension.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41693 | Mashov - CWE-80: Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41693</link><description>Mashov - CWE-80: Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7225 | SourceCodester Insurance Management System Edit Insurance Policy Page update_policy cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7225</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /Script/admin/core/update_policy of the component Edit Insurance Policy Page. The manipulation of the argument pname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272805 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48396 | Apache SeaTunnel Web: Authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48396</link><description>Web Authentication vulnerability in Apache SeaTunnel. Since the jwt key is hardcoded in the application, an attacker can forge
any token to log in any user.

Attacker can get secret key in /seatunnel-server/seatunnel-app/src/main/resources/application.yml and then create a token.
This issue affects Apache SeaTunnel: 1.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.0.1, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7224 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System lot_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7224</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /lot_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272804.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52888 | media: mediatek: vcodec: Only free buffer VA that is not NULL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52888</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: mediatek: vcodec: Only free buffer VA that is not NULL

In the MediaTek vcodec driver, while mtk_vcodec_mem_free() is mostly
called only when the buffer to free exists, there are some instances
that didn't do the check and triggered warnings in practice.

We believe those checks were forgotten unintentionally. Add the checks
back to fix the warnings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42099 | s390/dasd: Fix invalid dereferencing of indirect CCW data pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42099</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/dasd: Fix invalid dereferencing of indirect CCW data pointer

Fix invalid dereferencing of indirect CCW data pointer in
dasd_eckd_dump_sense() that leads to a kernel panic in error cases.

When using indirect addressing for DASD CCWs (IDAW) the CCW CDA pointer
does not contain the data address itself but a pointer to the IDAL.
This needs to be translated from physical to virtual as well before
using it.

This dereferencing is also used for dasd_page_cache and also fixed
although it is very unlikely that this code path ever gets used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42100 | clk: sunxi-ng: common: Don&amp;#x27;t call hw_to_ccu_common on hw without common</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42100</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clk: sunxi-ng: common: Don't call hw_to_ccu_common on hw without common

In order to set the rate range of a hw sunxi_ccu_probe calls
hw_to_ccu_common() assuming all entries in desc-&gt;ccu_clks are contained
in a ccu_common struct. This assumption is incorrect and, in
consequence, causes invalid pointer de-references.

Remove the faulty call. Instead, add one more loop that iterates over
the ccu_clks and sets the rate range, if required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42101 | drm/nouveau: fix null pointer dereference in nouveau_connector_get_modes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42101</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/nouveau: fix null pointer dereference in nouveau_connector_get_modes

In nouveau_connector_get_modes(), the return value of drm_mode_duplicate()
is assigned to mode, which will lead to a possible NULL pointer
dereference on failure of drm_mode_duplicate(). Add a check to avoid npd.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42102 | Revert &amp;quot;mm/writeback: fix possible divide-by-zero in wb_dirty_limits(), again&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42102</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "mm/writeback: fix possible divide-by-zero in wb_dirty_limits(), again"

Patch series "mm: Avoid possible overflows in dirty throttling".

Dirty throttling logic assumes dirty limits in page units fit into
32-bits.  This patch series makes sure this is true (see patch 2/2 for
more details).


This patch (of 2):

This reverts commit 9319b647902cbd5cc884ac08a8a6d54ce111fc78.

The commit is broken in several ways.  Firstly, the removed (u64) cast
from the multiplication will introduce a multiplication overflow on 32-bit
archs if wb_thresh * bg_thresh &gt;= 1&lt;&lt;32 (which is actually common - the
default settings with 4GB of RAM will trigger this).  Secondly, the
div64_u64() is unnecessarily expensive on 32-bit archs.  We have
div64_ul() in case we want to be safe &amp; cheap.  Thirdly, if dirty
thresholds are larger than 1&lt;&lt;32 pages, then dirty balancing is going to
blow up in many other spectacular ways anyway so trying to fix one
possible overflow is just moot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42103 | btrfs: fix adding block group to a reclaim list and the unused list during reclaim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42103</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix adding block group to a reclaim list and the unused list during reclaim

There is a potential parallel list adding for retrying in
btrfs_reclaim_bgs_work and adding to the unused list. Since the block
group is removed from the reclaim list and it is on a relocation work,
it can be added into the unused list in parallel. When that happens,
adding it to the reclaim list will corrupt the list head and trigger
list corruption like below.

Fix it by taking fs_info-&gt;unused_bgs_lock.

  [177.504][T2585409] BTRFS error (device nullb1): error relocating ch= unk 2415919104
  [177.514][T2585409] list_del corruption. next-&gt;prev should be ff1100= 0344b119c0, but was ff11000377e87c70. (next=3Dff110002390cd9c0)
  [177.529][T2585409] ------------[ cut here ]------------
  [177.537][T2585409] kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:65!
  [177.545][T2585409] Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN NOPTI
  [177.555][T2585409] CPU: 9 PID: 2585409 Comm: kworker/u128:2 Tainted: G        W          6.10.0-rc5-kts #1
  [177.568][T2585409] Hardware name: Supermicro SYS-520P-WTR/X12SPW-TF, BIOS 1.2 02/14/2022
  [177.579][T2585409] Workqueue: events_unbound btrfs_reclaim_bgs_work[btrfs]
  [177.589][T2585409] RIP: 0010:__list_del_entry_valid_or_report.cold+0x70/0x72
  [177.624][T2585409] RSP: 0018:ff11000377e87a70 EFLAGS: 00010286
  [177.633][T2585409] RAX: 000000000000006d RBX: ff11000344b119c0 RCX:0000000000000000
  [177.644][T2585409] RDX: 000000000000006d RSI: 0000000000000008 RDI:ffe21c006efd0f40
  [177.655][T2585409] RBP: ff110002e0509f78 R08: 0000000000000001 R09:ffe21c006efd0f08
  [177.665][T2585409] R10: ff11000377e87847 R11: 0000000000000000 R12:ff110002390cd9c0
  [177.676][T2585409] R13: ff11000344b119c0 R14: ff110002e0508000 R15:dffffc0000000000
  [177.687][T2585409] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ff11000fec880000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  [177.700][T2585409] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  [177.709][T2585409] CR2: 00007f06bc7b1978 CR3: 0000001021e86005 CR4:0000000000771ef0
  [177.720][T2585409] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2:0000000000000000
  [177.731][T2585409] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7:0000000000000400
  [177.742][T2585409] PKRU: 55555554
  [177.748][T2585409] Call Trace:
  [177.753][T2585409]  
  [177.759][T2585409]  ? __die_body.cold+0x19/0x27
  [177.766][T2585409]  ? die+0x2e/0x50
  [177.772][T2585409]  ? do_trap+0x1ea/0x2d0
  [177.779][T2585409]  ? __list_del_entry_valid_or_report.cold+0x70/0x72
  [177.788][T2585409]  ? do_error_trap+0xa3/0x160
  [177.795][T2585409]  ? __list_del_entry_valid_or_report.cold+0x70/0x72
  [177.805][T2585409]  ? handle_invalid_op+0x2c/0x40
  [177.812][T2585409]  ? __list_del_entry_valid_or_report.cold+0x70/0x72
  [177.820][T2585409]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x2d/0x40
  [177.827][T2585409]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
  [177.834][T2585409]  ? __list_del_entry_valid_or_report.cold+0x70/0x72
  [177.843][T2585409]  btrfs_delete_unused_bgs+0x3d9/0x14c0 [btrfs]

There is a similar retry_list code in btrfs_delete_unused_bgs(), but it is
safe, AFAICS. Since the block group was in the unused list, the used bytes
should be 0 when it was added to the unused list. Then, it checks
block_group-&gt;{used,reserved,pinned} are still 0 under the
block_group-&gt;lock. So, they should be still eligible for the unused list,
not the reclaim list.

The reason it is safe there it's because because we're holding
space_info-&gt;groups_sem in write mode.

That means no other task can allocate from the block group, so while we
are at deleted_unused_bgs() it's not possible for other tasks to
allocate and deallocate extents from the block group, so it can't be
added to the unused list or the reclaim list by anyone else.

The bug can be reproduced by btrfs/166 after a few rounds. In practice
this can be hit when relocation cannot find more chunk space and ends
with ENOSPC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42104 | nilfs2: add missing check for inode numbers on directory entries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42104</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: add missing check for inode numbers on directory entries

Syzbot reported that mounting and unmounting a specific pattern of
corrupted nilfs2 filesystem images causes a use-after-free of metadata
file inodes, which triggers a kernel bug in lru_add_fn().

As Jan Kara pointed out, this is because the link count of a metadata file
gets corrupted to 0, and nilfs_evict_inode(), which is called from iput(),
tries to delete that inode (ifile inode in this case).

The inconsistency occurs because directories containing the inode numbers
of these metadata files that should not be visible in the namespace are
read without checking.

Fix this issue by treating the inode numbers of these internal files as
errors in the sanity check helper when reading directory folios/pages.

Also thanks to Hillf Danton and Matthew Wilcox for their initial mm-layer
analysis.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42105 | nilfs2: fix inode number range checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42105</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix inode number range checks

Patch series "nilfs2: fix potential issues related to reserved inodes".

This series fixes one use-after-free issue reported by syzbot, caused by
nilfs2's internal inode being exposed in the namespace on a corrupted
filesystem, and a couple of flaws that cause problems if the starting
number of non-reserved inodes written in the on-disk super block is
intentionally (or corruptly) changed from its default value.  


This patch (of 3):

In the current implementation of nilfs2, "nilfs-&gt;ns_first_ino", which
gives the first non-reserved inode number, is read from the superblock,
but its lower limit is not checked.

As a result, if a number that overlaps with the inode number range of
reserved inodes such as the root directory or metadata files is set in the
super block parameter, the inode number test macros (NILFS_MDT_INODE and
NILFS_VALID_INODE) will not function properly.

In addition, these test macros use left bit-shift calculations using with
the inode number as the shift count via the BIT macro, but the result of a
shift calculation that exceeds the bit width of an integer is undefined in
the C specification, so if "ns_first_ino" is set to a large value other
than the default value NILFS_USER_INO (=11), the macros may potentially
malfunction depending on the environment.

Fix these issues by checking the lower bound of "nilfs-&gt;ns_first_ino" and
by preventing bit shifts equal to or greater than the NILFS_USER_INO
constant in the inode number test macros.

Also, change the type of "ns_first_ino" from signed integer to unsigned
integer to avoid the need for type casting in comparisons such as the
lower bound check introduced this time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42106 | inet_diag: Initialize pad field in struct inet_diag_req_v2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42106</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

inet_diag: Initialize pad field in struct inet_diag_req_v2

KMSAN reported uninit-value access in raw_lookup() [1]. Diag for raw
sockets uses the pad field in struct inet_diag_req_v2 for the
underlying protocol. This field corresponds to the sdiag_raw_protocol
field in struct inet_diag_req_raw.

inet_diag_get_exact_compat() converts inet_diag_req to
inet_diag_req_v2, but leaves the pad field uninitialized. So the issue
occurs when raw_lookup() accesses the sdiag_raw_protocol field.

Fix this by initializing the pad field in
inet_diag_get_exact_compat(). Also, do the same fix in
inet_diag_dump_compat() to avoid the similar issue in the future.

[1]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in raw_lookup net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:49 [inline]
BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in raw_sock_get+0x657/0x800 net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:71
 raw_lookup net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:49 [inline]
 raw_sock_get+0x657/0x800 net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:71
 raw_diag_dump_one+0xa1/0x660 net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:99
 inet_diag_cmd_exact+0x7d9/0x980
 inet_diag_get_exact_compat net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1404 [inline]
 inet_diag_rcv_msg_compat+0x469/0x530 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1426
 sock_diag_rcv_msg+0x23d/0x740 net/core/sock_diag.c:282
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x537/0x670 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2564
 sock_diag_rcv+0x35/0x40 net/core/sock_diag.c:297
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1335 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0xe74/0x1240 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1361
 netlink_sendmsg+0x10c6/0x1260 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1905
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x332/0x3d0 net/socket.c:745
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x7f0/0xb70 net/socket.c:2585
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x271/0x3b0 net/socket.c:2639
 __sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2668 [inline]
 __do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2677 [inline]
 __se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2675 [inline]
 __x64_sys_sendmsg+0x27e/0x4a0 net/socket.c:2675
 x64_sys_call+0x135e/0x3ce0 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:47
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xd9/0x1e0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Uninit was stored to memory at:
 raw_sock_get+0x650/0x800 net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:71
 raw_diag_dump_one+0xa1/0x660 net/ipv4/raw_diag.c:99
 inet_diag_cmd_exact+0x7d9/0x980
 inet_diag_get_exact_compat net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1404 [inline]
 inet_diag_rcv_msg_compat+0x469/0x530 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1426
 sock_diag_rcv_msg+0x23d/0x740 net/core/sock_diag.c:282
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x537/0x670 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2564
 sock_diag_rcv+0x35/0x40 net/core/sock_diag.c:297
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1335 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0xe74/0x1240 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1361
 netlink_sendmsg+0x10c6/0x1260 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1905
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x332/0x3d0 net/socket.c:745
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x7f0/0xb70 net/socket.c:2585
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x271/0x3b0 net/socket.c:2639
 __sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2668 [inline]
 __do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2677 [inline]
 __se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2675 [inline]
 __x64_sys_sendmsg+0x27e/0x4a0 net/socket.c:2675
 x64_sys_call+0x135e/0x3ce0 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:47
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xd9/0x1e0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Local variable req.i created at:
 inet_diag_get_exact_compat net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1396 [inline]
 inet_diag_rcv_msg_compat+0x2a6/0x530 net/ipv4/inet_diag.c:1426
 sock_diag_rcv_msg+0x23d/0x740 net/core/sock_diag.c:282

CPU: 1 PID: 8888 Comm: syz-executor.6 Not tainted 6.10.0-rc4-00217-g35bb670d65fc #32
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42107 | ice: Don&amp;#x27;t process extts if PTP is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42107</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: Don't process extts if PTP is disabled

The ice_ptp_extts_event() function can race with ice_ptp_release() and
result in a NULL pointer dereference which leads to a kernel panic.

Panic occurs because the ice_ptp_extts_event() function calls
ptp_clock_event() with a NULL pointer. The ice driver has already
released the PTP clock by the time the interrupt for the next external
timestamp event occurs.

To fix this, modify the ice_ptp_extts_event() function to check the
PTP state and bail early if PTP is not ready.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42108 | net: rswitch: Avoid use-after-free in rswitch_poll()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42108</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: rswitch: Avoid use-after-free in rswitch_poll()

The use-after-free is actually in rswitch_tx_free(), which is inlined in
rswitch_poll(). Since `skb` and `gq-&gt;skbs[gq-&gt;dirty]` are in fact the
same pointer, the skb is first freed using dev_kfree_skb_any(), then the
value in skb-&gt;len is used to update the interface statistics.

Let's move around the instructions to use skb-&gt;len before the skb is
freed.

This bug is trivial to reproduce using KFENCE. It will trigger a splat
every few packets. A simple ARP request or ICMP echo request is enough.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42109 | netfilter: nf_tables: unconditionally flush pending work before notifier</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42109</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: unconditionally flush pending work before notifier

syzbot reports:

KASAN: slab-uaf in nft_ctx_update include/net/netfilter/nf_tables.h:1831
KASAN: slab-uaf in nft_commit_release net/netfilter/nf_tables_api.c:9530
KASAN: slab-uaf int nf_tables_trans_destroy_work+0x152b/0x1750 net/netfilter/nf_tables_api.c:9597
Read of size 2 at addr ffff88802b0051c4 by task kworker/1:1/45
[..]
Workqueue: events nf_tables_trans_destroy_work
Call Trace:
 nft_ctx_update include/net/netfilter/nf_tables.h:1831 [inline]
 nft_commit_release net/netfilter/nf_tables_api.c:9530 [inline]
 nf_tables_trans_destroy_work+0x152b/0x1750 net/netfilter/nf_tables_api.c:9597

Problem is that the notifier does a conditional flush, but its possible
that the table-to-be-removed is still referenced by transactions being
processed by the worker, so we need to flush unconditionally.

We could make the flush_work depend on whether we found a table to delete
in nf-next to avoid the flush for most cases.

AFAICS this problem is only exposed in nf-next, with
commit e169285f8c56 ("netfilter: nf_tables: do not store nft_ctx in transaction objects"),
with this commit applied there is an unconditional fetch of
table-&gt;family which is whats triggering the above splat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42110 | net: ntb_netdev: Move ntb_netdev_rx_handler() to call netif_rx() from __netif_rx()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42110</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: ntb_netdev: Move ntb_netdev_rx_handler() to call netif_rx() from __netif_rx()

The following is emitted when using idxd (DSA) dmanegine as the data
mover for ntb_transport that ntb_netdev uses.

[74412.546922] BUG: using smp_processor_id() in preemptible [00000000] code: irq/52-idxd-por/14526
[74412.556784] caller is netif_rx_internal+0x42/0x130
[74412.562282] CPU: 6 PID: 14526 Comm: irq/52-idxd-por Not tainted 6.9.5 #5
[74412.569870] Hardware name: Intel Corporation ArcherCity/ArcherCity, BIOS EGSDCRB1.E9I.1752.P05.2402080856 02/08/2024
[74412.581699] Call Trace:
[74412.584514]  
[74412.586933]  dump_stack_lvl+0x55/0x70
[74412.591129]  check_preemption_disabled+0xc8/0xf0
[74412.596374]  netif_rx_internal+0x42/0x130
[74412.600957]  __netif_rx+0x20/0xd0
[74412.604743]  ntb_netdev_rx_handler+0x66/0x150 [ntb_netdev]
[74412.610985]  ntb_complete_rxc+0xed/0x140 [ntb_transport]
[74412.617010]  ntb_rx_copy_callback+0x53/0x80 [ntb_transport]
[74412.623332]  idxd_dma_complete_txd+0xe3/0x160 [idxd]
[74412.628963]  idxd_wq_thread+0x1a6/0x2b0 [idxd]
[74412.634046]  irq_thread_fn+0x21/0x60
[74412.638134]  ? irq_thread+0xa8/0x290
[74412.642218]  irq_thread+0x1a0/0x290
[74412.646212]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_fn+0x10/0x10
[74412.651071]  ? __pfx_irq_thread_dtor+0x10/0x10
[74412.656117]  ? __pfx_irq_thread+0x10/0x10
[74412.660686]  kthread+0x100/0x130
[74412.664384]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[74412.668639]  ret_from_fork+0x31/0x50
[74412.672716]  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
[74412.676978]  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
[74412.681457]  

The cause is due to the idxd driver interrupt completion handler uses
threaded interrupt and the threaded handler is not hard or soft interrupt
context. However __netif_rx() can only be called from interrupt context.
Change the call to netif_rx() in order to allow completion via normal
context for dmaengine drivers that utilize threaded irq handling.

While the following commit changed from netif_rx() to __netif_rx(),
baebdf48c360 ("net: dev: Makes sure netif_rx() can be invoked in any context."),
the change should've been a noop instead. However, the code precedes this
fix should've been using netif_rx_ni() or netif_rx_any_context().</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42111 | btrfs: always do the basic checks for btrfs_qgroup_inherit structure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42111</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: always do the basic checks for btrfs_qgroup_inherit structure

[BUG]
Syzbot reports the following regression detected by KASAN:

  BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in btrfs_qgroup_inherit+0x42e/0x2e20 fs/btrfs/qgroup.c:3277
  Read of size 8 at addr ffff88814628ca50 by task syz-executor318/5171

  CPU: 0 PID: 5171 Comm: syz-executor318 Not tainted 6.10.0-rc2-syzkaller-00010-g2ab795141095 #0
  Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 04/02/2024
  Call Trace:
   
   __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
   dump_stack_lvl+0x241/0x360 lib/dump_stack.c:114
   print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
   print_report+0x169/0x550 mm/kasan/report.c:488
   kasan_report+0x143/0x180 mm/kasan/report.c:601
   btrfs_qgroup_inherit+0x42e/0x2e20 fs/btrfs/qgroup.c:3277
   create_pending_snapshot+0x1359/0x29b0 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:1854
   create_pending_snapshots+0x195/0x1d0 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:1922
   btrfs_commit_transaction+0xf20/0x3740 fs/btrfs/transaction.c:2382
   create_snapshot+0x6a1/0x9e0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:875
   btrfs_mksubvol+0x58f/0x710 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1029
   btrfs_mksnapshot+0xb5/0xf0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1075
   __btrfs_ioctl_snap_create+0x387/0x4b0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1340
   btrfs_ioctl_snap_create_v2+0x1f2/0x3a0 fs/btrfs/ioctl.c:1422
   btrfs_ioctl+0x99e/0xc60
   vfs_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:51 [inline]
   __do_sys_ioctl fs/ioctl.c:907 [inline]
   __se_sys_ioctl+0xfc/0x170 fs/ioctl.c:893
   do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
   do_syscall_64+0xf3/0x230 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
  RIP: 0033:0x7fcbf1992509
  RSP: 002b:00007fcbf1928218 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000010
  RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007fcbf1a1f618 RCX: 00007fcbf1992509
  RDX: 0000000020000280 RSI: 0000000050009417 RDI: 0000000000000003
  RBP: 00007fcbf1a1f610 R08: 00007ffea1298e97 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00007fcbf19eb660
  R13: 00000000200002b8 R14: 00007fcbf19e60c0 R15: 0030656c69662f2e
   

And it also pinned it down to commit b5357cb268c4 ("btrfs: qgroup: do not
check qgroup inherit if qgroup is disabled").

[CAUSE]
That offending commit skips the whole qgroup inherit check if qgroup is
not enabled.

But that also skips the very basic checks like
num_ref_copies/num_excl_copies and the structure size checks.

Meaning if a qgroup enable/disable race is happening at the background,
and we pass a btrfs_qgroup_inherit structure when the qgroup is
disabled, the check would be completely skipped.

Then at the time of transaction commitment, qgroup is re-enabled and
btrfs_qgroup_inherit() is going to use the incorrect structure and
causing the above KASAN error.

[FIX]
Make btrfs_qgroup_check_inherit() only skip the source qgroup checks.
So that even if invalid btrfs_qgroup_inherit structure is passed in, we
can still reject invalid ones no matter if qgroup is enabled or not.

Furthermore we do already have an extra safety inside
btrfs_qgroup_inherit(), which would just ignore invalid qgroup sources,
so even if we only skip the qgroup source check we're still safe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42112 | net: txgbe: free isb resources at the right time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42112</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: txgbe: free isb resources at the right time

When using MSI/INTx interrupt, the shared interrupts are still being
handled in the device remove routine, before free IRQs. So isb memory
is still read after it is freed. Thus move wx_free_isb_resources()
from txgbe_close() to txgbe_remove(). And fix the improper isb free
action in txgbe_open() error handling path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42113 | net: txgbe: initialize num_q_vectors for MSI/INTx interrupts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42113</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: txgbe: initialize num_q_vectors for MSI/INTx interrupts

When using MSI/INTx interrupts, wx-&gt;num_q_vectors is uninitialized.
Thus there will be kernel panic in wx_alloc_q_vectors() to allocate
queue vectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42114 | wifi: cfg80211: restrict NL80211_ATTR_TXQ_QUANTUM values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42114</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: cfg80211: restrict NL80211_ATTR_TXQ_QUANTUM values

syzbot is able to trigger softlockups, setting NL80211_ATTR_TXQ_QUANTUM
to 2^31.

We had a similar issue in sch_fq, fixed with commit
d9e15a273306 ("pkt_sched: fq: do not accept silly TCA_FQ_QUANTUM")

watchdog: BUG: soft lockup - CPU#1 stuck for 26s! [kworker/1:0:24]
Modules linked in:
irq event stamp: 131135
 hardirqs last  enabled at (131134): [] __exit_to_kernel_mode arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:85 [inline]
 hardirqs last  enabled at (131134): [] exit_to_kernel_mode+0xdc/0x10c arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:95
 hardirqs last disabled at (131135): [] __el1_irq arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:533 [inline]
 hardirqs last disabled at (131135): [] el1_interrupt+0x24/0x68 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:551
 softirqs last  enabled at (125892): [] neigh_hh_init net/core/neighbour.c:1538 [inline]
 softirqs last  enabled at (125892): [] neigh_resolve_output+0x268/0x658 net/core/neighbour.c:1553
 softirqs last disabled at (125896): [] local_bh_disable+0x10/0x34 include/linux/bottom_half.h:19
CPU: 1 PID: 24 Comm: kworker/1:0 Not tainted 6.9.0-rc7-syzkaller-gfda5695d692c #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 03/27/2024
Workqueue: mld mld_ifc_work
pstate: 80400005 (Nzcv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
 pc : __list_del include/linux/list.h:195 [inline]
 pc : __list_del_entry include/linux/list.h:218 [inline]
 pc : list_move_tail include/linux/list.h:310 [inline]
 pc : fq_tin_dequeue include/net/fq_impl.h:112 [inline]
 pc : ieee80211_tx_dequeue+0x6b8/0x3b4c net/mac80211/tx.c:3854
 lr : __list_del_entry include/linux/list.h:218 [inline]
 lr : list_move_tail include/linux/list.h:310 [inline]
 lr : fq_tin_dequeue include/net/fq_impl.h:112 [inline]
 lr : ieee80211_tx_dequeue+0x67c/0x3b4c net/mac80211/tx.c:3854
sp : ffff800093d36700
x29: ffff800093d36a60 x28: ffff800093d36960 x27: dfff800000000000
x26: ffff0000d800ad50 x25: ffff0000d800abe0 x24: ffff0000d800abf0
x23: ffff0000e0032468 x22: ffff0000e00324d4 x21: ffff0000d800abf0
x20: ffff0000d800abf8 x19: ffff0000d800abf0 x18: ffff800093d363c0
x17: 000000000000d476 x16: ffff8000805519dc x15: ffff7000127a6cc8
x14: 1ffff000127a6cc8 x13: 0000000000000004 x12: ffffffffffffffff
x11: ffff7000127a6cc8 x10: 0000000000ff0100 x9 : 0000000000000000
x8 : 0000000000000000 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 0000000000000000
x5 : ffff80009287aa08 x4 : 0000000000000008 x3 : ffff80008034c7fc
x2 : ffff0000e0032468 x1 : 00000000da0e46b8 x0 : ffff0000e0032470
Call trace:
  __list_del include/linux/list.h:195 [inline]
  __list_del_entry include/linux/list.h:218 [inline]
  list_move_tail include/linux/list.h:310 [inline]
  fq_tin_dequeue include/net/fq_impl.h:112 [inline]
  ieee80211_tx_dequeue+0x6b8/0x3b4c net/mac80211/tx.c:3854
  wake_tx_push_queue net/mac80211/util.c:294 [inline]
  ieee80211_handle_wake_tx_queue+0x118/0x274 net/mac80211/util.c:315
  drv_wake_tx_queue net/mac80211/driver-ops.h:1350 [inline]
  schedule_and_wake_txq net/mac80211/driver-ops.h:1357 [inline]
  ieee80211_queue_skb+0x18e8/0x2244 net/mac80211/tx.c:1664
  ieee80211_tx+0x260/0x400 net/mac80211/tx.c:1966
  ieee80211_xmit+0x278/0x354 net/mac80211/tx.c:2062
  __ieee80211_subif_start_xmit+0xab8/0x122c net/mac80211/tx.c:4338
  ieee80211_subif_start_xmit+0xe0/0x438 net/mac80211/tx.c:4532
  __netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4903 [inline]
  netdev_start_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:4917 [inline]
  xmit_one net/core/dev.c:3531 [inline]
  dev_hard_start_xmit+0x27c/0x938 net/core/dev.c:3547
  __dev_queue_xmit+0x1678/0x33fc net/core/dev.c:4341
  dev_queue_xmit include/linux/netdevice.h:3091 [inline]
  neigh_resolve_output+0x558/0x658 net/core/neighbour.c:1563
  neigh_output include/net/neighbour.h:542 [inline]
  ip6_fini
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42115 | jffs2: Fix potential illegal address access in jffs2_free_inode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42115</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

jffs2: Fix potential illegal address access in jffs2_free_inode

During the stress testing of the jffs2 file system,the following
abnormal printouts were found:
[ 2430.649000] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address 0069696969696948
[ 2430.649622] Mem abort info:
[ 2430.649829]   ESR = 0x96000004
[ 2430.650115]   EC = 0x25: DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
[ 2430.650564]   SET = 0, FnV = 0
[ 2430.650795]   EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
[ 2430.651032]   FSC = 0x04: level 0 translation fault
[ 2430.651446] Data abort info:
[ 2430.651683]   ISV = 0, ISS = 0x00000004
[ 2430.652001]   CM = 0, WnR = 0
[ 2430.652558] [0069696969696948] address between user and kernel address ranges
[ 2430.653265] Internal error: Oops: 96000004 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[ 2430.654512] CPU: 2 PID: 20919 Comm: cat Not tainted 5.15.25-g512f31242bf6 #33
[ 2430.655008] Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
[ 2430.655517] pstate: 20000005 (nzCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[ 2430.656142] pc : kfree+0x78/0x348
[ 2430.656630] lr : jffs2_free_inode+0x24/0x48
[ 2430.657051] sp : ffff800009eebd10
[ 2430.657355] x29: ffff800009eebd10 x28: 0000000000000001 x27: 0000000000000000
[ 2430.658327] x26: ffff000038f09d80 x25: 0080000000000000 x24: ffff800009d38000
[ 2430.658919] x23: 5a5a5a5a5a5a5a5a x22: ffff000038f09d80 x21: ffff8000084f0d14
[ 2430.659434] x20: ffff0000bf9a6ac0 x19: 0169696969696940 x18: 0000000000000000
[ 2430.659969] x17: ffff8000b6506000 x16: ffff800009eec000 x15: 0000000000004000
[ 2430.660637] x14: 0000000000000000 x13: 00000001000820a1 x12: 00000000000d1b19
[ 2430.661345] x11: 0004000800000000 x10: 0000000000000001 x9 : ffff8000084f0d14
[ 2430.662025] x8 : ffff0000bf9a6b40 x7 : ffff0000bf9a6b48 x6 : 0000000003470302
[ 2430.662695] x5 : ffff00002e41dcc0 x4 : ffff0000bf9aa3b0 x3 : 0000000003470342
[ 2430.663486] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : ffff8000084f0d14 x0 : fffffc0000000000
[ 2430.664217] Call trace:
[ 2430.664528]  kfree+0x78/0x348
[ 2430.664855]  jffs2_free_inode+0x24/0x48
[ 2430.665233]  i_callback+0x24/0x50
[ 2430.665528]  rcu_do_batch+0x1ac/0x448
[ 2430.665892]  rcu_core+0x28c/0x3c8
[ 2430.666151]  rcu_core_si+0x18/0x28
[ 2430.666473]  __do_softirq+0x138/0x3cc
[ 2430.666781]  irq_exit+0xf0/0x110
[ 2430.667065]  handle_domain_irq+0x6c/0x98
[ 2430.667447]  gic_handle_irq+0xac/0xe8
[ 2430.667739]  call_on_irq_stack+0x28/0x54
The parameter passed to kfree was 5a5a5a5a, which corresponds to the target field of
the jffs_inode_info structure. It was found that all variables in the jffs_inode_info
structure were 5a5a5a5a, except for the first member sem. It is suspected that these
variables are not initialized because they were set to 5a5a5a5a during memory testing,
which is meant to detect uninitialized memory.The sem variable is initialized in the
function jffs2_i_init_once, while other members are initialized in
the function jffs2_init_inode_info.

The function jffs2_init_inode_info is called after iget_locked,
but in the iget_locked function, the destroy_inode process is triggered,
which releases the inode and consequently, the target member of the inode
is not initialized.In concurrent high pressure scenarios, iget_locked
may enter the destroy_inode branch as described in the code.

Since the destroy_inode functionality of jffs2 only releases the target,
the fix method is to set target to NULL in jffs2_i_init_once.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42116 | igc: fix a log entry using uninitialized netdev</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42116</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

igc: fix a log entry using uninitialized netdev

During successful probe, igc logs this:

[    5.133667] igc 0000:01:00.0 (unnamed net_device) (uninitialized): PHC added
                                ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
The reason is that igc_ptp_init() is called very early, even before
register_netdev() has been called. So the netdev_info() call works
on a partially uninitialized netdev.

Fix this by calling igc_ptp_init() after register_netdev(), right
after the media autosense check, just as in igb.  Add a comment,
just as in igb.

Now the log message is fine:

[    5.200987] igc 0000:01:00.0 eth0: PHC added</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42117 | drm/amd/display: ASSERT when failing to find index by plane/stream id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42117</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: ASSERT when failing to find index by plane/stream id

[WHY]
find_disp_cfg_idx_by_plane_id and find_disp_cfg_idx_by_stream_id returns
an array index and they return -1 when not found; however, -1 is not a
valid index number.

[HOW]
When this happens, call ASSERT(), and return a positive number (which is
fewer than callers' array size) instead.

This fixes 4 OVERRUN and 2 NEGATIVE_RETURNS issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42118 | drm/amd/display: Do not return negative stream id for array</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42118</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Do not return negative stream id for array

[WHY]
resource_stream_to_stream_idx returns an array index and it return -1
when not found; however, -1 is not a valid array index number.

[HOW]
When this happens, call ASSERT(), and return a zero instead.

This fixes an OVERRUN and an NEGATIVE_RETURNS issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42119 | drm/amd/display: Skip finding free audio for unknown engine_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42119</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Skip finding free audio for unknown engine_id

[WHY]
ENGINE_ID_UNKNOWN = -1 and can not be used as an array index. Plus, it
also means it is uninitialized and does not need free audio.

[HOW]
Skip and return NULL.

This fixes 2 OVERRUN issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42120 | drm/amd/display: Check pipe offset before setting vblank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42120</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check pipe offset before setting vblank

pipe_ctx has a size of MAX_PIPES so checking its index before accessing
the array.

This fixes an OVERRUN issue reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42121 | drm/amd/display: Check index msg_id before read or write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42121</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Check index msg_id before read or write

[WHAT]
msg_id is used as an array index and it cannot be a negative value, and
therefore cannot be equal to MOD_HDCP_MESSAGE_ID_INVALID (-1).

[HOW]
Check whether msg_id is valid before reading and setting.

This fixes 4 OVERRUN issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42122 | drm/amd/display: Add NULL pointer check for kzalloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42122</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Add NULL pointer check for kzalloc

[Why &amp; How]
Check return pointer of kzalloc before using it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42123 | drm/amdgpu: fix double free err_addr pointer warnings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42123</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: fix double free err_addr pointer warnings

In amdgpu_umc_bad_page_polling_timeout, the amdgpu_umc_handle_bad_pages
will be run many times so that double free err_addr in some special case.
So set the err_addr to NULL to avoid the warnings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42124 | scsi: qedf: Make qedf_execute_tmf() non-preemptible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42124</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: qedf: Make qedf_execute_tmf() non-preemptible

Stop calling smp_processor_id() from preemptible code in
qedf_execute_tmf90.  This results in BUG_ON() when running an RT kernel.

[ 659.343280] BUG: using smp_processor_id() in preemptible [00000000] code: sg_reset/3646
[ 659.343282] caller is qedf_execute_tmf+0x8b/0x360 [qedf]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42125 | wifi: rtw89: fw: scan offload prohibit all 6 GHz channel if no 6 GHz sband</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42125</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: rtw89: fw: scan offload prohibit all 6 GHz channel if no 6 GHz sband

We have some policy via BIOS to block uses of 6 GHz. In this case, 6 GHz
sband will be NULL even if it is WiFi 7 chip. So, add NULL handling here
to avoid crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42126 | powerpc: Avoid nmi_enter/nmi_exit in real mode interrupt.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42126</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc: Avoid nmi_enter/nmi_exit in real mode interrupt.

nmi_enter()/nmi_exit() touches per cpu variables which can lead to kernel
crash when invoked during real mode interrupt handling (e.g. early HMI/MCE
interrupt handler) if percpu allocation comes from vmalloc area.

Early HMI/MCE handlers are called through DEFINE_INTERRUPT_HANDLER_NMI()
wrapper which invokes nmi_enter/nmi_exit calls. We don't see any issue when
percpu allocation is from the embedded first chunk. However with
CONFIG_NEED_PER_CPU_PAGE_FIRST_CHUNK enabled there are chances where percpu
allocation can come from the vmalloc area.

With kernel command line "percpu_alloc=page" we can force percpu allocation
to come from vmalloc area and can see kernel crash in machine_check_early:

[    1.215714] NIP [c000000000e49eb4] rcu_nmi_enter+0x24/0x110
[    1.215717] LR [c0000000000461a0] machine_check_early+0xf0/0x2c0
[    1.215719] --- interrupt: 200
[    1.215720] [c000000fffd73180] [0000000000000000] 0x0 (unreliable)
[    1.215722] [c000000fffd731b0] [0000000000000000] 0x0
[    1.215724] [c000000fffd73210] [c000000000008364] machine_check_early_common+0x134/0x1f8

Fix this by avoiding use of nmi_enter()/nmi_exit() in real mode if percpu
first chunk is not embedded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42127 | drm/lima: fix shared irq handling on driver remove</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42127</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/lima: fix shared irq handling on driver remove

lima uses a shared interrupt, so the interrupt handlers must be prepared
to be called at any time. At driver removal time, the clocks are
disabled early and the interrupts stay registered until the very end of
the remove process due to the devm usage.
This is potentially a bug as the interrupts access device registers
which assumes clocks are enabled. A crash can be triggered by removing
the driver in a kernel with CONFIG_DEBUG_SHIRQ enabled.
This patch frees the interrupts at each lima device finishing callback
so that the handlers are already unregistered by the time we fully
disable clocks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42128 | leds: an30259a: Use devm_mutex_init() for mutex initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42128</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

leds: an30259a: Use devm_mutex_init() for mutex initialization

In this driver LEDs are registered using devm_led_classdev_register()
so they are automatically unregistered after module's remove() is done.
led_classdev_unregister() calls module's led_set_brightness() to turn off
the LEDs and that callback uses mutex which was destroyed already
in module's remove() so use devm API instead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42129 | leds: mlxreg: Use devm_mutex_init() for mutex initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42129</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

leds: mlxreg: Use devm_mutex_init() for mutex initialization

In this driver LEDs are registered using devm_led_classdev_register()
so they are automatically unregistered after module's remove() is done.
led_classdev_unregister() calls module's led_set_brightness() to turn off
the LEDs and that callback uses mutex which was destroyed already
in module's remove() so use devm API instead.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42130 | nfc/nci: Add the inconsistency check between the input data length and count</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42130</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfc/nci: Add the inconsistency check between the input data length and count

write$nci(r0, &amp;(0x7f0000000740)=ANY=[@ANYBLOB="610501"], 0xf)

Syzbot constructed a write() call with a data length of 3 bytes but a count value
of 15, which passed too little data to meet the basic requirements of the function
nci_rf_intf_activated_ntf_packet().

Therefore, increasing the comparison between data length and count value to avoid
problems caused by inconsistent data length and count.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42131 | mm: avoid overflows in dirty throttling logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42131</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: avoid overflows in dirty throttling logic

The dirty throttling logic is interspersed with assumptions that dirty
limits in PAGE_SIZE units fit into 32-bit (so that various multiplications
fit into 64-bits).  If limits end up being larger, we will hit overflows,
possible divisions by 0 etc.  Fix these problems by never allowing so
large dirty limits as they have dubious practical value anyway.  For
dirty_bytes / dirty_background_bytes interfaces we can just refuse to set
so large limits.  For dirty_ratio / dirty_background_ratio it isn't so
simple as the dirty limit is computed from the amount of available memory
which can change due to memory hotplug etc.  So when converting dirty
limits from ratios to numbers of pages, we just don't allow the result to
exceed UINT_MAX.

This is root-only triggerable problem which occurs when the operator
sets dirty limits to &gt;16 TB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42132 | bluetooth/hci: disallow setting handle bigger than HCI_CONN_HANDLE_MAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42132</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bluetooth/hci: disallow setting handle bigger than HCI_CONN_HANDLE_MAX

Syzbot hit warning in hci_conn_del() caused by freeing handle that was
not allocated using ida allocator.

This is caused by handle bigger than HCI_CONN_HANDLE_MAX passed by
hci_le_big_sync_established_evt(), which makes code think it's unset
connection.

Add same check for handle upper bound as in hci_conn_set_handle() to
prevent warning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42133 | Bluetooth: Ignore too large handle values in BIG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42133</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Ignore too large handle values in BIG

hci_le_big_sync_established_evt is necessary to filter out cases where the
handle value is belonging to ida id range, otherwise ida will be erroneously
released in hci_conn_cleanup.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42134 | virtio-pci: Check if is_avq is NULL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42134</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

virtio-pci: Check if is_avq is NULL

[bug]
In the virtio_pci_common.c function vp_del_vqs, vp_dev-&gt;is_avq is involved
to determine whether it is admin virtqueue, but this function vp_dev-&gt;is_avq
 may be empty. For installations, virtio_pci_legacy does not assign a value
 to vp_dev-&gt;is_avq.

[fix]
Check whether it is vp_dev-&gt;is_avq before use.

[test]
Test with virsh Attach device
Before this patch, the following command would crash the guest system

After applying the patch, everything seems to be working fine.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42135 | vhost_task: Handle SIGKILL by flushing work and exiting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42135</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vhost_task: Handle SIGKILL by flushing work and exiting

Instead of lingering until the device is closed, this has us handle
SIGKILL by:

1. marking the worker as killed so we no longer try to use it with
   new virtqueues and new flush operations.
2. setting the virtqueue to worker mapping so no new works are queued.
3. running all the exiting works.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42136 | cdrom: rearrange last_media_change check to avoid unintentional overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42136</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cdrom: rearrange last_media_change check to avoid unintentional overflow

When running syzkaller with the newly reintroduced signed integer wrap
sanitizer we encounter this splat:

[  366.015950] UBSAN: signed-integer-overflow in ../drivers/cdrom/cdrom.c:2361:33
[  366.021089] -9223372036854775808 - 346321 cannot be represented in type '__s64' (aka 'long long')
[  366.025894] program syz-executor.4 is using a deprecated SCSI ioctl, please convert it to SG_IO
[  366.027502] CPU: 5 PID: 28472 Comm: syz-executor.7 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc2-00035-gb3ef86b5a957 #1
[  366.027512] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
[  366.027518] Call Trace:
[  366.027523]  
[  366.027533]  dump_stack_lvl+0x93/0xd0
[  366.027899]  handle_overflow+0x171/0x1b0
[  366.038787] ata1.00: invalid multi_count 32 ignored
[  366.043924]  cdrom_ioctl+0x2c3f/0x2d10
[  366.063932]  ? __pm_runtime_resume+0xe6/0x130
[  366.071923]  sr_block_ioctl+0x15d/0x1d0
[  366.074624]  ? __pfx_sr_block_ioctl+0x10/0x10
[  366.077642]  blkdev_ioctl+0x419/0x500
[  366.080231]  ? __pfx_blkdev_ioctl+0x10/0x10
...

Historically, the signed integer overflow sanitizer did not work in the
kernel due to its interaction with `-fwrapv` but this has since been
changed [1] in the newest version of Clang. It was re-enabled in the
kernel with Commit 557f8c582a9ba8ab ("ubsan: Reintroduce signed overflow
sanitizer").

Let's rearrange the check to not perform any arithmetic, thus not
tripping the sanitizer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42137 | Bluetooth: qca: Fix BT enable failure again for QCA6390 after warm reboot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42137</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: qca: Fix BT enable failure again for QCA6390 after warm reboot

Commit 272970be3dab ("Bluetooth: hci_qca: Fix driver shutdown on closed
serdev") will cause below regression issue:

BT can't be enabled after below steps:
cold boot -&gt; enable BT -&gt; disable BT -&gt; warm reboot -&gt; BT enable failure
if property enable-gpios is not configured within DT|ACPI for QCA6390.

The commit is to fix a use-after-free issue within qca_serdev_shutdown()
by adding condition to avoid the serdev is flushed or wrote after closed
but also introduces this regression issue regarding above steps since the
VSC is not sent to reset controller during warm reboot.

Fixed by sending the VSC to reset controller within qca_serdev_shutdown()
once BT was ever enabled, and the use-after-free issue is also fixed by
this change since the serdev is still opened before it is flushed or wrote.

Verified by the reported machine Dell XPS 13 9310 laptop over below two
kernel commits:
commit e00fc2700a3f ("Bluetooth: btusb: Fix triggering coredump
implementation for QCA") of bluetooth-next tree.
commit b23d98d46d28 ("Bluetooth: btusb: Fix triggering coredump
implementation for QCA") of linus mainline tree.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42138 | mlxsw: core_linecards: Fix double memory deallocation in case of invalid INI file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42138</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mlxsw: core_linecards: Fix double memory deallocation in case of invalid INI file

In case of invalid INI file mlxsw_linecard_types_init() deallocates memory
but doesn't reset pointer to NULL and returns 0. In case of any error
occurred after mlxsw_linecard_types_init() call, mlxsw_linecards_init()
calls mlxsw_linecard_types_fini() which performs memory deallocation again.

Add pointer reset to NULL.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42139 | ice: Fix improper extts handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42139</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: Fix improper extts handling

Extts events are disabled and enabled by the application ts2phc.
However, in case where the driver is removed when the application is
running, a specific extts event remains enabled and can cause a kernel
crash.
As a side effect, when the driver is reloaded and application is started
again, remaining extts event for the channel from a previous run will
keep firing and the message "extts on unexpected channel" might be
printed to the user.

To avoid that, extts events shall be disabled when PTP is released.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42140 | riscv: kexec: Avoid deadlock in kexec crash path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42140</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: kexec: Avoid deadlock in kexec crash path

If the kexec crash code is called in the interrupt context, the
machine_kexec_mask_interrupts() function will trigger a deadlock while
trying to acquire the irqdesc spinlock and then deactivate irqchip in
irq_set_irqchip_state() function.

Unlike arm64, riscv only requires irq_eoi handler to complete EOI and
keeping irq_set_irqchip_state() will only leave this possible deadlock
without any use. So we simply remove it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42141 | Bluetooth: ISO: Check socket flag instead of hcon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42141</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: ISO: Check socket flag instead of hcon

This fixes the following Smatch static checker warning:

net/bluetooth/iso.c:1364 iso_sock_recvmsg()
error: we previously assumed 'pi-&gt;conn-&gt;hcon' could be null (line 1359)

net/bluetooth/iso.c
1347 static int iso_sock_recvmsg(struct socket *sock, struct msghdr *msg,
1348                             size_t len, int flags)
1349 {
1350         struct sock *sk = sock-&gt;sk;
1351         struct iso_pinfo *pi = iso_pi(sk);
1352
1353         BT_DBG("sk %p", sk);
1354
1355         if (test_and_clear_bit(BT_SK_DEFER_SETUP,
                                      &amp;amp;bt_sk(sk)-&gt;flags)) {
1356                 lock_sock(sk);
1357                 switch (sk-&gt;sk_state) {
1358                 case BT_CONNECT2:
1359                         if (pi-&gt;conn-&gt;hcon &amp;&amp;
                                     ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^ If -&gt;hcon is NULL

1360                             test_bit(HCI_CONN_PA_SYNC,
                                         &amp;amp;pi-&gt;conn-&gt;hcon-&gt;flags)) {
1361                                 iso_conn_big_sync(sk);
1362                                 sk-&gt;sk_state = BT_LISTEN;
1363                         } else {
--&gt; 1364                         iso_conn_defer_accept(pi-&gt;conn-&gt;hcon);
                                                       ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
                                                       then we're toast

1365                                 sk-&gt;sk_state = BT_CONFIG;
1366                         }
1367                         release_sock(sk);
1368                         return 0;
1369                 case BT_CONNECTED:
1370                         if (test_bit(BT_SK_PA_SYNC,</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42142 | net/mlx5: E-switch, Create ingress ACL when needed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42142</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: E-switch, Create ingress ACL when needed

Currently, ingress acl is used for three features. It is created only
when vport metadata match and prio tag are enabled. But active-backup
lag mode also uses it. It is independent of vport metadata match and
prio tag. And vport metadata match can be disabled using the
following devlink command:

 # devlink dev param set pci/0000:08:00.0 name esw_port_metadata \
	value false cmode runtime

If ingress acl is not created, will hit panic when creating drop rule
for active-backup lag mode. If always create it, there will be about
5% performance degradation.

Fix it by creating ingress acl when needed. If esw_port_metadata is
true, ingress acl exists, then create drop rule using existing
ingress acl. If esw_port_metadata is false, create ingress acl and
then create drop rule.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42143 | orangefs: fix out-of-bounds fsid access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42143</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

orangefs: fix out-of-bounds fsid access

Arnd Bergmann sent a patch to fsdevel, he says:

"orangefs_statfs() copies two consecutive fields of the superblock into
the statfs structure, which triggers a warning from the string fortification
helpers"

Jan Kara suggested an alternate way to do the patch to make it more readable.

I ran both ideas through xfstests and both seem fine. This patch
is based on Jan Kara's suggestion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42144 | thermal/drivers/mediatek/lvts_thermal: Check NULL ptr on lvts_data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42144</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thermal/drivers/mediatek/lvts_thermal: Check NULL ptr on lvts_data

Verify that lvts_data is not NULL before using it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42145 | IB/core: Implement a limit on UMAD receive List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42145</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

IB/core: Implement a limit on UMAD receive List

The existing behavior of ib_umad, which maintains received MAD
packets in an unbounded list, poses a risk of uncontrolled growth.
As user-space applications extract packets from this list, the rate
of extraction may not match the rate of incoming packets, leading
to potential list overflow.

To address this, we introduce a limit to the size of the list. After
considering typical scenarios, such as OpenSM processing, which can
handle approximately 100k packets per second, and the 1-second retry
timeout for most packets, we set the list size limit to 200k. Packets
received beyond this limit are dropped, assuming they are likely timed
out by the time they are handled by user-space.

Notably, packets queued on the receive list due to reasons like
timed-out sends are preserved even when the list is full.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42146 | drm/xe: Add outer runtime_pm protection to xe_live_ktest@xe_dma_buf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42146</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe: Add outer runtime_pm protection to xe_live_ktest@xe_dma_buf

Any kunit doing any memory access should get their own runtime_pm
outer references since they don't use the standard driver API
entries. In special this dma_buf from the same driver.

Found by pre-merge CI on adding WARN calls for unprotected
inner callers:

&lt;6&gt; [318.639739]     # xe_dma_buf_kunit: running xe_test_dmabuf_import_same_driver
&lt;4&gt; [318.639957] ------------[ cut here ]------------
&lt;4&gt; [318.639967] xe 0000:4d:00.0: Missing outer runtime PM protection
&lt;4&gt; [318.640049] WARNING: CPU: 117 PID: 3832 at drivers/gpu/drm/xe/xe_pm.c:533 xe_pm_runtime_get_noresume+0x48/0x60 [xe]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42147 | crypto: hisilicon/debugfs - Fix debugfs uninit process issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42147</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: hisilicon/debugfs - Fix debugfs uninit process issue

During the zip probe process, the debugfs failure does not stop
the probe. When debugfs initialization fails, jumping to the
error branch will also release regs, in addition to its own
rollback operation.

As a result, it may be released repeatedly during the regs
uninit process. Therefore, the null check needs to be added to
the regs uninit process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42148 | bnx2x: Fix multiple UBSAN array-index-out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42148</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bnx2x: Fix multiple UBSAN array-index-out-of-bounds

Fix UBSAN warnings that occur when using a system with 32 physical
cpu cores or more, or when the user defines a number of Ethernet
queues greater than or equal to FP_SB_MAX_E1x using the num_queues
module parameter.

Currently there is a read/write out of bounds that occurs on the array
"struct stats_query_entry query" present inside the "bnx2x_fw_stats_req"
struct in "drivers/net/ethernet/broadcom/bnx2x/bnx2x.h".
Looking at the definition of the "struct stats_query_entry query" array:

struct stats_query_entry query[FP_SB_MAX_E1x+
         BNX2X_FIRST_QUEUE_QUERY_IDX];

FP_SB_MAX_E1x is defined as the maximum number of fast path interrupts and
has a value of 16, while BNX2X_FIRST_QUEUE_QUERY_IDX has a value of 3
meaning the array has a total size of 19.
Since accesses to "struct stats_query_entry query" are offset-ted by
BNX2X_FIRST_QUEUE_QUERY_IDX, that means that the total number of Ethernet
queues should not exceed FP_SB_MAX_E1x (16). However one of these queues
is reserved for FCOE and thus the number of Ethernet queues should be set
to [FP_SB_MAX_E1x -1] (15) if FCOE is enabled or [FP_SB_MAX_E1x] (16) if
it is not.

This is also described in a comment in the source code in
drivers/net/ethernet/broadcom/bnx2x/bnx2x.h just above the Macro definition
of FP_SB_MAX_E1x. Below is the part of this explanation that it important
for this patch

/*
  * The total number of L2 queues, MSIX vectors and HW contexts (CIDs) is
  * control by the number of fast-path status blocks supported by the
  * device (HW/FW). Each fast-path status block (FP-SB) aka non-default
  * status block represents an independent interrupts context that can
  * serve a regular L2 networking queue. However special L2 queues such
  * as the FCoE queue do not require a FP-SB and other components like
  * the CNIC may consume FP-SB reducing the number of possible L2 queues
  *
  * If the maximum number of FP-SB available is X then:
  * a. If CNIC is supported it consumes 1 FP-SB thus the max number of
  *    regular L2 queues is Y=X-1
  * b. In MF mode the actual number of L2 queues is Y= (X-1/MF_factor)
  * c. If the FCoE L2 queue is supported the actual number of L2 queues
  *    is Y+1
  * d. The number of irqs (MSIX vectors) is either Y+1 (one extra for
  *    slow-path interrupts) or Y+2 if CNIC is supported (one additional
  *    FP interrupt context for the CNIC).
  * e. The number of HW context (CID count) is always X or X+1 if FCoE
  *    L2 queue is supported. The cid for the FCoE L2 queue is always X.
  */

However this driver also supports NICs that use the E2 controller which can
handle more queues due to having more FP-SB represented by FP_SB_MAX_E2.
Looking at the commits when the E2 support was added, it was originally
using the E1x parameters: commit f2e0899f0f27 ("bnx2x: Add 57712 support").
Back then FP_SB_MAX_E2 was set to 16 the same as E1x. However the driver
was later updated to take full advantage of the E2 instead of having it be
limited to the capabilities of the E1x. But as far as we can tell, the
array "stats_query_entry query" was still limited to using the FP-SB
available to the E1x cards as part of an oversignt when the driver was
updated to take full advantage of the E2, and now with the driver being
aware of the greater queue size supported by E2 NICs, it causes the UBSAN
warnings seen in the stack traces below.

This patch increases the size of the "stats_query_entry query" array by
replacing FP_SB_MAX_E1x with FP_SB_MAX_E2 to be large enough to handle
both types of NICs.

Stack traces:

UBSAN: array-index-out-of-bounds in
       drivers/net/ethernet/broadcom/bnx2x/bnx2x_stats.c:1529:11
index 20 is out of range for type 'stats_query_entry [19]'
CPU: 12 PID: 858 Comm: systemd-network Not tainted 6.9.0-060900rc7-generic
	     #202405052133
Hardware name: HP ProLiant DL360 Gen9/ProLiant DL360 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42149 | fs: don&amp;#x27;t misleadingly warn during thaw operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42149</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs: don't misleadingly warn during thaw operations

The block device may have been frozen before it was claimed by a
filesystem. Concurrently another process might try to mount that
frozen block device and has temporarily claimed the block device for
that purpose causing a concurrent fs_bdev_thaw() to end up here. The
mounter is already about to abort mounting because they still saw an
elevanted bdev-&gt;bd_fsfreeze_count so get_bdev_super() will return
NULL in that case.

For example, P1 calls dm_suspend() which calls into bdev_freeze() before
the block device has been claimed by the filesystem. This brings
bdev-&gt;bd_fsfreeze_count to 1 and no call into fs_bdev_freeze() is
required.

Now P2 tries to mount that frozen block device. It claims it and checks
bdev-&gt;bd_fsfreeze_count. As it's elevated it aborts mounting.

In the meantime P3 called dm_resume(). P3 sees that the block device is
already claimed by a filesystem and calls into fs_bdev_thaw().

P3 takes a passive reference and realizes that the filesystem isn't
ready yet. P3 puts itself to sleep to wait for the filesystem to become
ready.

P2 now puts the last active reference to the filesystem and marks it as
dying. P3 gets woken, sees that the filesystem is dying and
get_bdev_super() fails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42150 | net: txgbe: remove separate irq request for MSI and INTx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42150</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: txgbe: remove separate irq request for MSI and INTx

When using MSI or INTx interrupts, request_irq() for pdev-&gt;irq will
conflict with request_threaded_irq() for txgbe-&gt;misc.irq, to cause
system crash. So remove txgbe_request_irq() for MSI/INTx case, and
rename txgbe_request_msix_irqs() since it only request for queue irqs.

Add wx-&gt;misc_irq_domain to determine whether the driver creates an IRQ
domain and threaded request the IRQs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42151 | bpf: mark bpf_dummy_struct_ops.test_1 parameter as nullable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42151</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: mark bpf_dummy_struct_ops.test_1 parameter as nullable

Test case dummy_st_ops/dummy_init_ret_value passes NULL as the first
parameter of the test_1() function. Mark this parameter as nullable to
make verifier aware of such possibility.
Otherwise, NULL check in the test_1() code:

      SEC("struct_ops/test_1")
      int BPF_PROG(test_1, struct bpf_dummy_ops_state *state)
      {
            if (!state)
                    return ...;

            ... access state ...
      }

Might be removed by verifier, thus triggering NULL pointer dereference
under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42152 | nvmet: fix a possible leak when destroy a ctrl during qp establishment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42152</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet: fix a possible leak when destroy a ctrl during qp establishment

In nvmet_sq_destroy we capture sq-&gt;ctrl early and if it is non-NULL we
know that a ctrl was allocated (in the admin connect request handler)
and we need to release pending AERs, clear ctrl-&gt;sqs and sq-&gt;ctrl
(for nvme-loop primarily), and drop the final reference on the ctrl.

However, a small window is possible where nvmet_sq_destroy starts (as
a result of the client giving up and disconnecting) concurrently with
the nvme admin connect cmd (which may be in an early stage). But *before*
kill_and_confirm of sq-&gt;ref (i.e. the admin connect managed to get an sq
live reference). In this case, sq-&gt;ctrl was allocated however after it was
captured in a local variable in nvmet_sq_destroy.
This prevented the final reference drop on the ctrl.

Solve this by re-capturing the sq-&gt;ctrl after all inflight request has
completed, where for sure sq-&gt;ctrl reference is final, and move forward
based on that.

This issue was observed in an environment with many hosts connecting
multiple ctrls simoutanuosly, creating a delay in allocating a ctrl
leading up to this race window.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42153 | i2c: pnx: Fix potential deadlock warning from del_timer_sync() call in isr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42153</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: pnx: Fix potential deadlock warning from del_timer_sync() call in isr

When del_timer_sync() is called in an interrupt context it throws a warning
because of potential deadlock. The timer is used only to exit from
wait_for_completion() after a timeout so replacing the call with
wait_for_completion_timeout() allows to remove the problematic timer and
its related functions altogether.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42154 | tcp_metrics: validate source addr length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42154</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp_metrics: validate source addr length

I don't see anything checking that TCP_METRICS_ATTR_SADDR_IPV4
is at least 4 bytes long, and the policy doesn't have an entry
for this attribute at all (neither does it for IPv6 but v6 is
manually validated).</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42155 | s390/pkey: Wipe copies of protected- and secure-keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42155</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/pkey: Wipe copies of protected- and secure-keys

Although the clear-key of neither protected- nor secure-keys is
accessible, this key material should only be visible to the calling
process. So wipe all copies of protected- or secure-keys from stack,
even in case of an error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42156 | s390/pkey: Wipe copies of clear-key structures on failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42156</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/pkey: Wipe copies of clear-key structures on failure

Wipe all sensitive data from stack for all IOCTLs, which convert a
clear-key into a protected- or secure-key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42157 | s390/pkey: Wipe sensitive data on failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42157</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/pkey: Wipe sensitive data on failure

Wipe sensitive data from stack also if the copy_to_user() fails.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42158 | s390/pkey: Use kfree_sensitive() to fix Coccinelle warnings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42158</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/pkey: Use kfree_sensitive() to fix Coccinelle warnings

Replace memzero_explicit() and kfree() with kfree_sensitive() to fix
warnings reported by Coccinelle:

WARNING opportunity for kfree_sensitive/kvfree_sensitive (line 1506)
WARNING opportunity for kfree_sensitive/kvfree_sensitive (line 1643)
WARNING opportunity for kfree_sensitive/kvfree_sensitive (line 1770)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42159 | scsi: mpi3mr: Sanitise num_phys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42159</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: mpi3mr: Sanitise num_phys

Information is stored in mr_sas_port-&gt;phy_mask, values larger then size of
this field shouldn't be allowed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42160 | f2fs: check validation of fault attrs in f2fs_build_fault_attr()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42160</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: check validation of fault attrs in f2fs_build_fault_attr()

- It missed to check validation of fault attrs in parse_options(),
let's fix to add check condition in f2fs_build_fault_attr().
- Use f2fs_build_fault_attr() in __sbi_store() to clean up code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42161 | bpf: Avoid uninitialized value in BPF_CORE_READ_BITFIELD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42161</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Avoid uninitialized value in BPF_CORE_READ_BITFIELD

[Changes from V1:
 - Use a default branch in the switch statement to initialize `val'.]

GCC warns that `val' may be used uninitialized in the
BPF_CRE_READ_BITFIELD macro, defined in bpf_core_read.h as:

	[...]
	unsigned long long val;						      \
	[...]								      \
	switch (__CORE_RELO(s, field, BYTE_SIZE)) {			      \
	case 1: val = *(const unsigned char *)p; break;			      \
	case 2: val = *(const unsigned short *)p; break;		      \
	case 4: val = *(const unsigned int *)p; break;			      \
	case 8: val = *(const unsigned long long *)p; break;		      \
        }       							      \
	[...]
	val;								      \
	}								      \

This patch adds a default entry in the switch statement that sets
`val' to zero in order to avoid the warning, and random values to be
used in case __builtin_preserve_field_info returns unexpected values
for BPF_FIELD_BYTE_SIZE.

Tested in bpf-next master.
No regressions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42162 | gve: Account for stopped queues when reading NIC stats</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42162</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gve: Account for stopped queues when reading NIC stats

We now account for the fact that the NIC might send us stats for a
subset of queues. Without this change, gve_get_ethtool_stats might make
an invalid access on the priv-&gt;stats_report-&gt;stats array.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42223 | media: dvb-frontends: tda10048: Fix integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42223</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: dvb-frontends: tda10048: Fix integer overflow

state-&gt;xtal_hz can be up to 16M, so it can overflow a 32 bit integer
when multiplied by pll_mfactor.

Create a new 64 bit variable to hold the calculations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42224 | net: dsa: mv88e6xxx: Correct check for empty list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42224</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: dsa: mv88e6xxx: Correct check for empty list

Since commit a3c53be55c95 ("net: dsa: mv88e6xxx: Support multiple MDIO
busses") mv88e6xxx_default_mdio_bus() has checked that the
return value of list_first_entry() is non-NULL.

This appears to be intended to guard against the list chip-&gt;mdios being
empty.  However, it is not the correct check as the implementation of
list_first_entry is not designed to return NULL for empty lists.

Instead, use list_first_entry_or_null() which does return NULL if the
list is empty.

Flagged by Smatch.
Compile tested only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42225 | wifi: mt76: replace skb_put with skb_put_zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42225</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mt76: replace skb_put with skb_put_zero

Avoid potentially reusing uninitialized data</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42226 | usb: xhci: prevent potential failure in handle_tx_event() for Transfer events without TRB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42226</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: xhci: prevent potential failure in handle_tx_event() for Transfer events without TRB

Some transfer events don't always point to a TRB, and consequently don't
have a endpoint ring. In these cases, function handle_tx_event() should
not proceed, because if 'ep-&gt;skip' is set, the pointer to the endpoint
ring is used.

To prevent a potential failure and make the code logical, return after
checking the completion code for a Transfer event without TRBs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42227 | drm/amd/display: Fix overlapping copy within dml_core_mode_programming</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42227</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Fix overlapping copy within dml_core_mode_programming

[WHY]
&amp;amp;mode_lib-&gt;mp.Watermark and &amp;amp;locals-&gt;Watermark are
the same address. memcpy may lead to unexpected behavior.

[HOW]
memmove should be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42228 | drm/amdgpu: Using uninitialized value *size when calling amdgpu_vce_cs_reloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42228</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Using uninitialized value *size when calling amdgpu_vce_cs_reloc

Initialize the size before calling amdgpu_vce_cs_reloc, such as case 0x03000001.
V2: To really improve the handling we would actually
   need to have a separate value of 0xffffffff.(Christian)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42229 | crypto: aead,cipher - zeroize key buffer after use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42229</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: aead,cipher - zeroize key buffer after use

I.G 9.7.B for FIPS 140-3 specifies that variables temporarily holding
cryptographic information should be zeroized once they are no longer
needed. Accomplish this by using kfree_sensitive for buffers that
previously held the private key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42230 | powerpc/pseries: Fix scv instruction crash with kexec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42230</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc/pseries: Fix scv instruction crash with kexec

kexec on pseries disables AIL (reloc_on_exc), required for scv
instruction support, before other CPUs have been shut down. This means
they can execute scv instructions after AIL is disabled, which causes an
interrupt at an unexpected entry location that crashes the kernel.

Change the kexec sequence to disable AIL after other CPUs have been
brought down.

As a refresher, the real-mode scv interrupt vector is 0x17000, and the
fixed-location head code probably couldn't easily deal with implementing
such high addresses so it was just decided not to support that interrupt
at all.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42231 | btrfs: zoned: fix calc_available_free_space() for zoned mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42231</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: zoned: fix calc_available_free_space() for zoned mode

calc_available_free_space() returns the total size of metadata (or
system) block groups, which can be allocated from unallocated disk
space. The logic is wrong on zoned mode in two places.

First, the calculation of data_chunk_size is wrong. We always allocate
one zone as one chunk, and no partial allocation of a zone. So, we
should use zone_size (= data_sinfo-&gt;chunk_size) as it is.

Second, the result "avail" may not be zone aligned. Since we always
allocate one zone as one chunk on zoned mode, returning non-zone size
aligned bytes will result in less pressure on the async metadata reclaim
process.

This is serious for the nearly full state with a large zone size device.
Allowing over-commit too much will result in less async reclaim work and
end up in ENOSPC. We can align down to the zone size to avoid that.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7223 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System view_model.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7223</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view_model.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272803.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7222 | SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7222</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Lot Reservation Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /home.php. The manipulation of the argument type leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272802 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7100 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via bt_bb_button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7100</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:53:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40094 | GraphQL Java (aka graphql-java) before 21.5 does not properly consider ExecutableNormalizedFields (ENFs) as part of preventing denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40094</link><description>GraphQL Java (aka graphql-java) before 21.5 does not properly consider ExecutableNormalizedFields (ENFs) as part of preventing denial of service via introspection queries. 20.9 and 19.11 are also fixed versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7221 | SourceCodester School Log Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7221</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester School Log Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272792.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1286 | Paid Memberships Pro - Membership Maps Add On &amp;lt; 0.7 - Contributor+ Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1286</link><description>The pmpro-membership-maps WordPress plugin before 0.7 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from leaking sensitive information about users with a membership on the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1287 | Paid Memberships Pro - Member Directory Add On &amp;lt; 1.2.6 - Contributor+ Sensitive Information Disclosure and SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1287</link><description>The pmpro-member-directory WordPress plugin before 1.2.6 does not prevent users with at least the contributor role from leaking other users' sensitive information, including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3113 | FormFlow &amp;lt; 2.12.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3113</link><description>The FormFlow: WhatsApp Social and Advanced Form Builder with Easy Lead Collection WordPress plugin before 2.12.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3669 | Web Directory Free &amp;lt; 1.7.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3669</link><description>The Web Directory Free WordPress plugin before 1.7.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3986 | SportsPress &amp;lt; 2.7.22 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3986</link><description>The SportsPress  WordPress plugin before 2.7.22 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4096 | Responsive Tabs &amp;lt;= 4.0.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4096</link><description>The Responsive Tabs WordPress plugin through 4.0.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its Tab settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributors and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5765 | WpStickyBar &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5765</link><description>The WpStickyBar  WordPress plugin through 2.1.0 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5807 | Business Card &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Admin+ File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5807</link><description>The Business Card WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not prevent high privilege users like administrators from uploading malicious PHP files, which could allow them to run arbitrary code on servers hosting their site, even in MultiSite configurations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5808 | WP Ajax Contact Form &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Arbitrary Email Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5808</link><description>The WP Ajax Contact Form WordPress plugin through 2.2.2 does not have CSRF check in place when deleting emails from the email list, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5809 | WP Ajax Contact Form &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5809</link><description>The WP Ajax Contact Form WordPress plugin through 2.2.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against admin users</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5975 | CZ Loan Management &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5975</link><description>The CZ Loan Management WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6021 | Donation Block for PayPal &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6021</link><description>The Donation Block For PayPal WordPress plugin through 2.1.0 does not sanitise and escape form submissions, leading to a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6223 | Send email only on Reply to My Comment &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6223</link><description>The Send email only on Reply to My Comment WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6224 | Send email only on Reply to My Comment &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6224</link><description>The Send email only on Reply to My Comment WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6226 | WpStickyBar &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6226</link><description>The WpStickyBar  WordPress plugin through 2.1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6230 | Pardakht Delkhah &amp;lt;= 2.9.8 - Form Fields Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6230</link><description>The پلاگین پرداخت دلخواه WordPress plugin through 2.9.8 does not have CSRF check in place when resetting its form fields, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6536 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt; 3.3.99 - Editor+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6536</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager WordPress plugin before 3.3.99 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors and admins to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7220 | SourceCodester School Log Management System print_barcode.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7220</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester School Log Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/print_barcode.php. The manipulation of the argument tbl leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272791.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7219 | SourceCodester School Log Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7219</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester School Log Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272790 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7218 | SourceCodester School Log Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7218</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Log Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_student. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272789 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 05:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7217 | TOTOLINK CA300-PoE cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7217</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK CA300-PoE 6.2c.884. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272788. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7216 | TOTOLINK LR1200 shadow.sample hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7216</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 04:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7215 | TOTOLINK LR1200 cstecgi.cgi NTPSyncWithHost command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK LR1200 9.3.1cu.2832 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function NTPSyncWithHost of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument host_time leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7214 | TOTOLINK LR350 cstecgi.cgi setWanCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7214</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWanCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument hostName leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-272785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 03:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7213 | TOTOLINK A7000R cstecgi.cgi setWizardCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7213</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. Affected is the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272784. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7212 | TOTOLINK A7000R cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7212</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A7000R 9.1.0u.6268_B20220504. This issue affects the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272783. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>