<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:12:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-34088 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, it is possible for the get_edge() function in ospf_te.c in the OSPF daemon to return a NULL pointer. In case...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34088</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, it is possible for the get_edge() function in ospf_te.c in the OSPF daemon to return a NULL pointer. In cases where calling functions do not handle the returned NULL value, the OSPF daemon crashes, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50053 | An issue in Foundation.app Foundation platform 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Web3 authentication proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50053</link><description>An issue in Foundation.app Foundation platform 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Web3 authentication process of Foundation, the signed message lacks a nonce (random number)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50059 | An issue ingalxe.com Galxe platform 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Web3 authentication process of Galx...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50059</link><description>An issue ingalxe.com Galxe platform 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Web3 authentication process of Galxe, the signed message lacks a nonce (random number)</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26331 | ReCrystallize Server 5.10.0.0 uses a authorization mechanism that relies on the value of a cookie, but it does not bind the cookie value to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26331</link><description>ReCrystallize Server 5.10.0.0 uses a authorization mechanism that relies on the value of a cookie, but it does not bind the cookie value to a session ID. Attackers can easily modify the cookie value, within a browser or by implementing client-side code outside of a browser. Attackers can bypass the authentication mechanism by modifying the cookie to contain an expected value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28269 | ReCrystallize Server 5.10.0.0 allows administrators to upload files to the server. The file upload is not restricted, leading to the ability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28269</link><description>ReCrystallize Server 5.10.0.0 allows administrators to upload files to the server. The file upload is not restricted, leading to the ability to upload of malicious files. This could result in a Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3411 | Insufficient Randomness When Validating an IPMI Authenticated Session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3411</link><description>Implementations of IPMI Authenticated sessions does not provide enough randomness to protect from session hijacking, allowing an attacker to use either predictable IPMI Session ID or weak BMC Random Number to bypass security controls using spoofed IPMI packets to manage BMC device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-27478 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in Simplcommerce v.40734964b0811f3cbaf64b6dac261683d256f961 thru 3103357200c70b4767986544e01b19dbf1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27478</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in Simplcommerce v.40734964b0811f3cbaf64b6dac261683d256f961 thru 3103357200c70b4767986544e01b19dbf11505a7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the search bar feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49473 | Shenzhen JF6000 Cloud Media Collaboration Processing Platform firmware version V1.2.0 and software version V2.0.0 build 6245 is vulnerable t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49473</link><description>Shenzhen JF6000 Cloud Media Collaboration Processing Platform firmware version V1.2.0 and software version V2.0.0 build 6245 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22546 | TRENDnet TEW-815DAP 1.0.2.0 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the do_setNTP function. An authenticated attacker with administrator priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22546</link><description>TRENDnet TEW-815DAP 1.0.2.0 is vulnerable to Command Injection via the do_setNTP function. An authenticated attacker with administrator privileges can leverage this vulnerability over the network via a malicious POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33101 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /action/anti.php of ThinkSAAS v3.7.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33101</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /action/anti.php of ThinkSAAS v3.7.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the word parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33102 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /pubs/counter.php of ThinkSAAS v3.7.0 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33102</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /pubs/counter.php of ThinkSAAS v3.7.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the code parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33103 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Media Manager component of DokuWiki 2024-02-06a allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33103</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the Media Manager component of DokuWiki 2024-02-06a allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33831 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Advanced Expectation - Response module of yapi v1.10.2 allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33831</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Advanced Expectation - Response module of yapi v1.10.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the body field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33832 | OneNav v0.9.35-20240318 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component /index.php?c=api&amp;method=get_link_in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33832</link><description>OneNav v0.9.35-20240318 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component /index.php?c=api&amp;amp;method=get_link_info.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19752 | nvOC through 3.2 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19752</link><description>nvOC through 3.2 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io. NOTE: as of 2019-12-01, the vendor indicated plans to fix this in the next image build.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19753 | SimpleMiningOS through v1259 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes id...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19753</link><description>SimpleMiningOS through v1259 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io. NOTE: the vendor indicated that they have no plans to fix this, and discourage deployment using public IPv4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19754 | HiveOS through 0.6-102@191212 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19754</link><description>HiveOS through 0.6-102@191212 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io. NOTE: as of 2019-09-26, the vendor indicated that they would consider fixing this.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19755 | ethOS through 1.3.3 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19755</link><description>ethOS through 1.3.3 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io. NOTE: as of 2019-12-01, the vendor indicated that they plan to fix this.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-5200 | Minerbabe through V4.16 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5200</link><description>Minerbabe through V4.16 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19751 | easyMINE before 2019-12-05 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes iden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19751</link><description>easyMINE before 2019-12-05 ships with SSH host keys baked into the installation image, which allows man-in-the-middle attacks and makes identification of all public IPv4 nodes trivial with Shodan.io.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36268 | An issue in The Document Foundation Libreoffice v.7.4.7 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted .ppt file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36268</link><description>An issue in The Document Foundation Libreoffice v.7.4.7 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted .ppt file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23463 | Anti-Tampering bypass via Repair App functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23463</link><description>Anti-tampering protection of the Zscaler Client Connector can be bypassed under certain conditions when running the Repair App functionality. This affects Zscaler Client Connector on Windows prior to 4.2.1</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29320 | Wallos before 1.15.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the category and payment parameters to /subscriptions/get.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29320</link><description>Wallos before 1.15.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the category and payment parameters to /subscriptions/get.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33270 | An issue in FME Modules fileuploads v.2.0.3 and before and fixed in v2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33270</link><description>An issue in FME Modules fileuploads v.2.0.3 and before and fixed in v2.0.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the uploadfiles.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33273 | SQL injection vulnerability in shipup before v.3.3.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getShopID function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33273</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in shipup before v.3.3.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the getShopID function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2877 | Vault Enterprise Leaks Sensitive HTTP Request Headers in the Audit Log When Deployed With a Performance Standby Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2877</link><description>Vault Enterprise, when configured with performance standby nodes and a configured audit device, will inadvertently log request headers on the standby node. These logs may have included sensitive HTTP request information in cleartext.

This vulnerability, CVE-2024-2877, was fixed in Vault Enterprise 1.15.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:07:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33275 | SQL injection vulnerability in Webbax supernewsletter v.1.4.21 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Super News...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33275</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Webbax supernewsletter v.1.4.21 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Super Newsletter module in the product_search.php components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33274 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in FME Modules customfields v.2.2.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33274</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in FME Modules customfields v.2.2.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Custom Checkout Fields, Add Custom Fields to Checkout parameter of the ajax.php</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38002 | IBM Storage Scale session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38002</link><description>IBM Storage Scale 5.1.0.0 through 5.1.9.2 could allow an authenticated user to steal or manipulate an active session to gain access to the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  260208.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45385 | ProQuality pqprintshippinglabels before v.4.15.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via the pqprintshippinglabels module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45385</link><description>ProQuality pqprintshippinglabels before v.4.15.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via the pqprintshippinglabels module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33267 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Hero hfheropayment v.1.2.5 and before allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the HfHeropaymentGatewayB...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33267</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Hero hfheropayment v.1.2.5 and before allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the HfHeropaymentGatewayBackModuleFrontController::initContent() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25575 | A type confusion vulnerability vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Lock object. A specially crafted Javasc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25575</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Lock object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25648 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25648</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a ComboBox widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25938 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Barcode widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25938</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.1.0.23997 handles a Barcode widget. A specially crafted JavaScript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger reuse of a previously freed object, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33309 | An issue in TVS Motor Company Limited TVS Connet Android v.4.5.1 and iOS v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33309</link><description>An issue in TVS Motor Company Limited TVS Connet Android v.4.5.1 and iOS v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via an insecure API endpoint</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33465 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MajorDoMo before v.0662e5e allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the the thumb/thumb.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33465</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MajorDoMo before v.0662e5e allows an attacker to escalate privileges via the the thumb/thumb.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33308 | An issue in TVS Motor Company Limited TVS Connet Android v.4.5.1 and iOS v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Eme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33308</link><description>An issue in TVS Motor Company Limited TVS Connet Android v.4.5.1 and iOS v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Emergency Contact Feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28716 | An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28716</link><description>An issue in OpenStack Storlets yoga-eom allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the gateway.py component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4340 | Passing a heavily nested list to sqlparse.parse() leads to a Denial of Service due to RecursionError.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4340</link><description>Passing a heavily nested list to sqlparse.parse() leads to a Denial of Service due to RecursionError.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23772 | An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An Arbitrary file create vulnerability exists in the KSchedul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23772</link><description>An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An Arbitrary file create vulnerability exists in the KSchedulerSvc.exe, KUserAlert.exe, and Runkbot.exe components. This allows local attackers to create any file of their choice with NT Authority\SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23773 | An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An Arbitrary file delete vulnerability exists in the KSchedul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23773</link><description>An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An Arbitrary file delete vulnerability exists in the KSchedulerSvc.exe component. Local attackers can delete any file of their choice with NT Authority\SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23774 | An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An unquoted Windows search path vulnerability exists in the K...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23774</link><description>An issue was discovered in Quest KACE Agent for Windows 12.0.38 and 13.1.23.0. An unquoted Windows search path vulnerability exists in the KSchedulerSvc.exe and AMPTools.exe components. This allows local attackers to execute code of their choice with NT Authority\SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50914 | A Privilege Escalation issue in the inter-process communication procedure from GOG Galaxy (Beta) 2.0.67.2 through v2.0.71.2 allows authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50914</link><description>A Privilege Escalation issue in the inter-process communication procedure from GOG Galaxy (Beta) 2.0.67.2 through v2.0.71.2 allows authentictaed users to change the DACL of arbitrary system directories to include Everyone full control permissions by modifying the FixDirectoryPrivileges instruction parameters sent from GalaxyClient.exe to GalaxyClientService.exe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:04:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50915 | An issue exists in GalaxyClientService.exe in GOG Galaxy (Beta) 2.0.67.2 through 2.0.71.2 that could allow authenticated users to overwrite ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50915</link><description>An issue exists in GalaxyClientService.exe in GOG Galaxy (Beta) 2.0.67.2 through 2.0.71.2 that could allow authenticated users to overwrite and corrupt critical system files via a combination of an NTFS Junction and an RPC Object Manager symbolic link and could result in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46304 | modules/Users/models/Module.php in Vtiger CRM 7.5.0 allows a remote authenticated attacker to run arbitrary PHP code because an unprotected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46304</link><description>modules/Users/models/Module.php in Vtiger CRM 7.5.0 allows a remote authenticated attacker to run arbitrary PHP code because an unprotected endpoint allows them to write this code to the config.inc.php file (executed on every page load).</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2377 | A vulnerability exists in the too permissive HTTP response header web server settings of the SDM600. An attacker can take advantage of this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2377</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the too permissive HTTP response header web server settings of the SDM600. An attacker can take advantage of this and possibly carry out privileged actions and access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2378 | A vulnerability exists in the web-authentication component of the SDM600. If exploited an attacker could escalate privileges on af-fected in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2378</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the web-authentication component of the SDM600. If exploited an attacker could escalate privileges on af-fected installations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:06:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2617 | A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 that allows for authenticated and authorized users to bypass secure update. If a
malicious actor succes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2617</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the RTU500 that allows for authenticated and authorized users to bypass secure update. If a
malicious actor successfully exploits this vulnerability, they
could use it to update the RTU500 with unsigned firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:06:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22405 | XADMaster may not apply quarantine attribute correctly to extracted files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22405</link><description>XADMaster is an objective-C library for archive and file unarchiving and extraction. When extracting a specially crafted zip archive XADMaster may not apply quarantine attribute correctly. Such behaviour may circumvent Gatekeeper checks on the system. Only macOS installations are affected. This issue was fixed in XADMaster 1.10.8. It is recommended to upgrade to the latest version. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4336 | Múltiple vulnerabilities on Adive Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4336</link><description>Adive Framework 2.0.8, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in a persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /adive/admin/tables/add, in multiple parameters. An attacker could retrieve the session details of an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4337 | Múltiple vulnerabilities on Adive Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4337</link><description>Adive Framework 2.0.8, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in a persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /adive/admin/nav/add, in multiple parameters. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve the session details of an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1895 | The Event Monster – Event Management, Tickets Booking, Upcoming Event plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1895</link><description>The Event Monster – Event Management, Tickets Booking, Upcoming Event plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 via deserialization via shortcode of untrusted input from a custom meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2663 | The ZD YouTube FLV Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2663</link><description>The ZD YouTube FLV Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 via the $_GET['image'] parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3072 | The ACF Front End Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3072</link><description>The ACF Front End Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_texts() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary post title, content, and ACF data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4185 | The Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Verification and Authentication Bypass in all ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4185</link><description>The Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Email Verification and Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.4 via the use of insufficiently random activation code. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the email verification, and if both the "Login the user automatically after the account is verified" and "Verify account for current users" options are checked, then it potentially makes it possible for attackers to bypass authentication for other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31837 | DMitry (Deepmagic Information Gathering Tool) 1.3a has a format-string vulnerability, with a threat model similar to CVE-2017-7938.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31837</link><description>DMitry (Deepmagic Information Gathering Tool) 1.3a has a format-string vulnerability, with a threat model similar to CVE-2017-7938.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4225 | NGDIN_ST v2.0D.0062 - Multiple Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4225</link><description>Multiple security vulnerabilities has been discovered in web interface of NetGuardian DIN Remote Telemetry Unit (RTU), by DPS Telecom. Attackers can exploit those security vulnerabilities to perform critical actions such as escalate user's privilege, steal user's credential, Cross Site Scripting (XSS) and Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF).</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1371 | The LeadConnector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification &amp; loss of data due to a missing capability check on the lc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1371</link><description>The LeadConnector plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification &amp; loss of data due to a missing capability check on the lc_public_api_proxy() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0216 | The Google Doc Embedder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery via the 'gview' shortcode in versions up to, and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0216</link><description>The Google Doc Embedder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery via the 'gview' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.6.4. This can allow authenticated attackers with contributor-level permissions or above to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4226 | It was identified that in certain versions of Octopus Server, that a user created with no permissions could view all users, user roles and p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4226</link><description>It was identified that in certain versions of Octopus Server, that a user created with no permissions could view all users, user roles and permissions. This functionality was removed in versions of Octopus Server after the fixed versions listed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4327 | Apryse WebViewer PDF Document cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4327</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apryse WebViewer up to 10.8.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component PDF Document Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 10.9 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262419. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure and explains that the documentation recommends a strict Content Security Policy and the issue was fixed in release 10.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 01:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52724 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN onos-kpimon 0.4.7 allows out-of-bounds array access in the processIndicationFormat1 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52724</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN onos-kpimon 0.4.7 allows out-of-bounds array access in the processIndicationFormat1 function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52725 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-kpimon 0.4.7 allows blocking of the errCh channel within the Start function of the monitoring pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52725</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-kpimon 0.4.7 allows blocking of the errCh channel within the Start function of the monitoring package.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52726 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-ric-sdk-go 0.8.12 allows infinite repetition of the processing of an error (in the Subscribe fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52726</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-ric-sdk-go 0.8.12 allows infinite repetition of the processing of an error (in the Subscribe function implementation for the subscribed indication stream).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52727 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.25 allows an index out-of-range condition in parseAlignBits.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52727</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.25 allows an index out-of-range condition in parseAlignBits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52728 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.25 allows an index out-of-range condition in putBitString.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52728</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.25 allows an index out-of-range condition in putBitString.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34043 | O-RAN RICAPP kpimon-go I-Release has a segmentation violation via a certain E2AP-PDU message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34043</link><description>O-RAN RICAPP kpimon-go I-Release has a segmentation violation via a certain E2AP-PDU message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34044 | The O-RAN E2T I-Release buildPrometheusList function can have a NULL pointer dereference because peerInfo can be NULL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34044</link><description>The O-RAN E2T I-Release buildPrometheusList function can have a NULL pointer dereference because peerInfo can be NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34045 | The O-RAN E2T I-Release Prometheus metric Increment function can crash in sctpThread.cpp for message.peerInfo-&gt;counters[IN_INITI][MSG_COUNTE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34045</link><description>The O-RAN E2T I-Release Prometheus metric Increment function can crash in sctpThread.cpp for message.peerInfo-&gt;counters[IN_INITI][MSG_COUNTER][ProcedureCode_id_E2setup]-&gt;Increment().</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34046 | The O-RAN E2T I-Release Prometheus metric Increment function can crash in sctpThread.cpp for message.peerInfo-&gt;sctpParams-&gt;e2tCounters[IN_SU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34046</link><description>The O-RAN E2T I-Release Prometheus metric Increment function can crash in sctpThread.cpp for message.peerInfo-&gt;sctpParams-&gt;e2tCounters[IN_SUCC][MSG_COUNTER][ProcedureCode_id_RICsubscription]-&gt;Increment().</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34047 | O-RAN RIC I-Release e2mgr lacks array size checks in RicServiceUpdateHandler.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34047</link><description>O-RAN RIC I-Release e2mgr lacks array size checks in RicServiceUpdateHandler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34048 | O-RAN RIC I-Release e2mgr lacks array size checks in E2nodeConfigUpdateNotificationHandler.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34048</link><description>O-RAN RIC I-Release e2mgr lacks array size checks in E2nodeConfigUpdateNotificationHandler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34049 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN Rimedo rimedo-ts 0.1.1 has a slice bounds out-of-range panic in "return plmnIdString[0:3], plmnIdString[3:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34049</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN Rimedo rimedo-ts 0.1.1 has a slice bounds out-of-range panic in "return plmnIdString[0:3], plmnIdString[3:]" in reader.go.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34050 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN Rimedo rimedo-ts 0.1.1 has a slice bounds out-of-range panic in "return uint64(b[2])&lt;&lt;16 | uint64(b[1])&lt;&lt;8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34050</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN Rimedo rimedo-ts 0.1.1 has a slice bounds out-of-range panic in "return uint64(b[2])&lt;&lt;16 | uint64(b[1])&lt;&lt;8 | uint64(b[0])" in reader.go.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33522 | Privilege escalation in Calico CNI install binary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33522</link><description>In vulnerable versions of Calico (v3.27.2 and below), Calico Enterprise (v3.19.0-1, v3.18.1, v3.17.3 and below), and Calico Cloud (v19.2.0 and below), an attacker who has local access to the Kubernetes node, can escalate their privileges by exploiting a vulnerability in the Calico CNI install binary. The issue arises from an incorrect SUID (Set User ID) bit configuration in the binary, combined with the ability to control the input binary, allowing an attacker to execute an arbitrary binary with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 22:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50432 | simple-dhcp-server through ec976d2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (daemon crash) by sending a DHCP packet without any ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50432</link><description>simple-dhcp-server through ec976d2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (daemon crash) by sending a DHCP packet without any option fields, which causes free_packet in dhcp_packet.c to dereference a NULL pointer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50433 | marshall in dhcp_packet.c in simple-dhcp-server through ec976d2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending a malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50433</link><description>marshall in dhcp_packet.c in simple-dhcp-server through ec976d2 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending a malicious DHCP packet. The crash is caused by a type confusion bug that results in a large memory allocation; when this memory allocation fails the DHCP server will crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50434 | emdns_resolve_raw in emdns.c in emdns through fbd1eef calls strlen with an input that may not be '\0' terminated, leading to a stack-based b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50434</link><description>emdns_resolve_raw in emdns.c in emdns through fbd1eef calls strlen with an input that may not be '\0' terminated, leading to a stack-based buffer over-read. This can be triggered by a remote adversary that can send DNS requests to the emdns server. The impact could vary depending on the system libraries, compiler, and processor architecture. Code before be565c3 is unaffected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33401 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7.113 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via the mnum parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33401</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7.113 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via the mnum parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31889 | An issue discovered in httpd in ASUS RT-AC51U with firmware version up to and including 3.0.0.4.380.8591 allows local attackers to cause a d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31889</link><description>An issue discovered in httpd in ASUS RT-AC51U with firmware version up to and including 3.0.0.4.380.8591 allows local attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27518 | An issue in SUPERAntiSyware Professional X 10.0.1262 and 10.0.1264 allows unprivileged attackers to escalate privileges via a restore of a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27518</link><description>An issue in SUPERAntiSyware Professional X 10.0.1262 and 10.0.1264 allows unprivileged attackers to escalate privileges via a restore of a crafted DLL file into the C:\Program Files\SUPERAntiSpyware folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33350 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in TaoCMS v.3.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33350</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in TaoCMS v.3.0.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the include/model/file.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46566 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in msoulier tftpy commit 467017b844bf6e31745138a30e2509145b0c529c allows a remote attacker to cause a denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46566</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in msoulier tftpy commit 467017b844bf6e31745138a30e2509145b0c529c allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the parse function in the TftpPacketFactory class.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46960 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in PyPXE v.1.8.4 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the handle function in the tftp mod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46960</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in PyPXE v.1.8.4 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the handle function in the tftp module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28294 | Limbas up to v5.2.14 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the ftid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28294</link><description>Limbas up to v5.2.14 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the ftid parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46565 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in osrg gobgp commit 419c50dfac578daa4d11256904d0dc182f1a9b22 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46565</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in osrg gobgp commit 419c50dfac578daa4d11256904d0dc182f1a9b22 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the handlingError function in pkg/server/fsm.go.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33271 | An issue in FME Modules eventsmanager before 4.4.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information from the ps_customer component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33271</link><description>An issue in FME Modules eventsmanager before 4.4.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information from the ps_customer component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33276 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FME Modules preorderandnotication v.3.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33276</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FME Modules preorderandnotication v.3.1.0 and before allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the PreorderModel::getIdProductAttributesByIdAttributes() method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33269 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Prestaddons flashsales 1.9.7 and before allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the FsModel::get...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33269</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Prestaddons flashsales 1.9.7 and before allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the FsModel::getFlashSales method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33268 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Digincube mdgiftproduct before 1.4.1 allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the MdGiftRule::add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33268</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Digincube mdgiftproduct before 1.4.1 allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the MdGiftRule::addGiftToCart method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31801 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in NEXSYS-ONE before v.Rev.15320 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31801</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in NEXSYS-ONE before v.Rev.15320 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33272 | SQL injection vulnerability in KnowBand for PrestaShop autosuggest before 2.0.0 allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the Aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33272</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in KnowBand for PrestaShop autosuggest before 2.0.0 allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the AutosuggestSearchModuleFrontController::initContent(), and AutosuggestSearchModuleFrontController::getKbProducts() components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33266 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Helloshop deliveryorderautoupdate v.2.8.1 and before allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33266</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Helloshop deliveryorderautoupdate v.2.8.1 and before allows an attacker to run arbitrary SQL commands via the DeliveryorderautoupdateOrdersModuleFrontController::initContent function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33435 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Guangzhou Yingshi Electronic Technology Co. Ncast Yingshi high-definition intelligent recording and pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33435</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Guangzhou Yingshi Electronic Technology Co. Ncast Yingshi high-definition intelligent recording and playback system 2007-2017 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /manage/IPSetup.php backend function</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31747 | An issue in Yealink VP59 Microsoft Teams Phone firmware 91.15.0.118 (fixed in 122.15.0.142) allows a physically proximate attacker to disabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31747</link><description>An issue in Yealink VP59 Microsoft Teams Phone firmware 91.15.0.118 (fixed in 122.15.0.142) allows a physically proximate attacker to disable the phone lock via the Walkie Talkie menu option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0840 | Grandstream UCM Series IP PBX HTTP Parameter Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0840</link><description>The Grandstream UCM Series IP PBX before firmware version 1.0.20.52 is affected by a parameter injection vulnerability in the HTTP interface. A remote and authenticated attacker can execute arbitrary code by sending a crafted HTTP request. Authentication may be possible using a default user and password. Affected models are the UCM6202, UCM6204, UCM6208, and UCM6510.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51710 | EMS SQL Manager 3.6.2 (build 55333) for Oracle allows DLL hijacking: a user can trigger the execution of arbitrary code every time the produ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51710</link><description>EMS SQL Manager 3.6.2 (build 55333) for Oracle allows DLL hijacking: a user can trigger the execution of arbitrary code every time the product is executed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52080 | IEIT NF5280M6 UEFI firmware through 8.4 has a pool overflow vulnerability, caused by improper use of the gRT-&gt;GetVariable() function. Attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52080</link><description>IEIT NF5280M6 UEFI firmware through 8.4 has a pool overflow vulnerability, caused by improper use of the gRT-&gt;GetVariable() function. Attackers with access to local NVRAM variables can exploit this by modifying these variables on SPI Flash, resulting in memory data being tampered with. When critical data in memory data is tampered with,a crash may occur.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28320 | Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in Hospital Management System 1.0 allows attackers to manipulate user parameters for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28320</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability in Hospital Management System 1.0 allows attackers to manipulate user parameters for unauthorized access and modifications via crafted POST request to /patient/edit-user.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33338 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in jizhicms v.2.5.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted article public...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33338</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in jizhicms v.2.5.4 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted article publication request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33345 | D-Link DIR-823G A1V1.0.2B05 was found to contain a Null-pointer dereference in the main function of upload_firmware.cgi, which allows remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33345</link><description>D-Link DIR-823G A1V1.0.2B05 was found to contain a Null-pointer dereference in the main function of upload_firmware.cgi, which allows remote attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31705 | An issue in Infotel Conseil GLPI v.10.X.X and after allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the insufficient validation of us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31705</link><description>An issue in Infotel Conseil GLPI v.10.X.X and after allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the insufficient validation of user-supplied input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51254 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Jfinalcms v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the frien...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51254</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Jfinalcms v.5.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the friendship link component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31823 | An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31823</link><description>An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the removeSecondaryImage method of the Publish.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31820 | An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31820</link><description>An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the getLangFolderForEdit method of the Languages.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31821 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31821</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the manageQuantitiesAndProcurement method of the Orders_model.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33438 | File Upload vulnerability in CubeCart before 6.5.5 allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .phar file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33438</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in CubeCart before 6.5.5 allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .phar file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31822 | An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31822</link><description>An issue in Ecommerce-CodeIgniter-Bootstrap commit v. d22b54e8915f167a135046ceb857caaf8479c4da allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the saveLanguageFiles method of the Languages.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33443 | An issue in onethink v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the AddonsController.class.php compone...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33443</link><description>An issue in onethink v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the AddonsController.class.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31621 | An issue in FlowiseAI Inc Flowise v.1.6.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the api/v1 c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31621</link><description>An issue in FlowiseAI Inc Flowise v.1.6.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the api/v1 component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33445 | An issue in hisiphp v2.0.111 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the SystemPlugins::mkInfo parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33445</link><description>An issue in hisiphp v2.0.111 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the SystemPlugins::mkInfo parameter in the SystemPlugins.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33449 | An SSRF issue in the PDFMyURL service allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a POST request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33449</link><description>An SSRF issue in the PDFMyURL service allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a POST request in the url parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33444 | SQL injection vulnerability in onethink v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the ModelModel.class.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33444</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in onethink v.1.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the ModelModel.class.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32493 | An issue was discovered in Znuny LTS 6.5.1 through 6.5.7 and Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where a logged-in agent is able to inject SQL in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32493</link><description>An issue was discovered in Znuny LTS 6.5.1 through 6.5.7 and Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where a logged-in agent is able to inject SQL in the draft form ID parameter of an AJAX request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32491 | An issue was discovered in Znuny and Znuny LTS 6.0.31 through 6.5.7 and Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where a logged-in user can upload a file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32491</link><description>An issue was discovered in Znuny and Znuny LTS 6.0.31 through 6.5.7 and Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where a logged-in user can upload a file (via a manipulated AJAX Request) to an arbitrary writable location by traversing paths. Arbitrary code can be executed if this location is publicly available through the web server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32492 | An issue was discovered in Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where the ticket detail view in the customer front allows the execution of external Ja...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32492</link><description>An issue was discovered in Znuny 7.0.1 through 7.0.16 where the ticket detail view in the customer front allows the execution of external JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32269 | An issue in Yonganda YAD-LOJ V3.0.561 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted packet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32269</link><description>An issue in Yonganda YAD-LOJ V3.0.561 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32268 | An issue in Tuya Smart camera U6N v.3.2.5 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted packet to the network connecti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32268</link><description>An issue in Tuya Smart camera U6N v.3.2.5 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted packet to the network connection component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46270 | MacPaw The Unarchiver before 4.3.6 contains vulnerability related to missing quarantine attributes for extracted items.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46270</link><description>MacPaw The Unarchiver before 4.3.6 contains vulnerability related to missing quarantine attributes for extracted items.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48683 | Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48683</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 37758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48684 | Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48684</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure and manipulation due to missing authorization. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 37758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34010 | Local privilege escalation due to unquoted search path vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34010</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to unquoted search path vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 37758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34011 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34011</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 37758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34020 | A stack-based buffer overflow was found in the putSDN() function of mail.c in hcode through 2.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34020</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow was found in the putSDN() function of mail.c in hcode through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23995 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Beekeeper Studio 4.1.13 and earlier allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the column name of a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23995</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Beekeeper Studio 4.1.13 and earlier allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the column name of a database table in tabulator-popup-container.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1579 | Insufficient seeding of random number generator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1579</link><description>Incorrect Usage of Seeds in Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Secomea GateManager (Webserver modules) allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects GateManager: before 11.2.624071020.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1969 | Heap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1969</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Secomea GateManager (webserver modules) allows crash of GateManager.This issue affects GateManager: from 9.7 before 11.2.624095033.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27322 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in the R statistical programming language, on any version starting at 1.4.0 up to and not includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27322</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in the R statistical programming language, on any version starting at 1.4.0 up to and not including 4.4.0, enabling a maliciously crafted RDS (R Data Serialization) formatted file or R package to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33585 | WordPress Payment Gateway Based Fees and Discounts for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33585</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Payment Gateway Based Fees and Discounts for WooCommerce.This issue affects Payment Gateway Based Fees and Discounts for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.12.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33586 | WordPress Photo Gallery by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.20 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33586</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Photo Gallery Team Photo Gallery by 10Web.This issue affects Photo Gallery by 10Web: from n/a through 1.8.20.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33587 | WordPress Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33587</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Copy Content Protection Team Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking.This issue affects Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking: from n/a through 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33588 | WordPress basepress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33588</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in codeSavory Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress.This issue affects Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress: from n/a through 2.16.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4307 | SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4307</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank affecting version 1.0.2. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the database through different endpoints (/accounts/activities.php?id=1, /accounts/view-deposit.php?id=1, /accounts/view_cards. php?id=1, /accounts/wire-transfer.php?id=1 and /accounts/wiretransfer-pending.php?id=1, id parameter) and retrieve the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4309 | SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4309</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank affecting version 1.0.2. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the database through different endpoints (/user/transaction.php?id=1, /user/credit-debit_transaction.php?id=1,/user/view_transaction. php?id=1 and  /user/viewloantrans.php?id=1, id parameter) and retrieve the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4310 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HubBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4310</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HubBank affecting version 1.0.2. This vulnerability allows an attacker to send a specially crafted JavaScript payload to registration and profile forms and trigger the payload when any authenticated user loads the page, resulting in a session takeover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:54:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4308 | SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4308</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in HubBank affecting version 1.0.2. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted SQL query to the database through different endpoints (/admin/view_users.php?id=1, /admin/viewloan-trans.php?id=1, /admin/view -deposit.php?id=1, /admin/view-domtrans.php?id=1, /admin/delete_cards.php?id=1, /admin/view_cards.php?id=1 and  /admin/view_users.php?id=1, id parameter) and retrieve the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4306 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in HubBank</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4306</link><description>Critical unrestricted file upload vulnerability in HubBank affecting version 1.0.2. This vulnerability allows a registered user to upload malicious PHP files via upload document fields, resulting in webshell execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4304 | Vulnerability on SWAL platform from GT3 Soluciones</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4304</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting XSS vulnerability has been detected on GT3 Soluciones SWAL. This vulnerability consists in a reflected XSS in the Titular parameter inside Gestion 'Documental &gt; Seguimiento de Expedientes &gt; Alta de Expedientes'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33589 | WordPress KB Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33589</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPOmnia KB Support.This issue affects KB Support: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33590 | WordPress basepress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33590</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in codeSavory Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress.This issue affects Knowledge Base documentation &amp; wiki plugin – BasePress: from n/a through 2.16.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33591 | WordPress Easy Accept Payments for PayPal plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33591</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tips and Tricks HQ Easy Accept Payments.This issue affects Easy Accept Payments: from n/a through 4.9.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33593 | WordPress Smart Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.91 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33593</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RedNao Smart Forms.This issue affects Smart Forms: from n/a through 2.6.91.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33594 | WordPress Leaky Paywall plugin &amp;lt;= 4.20.8 - Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33594</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leaky Paywall.This issue affects Leaky Paywall: from n/a through 4.20.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33595 | WordPress Master Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5.4.1 - Broken Access Control on Duplicate Post vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33595</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jewel Theme Master Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Master Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.5.4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3375 | Broken Access Control  in Havelsan&amp;#x27;s Dialogue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3375</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Havelsan Inc. Dialogue allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Dialogue: from v1.83 before v1.83.1 or v1.84.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33596 | WordPress Five Star Restaurant Reservations plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33596</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Five Star Plugins Five Star Restaurant Reservations.This issue affects Five Star Restaurant Reservations: from n/a through 2.6.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28961 | Dell OpenManage Enterprise, versions 4.0.0 and 4.0.1, contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. A local low privileged mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28961</link><description>Dell OpenManage Enterprise, versions 4.0.0 and 4.0.1, contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. A local low privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to obtain credentials leading to unauthorized access with elevated privileges. This could lead to further attacks, thus Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33558 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Limited Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33558</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33597 | WordPress SSU plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33597</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ProFaceOff SSU.This issue affects SSU: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33635 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.17 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post/Page Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33635</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro: from n/a through 7.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33636 | WordPress WP Page Post Widget Clone plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33636</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mahesh Vora WP Page Post Widget Clone.This issue affects WP Page Post Widget Clone: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33684 | WordPress Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Broken Access Control to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33684</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pdfcrowd Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Save as PDF plugin by Pdfcrowd: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33652 | WordPress Client Dash plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33652</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Real Big Plugins Client Dash.This issue affects Client Dash: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33566 | WordPress OrderConvo plugin &amp;lt;= 12.4 - Unauthenticated API Access to Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33566</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in N-Media OrderConvo allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects OrderConvo: from n/a through 12.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33538 | WordPress Assistant – Every Day Productivity Apps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33538</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Fastline Media LLC Assistant – Every Day Productivity Apps.This issue affects Assistant – Every Day Productivity Apps: from n/a through 1.4.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33575 | WordPress User Meta plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33575</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in User Meta user-meta.This issue affects User Meta: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33637 | WordPress Solid Affiliate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33637</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Solid Plugins Solid Affiliate.This issue affects Solid Affiliate: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33627 | WordPress AGCA – Custom Dashboard &amp;amp; Login Page plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33627</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Cusmin Absolutely Glamorous Custom Admin.This issue affects Absolutely Glamorous Custom Admin: from n/a through 7.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33629 | WordPress Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33629</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Creative Motion Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail).This issue affects Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail): from n/a through 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33634 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.17 - Unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33634</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro: from n/a through 7.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33553 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33553</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33584 | WordPress Video Conferencing with Zoom plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.4 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33584</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Deepen Bajracharya Video Conferencing with Zoom.This issue affects Video Conferencing with Zoom: from n/a through 4.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33641 | WordPress Custom field finder plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33641</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Team Yoast Custom field finder.This issue affects Custom field finder: from n/a through 0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3192 | MailCleaner Admin Interface cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3192</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. Affected is an unknown function of the component Admin Interface. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262308.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:38:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3193 | MailCleaner Admin Endpoints os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3193</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Admin Endpoints. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-262309 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3194 | MailCleaner Log File Endpoint cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3194</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Log File Endpoint. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-262310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3195 | MailCleaner Admin Endpoints path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component Admin Endpoints. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262311.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3196 | MailCleaner SOAP Service getStats os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /mailcleaner.php/getStats of the component SOAP Service. The manipulation leads to os command injection. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262312.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33544 | WordPress WZone plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33544</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AA-Team WZone allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WZone: from n/a through 14.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33546 | WordPress WZone plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.10 - Arbitrary SQL Update Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33546</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AA-Team WZone allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WZone: from n/a through 14.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3191 | MailCleaner Email os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MailCleaner up to 2023.03.14. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Email Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262307.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33542 | WordPress Crelly Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33542</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Fabio Rinaldi Crelly Slider.This issue affects Crelly Slider: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33551 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core allows SQL Injection.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33559 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.5 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in 8theme XStore allows SQL Injection.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1905 | Smart Forms &amp;lt; 2.6.96 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1905</link><description>The Smart Forms  WordPress plugin before 2.6.96 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2505 | GamiPress &amp;lt; 6.8.9 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2505</link><description>The GamiPress  WordPress plugin before 6.8.9's access control mechanism fails to properly restrict access to its settings, permitting Authors to manipulate requests and extend access to lower privileged users, like Subscribers, despite initial settings prohibiting such access. This vulnerability resembles broken access control, enabling unauthorized users to modify critical GamiPress  WordPress plugin before 6.8.9 configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33632 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.17 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33632</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro: from n/a through 7.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33681 | WordPress Regenerate post permalink plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33681</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sandor Kovacs Regenerate post permalink allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Regenerate post permalink: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33686 | Broken Access Control vulnerability affecting multiple WordPress themes by Extend Themes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33686</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Extend Themes Pathway, Extend Themes Hugo WP, Extend Themes Althea WP, Extend Themes Elevate WP, Extend Themes Brite, Extend Themes Colibri WP, Extend Themes Vertice.This issue affects Pathway: from n/a through 1.0.15; Hugo WP: from n/a through 1.0.8; Althea WP: from n/a through 1.0.13; Elevate WP: from n/a through 1.0.15; Brite: from n/a through 1.0.11; Colibri WP: from n/a through 1.0.94; Vertice: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4303 |  ArmorX Android APP - MFA Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4303</link><description>ArmorX Android APP's multi-factor authentication (MFA) for the login function is not properly implemented. Remote attackers who obtain user credentials can bypass MFA, allowing them to successfully log into the APP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4302 | Super 8 livechat SDK - Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4302</link><description>Super 8 Live Chat online customer service platform fails to properly filter user input, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to insert JavaScript code into the chat box. When the message recipient views the message, they become susceptible to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33905 | In Telegram WebK before 2.0.0 (488), a crafted Mini Web App allows XSS via the postMessage web_app_open_link event type.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33905</link><description>In Telegram WebK before 2.0.0 (488), a crafted Mini Web App allows XSS via the postMessage web_app_open_link event type.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33537 | WordPress WP Portfolio theme &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33537</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Theme Horse WP Portfolio allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Portfolio: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52723 | In KDE libksieve before 23.03.80, kmanagesieve/session.cpp places a cleartext password in server logs because a username variable is acciden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52723</link><description>In KDE libksieve before 23.03.80, kmanagesieve/session.cpp places a cleartext password in server logs because a username variable is accidentally given a password value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33539 | WordPress WPZOOM Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.35 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPZOOM WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPZOOM Addons for Elementor (Templates, Widgets): from n/a through 1.1.35.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33540 | WordPress ColorNews theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33540</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGrill ColorNews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ColorNews: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33548 | WordPress WZone plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AA-Team WZone allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WZone: from n/a through 14.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33554 | WordPress XStore Core plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8theme XStore Core allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects XStore Core: from n/a through 5.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33562 | WordPress XStore theme &amp;lt;= 9.3.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33562</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 8theme XStore allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects XStore: from n/a through 9.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33571 | WordPress VOD Infomaniak plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Infomaniak Staff VOD Infomaniak allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects VOD Infomaniak: from n/a through 1.5.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33630 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.26 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.4.26.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33631 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.17 - Authenticated Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro: from n/a through 7.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33904 | In plugins/HookSystem.cpp in Hyprland through 0.39.1 (before 28c8561), through a race condition, a local attacker can cause execution of arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33904</link><description>In plugins/HookSystem.cpp in Hyprland through 0.39.1 (before 28c8561), through a race condition, a local attacker can cause execution of arbitrary assembly code by writing to a predictable temporary file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33633 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.17 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33633</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Piotnet Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor Pro: from n/a through 7.1.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33640 | WordPress Pretty Google Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33640</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LBell Pretty Google Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pretty Google Calendar: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33643 | WordPress Advanced Most Recent Posts Mod plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kailey Lampert Advanced Most Recent Posts Mod allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Most Recent Posts Mod: from n/a through 1.6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33645 | WordPress Easy Set Favicon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Eftakhairul Islam &amp; Sirajus Salayhin Easy Set Favicon allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Easy Set Favicon: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33646 | WordPress Sticky Anything plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Broken Access Control to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33646</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Toast Plugins Sticky Anything allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Sticky Anything: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33648 | WordPress Recencio Book Reviews plugin &amp;lt;= 1.66.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wzy Media Recencio Book Reviews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Recencio Book Reviews: from n/a through 1.66.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33649 | WordPress Opal Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33649</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WpOpal Opal Widgets For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Opal Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4301 | N-Reporter and N-Cloud from N-Partner - Os Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4301</link><description>N-Reporter and N-Cloud, products of the N-Partner, have an OS Command Injection vulnerability. Remote attackers with normal user privilege can execute arbitrary system commands by manipulating user inputs on a specific page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1874 | Command injection via array-ish $command parameter of proc_open()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1874</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.28, 8.2.* before 8.2.18, 8.3.* before 8.3.5, when using proc_open() command with array syntax, due to insufficient escaping, if the arguments of the executed command are controlled by a malicious user, the user can supply arguments that would execute arbitrary commands in Windows shell.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2757 | PHP mb_encode_mimeheader runs endlessly for some inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2757</link><description>In PHP 8.3.* before 8.3.5, function mb_encode_mimeheader() runs endlessly for some inputs that contain long strings of non-space characters followed by a space. This could lead to a potential DoS attack if a hostile user sends data to an application that uses this function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3096 | PHP function password_verify can erroneously return true when argument contains NUL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3096</link><description>In PHP  version 8.1.* before 8.1.28, 8.2.* before 8.2.18, 8.3.* before 8.3.5, if a password stored with password_hash() starts with a null byte (\x00), testing a blank string as the password via password_verify() will incorrectly return true.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2756 | __Host-/__Secure- cookie bypass due to partial CVE-2022-31629 fix</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2756</link><description>Due to an incomplete fix to  CVE-2022-31629 https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-c43m-486j-j32p , network and same-site attackers can set a standard insecure cookie in the victim's browser which is treated as a __Host- or __Secure- cookie by PHP applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4300 | E-WEBInformationCo. FS-EZViewer(Web) - Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4300</link><description>E-WEBInformationCo. FS-EZViewer(Web) exposes sensitive information in the service. A remote attacker can obtain the database configuration file path through the webpage source code without login. Accessing this path allows attacker to obtain the database credential with the highest privilege and database host IP address. With this information, attackers can connect to the database and perform actions such as adding, modifying, or deleting database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4299 | HGiga iSherlock - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4299</link><description>The system configuration interface of HGiga iSherlock (including MailSherlock, SpamSherock, AuditSherlock) fails to filter special characters in certain function parameters, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to exploit this vulnerability for Command Injection attacks, enabling execution of arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4298 | HGiga iSherlock - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4298</link><description>The email search interface of HGiga iSherlock (including MailSherlock, SpamSherock, AuditSherlock) fails to filter special characters in certain function parameters, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to exploit this vulnerability for Command Injection attacks, enabling execution of arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 02:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4297 | HGiga iSherlock - Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4297</link><description>The system configuration interface of HGiga iSherlock (including MailSherlock, SpamSherlock, AuditSherlock) fails to filter special characters in certain function parameters, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to exploit this vulnerability to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 02:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4296 | HGiga iSherlock - Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4296</link><description>The account management interface of HGiga iSherlock (including MailSherlock, SpamSherlock, AuditSherlock) fails to filter special characters in certain function parameters, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to exploit this vulnerability to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33903 | In CARLA through 0.9.15.2, the collision sensor mishandles some situations involving pedestrians or bicycles, in part because the collision ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33903</link><description>In CARLA through 0.9.15.2, the collision sensor mishandles some situations involving pedestrians or bicycles, in part because the collision sensor function is not exposed to the Blueprint library.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 01:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33899 | RARLAB WinRAR before 7.00, on Linux and UNIX platforms, allows attackers to spoof the screen output, or cause a denial of service, via ANSI ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33899</link><description>RARLAB WinRAR before 7.00, on Linux and UNIX platforms, allows attackers to spoof the screen output, or cause a denial of service, via ANSI escape sequences.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 23:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33891 | Delinea Secret Server before 11.7.000001 allows attackers to bypass authentication via the SOAP API in SecretServer/webservices/SSWebService...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33891</link><description>Delinea Secret Server before 11.7.000001 allows attackers to bypass authentication via the SOAP API in SecretServer/webservices/SSWebService.asmx. This is related to a hardcoded key, the use of the integer 2 for the Admin user, and removal of the oauthExpirationId attribute.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 22:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33883 | The ejs (aka Embedded JavaScript templates) package before 3.1.10 for Node.js lacks certain pollution protection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33883</link><description>The ejs (aka Embedded JavaScript templates) package before 3.1.10 for Node.js lacks certain pollution protection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48631 | ext4: fix bug in extents parsing when eh_entries == 0 and eh_depth &amp;gt; 0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48631</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ext4: fix bug in extents parsing when eh_entries == 0 and eh_depth &gt; 0

When walking through an inode extents, the ext4_ext_binsearch_idx() function
assumes that the extent header has been previously validated.  However, there
are no checks that verify that the number of entries (eh-&gt;eh_entries) is
non-zero when depth is &gt; 0.  And this will lead to problems because the
EXT_FIRST_INDEX() and EXT_LAST_INDEX() will return garbage and result in this:

[  135.245946] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  135.247579] kernel BUG at fs/ext4/extents.c:2258!
[  135.249045] invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[  135.250320] CPU: 2 PID: 238 Comm: tmp118 Not tainted 5.19.0-rc8+ #4
[  135.252067] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.15.0-0-g2dd4b9b-rebuilt.opensuse.org 04/01/2014
[  135.255065] RIP: 0010:ext4_ext_map_blocks+0xc20/0xcb0
[  135.256475] Code:
[  135.261433] RSP: 0018:ffffc900005939f8 EFLAGS: 00010246
[  135.262847] RAX: 0000000000000024 RBX: ffffc90000593b70 RCX: 0000000000000023
[  135.264765] RDX: ffff8880038e5f10 RSI: 0000000000000003 RDI: ffff8880046e922c
[  135.266670] RBP: ffff8880046e9348 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffff888002ca580c
[  135.268576] R10: 0000000000002602 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000024
[  135.270477] R13: 0000000000000000 R14: 0000000000000024 R15: 0000000000000000
[  135.272394] FS:  00007fdabdc56740(0000) GS:ffff88807dd00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  135.274510] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  135.276075] CR2: 00007ffc26bd4f00 CR3: 0000000006261004 CR4: 0000000000170ea0
[  135.277952] Call Trace:
[  135.278635]  
[  135.279247]  ? preempt_count_add+0x6d/0xa0
[  135.280358]  ? percpu_counter_add_batch+0x55/0xb0
[  135.281612]  ? _raw_read_unlock+0x18/0x30
[  135.282704]  ext4_map_blocks+0x294/0x5a0
[  135.283745]  ? xa_load+0x6f/0xa0
[  135.284562]  ext4_mpage_readpages+0x3d6/0x770
[  135.285646]  read_pages+0x67/0x1d0
[  135.286492]  ? folio_add_lru+0x51/0x80
[  135.287441]  page_cache_ra_unbounded+0x124/0x170
[  135.288510]  filemap_get_pages+0x23d/0x5a0
[  135.289457]  ? path_openat+0xa72/0xdd0
[  135.290332]  filemap_read+0xbf/0x300
[  135.291158]  ? _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x17/0x40
[  135.292192]  new_sync_read+0x103/0x170
[  135.293014]  vfs_read+0x15d/0x180
[  135.293745]  ksys_read+0xa1/0xe0
[  135.294461]  do_syscall_64+0x3c/0x80
[  135.295284]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x46/0xb0

This patch simply adds an extra check in __ext4_ext_check(), verifying that
eh_entries is not 0 when eh_depth is &gt; 0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48632 | i2c: mlxbf: prevent stack overflow in mlxbf_i2c_smbus_start_transaction()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48632</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: mlxbf: prevent stack overflow in mlxbf_i2c_smbus_start_transaction()

memcpy() is called in a loop while 'operation-&gt;length' upper bound
is not checked and 'data_idx' also increments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48633 | drm/gma500: Fix WARN_ON(lock-&amp;gt;magic != lock) error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48633</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/gma500: Fix WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock) error

psb_gem_unpin() calls dma_resv_lock() but the underlying ww_mutex
gets destroyed by drm_gem_object_release() move the
drm_gem_object_release() call in psb_gem_free_object() to after
the unpin to fix the below warning:

[   79.693962] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   79.693992] DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
[   79.694015] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 240 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:582 __ww_mutex_lock.constprop.0+0x569/0xfb0
[   79.694052] Modules linked in: rfcomm snd_seq_dummy snd_hrtimer qrtr bnep ath9k ath9k_common ath9k_hw snd_hda_codec_realtek snd_hda_codec_generic ledtrig_audio snd_hda_codec_hdmi snd_hda_intel ath3k snd_intel_dspcfg mac80211 snd_intel_sdw_acpi btusb snd_hda_codec btrtl btbcm btintel btmtk bluetooth at24 snd_hda_core snd_hwdep uvcvideo snd_seq libarc4 videobuf2_vmalloc ath videobuf2_memops videobuf2_v4l2 videobuf2_common snd_seq_device videodev acer_wmi intel_powerclamp coretemp mc snd_pcm joydev sparse_keymap ecdh_generic pcspkr wmi_bmof cfg80211 i2c_i801 i2c_smbus snd_timer snd r8169 rfkill lpc_ich soundcore acpi_cpufreq zram rtsx_pci_sdmmc mmc_core serio_raw rtsx_pci gma500_gfx(E) video wmi ip6_tables ip_tables i2c_dev fuse
[   79.694436] CPU: 0 PID: 240 Comm: plymouthd Tainted: G        W   E      6.0.0-rc3+ #490
[   79.694457] Hardware name: Packard Bell dot s/SJE01_CT, BIOS V1.10 07/23/2013
[   79.694469] RIP: 0010:__ww_mutex_lock.constprop.0+0x569/0xfb0
[   79.694496] Code: ff 85 c0 0f 84 15 fb ff ff 8b 05 ca 3c 11 01 85 c0 0f 85 07 fb ff ff 48 c7 c6 30 cb 84 aa 48 c7 c7 a3 e1 82 aa e8 ac 29 f8 ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 ed fa ff ff e8 5b 83 8a ff 85 c0 74 10 44 8b 0d 98 3c 11
[   79.694513] RSP: 0018:ffffad1dc048bbe0 EFLAGS: 00010282
[   79.694623] RAX: 0000000000000028 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 0000000000000000
[   79.694636] RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: ffffffffaa8b0ffc RDI: 00000000ffffffff
[   79.694650] RBP: ffffad1dc048bc80 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: ffffad1dc048ba90
[   79.694662] R10: 0000000000000003 R11: ffffffffaad62fe8 R12: ffff9ff302103138
[   79.694675] R13: ffff9ff306ec8000 R14: ffff9ff307779078 R15: ffff9ff3014c0270
[   79.694690] FS:  00007ff1cccf1740(0000) GS:ffff9ff3bc200000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[   79.694705] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[   79.694719] CR2: 0000559ecbcb4420 CR3: 0000000013210000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
[   79.694734] Call Trace:
[   79.694749]  
[   79.694761]  ? __schedule+0x47f/0x1670
[   79.694796]  ? psb_gem_unpin+0x27/0x1a0 [gma500_gfx]
[   79.694830]  ? lock_is_held_type+0xe3/0x140
[   79.694864]  ? ww_mutex_lock+0x38/0xa0
[   79.694885]  ? __cond_resched+0x1c/0x30
[   79.694902]  ww_mutex_lock+0x38/0xa0
[   79.694925]  psb_gem_unpin+0x27/0x1a0 [gma500_gfx]
[   79.694964]  psb_gem_unpin+0x199/0x1a0 [gma500_gfx]
[   79.694996]  drm_gem_object_release_handle+0x50/0x60
[   79.695020]  ? drm_gem_object_handle_put_unlocked+0xf0/0xf0
[   79.695042]  idr_for_each+0x4b/0xb0
[   79.695066]  ? _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x30/0x60
[   79.695095]  drm_gem_release+0x1c/0x30
[   79.695118]  drm_file_free.part.0+0x1ea/0x260
[   79.695150]  drm_release+0x6a/0x120
[   79.695175]  __fput+0x9f/0x260
[   79.695203]  task_work_run+0x59/0xa0
[   79.695227]  do_exit+0x387/0xbe0
[   79.695250]  ? seqcount_lockdep_reader_access.constprop.0+0x82/0x90
[   79.695275]  ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x7d/0x100
[   79.695304]  do_group_exit+0x33/0xb0
[   79.695331]  __x64_sys_exit_group+0x14/0x20
[   79.695353]  do_syscall_64+0x58/0x80
[   79.695376]  ? up_read+0x17/0x20
[   79.695401]  ? lock_is_held_type+0xe3/0x140
[   79.695429]  ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x22/0x30
[   79.695450]  ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x7d/0x100
[   79.695473]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd
[   79.695493] RIP: 0033:0x7ff1ccefe3f1
[   79.695516] Code: Unable to access opcode bytes at RIP 0x7ff1ccefe3c7.
[   79.695607] RSP: 002b:00007ffed4413378 EFLAGS: 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48634 | drm/gma500: Fix BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48634</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/gma500: Fix BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context errors

gma_crtc_page_flip() was holding the event_lock spinlock while calling
crtc_funcs-&gt;mode_set_base() which takes ww_mutex.

The only reason to hold event_lock is to clear gma_crtc-&gt;page_flip_event
on mode_set_base() errors.

Instead unlock it after setting gma_crtc-&gt;page_flip_event and on
errors re-take the lock and clear gma_crtc-&gt;page_flip_event it
it is still set.

This fixes the following WARN/stacktrace:

[  512.122953] BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at kernel/locking/mutex.c:870
[  512.123004] in_atomic(): 1, irqs_disabled(): 1, non_block: 0, pid: 1253, name: gnome-shell
[  512.123031] preempt_count: 1, expected: 0
[  512.123048] RCU nest depth: 0, expected: 0
[  512.123066] INFO: lockdep is turned off.
[  512.123080] irq event stamp: 0
[  512.123094] hardirqs last  enabled at (0): [&lt;0000000000000000&gt;] 0x0
[  512.123134] hardirqs last disabled at (0): [] copy_process+0x9fc/0x1de0
[  512.123176] softirqs last  enabled at (0): [] copy_process+0x9fc/0x1de0
[  512.123207] softirqs last disabled at (0): [&lt;0000000000000000&gt;] 0x0
[  512.123233] Preemption disabled at:
[  512.123241] [&lt;0000000000000000&gt;] 0x0
[  512.123275] CPU: 3 PID: 1253 Comm: gnome-shell Tainted: G        W         5.19.0+ #1
[  512.123304] Hardware name: Packard Bell dot s/SJE01_CT, BIOS V1.10 07/23/2013
[  512.123323] Call Trace:
[  512.123346]  
[  512.123370]  dump_stack_lvl+0x5b/0x77
[  512.123412]  __might_resched.cold+0xff/0x13a
[  512.123458]  ww_mutex_lock+0x1e/0xa0
[  512.123495]  psb_gem_pin+0x2c/0x150 [gma500_gfx]
[  512.123601]  gma_pipe_set_base+0x76/0x240 [gma500_gfx]
[  512.123708]  gma_crtc_page_flip+0x95/0x130 [gma500_gfx]
[  512.123808]  drm_mode_page_flip_ioctl+0x57d/0x5d0
[  512.123897]  ? drm_mode_cursor2_ioctl+0x10/0x10
[  512.123936]  drm_ioctl_kernel+0xa1/0x150
[  512.123984]  drm_ioctl+0x21f/0x420
[  512.124025]  ? drm_mode_cursor2_ioctl+0x10/0x10
[  512.124070]  ? rcu_read_lock_bh_held+0xb/0x60
[  512.124104]  ? lock_release+0x1ef/0x2d0
[  512.124161]  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x8d/0xd0
[  512.124203]  do_syscall_64+0x58/0x80
[  512.124239]  ? do_syscall_64+0x67/0x80
[  512.124267]  ? trace_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x55/0xe0
[  512.124300]  ? do_syscall_64+0x67/0x80
[  512.124340]  ? rcu_read_lock_sched_held+0x10/0x80
[  512.124377]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd
[  512.124411] RIP: 0033:0x7fcc4a70740f
[  512.124442] Code: 00 48 89 44 24 18 31 c0 48 8d 44 24 60 c7 04 24 10 00 00 00 48 89 44 24 08 48 8d 44 24 20 48 89 44 24 10 b8 10 00 00 00 0f 05 &lt;89&gt; c2 3d 00 f0 ff ff 77 18 48 8b 44 24 18 64 48 2b 04 25 28 00 00
[  512.124470] RSP: 002b:00007ffda73f5390 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000010
[  512.124503] RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 000055cc9e474500 RCX: 00007fcc4a70740f
[  512.124524] RDX: 00007ffda73f5420 RSI: 00000000c01864b0 RDI: 0000000000000009
[  512.124544] RBP: 00007ffda73f5420 R08: 000055cc9c0b0cb0 R09: 0000000000000034
[  512.124564] R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00000000c01864b0
[  512.124584] R13: 0000000000000009 R14: 000055cc9df484d0 R15: 000055cc9af5d0c0
[  512.124647]</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48635 | fsdax: Fix infinite loop in dax_iomap_rw()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48635</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fsdax: Fix infinite loop in dax_iomap_rw()

I got an infinite loop and a WARNING report when executing a tail command
in virtiofs.

  WARNING: CPU: 10 PID: 964 at fs/iomap/iter.c:34 iomap_iter+0x3a2/0x3d0
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 10 PID: 964 Comm: tail Not tainted 5.19.0-rc7
  Call Trace:
  
  dax_iomap_rw+0xea/0x620
  ? __this_cpu_preempt_check+0x13/0x20
  fuse_dax_read_iter+0x47/0x80
  fuse_file_read_iter+0xae/0xd0
  new_sync_read+0xfe/0x180
  ? 0xffffffff81000000
  vfs_read+0x14d/0x1a0
  ksys_read+0x6d/0xf0
  __x64_sys_read+0x1a/0x20
  do_syscall_64+0x3b/0x90
  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

The tail command will call read() with a count of 0. In this case,
iomap_iter() will report this WARNING, and always return 1 which casuing
the infinite loop in dax_iomap_rw().

Fixing by checking count whether is 0 in dax_iomap_rw().</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48636 | s390/dasd: fix Oops in dasd_alias_get_start_dev due to missing pavgroup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48636</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/dasd: fix Oops in dasd_alias_get_start_dev due to missing pavgroup

Fix Oops in dasd_alias_get_start_dev() function caused by the pavgroup
pointer being NULL.

The pavgroup pointer is checked on the entrance of the function but
without the lcu-&gt;lock being held. Therefore there is a race window
between dasd_alias_get_start_dev() and _lcu_update() which sets
pavgroup to NULL with the lcu-&gt;lock held.

Fix by checking the pavgroup pointer with lcu-&gt;lock held.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48637 | bnxt: prevent skb UAF after handing over to PTP worker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48637</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bnxt: prevent skb UAF after handing over to PTP worker

When reading the timestamp is required bnxt_tx_int() hands
over the ownership of the completed skb to the PTP worker.
The skb should not be used afterwards, as the worker may
run before the rest of our code and free the skb, leading
to a use-after-free.

Since dev_kfree_skb_any() accepts NULL make the loss of
ownership more obvious and set skb to NULL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48638 | cgroup: cgroup_get_from_id() must check the looked-up kn is a directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48638</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cgroup: cgroup_get_from_id() must check the looked-up kn is a directory

cgroup has to be one kernfs dir, otherwise kernel panic is caused,
especially cgroup id is provide from userspace.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48639 | net: sched: fix possible refcount leak in tc_new_tfilter()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48639</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: fix possible refcount leak in tc_new_tfilter()

tfilter_put need to be called to put the refount got by tp-&gt;ops-&gt;get to
avoid possible refcount leak when chain-&gt;tmplt_ops != NULL and
chain-&gt;tmplt_ops != tp-&gt;ops.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48640 | bonding: fix NULL deref in bond_rr_gen_slave_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48640</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bonding: fix NULL deref in bond_rr_gen_slave_id

Fix a NULL dereference of the struct bonding.rr_tx_counter member because
if a bond is initially created with an initial mode != zero (Round Robin)
the memory required for the counter is never created and when the mode is
changed there is never any attempt to verify the memory is allocated upon
switching modes.

This causes the following Oops on an aarch64 machine:
    [  334.686773] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address ffff2c91ac905000
    [  334.694703] Mem abort info:
    [  334.697486]   ESR = 0x0000000096000004
    [  334.701234]   EC = 0x25: DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
    [  334.706536]   SET = 0, FnV = 0
    [  334.709579]   EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
    [  334.712719]   FSC = 0x04: level 0 translation fault
    [  334.717586] Data abort info:
    [  334.720454]   ISV = 0, ISS = 0x00000004
    [  334.724288]   CM = 0, WnR = 0
    [  334.727244] swapper pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp=000008044d662000
    [  334.733944] [ffff2c91ac905000] pgd=0000000000000000, p4d=0000000000000000
    [  334.740734] Internal error: Oops: 96000004 [#1] SMP
    [  334.745602] Modules linked in: bonding tls veth rfkill sunrpc arm_spe_pmu vfat fat acpi_ipmi ipmi_ssif ixgbe igb i40e mdio ipmi_devintf ipmi_msghandler arm_cmn arm_dsu_pmu cppc_cpufreq acpi_tad fuse zram crct10dif_ce ast ghash_ce sbsa_gwdt nvme drm_vram_helper drm_ttm_helper nvme_core ttm xgene_hwmon
    [  334.772217] CPU: 7 PID: 2214 Comm: ping Not tainted 6.0.0-rc4-00133-g64ae13ed4784 #4
    [  334.779950] Hardware name: GIGABYTE R272-P31-00/MP32-AR1-00, BIOS F18v (SCP: 1.08.20211002) 12/01/2021
    [  334.789244] pstate: 60400009 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
    [  334.796196] pc : bond_rr_gen_slave_id+0x40/0x124 [bonding]
    [  334.801691] lr : bond_xmit_roundrobin_slave_get+0x38/0xdc [bonding]
    [  334.807962] sp : ffff8000221733e0
    [  334.811265] x29: ffff8000221733e0 x28: ffffdbac8572d198 x27: ffff80002217357c
    [  334.818392] x26: 000000000000002a x25: ffffdbacb33ee000 x24: ffff07ff980fa000
    [  334.825519] x23: ffffdbacb2e398ba x22: ffff07ff98102000 x21: ffff07ff981029c0
    [  334.832646] x20: 0000000000000001 x19: ffff07ff981029c0 x18: 0000000000000014
    [  334.839773] x17: 0000000000000000 x16: ffffdbacb1004364 x15: 0000aaaabe2f5a62
    [  334.846899] x14: ffff07ff8e55d968 x13: ffff07ff8e55db30 x12: 0000000000000000
    [  334.854026] x11: ffffdbacb21532e8 x10: 0000000000000001 x9 : ffffdbac857178ec
    [  334.861153] x8 : ffff07ff9f6e5a28 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 000000007c2b3742
    [  334.868279] x5 : ffff2c91ac905000 x4 : ffff2c91ac905000 x3 : ffff07ff9f554400
    [  334.875406] x2 : ffff2c91ac905000 x1 : 0000000000000001 x0 : ffff07ff981029c0
    [  334.882532] Call trace:
    [  334.884967]  bond_rr_gen_slave_id+0x40/0x124 [bonding]
    [  334.890109]  bond_xmit_roundrobin_slave_get+0x38/0xdc [bonding]
    [  334.896033]  __bond_start_xmit+0x128/0x3a0 [bonding]
    [  334.901001]  bond_start_xmit+0x54/0xb0 [bonding]
    [  334.905622]  dev_hard_start_xmit+0xb4/0x220
    [  334.909798]  __dev_queue_xmit+0x1a0/0x720
    [  334.913799]  arp_xmit+0x3c/0xbc
    [  334.916932]  arp_send_dst+0x98/0xd0
    [  334.920410]  arp_solicit+0xe8/0x230
    [  334.923888]  neigh_probe+0x60/0xb0
    [  334.927279]  __neigh_event_send+0x3b0/0x470
    [  334.931453]  neigh_resolve_output+0x70/0x90
    [  334.935626]  ip_finish_output2+0x158/0x514
    [  334.939714]  __ip_finish_output+0xac/0x1a4
    [  334.943800]  ip_finish_output+0x40/0xfc
    [  334.947626]  ip_output+0xf8/0x1a4
    [  334.950931]  ip_send_skb+0x5c/0x100
    [  334.954410]  ip_push_pending_frames+0x3c/0x60
    [  334.958758]  raw_sendmsg+0x458/0x6d0
    [  334.962325]  inet_sendmsg+0x50/0x80
    [  334.965805]  sock_sendmsg+0x60/0x6c
    [  334.969286]  __sys_sendto+0xc8/0x134
    [  334.972853]  __arm64_sys_sendto+0x34/0x4c
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48641 | netfilter: ebtables: fix memory leak when blob is malformed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48641</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ebtables: fix memory leak when blob is malformed

The bug fix was incomplete, it "replaced" crash with a memory leak.
The old code had an assignment to "ret" embedded into the conditional,
restore this.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48642 | netfilter: nf_tables: fix percpu memory leak at nf_tables_addchain()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48642</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: fix percpu memory leak at nf_tables_addchain()

It seems to me that percpu memory for chain stats started leaking since
commit 3bc158f8d0330f0a ("netfilter: nf_tables: map basechain priority to
hardware priority") when nft_chain_offload_priority() returned an error.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48643 | netfilter: nf_tables: fix nft_counters_enabled underflow at nf_tables_addchain()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48643</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: fix nft_counters_enabled underflow at nf_tables_addchain()

syzbot is reporting underflow of nft_counters_enabled counter at
nf_tables_addchain() [1], for commit 43eb8949cfdffa76 ("netfilter:
nf_tables: do not leave chain stats enabled on error") missed that
nf_tables_chain_destroy() after nft_basechain_init() in the error path of
nf_tables_addchain() decrements the counter because nft_basechain_init()
makes nft_is_base_chain() return true by setting NFT_CHAIN_BASE flag.

Increment the counter immediately after returning from
nft_basechain_init().</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48644 | net/sched: taprio: avoid disabling offload when it was never enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48644</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: taprio: avoid disabling offload when it was never enabled

In an incredibly strange API design decision, qdisc-&gt;destroy() gets
called even if qdisc-&gt;init() never succeeded, not exclusively since
commit 87b60cfacf9f ("net_sched: fix error recovery at qdisc creation"),
but apparently also earlier (in the case of qdisc_create_dflt()).

The taprio qdisc does not fully acknowledge this when it attempts full
offload, because it starts off with q-&gt;flags = TAPRIO_FLAGS_INVALID in
taprio_init(), then it replaces q-&gt;flags with TCA_TAPRIO_ATTR_FLAGS
parsed from netlink (in taprio_change(), tail called from taprio_init()).

But in taprio_destroy(), we call taprio_disable_offload(), and this
determines what to do based on FULL_OFFLOAD_IS_ENABLED(q-&gt;flags).

But looking at the implementation of FULL_OFFLOAD_IS_ENABLED()
(a bitwise check of bit 1 in q-&gt;flags), it is invalid to call this macro
on q-&gt;flags when it contains TAPRIO_FLAGS_INVALID, because that is set
to U32_MAX, and therefore FULL_OFFLOAD_IS_ENABLED() will return true on
an invalid set of flags.

As a result, it is possible to crash the kernel if user space forces an
error between setting q-&gt;flags = TAPRIO_FLAGS_INVALID, and the calling
of taprio_enable_offload(). This is because drivers do not expect the
offload to be disabled when it was never enabled.

The error that we force here is to attach taprio as a non-root qdisc,
but instead as child of an mqprio root qdisc:

$ tc qdisc add dev swp0 root handle 1: \
	mqprio num_tc 8 map 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 \
	queues 1@0 1@1 1@2 1@3 1@4 1@5 1@6 1@7 hw 0
$ tc qdisc replace dev swp0 parent 1:1 \
	taprio num_tc 8 map 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 \
	queues 1@0 1@1 1@2 1@3 1@4 1@5 1@6 1@7 base-time 0 \
	sched-entry S 0x7f 990000 sched-entry S 0x80 100000 \
	flags 0x0 clockid CLOCK_TAI
Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address fffffffffffffff8
[fffffffffffffff8] pgd=0000000000000000, p4d=0000000000000000
Internal error: Oops: 96000004 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
Call trace:
 taprio_dump+0x27c/0x310
 vsc9959_port_setup_tc+0x1f4/0x460
 felix_port_setup_tc+0x24/0x3c
 dsa_slave_setup_tc+0x54/0x27c
 taprio_disable_offload.isra.0+0x58/0xe0
 taprio_destroy+0x80/0x104
 qdisc_create+0x240/0x470
 tc_modify_qdisc+0x1fc/0x6b0
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x12c/0x390
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x5c/0x130
 rtnetlink_rcv+0x1c/0x2c

Fix this by keeping track of the operations we made, and undo the
offload only if we actually did it.

I've added "bool offloaded" inside a 4 byte hole between "int clockid"
and "atomic64_t picos_per_byte". Now the first cache line looks like
below:

$ pahole -C taprio_sched net/sched/sch_taprio.o
struct taprio_sched {
        struct Qdisc * *           qdiscs;               /*     0     8 */
        struct Qdisc *             root;                 /*     8     8 */
        u32                        flags;                /*    16     4 */
        enum tk_offsets            tk_offset;            /*    20     4 */
        int                        clockid;              /*    24     4 */
        bool                       offloaded;            /*    28     1 */

        /* XXX 3 bytes hole, try to pack */

        atomic64_t                 picos_per_byte;       /*    32     0 */

        /* XXX 8 bytes hole, try to pack */

        spinlock_t                 current_entry_lock;   /*    40     0 */

        /* XXX 8 bytes hole, try to pack */

        struct sched_entry *       current_entry;        /*    48     8 */
        struct sched_gate_list *   oper_sched;           /*    56     8 */
        /* --- cacheline 1 boundary (64 bytes) --- */</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48645 | net: enetc: deny offload of tc-based TSN features on VF interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48645</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: enetc: deny offload of tc-based TSN features on VF interfaces

TSN features on the ENETC (taprio, cbs, gate, police) are configured
through a mix of command BD ring messages and port registers:
enetc_port_rd(), enetc_port_wr().

Port registers are a region of the ENETC memory map which are only
accessible from the PCIe Physical Function. They are not accessible from
the Virtual Functions.

Moreover, attempting to access these registers crashes the kernel:

$ echo 1 &gt; /sys/bus/pci/devices/0000\:00\:00.0/sriov_numvfs
pci 0000:00:01.0: [1957:ef00] type 00 class 0x020001
fsl_enetc_vf 0000:00:01.0: Adding to iommu group 15
fsl_enetc_vf 0000:00:01.0: enabling device (0000 -&gt; 0002)
fsl_enetc_vf 0000:00:01.0 eno0vf0: renamed from eth0
$ tc qdisc replace dev eno0vf0 root taprio num_tc 8 map 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 \
	queues 1@0 1@1 1@2 1@3 1@4 1@5 1@6 1@7 base-time 0 \
	sched-entry S 0x7f 900000 sched-entry S 0x80 100000 flags 0x2
Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address ffff800009551a08
Internal error: Oops: 96000007 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
pc : enetc_setup_tc_taprio+0x170/0x47c
lr : enetc_setup_tc_taprio+0x16c/0x47c
Call trace:
 enetc_setup_tc_taprio+0x170/0x47c
 enetc_setup_tc+0x38/0x2dc
 taprio_change+0x43c/0x970
 taprio_init+0x188/0x1e0
 qdisc_create+0x114/0x470
 tc_modify_qdisc+0x1fc/0x6c0
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x12c/0x390

Split enetc_setup_tc() into separate functions for the PF and for the
VF drivers. Also remove enetc_qos.o from being included into
enetc-vf.ko, since it serves absolutely no purpose there.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48646 | sfc/siena: fix null pointer dereference in efx_hard_start_xmit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48646</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sfc/siena: fix null pointer dereference in efx_hard_start_xmit

Like in previous patch for sfc, prevent potential (but unlikely) NULL
pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48647 | sfc: fix TX channel offset when using legacy interrupts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48647</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sfc: fix TX channel offset when using legacy interrupts

In legacy interrupt mode the tx_channel_offset was hardcoded to 1, but
that's not correct if efx_sepparate_tx_channels is false. In that case,
the offset is 0 because the tx queues are in the single existing channel
at index 0, together with the rx queue.

Without this fix, as soon as you try to send any traffic, it tries to
get the tx queues from an uninitialized channel getting these errors:
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 0 at drivers/net/ethernet/sfc/tx.c:540 efx_hard_start_xmit+0x12e/0x170 [sfc]
  [...]
  RIP: 0010:efx_hard_start_xmit+0x12e/0x170 [sfc]
  [...]
  Call Trace:
   
   dev_hard_start_xmit+0xd7/0x230
   sch_direct_xmit+0x9f/0x360
   __dev_queue_xmit+0x890/0xa40
  [...]
  BUG: unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at 0000000000000020
  [...]
  RIP: 0010:efx_hard_start_xmit+0x153/0x170 [sfc]
  [...]
  Call Trace:
   
   dev_hard_start_xmit+0xd7/0x230
   sch_direct_xmit+0x9f/0x360
   __dev_queue_xmit+0x890/0xa40
  [...]</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48648 | sfc: fix null pointer dereference in efx_hard_start_xmit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48648</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sfc: fix null pointer dereference in efx_hard_start_xmit

Trying to get the channel from the tx_queue variable here is wrong
because we can only be here if tx_queue is NULL, so we shouldn't
dereference it. As the above comment in the code says, this is very
unlikely to happen, but it's wrong anyway so let's fix it.

I hit this issue because of a different bug that caused tx_queue to be
NULL. If that happens, this is the error message that we get here:
  BUG: unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at 0000000000000020
  [...]
  RIP: 0010:efx_hard_start_xmit+0x153/0x170 [sfc]</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48649 | mm/slab_common: fix possible double free of kmem_cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48649</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/slab_common: fix possible double free of kmem_cache

When doing slub_debug test, kfence's 'test_memcache_typesafe_by_rcu'
kunit test case cause a use-after-free error:

  BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in kobject_del+0x14/0x30
  Read of size 8 at addr ffff888007679090 by task kunit_try_catch/261

  CPU: 1 PID: 261 Comm: kunit_try_catch Tainted: G    B            N 6.0.0-rc5-next-20220916 #17
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
  Call Trace:
   
   dump_stack_lvl+0x34/0x48
   print_address_description.constprop.0+0x87/0x2a5
   print_report+0x103/0x1ed
   kasan_report+0xb7/0x140
   kobject_del+0x14/0x30
   kmem_cache_destroy+0x130/0x170
   test_exit+0x1a/0x30
   kunit_try_run_case+0xad/0xc0
   kunit_generic_run_threadfn_adapter+0x26/0x50
   kthread+0x17b/0x1b0
   

The cause is inside kmem_cache_destroy():

kmem_cache_destroy
    acquire lock/mutex
    shutdown_cache
        schedule_work(kmem_cache_release) (if RCU flag set)
    release lock/mutex
    kmem_cache_release (if RCU flag not set)

In some certain timing, the scheduled work could be run before
the next RCU flag checking, which can then get a wrong value
and lead to double kmem_cache_release().

Fix it by caching the RCU flag inside protected area, just like 'refcnt'</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48650 | scsi: qla2xxx: Fix memory leak in __qlt_24xx_handle_abts()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48650</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: qla2xxx: Fix memory leak in __qlt_24xx_handle_abts()

Commit 8f394da36a36 ("scsi: qla2xxx: Drop TARGET_SCF_LOOKUP_LUN_FROM_TAG")
made the __qlt_24xx_handle_abts() function return early if
tcm_qla2xxx_find_cmd_by_tag() didn't find a command, but it missed to clean
up the allocated memory for the management command.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48651 | ipvlan: Fix out-of-bound bugs caused by unset skb-&amp;gt;mac_header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48651</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipvlan: Fix out-of-bound bugs caused by unset skb-&gt;mac_header

If an AF_PACKET socket is used to send packets through ipvlan and the
default xmit function of the AF_PACKET socket is changed from
dev_queue_xmit() to packet_direct_xmit() via setsockopt() with the option
name of PACKET_QDISC_BYPASS, the skb-&gt;mac_header may not be reset and
remains as the initial value of 65535, this may trigger slab-out-of-bounds
bugs as following:

=================================================================
UG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in ipvlan_xmit_mode_l2+0xdb/0x330 [ipvlan]
PU: 2 PID: 1768 Comm: raw_send Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.0.0-rc4+ #6
ardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.14.0-1.fc33
all Trace:
print_address_description.constprop.0+0x1d/0x160
print_report.cold+0x4f/0x112
kasan_report+0xa3/0x130
ipvlan_xmit_mode_l2+0xdb/0x330 [ipvlan]
ipvlan_start_xmit+0x29/0xa0 [ipvlan]
__dev_direct_xmit+0x2e2/0x380
packet_direct_xmit+0x22/0x60
packet_snd+0x7c9/0xc40
sock_sendmsg+0x9a/0xa0
__sys_sendto+0x18a/0x230
__x64_sys_sendto+0x74/0x90
do_syscall_64+0x3b/0x90
entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

The root cause is:
  1. packet_snd() only reset skb-&gt;mac_header when sock-&gt;type is SOCK_RAW
     and skb-&gt;protocol is not specified as in packet_parse_headers()

  2. packet_direct_xmit() doesn't reset skb-&gt;mac_header as dev_queue_xmit()

In this case, skb-&gt;mac_header is 65535 when ipvlan_xmit_mode_l2() is
called. So when ipvlan_xmit_mode_l2() gets mac header with eth_hdr() which
use "skb-&gt;head + skb-&gt;mac_header", out-of-bound access occurs.

This patch replaces eth_hdr() with skb_eth_hdr() in ipvlan_xmit_mode_l2()
and reset mac header in multicast to solve this out-of-bound bug.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48652 | ice: Fix crash by keep old cfg when update TCs more than queues</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48652</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: Fix crash by keep old cfg when update TCs more than queues

There are problems if allocated queues less than Traffic Classes.

Commit a632b2a4c920 ("ice: ethtool: Prohibit improper channel config
for DCB") already disallow setting less queues than TCs.

Another case is if we first set less queues, and later update more TCs
config due to LLDP, ice_vsi_cfg_tc() will failed but left dirty
num_txq/rxq and tc_cfg in vsi, that will cause invalid pointer access.

[   95.968089] ice 0000:3b:00.1: More TCs defined than queues/rings allocated.
[   95.968092] ice 0000:3b:00.1: Trying to use more Rx queues (8), than were allocated (1)!
[   95.968093] ice 0000:3b:00.1: Failed to config TC for VSI index: 0
[   95.969621] general protection fault: 0000 [#1] SMP NOPTI
[   95.969705] CPU: 1 PID: 58405 Comm: lldpad Kdump: loaded Tainted: G     U  W  O     --------- -t - 4.18.0 #1
[   95.969867] Hardware name: O.E.M/BC11SPSCB10, BIOS 8.23 12/30/2021
[   95.969992] RIP: 0010:devm_kmalloc+0xa/0x60
[   95.970052] Code: 5c ff ff ff 31 c0 5b 5d 41 5c c3 b8 f4 ff ff ff eb f4 0f 1f 40 00 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 44 00 00 48 89 f8 89 d1 &lt;8b&gt; 97 60 02 00 00 48 8d 7e 18 48 39 f7 72 3f 55 89 ce 53 48 8b 4c
[   95.970344] RSP: 0018:ffffc9003f553888 EFLAGS: 00010206
[   95.970425] RAX: dead000000000200 RBX: ffffea003c425b00 RCX: 00000000006080c0
[   95.970536] RDX: 00000000006080c0 RSI: 0000000000000200 RDI: dead000000000200
[   95.970648] RBP: dead000000000200 R08: 00000000000463c0 R09: ffff888ffa900000
[   95.970760] R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000002 R12: ffff888ff6b40100
[   95.970870] R13: ffff888ff6a55018 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffff888ff6a55460
[   95.970981] FS:  00007f51b7d24700(0000) GS:ffff88903ee80000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[   95.971108] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[   95.971197] CR2: 00007fac5410d710 CR3: 0000000f2c1de002 CR4: 00000000007606e0
[   95.971309] DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
[   95.971419] DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
[   95.971530] PKRU: 55555554
[   95.971573] Call Trace:
[   95.971622]  ice_setup_rx_ring+0x39/0x110 [ice]
[   95.971695]  ice_vsi_setup_rx_rings+0x54/0x90 [ice]
[   95.971774]  ice_vsi_open+0x25/0x120 [ice]
[   95.971843]  ice_open_internal+0xb8/0x1f0 [ice]
[   95.971919]  ice_ena_vsi+0x4f/0xd0 [ice]
[   95.971987]  ice_dcb_ena_dis_vsi.constprop.5+0x29/0x90 [ice]
[   95.972082]  ice_pf_dcb_cfg+0x29a/0x380 [ice]
[   95.972154]  ice_dcbnl_setets+0x174/0x1b0 [ice]
[   95.972220]  dcbnl_ieee_set+0x89/0x230
[   95.972279]  ? dcbnl_ieee_del+0x150/0x150
[   95.972341]  dcb_doit+0x124/0x1b0
[   95.972392]  rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x243/0x2f0
[   95.972457]  ? dcb_doit+0x14d/0x1b0
[   95.972510]  ? __kmalloc_node_track_caller+0x1d3/0x280
[   95.972591]  ? rtnl_calcit.isra.31+0x100/0x100
[   95.972661]  netlink_rcv_skb+0xcf/0xf0
[   95.972720]  netlink_unicast+0x16d/0x220
[   95.972781]  netlink_sendmsg+0x2ba/0x3a0
[   95.975891]  sock_sendmsg+0x4c/0x50
[   95.979032]  ___sys_sendmsg+0x2e4/0x300
[   95.982147]  ? kmem_cache_alloc+0x13e/0x190
[   95.985242]  ? __wake_up_common_lock+0x79/0x90
[   95.988338]  ? __check_object_size+0xac/0x1b0
[   95.991440]  ? _copy_to_user+0x22/0x30
[   95.994539]  ? move_addr_to_user+0xbb/0xd0
[   95.997619]  ? __sys_sendmsg+0x53/0x80
[   96.000664]  __sys_sendmsg+0x53/0x80
[   96.003747]  do_syscall_64+0x5b/0x1d0
[   96.006862]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x65/0xca

Only update num_txq/rxq when passed check, and restore tc_cfg if setup
queue map failed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48653 | ice: Don&amp;#x27;t double unplug aux on peer initiated reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48653</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: Don't double unplug aux on peer initiated reset

In the IDC callback that is accessed when the aux drivers request a reset,
the function to unplug the aux devices is called.  This function is also
called in the ice_prepare_for_reset function. This double call is causing
a "scheduling while atomic" BUG.

[  662.676430] ice 0000:4c:00.0 rocep76s0: cqp opcode = 0x1 maj_err_code = 0xffff min_err_code = 0x8003

[  662.676609] ice 0000:4c:00.0 rocep76s0: [Modify QP Cmd Error][op_code=8] status=-29 waiting=1 completion_err=1 maj=0xffff min=0x8003

[  662.815006] ice 0000:4c:00.0 rocep76s0: ICE OICR event notification: oicr = 0x10000003

[  662.815014] ice 0000:4c:00.0 rocep76s0: critical PE Error, GLPE_CRITERR=0x00011424

[  662.815017] ice 0000:4c:00.0 rocep76s0: Requesting a reset

[  662.815475] BUG: scheduling while atomic: swapper/37/0/0x00010002

[  662.815475] BUG: scheduling while atomic: swapper/37/0/0x00010002
[  662.815477] Modules linked in: rpcsec_gss_krb5 auth_rpcgss nfsv4 dns_resolver nfs lockd grace fscache netfs rfkill 8021q garp mrp stp llc vfat fat rpcrdma intel_rapl_msr intel_rapl_common sunrpc i10nm_edac rdma_ucm nfit ib_srpt libnvdimm ib_isert iscsi_target_mod x86_pkg_temp_thermal intel_powerclamp coretemp target_core_mod snd_hda_intel ib_iser snd_intel_dspcfg libiscsi snd_intel_sdw_acpi scsi_transport_iscsi kvm_intel iTCO_wdt rdma_cm snd_hda_codec kvm iw_cm ipmi_ssif iTCO_vendor_support snd_hda_core irqbypass crct10dif_pclmul crc32_pclmul ghash_clmulni_intel snd_hwdep snd_seq snd_seq_device rapl snd_pcm snd_timer isst_if_mbox_pci pcspkr isst_if_mmio irdma intel_uncore idxd acpi_ipmi joydev isst_if_common snd mei_me idxd_bus ipmi_si soundcore i2c_i801 mei ipmi_devintf i2c_smbus i2c_ismt ipmi_msghandler acpi_power_meter acpi_pad rv(OE) ib_uverbs ib_cm ib_core xfs libcrc32c ast i2c_algo_bit drm_vram_helper drm_kms_helper syscopyarea sysfillrect sysimgblt fb_sys_fops drm_ttm_helpe
 r ttm
[  662.815546]  nvme nvme_core ice drm crc32c_intel i40e t10_pi wmi pinctrl_emmitsburg dm_mirror dm_region_hash dm_log dm_mod fuse
[  662.815557] Preemption disabled at:
[  662.815558] [&lt;0000000000000000&gt;] 0x0
[  662.815563] CPU: 37 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/37 Kdump: loaded Tainted: G S         OE     5.17.1 #2
[  662.815566] Hardware name: Intel Corporation D50DNP/D50DNP, BIOS SE5C6301.86B.6624.D18.2111021741 11/02/2021
[  662.815568] Call Trace:
[  662.815572]  
[  662.815574]  dump_stack_lvl+0x33/0x42
[  662.815581]  __schedule_bug.cold.147+0x7d/0x8a
[  662.815588]  __schedule+0x798/0x990
[  662.815595]  schedule+0x44/0xc0
[  662.815597]  schedule_preempt_disabled+0x14/0x20
[  662.815600]  __mutex_lock.isra.11+0x46c/0x490
[  662.815603]  ? __ibdev_printk+0x76/0xc0 [ib_core]
[  662.815633]  device_del+0x37/0x3d0
[  662.815639]  ice_unplug_aux_dev+0x1a/0x40 [ice]
[  662.815674]  ice_schedule_reset+0x3c/0xd0 [ice]
[  662.815693]  irdma_iidc_event_handler.cold.7+0xb6/0xd3 [irdma]
[  662.815712]  ? bitmap_find_next_zero_area_off+0x45/0xa0
[  662.815719]  ice_send_event_to_aux+0x54/0x70 [ice]
[  662.815741]  ice_misc_intr+0x21d/0x2d0 [ice]
[  662.815756]  __handle_irq_event_percpu+0x4c/0x180
[  662.815762]  handle_irq_event_percpu+0xf/0x40
[  662.815764]  handle_irq_event+0x34/0x60
[  662.815766]  handle_edge_irq+0x9a/0x1c0
[  662.815770]  __common_interrupt+0x62/0x100
[  662.815774]  common_interrupt+0xb4/0xd0
[  662.815779]  
[  662.815780]  
[  662.815780]  asm_common_interrupt+0x1e/0x40
[  662.815785] RIP: 0010:cpuidle_enter_state+0xd6/0x380
[  662.815789] Code: 49 89 c4 0f 1f 44 00 00 31 ff e8 65 d7 95 ff 45 84 ff 74 12 9c 58 f6 c4 02 0f 85 64 02 00 00 31 ff e8 ae c5 9c ff fb 45 85 f6 &lt;0f&gt; 88 12 01 00 00 49 63 d6 4c 2b 24 24 48 8d 04 52 48 8d 04 82 49
[  662.815791] RSP: 0018:ff2c2c4f18edbe80 EFLAGS: 00000202
[  662.815793] RAX: ff280805df140000 RBX: 0000000000000002 RCX: 000000000000001f
[  662.815795] RDX: 0000009a52da2d08 R
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48654 | netfilter: nfnetlink_osf: fix possible bogus match in nf_osf_find()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48654</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nfnetlink_osf: fix possible bogus match in nf_osf_find()

nf_osf_find() incorrectly returns true on mismatch, this leads to
copying uninitialized memory area in nft_osf which can be used to leak
stale kernel stack data to userspace.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48655 | firmware: arm_scmi: Harden accesses to the reset domains</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48655</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: arm_scmi: Harden accesses to the reset domains

Accessing reset domains descriptors by the index upon the SCMI drivers
requests through the SCMI reset operations interface can potentially
lead to out-of-bound violations if the SCMI driver misbehave.

Add an internal consistency check before any such domains descriptors
accesses.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48656 | dmaengine: ti: k3-udma-private: Fix refcount leak bug in of_xudma_dev_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48656</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dmaengine: ti: k3-udma-private: Fix refcount leak bug in of_xudma_dev_get()

We should call of_node_put() for the reference returned by
of_parse_phandle() in fail path or when it is not used anymore.
Here we only need to move the of_node_put() before the check.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48657 | arm64: topology: fix possible overflow in amu_fie_setup()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48657</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

arm64: topology: fix possible overflow in amu_fie_setup()

cpufreq_get_hw_max_freq() returns max frequency in kHz as *unsigned int*,
while freq_inv_set_max_ratio() gets passed this frequency in Hz as 'u64'.
Multiplying max frequency by 1000 can potentially result in overflow --
multiplying by 1000ULL instead should avoid that...

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with the SVACE static
analysis tool.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48658 | mm: slub: fix flush_cpu_slab()/__free_slab() invocations in task context.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48658</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: slub: fix flush_cpu_slab()/__free_slab() invocations in task context.

Commit 5a836bf6b09f ("mm: slub: move flush_cpu_slab() invocations
__free_slab() invocations out of IRQ context") moved all flush_cpu_slab()
invocations to the global workqueue to avoid a problem related
with deactivate_slab()/__free_slab() being called from an IRQ context
on PREEMPT_RT kernels.

When the flush_all_cpu_locked() function is called from a task context
it may happen that a workqueue with WQ_MEM_RECLAIM bit set ends up
flushing the global workqueue, this will cause a dependency issue.

 workqueue: WQ_MEM_RECLAIM nvme-delete-wq:nvme_delete_ctrl_work [nvme_core]
   is flushing !WQ_MEM_RECLAIM events:flush_cpu_slab
 WARNING: CPU: 37 PID: 410 at kernel/workqueue.c:2637
   check_flush_dependency+0x10a/0x120
 Workqueue: nvme-delete-wq nvme_delete_ctrl_work [nvme_core]
 RIP: 0010:check_flush_dependency+0x10a/0x120[  453.262125] Call Trace:
 __flush_work.isra.0+0xbf/0x220
 ? __queue_work+0x1dc/0x420
 flush_all_cpus_locked+0xfb/0x120
 __kmem_cache_shutdown+0x2b/0x320
 kmem_cache_destroy+0x49/0x100
 bioset_exit+0x143/0x190
 blk_release_queue+0xb9/0x100
 kobject_cleanup+0x37/0x130
 nvme_fc_ctrl_free+0xc6/0x150 [nvme_fc]
 nvme_free_ctrl+0x1ac/0x2b0 [nvme_core]

Fix this bug by creating a workqueue for the flush operation with
the WQ_MEM_RECLAIM bit set.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48659 | mm/slub: fix to return errno if kmalloc() fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48659</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/slub: fix to return errno if kmalloc() fails

In create_unique_id(), kmalloc(, GFP_KERNEL) can fail due to
out-of-memory, if it fails, return errno correctly rather than
triggering panic via BUG_ON();

kernel BUG at mm/slub.c:5893!
Internal error: Oops - BUG: 0 [#1] PREEMPT SMP

Call trace:
 sysfs_slab_add+0x258/0x260 mm/slub.c:5973
 __kmem_cache_create+0x60/0x118 mm/slub.c:4899
 create_cache mm/slab_common.c:229 [inline]
 kmem_cache_create_usercopy+0x19c/0x31c mm/slab_common.c:335
 kmem_cache_create+0x1c/0x28 mm/slab_common.c:390
 f2fs_kmem_cache_create fs/f2fs/f2fs.h:2766 [inline]
 f2fs_init_xattr_caches+0x78/0xb4 fs/f2fs/xattr.c:808
 f2fs_fill_super+0x1050/0x1e0c fs/f2fs/super.c:4149
 mount_bdev+0x1b8/0x210 fs/super.c:1400
 f2fs_mount+0x44/0x58 fs/f2fs/super.c:4512
 legacy_get_tree+0x30/0x74 fs/fs_context.c:610
 vfs_get_tree+0x40/0x140 fs/super.c:1530
 do_new_mount+0x1dc/0x4e4 fs/namespace.c:3040
 path_mount+0x358/0x914 fs/namespace.c:3370
 do_mount fs/namespace.c:3383 [inline]
 __do_sys_mount fs/namespace.c:3591 [inline]
 __se_sys_mount fs/namespace.c:3568 [inline]
 __arm64_sys_mount+0x2f8/0x408 fs/namespace.c:3568</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48660 | gpiolib: cdev: Set lineevent_state::irq after IRQ register successfully</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48660</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpiolib: cdev: Set lineevent_state::irq after IRQ register successfully

When running gpio test on nxp-ls1028 platform with below command
gpiomon --num-events=3 --rising-edge gpiochip1 25
There will be a warning trace as below:
Call trace:
free_irq+0x204/0x360
lineevent_free+0x64/0x70
gpio_ioctl+0x598/0x6a0
__arm64_sys_ioctl+0xb4/0x100
invoke_syscall+0x5c/0x130
......
el0t_64_sync+0x1a0/0x1a4
The reason of this issue is that calling request_threaded_irq()
function failed, and then lineevent_free() is invoked to release
the resource. Since the lineevent_state::irq was already set, so
the subsequent invocation of free_irq() would trigger the above
warning call trace. To fix this issue, set the lineevent_state::irq
after the IRQ register successfully.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48661 | gpio: mockup: Fix potential resource leakage when register a chip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: mockup: Fix potential resource leakage when register a chip

If creation of software node fails, the locally allocated string
array is left unfreed. Free it on error path.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48662 | drm/i915/gem: Really move i915_gem_context.link under ref protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48662</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/i915/gem: Really move i915_gem_context.link under ref protection

i915_perf assumes that it can use the i915_gem_context reference to
protect its i915-&gt;gem.contexts.list iteration. However, this requires
that we do not remove the context from the list until after we drop the
final reference and release the struct. If, as currently, we remove the
context from the list during context_close(), the link.next pointer may
be poisoned while we are holding the context reference and cause a GPF:

[ 4070.573157] i915 0000:00:02.0: [drm:i915_perf_open_ioctl [i915]] filtering on ctx_id=0x1fffff ctx_id_mask=0x1fffff
[ 4070.574881] general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdead000000000100: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[ 4070.574897] CPU: 1 PID: 284392 Comm: amd_performance Tainted: G            E     5.17.9 #180
[ 4070.574903] Hardware name: Intel Corporation NUC7i5BNK/NUC7i5BNB, BIOS BNKBL357.86A.0052.2017.0918.1346 09/18/2017
[ 4070.574907] RIP: 0010:oa_configure_all_contexts.isra.0+0x222/0x350 [i915]
[ 4070.574982] Code: 08 e8 32 6e 10 e1 4d 8b 6d 50 b8 ff ff ff ff 49 83 ed 50 f0 41 0f c1 04 24 83 f8 01 0f 84 e3 00 00 00 85 c0 0f 8e fa 00 00 00 &lt;49&gt; 8b 45 50 48 8d 70 b0 49 8d 45 50 48 39 44 24 10 0f 85 34 fe ff
[ 4070.574990] RSP: 0018:ffffc90002077b78 EFLAGS: 00010202
[ 4070.574995] RAX: 0000000000000002 RBX: 0000000000000002 RCX: 0000000000000000
[ 4070.575000] RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: ffffc90002077b20 RDI: ffff88810ddc7c68
[ 4070.575004] RBP: 0000000000000001 R08: ffff888103242648 R09: fffffffffffffffc
[ 4070.575008] R10: ffffffff82c50bc0 R11: 0000000000025c80 R12: ffff888101bf1860
[ 4070.575012] R13: dead0000000000b0 R14: ffffc90002077c04 R15: ffff88810be5cabc
[ 4070.575016] FS:  00007f1ed50c0780(0000) GS:ffff88885ec80000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[ 4070.575021] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[ 4070.575025] CR2: 00007f1ed5590280 CR3: 000000010ef6f005 CR4: 00000000003706e0
[ 4070.575029] Call Trace:
[ 4070.575033]  
[ 4070.575037]  lrc_configure_all_contexts+0x13e/0x150 [i915]
[ 4070.575103]  gen8_enable_metric_set+0x4d/0x90 [i915]
[ 4070.575164]  i915_perf_open_ioctl+0xbc0/0x1500 [i915]
[ 4070.575224]  ? asm_common_interrupt+0x1e/0x40
[ 4070.575232]  ? i915_oa_init_reg_state+0x110/0x110 [i915]
[ 4070.575290]  drm_ioctl_kernel+0x85/0x110
[ 4070.575296]  ? update_load_avg+0x5f/0x5e0
[ 4070.575302]  drm_ioctl+0x1d3/0x370
[ 4070.575307]  ? i915_oa_init_reg_state+0x110/0x110 [i915]
[ 4070.575382]  ? gen8_gt_irq_handler+0x46/0x130 [i915]
[ 4070.575445]  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x3c4/0x8d0
[ 4070.575451]  ? __do_softirq+0xaa/0x1d2
[ 4070.575456]  do_syscall_64+0x35/0x80
[ 4070.575461]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x44/0xae
[ 4070.575467] RIP: 0033:0x7f1ed5c10397
[ 4070.575471] Code: 3c 1c e8 1c ff ff ff 85 c0 79 87 49 c7 c4 ff ff ff ff 5b 5d 4c 89 e0 41 5c c3 66 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 b8 10 00 00 00 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 8b 0d a9 da 0d 00 f7 d8 64 89 01 48
[ 4070.575478] RSP: 002b:00007ffd65c8d7a8 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 0000000000000010
[ 4070.575484] RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 0000000000000006 RCX: 00007f1ed5c10397
[ 4070.575488] RDX: 00007ffd65c8d7c0 RSI: 0000000040106476 RDI: 0000000000000006
[ 4070.575492] RBP: 00005620972f9c60 R08: 000000000000000a R09: 0000000000000005
[ 4070.575496] R10: 000000000000000d R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 000000000000000a
[ 4070.575500] R13: 000000000000000d R14: 0000000000000000 R15: 00007ffd65c8d7c0
[ 4070.575505]  
[ 4070.575507] Modules linked in: nls_ascii(E) nls_cp437(E) vfat(E) fat(E) i915(E) x86_pkg_temp_thermal(E) intel_powerclamp(E) crct10dif_pclmul(E) crc32_pclmul(E) crc32c_intel(E) aesni_intel(E) crypto_simd(E) intel_gtt(E) cryptd(E) ttm(E) rapl(E) intel_cstate(E) drm_kms_helper(E) cfbfillrect(E) syscopyarea(E) cfbimgblt(E) intel_uncore(E) sysfillrect(E) mei_me(E) sysimgblt(E) i2c_i801(E) fb_sys_fops(E) mei(E) intel_pch_thermal(E) i2c_smbus
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48663 | gpio: mockup: fix NULL pointer dereference when removing debugfs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gpio: mockup: fix NULL pointer dereference when removing debugfs

We now remove the device's debugfs entries when unbinding the driver.
This now causes a NULL-pointer dereference on module exit because the
platform devices are unregistered *after* the global debugfs directory
has been recursively removed. Fix it by unregistering the devices first.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48664 | btrfs: fix hang during unmount when stopping a space reclaim worker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix hang during unmount when stopping a space reclaim worker

Often when running generic/562 from fstests we can hang during unmount,
resulting in a trace like this:

  Sep 07 11:52:00 debian9 unknown: run fstests generic/562 at 2022-09-07 11:52:00
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: INFO: task umount:49438 blocked for more than 120 seconds.
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:       Not tainted 6.0.0-rc2-btrfs-next-122 #1
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: "echo 0 &gt; /proc/sys/kernel/hung_task_timeout_secs" disables this message.
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: task:umount          state:D stack:    0 pid:49438 ppid: 25683 flags:0x00004000
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: Call Trace:
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  __schedule+0x3c8/0xec0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? rcu_read_lock_sched_held+0x12/0x70
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  schedule+0x5d/0xf0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  schedule_timeout+0xf1/0x130
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? lock_release+0x224/0x4a0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? lock_acquired+0x1a0/0x420
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? trace_hardirqs_on+0x2c/0xd0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  __wait_for_common+0xac/0x200
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? usleep_range_state+0xb0/0xb0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  __flush_work+0x26d/0x530
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? flush_workqueue_prep_pwqs+0x140/0x140
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? trace_clock_local+0xc/0x30
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  __cancel_work_timer+0x11f/0x1b0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? close_ctree+0x12b/0x5b3 [btrfs]
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? __trace_bputs+0x10b/0x170
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  close_ctree+0x152/0x5b3 [btrfs]
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  ? evict_inodes+0x166/0x1c0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  generic_shutdown_super+0x71/0x120
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  kill_anon_super+0x14/0x30
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  btrfs_kill_super+0x12/0x20 [btrfs]
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  deactivate_locked_super+0x2e/0xa0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  cleanup_mnt+0x100/0x160
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  task_work_run+0x59/0xa0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  exit_to_user_mode_prepare+0x1a6/0x1b0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  syscall_exit_to_user_mode+0x16/0x40
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  do_syscall_64+0x48/0x90
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: RIP: 0033:0x7fcde59a57a7
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: RSP: 002b:00007ffe914217c8 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 00000000000000a6
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 00007fcde5ae8264 RCX: 00007fcde59a57a7
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: 000055b57556cdd0
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: RBP: 000055b57556cba0 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 00007ffe91420570
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000000
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel: R13: 000055b57556cdd0 R14: 000055b57556ccb8 R15: 0000000000000000
  Sep 07 11:55:32 debian9 kernel:  

What happens is the following:

1) The cleaner kthread tries to start a transaction to delete an unused
   block group, but the metadata reservation can not be satisfied right
   away, so a reservation ticket is created and it starts the async
   metadata reclaim task (fs_info-&gt;async_reclaim_work);

2) Writeback for all the filler inodes with an i_size of 2K starts
   (generic/562 creates a lot of 2K files with the goal of filling
   metadata space). We try to create an inline extent for them, but we
   fail when trying to insert the inline extent with -ENOSPC (at
   cow_file_range_inline()) - since this is not critical, we fallback
   to non-inline mode (back to cow_file_range()), reserve extents
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48665 | exfat: fix overflow for large capacity partition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48665</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

exfat: fix overflow for large capacity partition

Using int type for sector index, there will be overflow in a large
capacity partition.

For example, if storage with sector size of 512 bytes and partition
capacity is larger than 2TB, there will be overflow.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48666 | scsi: core: Fix a use-after-free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48666</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: core: Fix a use-after-free

There are two .exit_cmd_priv implementations. Both implementations use
resources associated with the SCSI host. Make sure that these resources are
still available when .exit_cmd_priv is called by waiting inside
scsi_remove_host() until the tag set has been freed.

This commit fixes the following use-after-free:

==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: use-after-free in srp_exit_cmd_priv+0x27/0xd0 [ib_srp]
Read of size 8 at addr ffff888100337000 by task multipathd/16727
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x34/0x44
 print_report.cold+0x5e/0x5db
 kasan_report+0xab/0x120
 srp_exit_cmd_priv+0x27/0xd0 [ib_srp]
 scsi_mq_exit_request+0x4d/0x70
 blk_mq_free_rqs+0x143/0x410
 __blk_mq_free_map_and_rqs+0x6e/0x100
 blk_mq_free_tag_set+0x2b/0x160
 scsi_host_dev_release+0xf3/0x1a0
 device_release+0x54/0xe0
 kobject_put+0xa5/0x120
 device_release+0x54/0xe0
 kobject_put+0xa5/0x120
 scsi_device_dev_release_usercontext+0x4c1/0x4e0
 execute_in_process_context+0x23/0x90
 device_release+0x54/0xe0
 kobject_put+0xa5/0x120
 scsi_disk_release+0x3f/0x50
 device_release+0x54/0xe0
 kobject_put+0xa5/0x120
 disk_release+0x17f/0x1b0
 device_release+0x54/0xe0
 kobject_put+0xa5/0x120
 dm_put_table_device+0xa3/0x160 [dm_mod]
 dm_put_device+0xd0/0x140 [dm_mod]
 free_priority_group+0xd8/0x110 [dm_multipath]
 free_multipath+0x94/0xe0 [dm_multipath]
 dm_table_destroy+0xa2/0x1e0 [dm_mod]
 __dm_destroy+0x196/0x350 [dm_mod]
 dev_remove+0x10c/0x160 [dm_mod]
 ctl_ioctl+0x2c2/0x590 [dm_mod]
 dm_ctl_ioctl+0x5/0x10 [dm_mod]
 __x64_sys_ioctl+0xb4/0xf0
 dm_ctl_ioctl+0x5/0x10 [dm_mod]
 __x64_sys_ioctl+0xb4/0xf0
 do_syscall_64+0x3b/0x90
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x46/0xb0</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48667 | smb3: fix temporary data corruption in insert range</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb3: fix temporary data corruption in insert range

insert range doesn't discard the affected cached region
so can risk temporarily corrupting file data.

Also includes some minor cleanup (avoiding rereading
inode size repeatedly unnecessarily) to make it clearer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48668 | smb3: fix temporary data corruption in collapse range</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48668</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb3: fix temporary data corruption in collapse range

collapse range doesn't discard the affected cached region
so can risk temporarily corrupting the file data. This
fixes xfstest generic/031

I also decided to merge a minor cleanup to this into the same patch
(avoiding rereading inode size repeatedly unnecessarily) to make it
clearer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:18:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25050 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25050</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5 and IBM Rational Development Studio for i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5 networking and compiler infrastructure could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call. A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privileges.  IBM X-Force ID:  283242.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26927 | ASoC: SOF: Add some bounds checking to firmware data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26927</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: SOF: Add some bounds checking to firmware data

Smatch complains about "head-&gt;full_size - head-&gt;header_size" can
underflow.  To some extent, we're always going to have to trust the
firmware a bit.  However, it's easy enough to add a check for negatives,
and let's add a upper bounds check as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 11:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26928 | smb: client: fix potential UAF in cifs_debug_files_proc_show()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26928</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: fix potential UAF in cifs_debug_files_proc_show()

Skip sessions that are being teared down (status == SES_EXITING) to
avoid UAF.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 11:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>