<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 05:17:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1302 | Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1302</link><description>Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can execute aribitrary code on the system by exploiting the unsafe default usage of eval='safe' mode.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is caused by an incomplete fix for [CVE-2024-21534](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-JSONPATHPLUS-7945884).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 05:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0995 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0995</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0996 | Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0996</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0997 | Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0997</link><description>Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0998 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0998</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5461 | Command or parameter injection via unique embedded switch SNMP commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5461</link><description>Implementation of the Simple Network 
Management Protocol (SNMP) operating on the Brocade 6547 (FC5022) 
embedded switch blade, makes internal script calls to system.sh from 
within the SNMP binary. An authenticated attacker could perform command 
or parameter injection on SNMP operations that are only enabled on the 
Brocade 6547 (FC5022) embedded switch. This injection could allow the 
authenticated attacker to issue commands as Root.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5462 | Brocade Fabric OS may capture SNMP Passwords in clear text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5462</link><description>If Brocade Fabric OS before Fabric OS 9.2.0 configuration settings are not set to encrypt SNMP passwords, then the SNMP privsecret / authsecret fields can be exposed in plaintext. The plaintext passwords can be exposed in a configupload capture or a supportsave capture if encryption of passwords is not enabled. An attacker can use these passwords to fetch values of the supported OIDs via SNMPv3 queries. There are also a limited number of MIB objects that can be modified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26819 | Monero through 0.18.3.4 before ec74ff4 does not have response limits on HTTP server connections.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26819</link><description>Monero through 0.18.3.4 before ec74ff4 does not have response limits on HTTP server connections.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4282 | Weak TLS Ciphers on Brocade SANnav OVA SSH port 22</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4282</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before SANnav 2.3.1b enables SHA1 deprecated setting for SSH for port 22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10405 | Weak TLS Ciphers on Brocade SANnav port 443 &amp;amp; 18082</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10405</link><description>Brocade SANnav before SANnav 2.3.1b 
enables weak TLS ciphers on ports 443 and 18082. In case of a successful
 exploit, an attacker can read Brocade SANnav data stream that includes 
monitored Brocade Fabric OS switches performance data, port status, 
zoning information, WWNs, IP Addresses, but no customer data, no 
personal data and no secrets or passwords, as it travels across the 
network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21401 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21401</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28693 | Unprotected alternative channel of return branch target prediction in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28693</link><description>Unprotected alternative channel of return branch target prediction in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-26083 | Generation of weak initialization vector in an Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software library before version 2021.5 may allow an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26083</link><description>Generation of weak initialization vector in an Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software library before version 2021.5 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31144 | Xapi: Metadata injection attack against backup/restore functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31144</link><description>For a brief summary of Xapi terminology, see:

   https://xapi-project.github.io/xen-api/overview.html#object-model-overview 

Xapi contains functionality to backup and restore metadata about Virtual
Machines and Storage Repositories (SRs).

The metadata itself is stored in a Virtual Disk Image (VDI) inside an
SR.  This is used for two purposes; a general backup of metadata
(e.g. to recover from a host failure if the filer is still good), and
Portable SRs (e.g. using an external hard drive to move VMs to another
host).

Metadata is only restored as an explicit administrator action, but
occurs in cases where the host has no information about the SR, and must
locate the metadata VDI in order to retrieve the metadata.

The metadata VDI is located by searching (in UUID alphanumeric order)
each VDI, mounting it, and seeing if there is a suitable metadata file
present.  The first matching VDI is deemed to be the metadata VDI, and
is restored from.

In the general case, the content of VDIs are controlled by the VM owner,
and should not be trusted by the host administrator.

A malicious guest can manipulate its disk to appear to be a metadata
backup.

A guest cannot choose the UUIDs of its VDIs, but a guest with one disk
has a 50% chance of sorting ahead of the legitimate metadata backup.  A
guest with two disks has a 75% chance, etc.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0592 | SICK Lector8xx and InspectorP8xx vulnerable for code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0592</link><description>The vulnerability may allow a remote low priviledged attacker to run arbitrary shell commands by manipulating the firmware file and uploading it to the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0593 | SICK Lector8xx and InspectorP8xx vulnerable for code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0593</link><description>The vulnerability may allow a remote low priviledged attacker to run arbitrary shell commands by using lower-level functions to interact with the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25288 | @octokit/plugin-paginate-rest has a Regular Expression in iterator that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25288</link><description>@octokit/plugin-paginate-rest is the Octokit plugin to paginate REST API endpoint responses. For versions starting in 1.0.0 and prior to 11.4.1 of the npm package `@octokit/plugin-paginate-rest`, when calling `octokit.paginate.iterator()`, a specially crafted `octokit` instance—particularly with a malicious `link` parameter in the `headers` section of the `request`—can trigger a ReDoS attack. Version 11.4.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25289 | @octokit/request-error has a Regular Expression in index that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25289</link><description>@octokit/request-error is an error class for Octokit request errors. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 6.1.7, a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the processing of HTTP request headers. By sending an authorization header containing an excessively long sequence of spaces followed by a newline and "@", an attacker can exploit inefficient regular expression processing, leading to excessive resource consumption. This can significantly degrade server performance or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, impacting availability. Version 6.1.7 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25290 | @octokit/request has a Regular Expression in fetchWrapper that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25290</link><description>@octokit/request sends parameterized requests to GitHub’s APIs with sensible defaults in browsers and Node. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 9.2.1, the regular expression `/&lt;([^&gt;]+)&gt;; rel="deprecation"/` used to match the `link` header in HTTP responses is vulnerable to a ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) attack. This vulnerability arises due to the unbounded nature of the regex's matching behavior, which can lead to catastrophic backtracking when processing specially crafted input. An attacker could exploit this flaw by sending a malicious `link` header, resulting in excessive CPU usage and potentially causing the server to become unresponsive, impacting service availability. Version 9.2.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25285 | @octokit/endpoint has a Regular Expression in parse that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25285</link><description>@octokit/endpoint turns REST API endpoints into generic request options. Starting in version 4.1.0 and prior to version 10.1.3, by crafting specific `options` parameters, the `endpoint.parse(options)` call can be triggered, leading to a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) attack. This causes the program to hang and results in high CPU utilization. The issue occurs in the `parse` function within the `parse.ts` file of the npm package `@octokit/endpoint`. Version 10.1.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25304 | Vega allows Cross-site Scripting via the vlSelectionTuples function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25304</link><description>Vega is a visualization grammar, a declarative format for creating, saving, and sharing interactive visualization designs. Prior to version 5.26.0 of vega and 5.4.2 of vega-selections, the `vlSelectionTuples` function can be used to call JavaScript functions, leading to cross-site scripting.`vlSelectionTuples` calls multiple functions that can be controlled by an attacker, including one call with an attacker-controlled argument. This can be used to call `Function()` with arbitrary JavaScript and the resulting function can be called with `vlSelectionTuples` or using a type coercion to call `toString` or `valueOf`. Version 5.26.0 of vega and 5.4.2 of vega-selections fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25296 | Label Studio allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via GET request to `/projects/upload-example` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25296</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. Prior to version 1.16.0, Label Studio's `/projects/upload-example` endpoint allows injection of arbitrary HTML through a `GET` request with an appropriately crafted `label_config` query parameter. By crafting a specially formatted XML label config with inline task data containing malicious HTML/JavaScript, an attacker can achieve Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). While the application has a Content Security Policy (CSP), it is only set in report-only mode, making it ineffective at preventing script execution. The vulnerability exists because the upload-example endpoint renders user-provided HTML content without proper sanitization on a GET request. This allows attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers by getting them to visit a maliciously crafted URL. This is considered vulnerable because it enables attackers to execute JavaScript in victims' contexts, potentially allowing theft of sensitive data, session hijacking, or other malicious actions. Version 1.16.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25297 | Label Studio allows Server-Side Request Forgery in the S3 Storage Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25297</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. Prior to version 1.16.0, Label Studio's S3 storage integration feature contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in its endpoint configuration. When creating an S3 storage connection, the application allows users to specify a custom S3 endpoint URL via the s3_endpoint parameter. This endpoint URL is passed directly to the boto3 AWS SDK without proper validation or restrictions on the protocol or destination. The vulnerability allows an attacker to make the application send HTTP requests to arbitrary internal services by specifying them as the S3 endpoint. When the storage sync operation is triggered, the application attempts to make S3 API calls to the specified endpoint, effectively making HTTP requests to the target service and returning the response in error messages. This SSRF vulnerability enables attackers to bypass network segmentation and access internal services that should not be accessible from the external network. The vulnerability is particularly severe because error messages from failed requests contain the full response body, allowing data exfiltration from internal services. Version 1.16.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0503 | Leaked User IDs and Metadata of Deleted DMs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0503</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.6 fail to filter out DMs from the deleted channels endpoint which allows an attacker to infer user IDs and other metadata from deleted DMs if someone had manually marked DMs as deleted in the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26507 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26507</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26508 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26508</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26506 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26506</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25206 | Incorrect input validation could allow an authenticated user to read sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25206</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. Prior to version 5.1.15, an incorrect input validation could allow an authenticated user to read sensitive information, including login token or other content stored in the database. This could lead to privilege escalation if cookies are enabled (default setting). Users must upgrade to eLabFTW version 5.1.15 to receive a fix. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25295 | Label Studio has a Path Traversal Vulnerability via image Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25295</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. A path traversal vulnerability in Label Studio SDK versions prior to 1.0.10 allows unauthorized file access outside the intended directory structure. The flaw exists in the VOC, COCO and YOLO export functionalities. These functions invoke a `download` function on the `label-studio-sdk` python package, which fails to validate file paths when processing image references during task exports. By creating tasks with path traversal sequences in the image field, an attacker can force the application to read files from arbitrary server filesystem locations when exporting projects in any of the mentioned formats. This is authentication-required vulnerability allowing arbitrary file reads from the server filesystem. It may lead to potential exposure of sensitive information like configuration files, credentials, and confidential data. Label Studio versions before 1.16.0 specified SDK versions prior to 1.0.10 as dependencies, and the issue was confirmed in Label Studio version 1.13.2.dev0; therefore, Label Studio users should upgrade to 1.16.0 or newer to mitigate it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8893 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GoodWe Technologies Co., Ltd. GW1500‑XS allows anyone in physical proximity to the device to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8893</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GoodWe Technologies Co., Ltd. GW1500‑XS allows anyone in physical proximity to the device to fully access the web interface of the inverter via Wi‑Fi.This issue affects GW1500‑XS: 1.1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25204 | `gh attestation verify` returns incorrect exit code during verification if no attestations are present</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25204</link><description>`gh` is GitHub’s official command line tool. Starting in version 2.49.0 and prior to version 2.67.0, under certain conditions, a bug in GitHub's Artifact Attestation cli tool `gh attestation verify` causes it to return a zero exit status when no attestations are present. This behavior is incorrect: When no attestations are present, `gh attestation verify` should return a non-zero exit status code, thereby signaling verification failure. An attacker can abuse this flaw to, for example, deploy malicious artifacts in any system that uses `gh attestation verify`'s exit codes to gatekeep deployments. Users are advised to update `gh` to patched version `v2.67.0` as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25991 | SQL Injection vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25991</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25992 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inquire_inout_item.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25992</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inquire_inout_item.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25993 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameter "itemid."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25993</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameter "itemid."</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25997 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in FeMiner wms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the databak.php componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25997</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in FeMiner wms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the databak.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3220 | Default mimetype known files writeable on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3220</link><description>There is a defect in the CPython standard library module “mimetypes” where on Windows the default list of known file locations are writable meaning other users can create invalid files to cause MemoryError to be raised on Python runtime startup or have file extensions be interpreted as the incorrect file type.

This defect is caused by the default locations of Linux and macOS platforms (such as “/etc/mime.types”) also being used on Windows, where they are user-writable locations (“C:\etc\mime.types”).

To work-around this issue a user can call mimetypes.init() with an empty list (“[]”) on Windows platforms to avoid using the default list of known file locations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57790 | IXON B.V. IXrouter IX2400 (Industrial Edge Gateway) v3.0 was discovered to contain hardcoded root credentials stored in the non-volatile fla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57790</link><description>IXON B.V. IXrouter IX2400 (Industrial Edge Gateway) v3.0 was discovered to contain hardcoded root credentials stored in the non-volatile flash memory. This vulnerability allows physically proximate attackers to gain root access via UART or SSH.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25990 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25990</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25994 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameters date1, date2,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25994</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameters date1, date2, id.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26157 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /bpms/index.php in Source Code and Project Beauty Parlour Management System V1.1, which allows re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26157</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /bpms/index.php in Source Code and Project Beauty Parlour Management System V1.1, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the name POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26158 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the manage-employee.php page of Kashipara Online Attendance Management S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26158</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the manage-employee.php page of Kashipara Online Attendance Management System V1.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary scripts via the department parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56463 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56463</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25988 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.8 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the custom Link title paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25988</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.8 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the custom Link title parameter and the Title parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26156 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /shopping/track-orders.php in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal v2.1, which allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26156</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /shopping/track-orders.php in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal v2.1, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via orderid POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57778 | An issue in Orbe ONetView Roeador Onet-1200 Orbe 1680210096 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the servers response from st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57778</link><description>An issue in Orbe ONetView Roeador Onet-1200 Orbe 1680210096 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the servers response from status code 500 to status code 200.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57725 | An issue in the Arcadyan Livebox Fibra PRV3399B_B_LT allows a remote or local attacker to modify the GPON link value without authentication,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57725</link><description>An issue in the Arcadyan Livebox Fibra PRV3399B_B_LT allows a remote or local attacker to modify the GPON link value without authentication, causing an internet service disruption via the /firstconnection.cgi endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56973 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Alvaria, Inc Unified IP Unified Director before v.7.2SP2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56973</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Alvaria, Inc Unified IP Unified Director before v.7.2SP2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the source and filename parameters to the ProcessUploadFromURL.jsp component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25745 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetQuick...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25745</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetQuickVPNSettings module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56477 | IBM Power Hardware Management Console directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56477</link><description>IBM Power Hardware Management Console V10.3.1050.0 could allow an authenticated user to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25740 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PSK parameter in the SetQuickVPNSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25740</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PSK parameter in the SetQuickVPNSettings module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52895 | IBM i denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52895</link><description>IBM i 7.4 and 7.5 is vulnerable to a database access denial of service caused by a bypass of a database capabilities restriction check. A privileged bad actor can remove or otherwise impact database infrastructure files resulting in incorrect behavior of software products that rely upon the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56180 | Apache EventMesh: raft Hessian Deserialization Vulnerability allowing remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56180</link><description>CWE-502 Deserialization of Untrusted Data at the eventmesh-meta-raft plugin module in Apache EventMesh master branch without release version on windows\linux\mac os e.g. platforms allows attackers to send controlled message and remote code execute via hessian deserialization rpc protocol. Users can use the code under the master branch in project repo or version 1.11.0 to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12651 | Sensitive Data Exposure in PTT Inc.&amp;#x27;s HGS Mobile App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12651</link><description>Exposed Dangerous Method or Function vulnerability in PTT Inc. HGS Mobile App allows Manipulating User-Controlled Variables.This issue affects HGS Mobile App: before 6.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0178 | WatchGaurd Firebox Host Header Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0178</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows an attacker to manipulate the value of the HTTP Host header in requests sent to the Web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to redirect users to malicious websites, poison the web cache, or inject malicious JavaScript into responses sent by the Web UI.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 up to and including 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1071 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in spamBlocker Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1071</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the spamBlocker module. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.5.12+701324, from 12.6 through 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1239 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Blocked Sites List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the Blocked Sites list. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.5.12+701324, from 12.6 through 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13152 | SQLi in BSS Software&amp;#x27;s Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13152</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled SQL Primary Key vulnerability in BSS Software Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel: before 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52500 | WordPress Monetag Official Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52500</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in monetagwp Monetag Official Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Monetag Official Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0867 | Privilege Escalation in MEAC300-FNADE4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0867</link><description>The standard user uses the run as function to start the MEAC applications with administrative privileges. To ensure that the system can startup on its own, the credentials of the administrator were stored. Consequently, the EPC2 user can execute any command with administrative privileges. This allows a privilege escalation to the administrative level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22698 | WordPress Accessibility Suite by Ability, Inc plugin &amp;lt;= 4.16 - Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22698</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ability, Inc Accessibility Suite by Online ADA allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Suite by Online ADA: from n/a through 4.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22702 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22702</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EPC Photography. This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22705 | WordPress Disqus Popular Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - CSRF to Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22705</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in godthor Disqus Popular Posts allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Disqus Popular Posts: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23428 | WordPress QMean plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound QMean – WordPress Did You Mean allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects QMean – WordPress Did You Mean: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23431 | WordPress Envato Affiliater plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23431</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Envato Affiliater allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Envato Affiliater: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23474 | WordPress Live Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23474</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mike Martel Live Dashboard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Live Dashboard: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23492 | WordPress 淘宝客插件 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23492</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CantonBolo WordPress 淘宝客插件 allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress 淘宝客插件: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23523 | WordPress HSS Embed Streaming Video plugin &amp;lt;= 3.23 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23523</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hoststreamsell HSS Embed Streaming Video allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects HSS Embed Streaming Video: from n/a through 3.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23525 | WordPress Kv Compose Email From Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kvvaradha Kv Compose Email From Dashboard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Kv Compose Email From Dashboard: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23534 | WordPress WPLingo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mark Winiarski WPLingo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WPLingo: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23568 | WordPress WP Login Attempt Log plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23568</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fredsted WP Login Attempt Log allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Login Attempt Log: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23571 | WordPress Internal Links Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.51 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Internal Links Generator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Internal Links Generator: from n/a through 3.51.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23598 | WordPress Recip.ly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in craig.edmunds@gmail.com Recip.ly allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Recip.ly: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23646 | WordPress Library Instruction Recorder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Brooks Library Instruction Recorder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Library Instruction Recorder: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23647 | WordPress WP-Clap plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ariagle WP-Clap allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP-Clap: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23648 | WordPress AdsMiddle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wjharil AdsMiddle allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AdsMiddle: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23650 | WordPress Tidy.ro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23650</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in razvypp Tidy.ro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tidy.ro: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23651 | WordPress Scroll Top plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Scroll Top allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Scroll Top: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23652 | WordPress Add custom content after post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Add custom content after post allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Add custom content after post: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23653 | WordPress Form To Online Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Form To Online Booking allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Form To Online Booking: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23655 | WordPress Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23657 | WordPress WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23658 | WordPress Advanced Angular Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23658</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tauhidul Alam Advanced Angular Contact Form allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Advanced Angular Contact Form: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23742 | WordPress Podamibe Twilio Private Call plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Podamibe Nepal Podamibe Twilio Private Call allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Podamibe Twilio Private Call: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23748 | WordPress Singsys -Awesome Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Singsys -Awesome Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Singsys -Awesome Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23750 | WordPress Custom Widget Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in devbunchuk Custom Widget Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Widget Creator: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23751 | WordPress Data Dash plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23751</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 Data Dash allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Data Dash: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23766 | WordPress OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23766</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ashamil OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments: from n/a through 2.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23771 | WordPress Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23771</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Murali Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress: from n/a through 2.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23786 | WordPress Email to Download Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23786</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DuoGeek Email to Download allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Email to Download: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23787 | WordPress Easy Bet Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23787</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Easy Bet allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Bet: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23788 | WordPress Easy Filter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23788</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Easy Filter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Filter: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23789 | WordPress URL Shortener WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23789</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tahminajannat URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce: from n/a through 9.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23790 | WordPress Easy Code Placement Plugin &amp;lt;= 18.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23790</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wassereimer Easy Code Placement allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Code Placement: from n/a through 18.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23851 | WordPress Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23851</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23853 | WordPress NoFollow Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23853</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in michelem NoFollow Free allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NoFollow Free: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23857 | WordPress Essential WP Real Estate Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23857</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Essential WP Real Estate allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Essential WP Real Estate: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23905 | WordPress Admin Options Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23905</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Johannes van Poelgeest Admin Options Pages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Admin Options Pages: from n/a through 0.9.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24554 | WordPress AWcode Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in awcode AWcode Toolkit allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AWcode Toolkit: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24558 | WordPress CRM Perks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CRM Perks: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24564 | WordPress Contact Form With Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aviplugins.com Contact Form With Shortcode allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Contact Form With Shortcode: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24565 | WordPress WP2LEADS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saleswonder Team Tobias WP2LEADS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP2LEADS: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24566 | WordPress Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tomáš Groulík Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation: from n/a through 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24567 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24567</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24592 | WordPress SysBasics Customize My Account for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.22 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SysBasics Customize My Account for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Customize My Account for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24607 | WordPress IdeaPush plugin &amp;lt;= 8.71 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24607</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Northern Beaches Websites IdeaPush allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects IdeaPush: from n/a through 8.71.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24614 | WordPress Post Timeline Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in agileLogix Post Timeline allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Post Timeline: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24615 | WordPress Analytics Cat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24615</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fatcatapps Analytics Cat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Analytics Cat: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24616 | WordPress Uix Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24616</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UIUX Lab Uix Page Builder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Uix Page Builder: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24617 | WordPress AcyMailing Plugin &amp;lt; 9.11.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24617</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AcyMailing Newsletter Team AcyMailing SMTP Newsletter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AcyMailing SMTP Newsletter: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24641 | WordPress Better WishList API plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rickonline_nl Better WishList API allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Better WishList API: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24688 | WordPress WP Mailster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.20.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24688</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.20.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24692 | WordPress Bulk Menu Edit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24692</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Michael Revellin-Clerc Bulk Menu Edit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Bulk Menu Edit: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24699 | WordPress WP Coder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6 -  CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24699</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company WP Coder allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This issue affects WP Coder: from n/a through 3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24700 | WordPress WP Event Aggregator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Event Aggregator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Event Aggregator: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26524 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26524</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoints which could lead to the OTP bombing/ flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26523 | Insufficient Authorization Vulnerability in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26523</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to insufficient authorization controls on certain API endpoints handling addition and deletion operations. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an authenticated remote attacker to modify information belonging to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26522 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability  in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26522</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to improper implementation of OTP validation mechanism in certain API endpoints. A remote attacker with valid credentials could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API responses.  

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) for other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13791 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read via downloadResponseFile Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13791</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the downloadResponseFile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0821 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0821</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52577 | Apache Ignite: Possible RCE when deserializing incoming messages by the server node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52577</link><description>In Apache Ignite versions from 2.6.0 and before 2.17.0, configured Class Serialization Filters are ignored for some Ignite endpoints. The vulnerability could be exploited if an attacker manually crafts an Ignite message containing a vulnerable object whose class is present in the Ignite server classpath and sends it to Ignite server endpoints. Deserialization of such a message by the Ignite server may result in the execution of arbitrary code on the Apache Ignite server side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13735 | HurryTimer &amp;lt;= 2.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Campaign Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13735</link><description>The HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of a campaign name. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26791 | DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26791</link><description>DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26789 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26789</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access sensitive information about AgentX Manager in a Logpoint deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1298 | Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1298</link><description>Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26788 | StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26788</link><description>StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22630 | WordPress Widget Options Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in MarketingFire Widget Options allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Widget Options: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9601 | Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;align&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;UniqueID&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9601</link><description>The Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’  and 'UniqueID' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57969 | app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57969</link><description>app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13493 | Sensly Online Presence &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13493</link><description>The Sensly Online Presence WordPress plugin through 0.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7052 | Forminator &amp;lt; 1.38.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7052</link><description>The Forminator Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.38.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13641 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13641</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via the 'attachment' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/attachment directory which can contain file attachments for order refunds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13692 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13692</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via several functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to overwrite linked refund image attachments, overwrite refund request message, overwrite order messages, and read order messages of other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2240 | Docker implementation in Brocade SANnav is missing Audit Rules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2240</link><description>Docker daemon in Brocade SANnav before SANnav 2.3.1b runs without auditing. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute various attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23406 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23406</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, which may lead to processing a specially crafted packet to cause the affected product crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1053 | Brocade SANnav encryption key is logged in the debug logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1053</link><description>Under certain error conditions at time of SANnav installation or upgrade, the encryption key can be written into and obtained from a Brocade SANnav supportsave.  An attacker with privileged access to the Brocade SANnav database could use the encryption key to obtain passwords used by Brocade SANnav.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26519 | musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26519</link><description>musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrusted EUC-KR text to UTF-8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10404 | Clear text password seen in switch-asset-collectors-mw in Brocade SANnav supportsave</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10404</link><description>CalInvocationHandler in Brocade 
SANnav before 2.3.1b logs sensitive information in clear text. The 
vulnerability could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view 
Brocade Fabric OS switch sensitive information in clear text. An 
attacker with administrative privileges could retrieve sensitive 
information including passwords; SNMP responses that contain AuthSecret 
and PrivSecret after collecting a “supportsave” or getting access to an 
already collected “supportsave”. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-29952</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55904 | IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55904</link><description>IBM DevOps Deploy 8.0 through 8.0.1.4, 8.1 through 8.1.0.0 / IBM UrbanCode Deploy 7.0 through 7.0.5.25, 7.1 through 7.1.2.21, 7.2 through 7.2.3.14, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.9 could allow a remote privileged authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending specially crafted input containing special elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54951 | Monica 4.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). A malicious user can create a malformed contact and use that contact in the "HOW Y...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54951</link><description>Monica 4.1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). A malicious user can create a malformed contact and use that contact in the "HOW YOU MET" customization options to trigger the XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22962 | A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22962</link><description>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters when debugging mode is enabled. An attacker with a valid session ID (sess_id) can send specially crafted POST requests to the /json endpoint, enabling arbitrary command execution on the underlying system. This vulnerability can lead to full system compromise, including unauthorized access, privilege escalation, and potentially full device takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53311 | A Stack buffer overflow in the arguments parameter in Immunity Inc. Immunity Debugger v1.85 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53311</link><description>A Stack buffer overflow in the arguments parameter in Immunity Inc. Immunity Debugger v1.85 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted input that exceeds the buffer size.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22960 | A session hijacking vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters. Unauthenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22960</link><description>A session hijacking vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters. Unauthenticated attackers can access exposed log files (/logs/debug/xteLog*), potentially revealing sensitive session-related information such as session IDs (sess_id) and authentication success tokens (user_check_password OK). Exploiting this flaw could allow attackers to hijack active sessions, gain unauthorized access, and escalate privileges on affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22961 | A critical information disclosure vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22961</link><description>A critical information disclosure vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of GatesAir Maxiva UAXT, VAXT transmitters due to Incorrect Access Control (CWE-284). Unauthenticated attackers can directly access sensitive database backup files (snapshot_users.db) via publicly exposed URLs (/logs/devcfg/snapshot/ and /logs/devcfg/user/). Exploiting this vulnerability allows retrieval of sensitive user data, including login credentials, potentially leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53309 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when an overly long string...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53309</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when an overly long string is passed to the "-f" parameter. This can lead to memory corruption, potentially allowing arbitrary code execution or causing a denial of service via specially crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53310 | A Structured Exception Handler based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53310</link><description>A Structured Exception Handler based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Effectmatrix Total Video Converter Command Line (TVCC) 2.50 when a specially crafted file is passed to the -ff parameter. The vulnerability occurs due to improper handling of file input with overly long characters, leading to memory corruption. This can result in arbitrary code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56908 | In Perfex Crm &lt; 3.2.1, an authenticated attacker can send a crafted HTTP POST request to the affected upload_sales_file endpoint. By providi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56908</link><description>In Perfex Crm &lt; 3.2.1, an authenticated attacker can send a crafted HTTP POST request to the affected upload_sales_file endpoint. By providing malicious input in the rel_id parameter, combined with improper input validation, the attacker can bypass restrictions and upload arbitrary files to directories of their choice, potentially leading to remote code execution or server compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57782 | An issue in Docker-proxy v18.09.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57782</link><description>An issue in Docker-proxy v18.09.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34401 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside profile folder there is a file, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34401</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside profile folder there is a file, which is encoded with proprietary UD2 codec. Due to missed size checks in the enapsulate file, attacker can achieve Out-of-Bound Read in heap memory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34402 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside file is encapsulate another file, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34402</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Inside file is encapsulate another file, which service will drop during processing. Due to missed checks, attacker can achieve Arbitrary File Write with service speech rights.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34403 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to this pins and get access to inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34403</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to this pins and get access to internal network. A race condition can be acquired and attacker can spoof “UserData” with desirable file path and access it though backup on USB.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34404 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to these pins and get access to int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34404</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 has Ethernet pins on Base Board to connect module CSB. Attacker can connect to these pins and get access to internal network. As a result, by accessing a specific port an attacker can send call request to all registered services in router and achieve command injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34406 | An issue was discovered on Mercedes Benz NTG 6. A possible integer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG (New Telem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34406</link><description>An issue was discovered on Mercedes Benz NTG 6. A possible integer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12054 | ZF Roll Stability Support Plus (RSSPlus) Authentication Bypass By Primary Weakness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12054</link><description>ZF Roll Stability Support Plus (RSSPlus) 
is vulnerable to an authentication bypass vulnerability targeting 
deterministic RSSPlus SecurityAccess service seeds, which may allow an 
attacker to remotely (proximal/adjacent with RF equipment or via pivot 
from J2497 telematics devices) call diagnostic functions intended for 
workshop or repair scenarios. This can impact system availability, 
potentially degrading performance or erasing software, however the 
vehicle remains in a safe vehicle state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37600 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible stack buffer overflow in the Service Bro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37600</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible stack buffer overflow in the Service Broker service affects NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, physical access to Ethernet pins of the head unit base board is needed. With a static IP address, an attacker can connect via the internal network to the Service Broker service. With prepared HTTP requests, an attacker can cause the Service-Broker service to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37601 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible heap buffer overflow exists in the user data import/e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37601</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible heap buffer overflow exists in the user data import/export function of NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to the USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37602 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible NULL pointer dereference in the Apple Ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37602</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6 through 2021. A possible NULL pointer dereference in the Apple Car Play function affects NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, physical access to Ethernet pins of the head unit base board is needed. With a static IP address, an attacker can connect via the internal network to the AirTunes / AirPlay service. With prepared HTTP requests, an attacker can cause the Car Play service to fail.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37603 | An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible type confusion exists in the user data import/export ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37603</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mercedes Benz NTG (New Telematics Generation) 6. A possible type confusion exists in the user data import/export function of NTG 6 head units. To perform this attack, local access to the USB interface of the car is needed. With prepared data, an attacker can cause the User-Data service to fail. The failed service instance will restart automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34397 | Mercedes Benz head-unit NTG 6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. During parsing you can trigger that the serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34397</link><description>Mercedes Benz head-unit NTG 6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. During parsing you can trigger that the service will be crashed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34398 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized arch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34398</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized archive according boost library. The boost library contains a vulnerability/null pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34399 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized arch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34399</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. Some values of this table are serialized archive according boost library. The version of boost library contains vulnerability integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34400 | Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. In case of parsing file, service try to defin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34400</link><description>Mercedes-Benz head-unit NTG6 contains functions to import or export profile settings over USB. In case of parsing file, service try to define header inside the file and convert it to null-terminated string. If character is missed, will return null pointer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57378 | Wazuh SIEM version 4.8.2 is affected by a broken access control vulnerability. This issue allows the unauthorized creation of internal users...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57378</link><description>Wazuh SIEM version 4.8.2 is affected by a broken access control vulnerability. This issue allows the unauthorized creation of internal users without assigning any existing user role, potentially leading to privilege escalation or unauthorized access to sensitive resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24836 | Qardio Heart Health IOS and Android Application and QardioARM A100 Uncaught Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24836</link><description>With a specially crafted Python script, an attacker could send 
continuous startMeasurement commands over an unencrypted Bluetooth 
connection to the affected device. This would prevent the device from 
connecting to a clinician's app to take patient readings and ostensibly 
flood it with requests, resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20615 | Qardio Heart Health IOS Mobile Application Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20615</link><description>The Qardio Arm iOS application exposes sensitive data such as usernames 
and passwords in a plist file. This allows an attacker to log in to 
production-level development accounts and access an engineering backdoor
 in the application. The engineering backdoor allows the attacker to 
send hex-based commands over a UI-based terminal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23421 | Qardio iOS and Android applications Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23421</link><description>An attacker could obtain firmware files and reverse engineer their 
intended use leading to loss of confidentiality and integrity of the 
hardware devices enabled by the Qardio iOS and Android applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25195 | Zulip events can leak private channel names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25195</link><description>Zulip is an open source team chat application. A weekly cron job (added in 50256f48314250978f521ef439cafa704e056539) demotes channels to being "inactive" after they have not received traffic for 180 days.  However, upon doing so, an event was sent to all users in the organization, not just users in the channel.  This event contained the name of the private channel. Similarly, the same commit (50256f48314250978f521ef439cafa704e056539) added functionality to notify clients when channels stopped being "inactive."  The first message sent to a private channel which had not previously had any messages for over 180 days (and were thus already marked "inactive") would leak an event to all users in the organization; this event also contained the name of the private channel. Commits 75be449d456d29fef27e9d1828bafa30174284b4 and a2a1a7f8d152296c8966f1380872c0ac69e5c87e fixed the issue. This vulnerability only existed in `main`, and was not part of any published versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25067 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25067</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager
 
is vulnerable to an OS command injection which could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22896 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22896</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager


stores credentials in cleartext, which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23411 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23411</link><description>mySCADA myPRO Manager
 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery (CSRF), which could allow 
an attacker to obtain sensitive information. An attacker would need to 
trick the victim in to visiting an attacker-controlled website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24865 | mySCADA myPRO Manager Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24865</link><description>The administrative web interface of 
mySCADA myPRO Manager

can be accessed without authentication 
which could allow an unauthorized attacker to retrieve sensitive 
information and upload files without the associated password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1283 | Dingtian DT-R0 Series Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1283</link><description>The Dingtian DT-R0 Series is vulnerable to an exploit that allows 
attackers to bypass login requirements by directly navigating to the 
main page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24861 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24861</link><description>An attacker may inject commands via specially-crafted post requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25281 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25281</link><description>An attacker may modify the URL to discover sensitive information about the target network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26473 | Outback Power Mojave Inverter Use of GET Request Method With Sensitive Query Strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26473</link><description>The Mojave Inverter uses the GET method for sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11344 | Type confusion vulnerability in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11344</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability has been identified in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices. The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11346 | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type in Postscript interpreter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11346</link><description>: Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type ('Type Confusion') vulnerability in Lexmark International CX, XC, CS, et. Al. (Postscript interpreter modules) allows Resource Injection.This issue affects CX, XC, CS, et. Al.: from 001.001:0 through 081.231, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P233, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P759, from *.*.P001 through *.*.P836.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11347 | Access of Resource Using Incompatible Type in Postscript interpreter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11347</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Lexmark International CX, XC, CS, et. Al. (Postscript interpreter modules) allows Forced Integer Overflow.The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code as an unprivileged user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11345 | Heap-based memory vulnerability in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11345</link><description>A heap-based memory vulnerability has been identified in the Postscript interpreter in various Lexmark devices. The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1127 | Combination Path Traversal and Concurrent Execution vulnerability exists within the embedded web server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1127</link><description>The vulnerability can be leveraged by an attacker to execute arbitrary code as an unprivileged user and/or modify the contents of any data on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24888 | Path traversal in SecureDrop Client API.download_reply()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24888</link><description>The SecureDrop Client is a desktop application for journalists to communicate with sources and work with submissions on the SecureDrop Workstation. Prior to version 0.14.1, a malicious SecureDrop Server could obtain code execution on the SecureDrop Client virtual machine (`sd-app`). SecureDrop Server itself has multiple layers of built-in hardening, and is a dedicated physical machine exposed on the internet only via Tor hidden services for the Source and Journalist interfaces, and optionally via remote SSH access over another Tor hidden service. A newsroom's SecureDrop Workstation communicates only with its own dedicated SecureDrop Server.

The SecureDrop Client runs in a dedicated Qubes virtual machine, named `sd-app`, as part of the SecureDrop Workstation. The private OpenPGP key used to decrypt submissions and replies is stored in a separate virtual machine and never accessed directly. The vulnerability lies in the code responsible for downloading replies. The filename of the reply is obtained from the `Content-Disposition` HTTP header and used to write the encrypted reply on disk. Note that filenames are generated and sanitized server-side, and files are downloaded in an encrypted format, so a remote attacker who has not achieved server compromise, such as one posing as a source, could not craft the HTTP response necessary for this attack.

While the filename is later checked to guard against path traversal before being moved into the Client’s data storage directory, the file has already been written to a potentially arbitrary location. In this case, `safe_move()` would detect the path traversal and fail, leaving the original downloaded file in the attacker-chosen directory. Code execution can be gained by writing an autostart file in `/home/user/.config/autostart/`.

Version 0.14.1 fixes the issue. As of time of publication, there is no known evidence of exploitation in the wild. This attack requires a previously compromised SecureDrop Server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24889 | Path traversal in sd-log Qubes virtual machine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24889</link><description>The SecureDrop Client is a desktop application for journalists to communicate with sources and work with submissions on the SecureDrop Workstation. Prior to versions 0.14.1 and 1.0.1, an attacker who has already gained code execution in a virtual machine on the SecureDrop Workstation could gain code execution in the `sd-log` virtual machine by sending a specially crafted log entry. The vulnerability is not exploitable remotely and requires an attacker to already have code execution on one of the other virtual machines (VMs) of the system. Due to the Workstation's underlying usage of Qubes for strong isolation, the vulnerability would have allowed lateral movement between any log-enabled VM and the `sd-log` VM, but no further. The SecureDrop workstation collects logs centrally in an isolated virtual machine named `sd-log` for easy export for support and debugging purposes. The `sd-log`  VM is completely isolated from the internet and ingests logs via a narrow Qubes RPC policy that allows for specific inter-VM communication via the Xen vchan protocol used by Qubes's qrexec mechanism. A path traversal bug was found in the logic used to choose where to write the log file for a specific VM: the VM name, used unsanitized in the destination path in `sd-log`, is supplied by the logging VM itself instead of being read from a trusted source, such as the Qubes environment variable `QREXEC_REMOTE_DOMAIN` that is used in the fixed implementation. An attacker could provide an arbitrary source VM name, possibly overwriting logs of other VMs, or writing a file named `syslog.log`, with attacker-controlled content, in arbitrary directories as a low-privileged user. A successful attack could potentially overwrite or add configuration to software that loads configuration files from a directory. This is exploitable to achieve code execution by setting the target directory to `/home/user/.config/autostart/` and letting it write `syslog.log`, because XFCE treats any file in that directory as a `.desktop` file regardless of its extension. Versions 0.14.1 and 1.0.1 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25387 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/manage-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25387</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/manage-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the propertytype POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25388 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/edit-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25388</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/edit-propertytype.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the editid GET request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25389 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/forgot-password.php in Phpgurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25389</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/forgot-password.php in Phpgurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactno POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22480 | Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery versions prior to 5.5.13.1 contain a symbolic link attack vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker with local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22480</link><description>Dell SupportAssist OS Recovery versions prior to 5.5.13.1 contain a symbolic link attack vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary file deletion and Elevation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12012 | A CWE-598 “Use of GET Request Method with Sensitive Query Strings” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12012</link><description>A CWE-598 “Use of GET Request Method with Sensitive Query Strings” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. Both the SHA-1 hash of the password as well as the session tokens are included as part of the URL and therefore exposed to information leakage scenarios. An attacker capable of accessing such values (e.g., victim browser, network traffic inspection) can exploit this vulnerability to leak both the password hash as well as session tokens and bypass the authentication mechanism using a pass-the-hash attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12013 | A CWE-1392 “Use of Default Credentials” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The device expose...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12013</link><description>A CWE-1392 “Use of Default Credentials” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The device exposes an FTP server with default and easy-to-guess admin credentials. A remote attacker capable of interacting with the FTP server could gain access and perform changes over resources exposed by the service such as configuration files where password hashes are saved or where network settings are stored.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12011 | A CWE-126 “Buffer Over-read” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The information disclosure c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12011</link><description>A CWE-126 “Buffer Over-read” was discovered affecting the 130.8005 TCP/IP Gateway running firmware version 12h. The information disclosure can be triggered by leveraging a memory leak affecting the web server. A remote unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability in order to leak valid authentication tokens from the process memory associated to users currently logged to the system and bypass the authentication mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25352 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/aboutus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25352</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/aboutus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the pagetitle POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25357 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/contactus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25357</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/contactus.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the email POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25354 | A SQL Injection was found in /admin/admin-profile.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25354</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in /admin/admin-profile.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactnumber POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25355 | A SQL Injection in was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25355</link><description>A SQL Injection in was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the fromdate POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25356 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25356</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php in PHPGurukul Land Record System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the " todate" POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26511 | Cassandra-Lucene-Index allows bypass of Cassandra RBAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26511</link><description>Systems running the Instaclustr 
fork of Stratio's Cassandra-Lucene-Index plugin versions 4.0-rc1-1.0.0 
through 4.0.16-1.0.0 and 4.1.2-1.0.0 through 4.1.8-1.0.0, installed into
 Apache Cassandra version 4.x, are susceptible to a vulnerability which 
when successfully exploited could allow authenticated Cassandra users to
 remotely bypass RBAC and escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24904 | libsignal-service-rs doesn&amp;#x27;t sanity check plaintext envelopes are not sanity-checked</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24904</link><description>libsignal-service-rs is a Rust version of the libsignal-service-java library which implements the core functionality to communicate with Signal servers. Prior to commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8, plaintext content envelopes could be injected by a server or a malicious client, and may have been able to bypass the end-to-end encryption and authentication. The vulnerability is fixed per 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8. The `Metadata` struct contains an additional `was_encrypted` field, which breaks the API, but should be easily resolvable. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25287 | Lakeus vulnerable to stored XSS via system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25287</link><description>Lakeus is a simple skin made for MediaWiki. Starting in version 1.8.0 and prior to versions 1.3.1+REL1.39, 1.3.1+REL1.42, and 1.4.0, Lakeus is vulnerable to store cross-site scripting via malicious system messages, though editing the messages requires high privileges. Those with `(editinterface)` rights can edit system messages that are improperly handled in order to send raw HTML. In the case of `lakeus-footermessage`, this will affect all users if the server is configured to link back to this repository. Otherwise, the system messages in themeDesigner.js are only used when the user enables it in their preferences. Versions 1.3.1+REL1.39, 1.3.1+REL1.42, and 1.4.0 contain a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25897 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'ip' parameter at /userRpm/WanStaticIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25897</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'ip' parameter at /userRpm/WanStaticIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25898 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the pskSecret parameter at /userRpm/WlanSecurityRpm.htm. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25898</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the pskSecret parameter at /userRpm/WlanSecurityRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25899 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'gw' parameter at /userRpm/WanDynamicIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25899</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the 'gw' parameter at /userRpm/WanDynamicIpV6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25900 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the username and password parameters at /userRpm/PPPoEv6CfgRpm....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25900</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11 via the username and password parameters at /userRpm/PPPoEv6CfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0426 | A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a large number of container checkpoint requests made to the unauthenticated kubelet read...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0426</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a large number of container checkpoint requests made to the unauthenticated kubelet read-only HTTP endpoint may cause a Node Denial of Service by filling the Node's disk.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24903 | libsignal-service-rs Doesn&amp;#x27;t Check Origin of Sync Messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24903</link><description>libsignal-service-rs is a Rust version of the libsignal-service-java library which implements the core functionality to communicate with Signal servers. Prior to commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8, any contact may forge a sync message, impersonating another device of the local user. The origin of sync messages is not checked. Patched libsignal-service can be found after commit 82d70f6720e762898f34ae76b0894b0297d9b2f8. The `Metadata` struct contains an additional `was_encrypted` field, which breaks the API, but should be easily resolvable. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25901 | A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11, triggered by the dnsserver1 and dnsserver2 parameters at /userRpm/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25901</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in TP-Link TL-WR841ND V11, triggered by the dnsserver1 and dnsserver2 parameters at /userRpm/WanSlaacCfgRpm.htm. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21701 | net: avoid race between device unregistration and ethnl ops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21701</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: avoid race between device unregistration and ethnl ops

The following trace can be seen if a device is being unregistered while
its number of channels are being modified.

  DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
  WARNING: CPU: 3 PID: 3754 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:564 __mutex_lock+0xc8a/0x1120
  CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 3754 Comm: ethtool Not tainted 6.13.0-rc6+ #771
  RIP: 0010:__mutex_lock+0xc8a/0x1120
  Call Trace:
   
   ethtool_check_max_channel+0x1ea/0x880
   ethnl_set_channels+0x3c3/0xb10
   ethnl_default_set_doit+0x306/0x650
   genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x1e3/0x2c0
   genl_rcv_msg+0x432/0x6f0
   netlink_rcv_skb+0x13d/0x3b0
   genl_rcv+0x28/0x40
   netlink_unicast+0x42e/0x720
   netlink_sendmsg+0x765/0xc20
   __sys_sendto+0x3ac/0x420
   __x64_sys_sendto+0xe0/0x1c0
   do_syscall_64+0x95/0x180
   entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

This is because unregister_netdevice_many_notify might run before the
rtnl lock section of ethnl operations, eg. set_channels in the above
example. In this example the rss lock would be destroyed by the device
unregistration path before being used again, but in general running
ethnl operations while dismantle has started is not a good idea.

Fix this by denying any operation on devices being unregistered. A check
was already there in ethnl_ops_begin, but not wide enough.

Note that the same issue cannot be seen on the ioctl version
(__dev_ethtool) because the device reference is retrieved from within
the rtnl lock section there. Once dismantle started, the net device is
unlisted and no reference will be found.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26538 | WordPress Prezi Embedder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26538</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan Rossiter Prezi Embedder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Prezi Embedder: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26539 | WordPress Embed Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in petkivim Embed Google Map allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Embed Google Map: from n/a through 3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26543 | WordPress Simple Responsive Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26543</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pukhraj Suthar Simple Responsive Menu allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Responsive Menu: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26545 | WordPress Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.22 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26545</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in shisuh Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Posts Line-up-Exactly by Milliard: from n/a through 0.0.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26547 | WordPress My Login Logout Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - CSRF to  Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26547</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nagarjunsonti My Login Logout Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects My Login Logout Plugin: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26549 | WordPress WP Html Page Sitemap plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26549</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in pa1 WP Html Page Sitemap allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Html Page Sitemap: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26550 | WordPress Global Meta Keyword &amp;amp; Description plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - CSRF to Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26550</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kunal Shivale Global Meta Keyword &amp; Description allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Global Meta Keyword &amp; Description: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26551 | WordPress Bootstrap collapse plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26551</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sureshdsk Bootstrap collapse allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bootstrap collapse: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26552 | WordPress Naver Syndication V2 plugin &amp;lt;= 0.8.3 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26552</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in badrHan Naver Syndication V2 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Naver Syndication V2: from n/a through 0.8.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26558 | WordPress Aparat Responsive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mkkmail Aparat Responsive allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Aparat Responsive: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26561 | WordPress Elfsight Yottie Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in elfsight Elfsight Yottie Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Elfsight Yottie Lite: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26562 | WordPress RSS FIlter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26562</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shambhu Patnaik RSS Filter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects RSS Filter: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26567 | WordPress Font Awesome WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26567</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in farjana55 Font Awesome WP allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Font Awesome WP: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26568 | WordPress Easy Amazon Product Information plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26568</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jensmueller Easy Amazon Product Information allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Amazon Product Information: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26569 | WordPress Post Thumbs Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26569</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in callmeforsox Post Thumbs allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Post Thumbs: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26570 | WordPress Glance That plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26570</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in uamv Glance That allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Glance That: from n/a through 4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26571 | WordPress Wibiya Toolbar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26571</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wibiya Wibiya Toolbar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Wibiya Toolbar: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26572 | WordPress WP PHPList Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26572</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jesseheap WP PHPList allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP PHPList: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26574 | WordPress Google Drive WP Media plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moch Amir Google Drive WP Media allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google Drive WP Media: from n/a through 2.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26577 | WordPress DX-auto-publish plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored  XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26577</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in daxiawp DX-auto-publish allows Stored XSS. This issue affects DX-auto-publish: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26578 | WordPress Simple Documentation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26578</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mathieuhays Simple Documentation allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Documentation: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26580 | WordPress Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26580</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CompleteWebResources Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Page/Post Specific Social Share Buttons: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26582 | WordPress TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26582</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blackbam TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TinyMCE Advanced qTranslate fix editor problems: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1247 | Io.quarkus:quarkus-rest: quarkus rest endpoint request parameter leakage due to shared instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1247</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus REST that allows request parameters to leak between concurrent requests if endpoints use field injection without a CDI scope. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate request data, impersonate users, or access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1094 | PostgreSQL quoting APIs miss neutralizing quoting syntax in text that fails encoding validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1094</link><description>Improper neutralization of quoting syntax in PostgreSQL libpq functions PQescapeLiteral(), PQescapeIdentifier(), PQescapeString(), and PQescapeStringConn() allows a database input provider to achieve SQL injection in certain usage patterns.  Specifically, SQL injection requires the application to use the function result to construct input to psql, the PostgreSQL interactive terminal.  Similarly, improper neutralization of quoting syntax in PostgreSQL command line utility programs allows a source of command line arguments to achieve SQL injection when client_encoding is BIG5 and server_encoding is one of EUC_TW or MULE_INTERNAL.  Versions before PostgreSQL 17.3, 16.7, 15.11, 14.16, and 13.19 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13182 | WP Directorybox Manager &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13182</link><description>The WP Directorybox Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.5. This is due to incorrect authentication in the 'wp_dp_parse_request' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1270 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in H6Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1270</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Anapi Group's h6web, allows an authenticated attacker to access other users' information by making a POST request and modifying the “pkrelated” parameter in the “/h6web/ha_datos_hermano.php” endpoint to refer to another user. In addition, the first request could also allow the attacker to impersonate other users. As a result, all requests made after exploitation of the IDOR vulnerability will be executed with the privileges of the impersonated user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1271 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in H6Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1271</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Anapi Group's h6web. This security flaw could allow an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into a URL. When a user accesses that URL, the injected code is executed in their browser, which can result in the theft of sensitive information, identity theft or the execution of unauthorised actions on behalf of the affected user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21700 | net: sched: Disallow replacing of child qdisc from one parent to another</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21700</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: sched: Disallow replacing of child qdisc from one parent to another

Lion Ackermann was able to create a UAF which can be abused for privilege
escalation with the following script

Step 1. create root qdisc
tc qdisc add dev lo root handle 1:0 drr

step2. a class for packet aggregation do demonstrate uaf
tc class add dev lo classid 1:1 drr

step3. a class for nesting
tc class add dev lo classid 1:2 drr

step4. a class to graft qdisc to
tc class add dev lo classid 1:3 drr

step5.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 1:1 handle 2:0 plug limit 1024

step6.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 1:2 handle 3:0 drr

step7.
tc class add dev lo classid 3:1 drr

step 8.
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 3:1 handle 4:0 pfifo

step 9. Display the class/qdisc layout

tc class ls dev lo
 class drr 1:1 root leaf 2: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:2 root leaf 3: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 3:1 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb

tc qdisc ls
 qdisc drr 1: dev lo root refcnt 2
 qdisc plug 2: dev lo parent 1:1
 qdisc pfifo 4: dev lo parent 3:1 limit 1000p
 qdisc drr 3: dev lo parent 1:2

step10. trigger the bug &lt;=== prevented by this patch
tc qdisc replace dev lo parent 1:3 handle 4:0

step 11. Redisplay again the qdiscs/classes

tc class ls dev lo
 class drr 1:1 root leaf 2: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:2 root leaf 3: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 1:3 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb
 class drr 3:1 root leaf 4: quantum 64Kb

tc qdisc ls
 qdisc drr 1: dev lo root refcnt 2
 qdisc plug 2: dev lo parent 1:1
 qdisc pfifo 4: dev lo parent 3:1 refcnt 2 limit 1000p
 qdisc drr 3: dev lo parent 1:2

Observe that a) parent for 4:0 does not change despite the replace request.
There can only be one parent.  b) refcount has gone up by two for 4:0 and
c) both class 1:3 and 3:1 are pointing to it.

Step 12.  send one packet to plug
echo "" | socat -u STDIN UDP4-DATAGRAM:127.0.0.1:8888,priority=$((0x10001))
step13.  send one packet to the grafted fifo
echo "" | socat -u STDIN UDP4-DATAGRAM:127.0.0.1:8888,priority=$((0x10003))

step14. lets trigger the uaf
tc class delete dev lo classid 1:3
tc class delete dev lo classid 1:1

The semantics of "replace" is for a del/add _on the same node_ and not
a delete from one node(3:1) and add to another node (1:3) as in step10.
While we could "fix" with a more complex approach there could be
consequences to expectations so the patch takes the preventive approach of
"disallow such config".

Joint work with Lion Ackermann</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13606 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13606</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'jssupportticketdata' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/jssupportticketdata directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13867 | Listivo - Classified Ads WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.67 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13867</link><description>The Listivo - Classified Ads WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.67 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46910 | Apache Atlas: An authenticated user can perform XSS and potentially impersonate another user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46910</link><description>An authenticated user can perform XSS and potentially impersonate another user.

This issue affects Apache Atlas versions 2.3.0 and earlier.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3303 | Improper Neutralization of Input Used for LLM Prompting in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3303</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 prior to 17.6.5, starting from 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and starting from 17.8 prior to 17.8.2, which allows an attacker to exfiltrate contents of a private issue using prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13639 | Read More &amp;amp; Accordion &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary &amp;#x27;Read More&amp;#x27; Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13639</link><description>The Read More &amp; Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the expmDeleteData() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary 'read more' posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13345 | Avada Builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.13 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13345</link><description>The Avada Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.13. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13346 | Avada Theme &amp;lt;= 7.11.13 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13346</link><description>The Avada | Website Builder For WordPress &amp; WooCommerce theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 7.11.13. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0661 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0661</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.36 via the duplicate_post() function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be duplicated. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, draft, or scheduled posts that they should not have access to by duplicating the post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 07:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0814 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the network
services running on the product whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0814</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the network
services running on the product when malicious IEC61850-MMS packets are sent to the device. The core
functionality of the breaker remains intact during the attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0815 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious ICMPV6 packets are s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0815</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious ICMPV6 packets are sent to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0816 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious IPV6 packets are sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0816</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause Denial-of-Service of the
product when malicious IPV6 packets are sent to the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47264 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in agent-related functionality in Synology Acti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47264</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in agent-related functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to delete arbitrary files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47265 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in encrypted share umount functionality in Syno...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47265</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in encrypted share umount functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users to write specific files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47266 | Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in share file list functionality in Synology Ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47266</link><description>Improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in share file list functionality in Synology Active Backup for Business before 2.7.1-13234, 2.7.1-23234 and 2.7.1-3234 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to read specific files containing non-sensitive information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0327 | CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists for two services (of which one managing audit
trail data and the other acting as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0327</link><description>CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists for two services (of which one managing audit
trail data and the other acting as server managing client request) that could cause a loss of Confidentiality,
Integrity and Availability of engineering workstation when an attacker with standard privilege modifies the
executable path of the windows services. To be exploited, services need to be restarted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12586 | Chalet Montagne Com Tools &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12586</link><description>The Chalet-Montagne.com Tools WordPress plugin through 2.7.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13119 | ProfilePress &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13119</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13120 | ProfilePress &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13120</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13121 | Paid Membership Plugin &amp;lt; 4.15.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13121</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content  WordPress plugin before 4.15.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13125 | Everest Forms &amp;lt; 3.0.8.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13125</link><description>The Everest Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.0.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0692 | Simple Video Management System &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0692</link><description>The Simple Video Management System WordPress plugin through 1.0.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1060 | CWE-319: Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that could result in the exposure
of data when network traffic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1060</link><description>CWE-319: Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability exists that could result in the exposure
of data when network traffic is being sniffed by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1070 | CWE-434: Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when a malicious file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1070</link><description>CWE-434: Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when a malicious file is downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 06:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1059 | CWE-770: Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability exists that could
cause communications to stop when malicious pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1059</link><description>CWE-770: Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability exists that could
cause communications to stop when malicious packets are sent to the webserver of the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1058 | CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when malicious firmware is do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1058</link><description>CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could render the device
inoperable when malicious firmware is downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10083 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause denial of service of engineering
workstation when specific driver in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10083</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause denial of service of engineering
workstation when specific driver interface is invoked locally by an authenticated user with crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 05:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10763 | Campress &amp;lt;= 1.35 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10763</link><description>The Campress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.35 via the 'campress_woocommerce_get_ajax_products' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13227 | Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings &amp;lt;= 1.0.235 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Rank Math API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13227</link><description>The Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Rank Math API in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.235 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13229 | Rank Math SEO &amp;lt;= 1.0.235 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Schema Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13229</link><description>The Rank Math SEO – AI SEO Tools to Dominate SEO Rankings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the update_metadata() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.235. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete any schema metadata assigned to any post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13770 | Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13770</link><description>The Puzzles | WP Magazine / Review with Store WordPress Theme + RTL theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 via deserialization of untrusted input 'view_more_posts' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. The developer opted to remove the software from the repository, so an update is not available and it is recommended to find a replacement software.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0837 | Puzzles &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0837</link><description>The Puzzles theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13644 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via De Gallery Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13644</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's De Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0896 | Orthanc Server Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0896</link><description>Orthanc server prior to version 1.5.8 does not enable basic authentication by default when remote access is enabled. This could result in unauthorized access by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1198 | Insufficient Session Expiration in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1198</link><description>An issue discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.11 prior to 17.6.5, 17.7 prior to 17.7.4, and 17.8 prior to 17.8.2 meant that long-lived connections in ActionCable potentially allowed revoked Personal Access Tokens access to streaming results.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7102 | Execution with Unnecessary Privileges in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7102</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.4 prior to 17.5.0 which allows an attacker to trigger a pipeline as another user under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8266 | Execution with Unnecessary Privileges in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8266</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.1 prior to 17.6.0, which allows an attacker with maintainer role to trigger a pipeline as project owner under certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25286 | Crayfish allows Remote Code Execution via Homarus Authorization header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25286</link><description>Crayfish is a collection of Islandora 8 microservices, one of which, Homarus, provides FFmpeg as a microservice. Prior to Crayfish version 4.1.0, remote code execution may be possible in web-accessible installations of Homarus in certain configurations. The issue has been patched in `islandora/crayfish:4.1.0`. Some workarounds are available. The exploit requires making a request against the Homarus's `/convert` endpoint; therefore, the ability to exploit is much reduced if the microservice is not directly accessible from the Internet, so: Prevent general access from the Internet from hitting Homarus. Alternatively or additionally, configure auth in Crayfish to be more strongly required, such that requests with `Authorization` headers that do not validate are rejected before the problematic CLI interpolation occurs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>