<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-31216 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5. An attacker with physical acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31216</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5. An attacker with physical access to a device may be able to override managed Wi-Fi profiles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31248 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31248</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.5, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31266 | A spoofing issue was addressed with improved truncation when displaying the fully qualified domain name This issue is fixed in Safari 18.5, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31266</link><description>A spoofing issue was addressed with improved truncation when displaying the fully qualified domain name This issue is fixed in Safari 18.5, macOS Sequoia 15.5. A website may be able to spoof the domain name in the title of a pop-up window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43374 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, visionOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43374</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.7, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, visionOS 2.5, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sequoia 15.5, watchOS 11.5. An attacker in physical proximity may be able to cause an out-of-bounds read in kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11087 | Zegen Core &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11087</link><description>The Zegen Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Upload in versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation and missing file type validation in the '/custom-font-code/custom-fonts-uploads.php' file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13524 | Improper resource release in the call termination process in AWS Wickr before version 6.62.13 on Windows, macOS and Linux may allow a call p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13524</link><description>Improper resource release in the call termination process in AWS Wickr before version 6.62.13 on Windows, macOS and Linux may allow a call participant to continue receiving audio input from another user after they close their call window. This issue occurs under certain conditions, which require the affected user to take a particular action within the application

To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade AWS Wickr, Wickr Gov and Wickr Enterprise desktop version to version 6.62.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36149 | IBM Concert Software clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36149</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48502 | Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to overwrite MSR registers, potentially resulting in crash or denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48502</link><description>Improper input validation within AMD uprof can allow a local attacker to overwrite MSR registers, potentially resulting in crash or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62608 | MLX has heap-buffer-overflow in load()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62608</link><description>MLX is an array framework for machine learning on Apple silicon. Prior to version 0.29.4, there is a heap buffer overflow in mlx::core::load() when parsing malicious NumPy .npy files. Attacker-controlled file causes 13-byte out-of-bounds read, leading to crash or information disclosure. This issue has been patched in version 0.29.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62609 | MLX has Wild Pointer Dereference in load_gguf()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62609</link><description>MLX is an array framework for machine learning on Apple silicon. Prior to version 0.29.4, there is a segmentation fault in mlx::core::load_gguf() when loading malicious GGUF files. Untrusted pointer from external gguflib library is dereferenced without validation, causing application crash. This issue has been patched in version 0.29.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62626 | Improper handling of insufficient entropy in the AMD CPUs could allow a local attacker to influence the values returned by the RDSEED instru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62626</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient entropy in the AMD CPUs could allow a local attacker to influence the values returned by the RDSEED instruction, potentially resulting in the consumption of insufficiently random values.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29934 | A bug within some AMD CPUs could allow a local admin-privileged attacker to run a SEV-SNP guest using stale TLB entries, potentially resulti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29934</link><description>A bug within some AMD CPUs could allow a local admin-privileged attacker to run a SEV-SNP guest using stale TLB entries, potentially resulting in loss of data integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64169 | Wazuh NULL pointer dereference in fim_alert line 666</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64169</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. From version 3.7.0 to before 4.12.0, fim_alert() implementation does not check whether oldsum-&gt;md5 is NULL or not before dereferencing it. A compromised agent can cause a crash of analysisd by sending a specially crafted message to the wazuh manager. This issue has been patched in version 4.12.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64767 | hpke-js reuses AEAD nonces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64767</link><description>hpke-js is a Hybrid Public Key Encryption (HPKE) module built on top of Web Cryptography API. Prior to version 1.7.5, the public SenderContext Seal() API has a race condition which allows for the same AEAD nonce to be re-used for multiple Seal() calls. This can lead to complete loss of Confidentiality and Integrity of the produced messages. This issue has been patched in version 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30201 | Wazuh NetNTLMv2 Hash Theft In Multiple Centralized Configuration Capabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30201</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. Prior to version 4.13.0, a vulnerability in Wazuh Agent allows authenticated attackers to force NTLM authentication through malicious UNC paths in various agent configuration settings, potentially leading NTLM relay attacks that would result privilege escalation and remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54866 | Wazuh installation fails to protected authd.pass on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54866</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. From version 4.3.0 to before 4.13.0, a missing ACL on "C:\Program Files (x86)\ossec-agent\authd.pass" exposes the password to all "Authenticated Users" on the local machine. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13132 | Dia: Increased Spoof Risk; Missing full screen toast</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13132</link><description>This vulnerability allowed a site to enter fullscreen, after a user click, without a full-screen notification (toast) appearing. Without this notification, users could potentially be misled about what site they were on if a malicious site renders a fake UI (like a fake address bar.)</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64483 | Wazuh API – Agent Configuration Has Improper Access Control in Agent Enrollment Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64483</link><description>Wazuh is a security detection, visibility, and compliance open source project. From version 4.9.0 to before 4.13.0, the Wazuh API – Agent Configuration in certain configurations allows authenticated users with read-only API roles to retrieve agent enrollment credentials through the /utils/configuration endpoint. These credentials can be used to register new agents within the same Wazuh tenant without requiring elevated permissions through the UI. This issue has been patched in version 4.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13470 | RNP 0.18.0 Vulnerable PKESK session keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13470</link><description>In RNP version 0.18.0 a refactoring regression causes the symmetric 
session key used for Public-Key Encrypted Session Key (PKESK) packets to
 be left uninitialized except for zeroing, resulting in it always being 
an all-zero byte array.

Any data encrypted using public-key encryption 
in this release can be decrypted trivially by supplying an all-zero 
session key, fully compromising confidentiality.

The vulnerability affects only public key encryption (PKESK packets).  Passphrase-based encryption (SKESK packets) is not affected.

Root cause: Vulnerable session key buffer used in PKESK packet generation.



The defect was introduced in commit `7bd9a8dc356aae756b40755be76d36205b6b161a` where initialization 
logic inside `encrypted_build_skesk()` only randomized the key for the 
SKESK path and omitted it for the PKESK path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12747 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12747</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 via uploaded files marked as private being exposed in wp-content without adequate protection.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive information from files that have been marked as private.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12973 | S2B AI Assistant – ChatBot, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Content &amp;amp; Image Generator &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Authenticated (Editor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12973</link><description>The S2B AI Assistant – ChatBot, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Content &amp; Image Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the storeFile() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13357 | Vault Terraform Provider Applied Incorrect Defaults for LDAP Auth Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13357</link><description>Vault’s Terraform Provider incorrectly set the default deny_null_bind parameter for the LDAP auth method to false by default, potentially resulting in an insecure configuration. If the underlying LDAP server allowed anonymous or unauthenticated binds, this could result in authentication bypass. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-13357, is fixed in Vault Terraform Provider v5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13432 | Terraform Enterprise state versions can be created by users with specific permissions without sufficient write access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13432</link><description>Terraform state versions can be created by a user with specific but insufficient permissions in a Terraform Enterprise workspace. This may allow for the alteration of infrastructure if a subsequent plan operation is approved by a user with approval permission or auto-applied. This vulnerability, CVE-2025-13432, is fixed in Terraform Enterprise version 1.1.1 and 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41115 | Incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41115</link><description>SCIM provisioning was introduced in Grafana Enterprise and Grafana Cloud in April to improve how organizations manage users and teams in Grafana by introducing automated user lifecycle management.

In Grafana versions 12.x where SCIM provisioning is enabled and configured, a vulnerability in user identity handling allows a malicious or compromised SCIM client to provision a user with a numeric externalId, which in turn could allow to override internal user IDs and lead to impersonation or privilege escalation.

This vulnerability applies only if all of the following conditions are met:
- `enableSCIM` feature flag set to true
- `user_sync_enabled` config option in the `[auth.scim]` block set to true</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11127 | Mstoreapp Mobile (App &amp;lt;= 2.08, Multivendor &amp;lt;= 9.0.1) - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11127</link><description>The Mstoreapp Mobile App WordPress plugin through 2.08 and Mstoreapp Mobile Multivendor through 9.0.1 do not properly verify users identify when using an AJAX action, allowing unauthenticated users to retrieve a valid session for arbitrary users by knowing their email address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10039 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference via &amp;#x27;eh_crm_ticket_single_view_client&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10039</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 via the 'eh_crm_ticket_single_view_client' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of all support tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10054 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Role Removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10054</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_remove_agent' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove the role and capabilities of any user with an Administrator, WSDesk Supervisor, or WSDesk Agents role.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12935 | FluentCRM - Marketing Automation For WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.9.84 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;fluentcrm_content&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12935</link><description>The FluentCRM – Email Newsletter, Automation, Email Marketing, Email Campaigns, Optins, Leads, and CRM Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'fluentcrm_content' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.84 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66053 | WordPress Enfold theme &amp;lt;= 7.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kriesi Enfold enfold allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enfold: from n/a through &lt;= 7.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66055 | WordPress Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66055</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Icegram Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters email-subscribers allows Object Injection.This issue affects Email Subscribers &amp; Newsletters: from n/a through &lt;= 5.9.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66056 | WordPress Uncanny Automator plugin &amp;lt; 6.10.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66056</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator uncanny-automator allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Uncanny Automator: from n/a through &lt; 6.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66057 | WordPress Bold Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in boldthemes Bold Page Builder bold-page-builder allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through &lt;= 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66059 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66059</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66060 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66060</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66061 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66061</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting seriously-simple-podcasting allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66062 | WordPress WP YouTube Lyte plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.28 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66062</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Frank Goossens WP YouTube Lyte wp-youtube-lyte allows Phishing.This issue affects WP YouTube Lyte: from n/a through &lt;= 1.7.28.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66063 | WordPress WP Google Review Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 17.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66063</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in jgwhite33 WP Google Review Slider wp-google-places-review-slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Google Review Slider: from n/a through &lt;= 17.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66064 | WordPress Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66064</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Syed Balkhi Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress rafflepress allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress: from n/a through &lt;= 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66065 | WordPress Gutenverse plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66065</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse gutenverse allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gutenverse: from n/a through &lt;= 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66066 | WordPress Envo Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66066</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EnvoThemes Envo Extra envo-extra allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Envo Extra: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66067 | WordPress Funnel Builder by FunnelKit plugin &amp;lt;= 3.13.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66067</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelKit Funnel Builder by FunnelKit funnel-builder allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Funnel Builder by FunnelKit: from n/a through &lt;= 3.13.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66069 | WordPress PPOM for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 33.0.16 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66069</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeisle PPOM for WooCommerce woocommerce-product-addon allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PPOM for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 33.0.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66071 | WordPress Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66071</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce custom-order-numbers-for-woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Custom Order Numbers for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.11.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66072 | WordPress UsersWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.47 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66072</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stiofan UsersWP userswp allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects UsersWP: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.47.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66073 | WordPress WP Webhooks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.8 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66073</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Cozmoslabs WP Webhooks wp-webhooks allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Webhooks: from n/a through &lt;= 3.3.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66075 | WordPress WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy Consent plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66075</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Legal Pages WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent gdpr-cookie-consent allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy Consent: from n/a through &lt;= 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66077 | WordPress Legal Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66077</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpWax Legal Pages legal-pages allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Legal Pages: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66079 | WordPress Gutenverse Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse Form gutenverse-form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gutenverse Form: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66081 | WordPress Head Meta Data plugin &amp;lt;= 20250327 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66081</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeff Starr Head Meta Data head-meta-data allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Head Meta Data: from n/a through &lt;= 20250327.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66082 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66082</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently mage-eventpress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through &lt;= 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66083 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66083</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam WpEvently mage-eventpress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WpEvently: from n/a through &lt;= 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66084 | WordPress FluentCommunity plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66084</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shahjahan Jewel FluentCommunity fluent-community allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FluentCommunity: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66085 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66085</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in tychesoftwares Arconix Shortcodes arconix-shortcodes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66086 | WordPress SMS Alert Order Notifications plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66086</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cozy Vision SMS Alert Order Notifications sms-alert allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SMS Alert Order Notifications: from n/a through &lt;= 3.8.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66087 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66087</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Property Hive PropertyHive propertyhive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66089 | WordPress Product Feed for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66089</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Product Feed for WooCommerce webtoffee-product-feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Product Feed for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66090 | WordPress SKT Skill Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66090</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sonalsinha21 SKT Skill Bar skt-skill-bar allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SKT Skill Bar: from n/a through &lt;= 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66091 | WordPress Stylish Cost Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Design Stylish Cost Calculator stylish-cost-calculator allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Stylish Cost Calculator: from n/a through &lt;= 8.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66092 | WordPress Accordion Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bqworks Accordion Slider accordion-slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Accordion Slider: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66093 | WordPress Extensions for Leaflet Map plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66093</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hupe13 Extensions for Leaflet Map extensions-leaflet-map allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Extensions for Leaflet Map: from n/a through &lt;= 4.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66095 | WordPress KiviCare plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.13 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66095</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Iqonic Design KiviCare kivicare-clinic-management-system allows SQL Injection.This issue affects KiviCare: from n/a through &lt;= 3.6.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66096 | WordPress Table Block by Tableberg plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66096</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Imtiaz Rayhan Table Block by Tableberg tableberg allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Table Block by Tableberg: from n/a through &lt;= 0.6.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66097 | WordPress I Order Terms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66097</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Igor Jerosimić I Order Terms i-order-terms allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects I Order Terms: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66098 | WordPress Travelers&amp;#x27; Map plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66098</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Camille V Travelers' Map travelers-map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Travelers' Map: from n/a through &lt;= 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66099 | WordPress Chat Help plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier Chat Help chat-help allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Chat Help: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66101 | WordPress CBX Bookmark &amp;amp; Favorite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66101</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sabuj Kundu CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite cbxwpbookmark allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CBX Bookmark &amp; Favorite: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66106 | WordPress Featured Post Creative plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66106</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Essential Plugin Featured Post Creative featured-post-creative allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Post Creative: from n/a through &lt;= 1.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66107 | WordPress Subscriptions &amp;amp; Memberships for PayPal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66107</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Scott Paterson Subscriptions &amp; Memberships for PayPal subscriptions-memberships-for-paypal allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Subscriptions &amp; Memberships for PayPal: from n/a through &lt;= 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66108 | WordPress TNC Toolbox: Web Performance plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66108</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Merlot Digital (by TNC) TNC Toolbox: Web Performance tnc-toolbox allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects TNC Toolbox: Web Performance: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66109 | WordPress Cart Weight for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66109</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in octolize Cart Weight for WooCommerce woo-cart-weight allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cart Weight for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 1.9.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66110 | WordPress Tiktok Feed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.22 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66110</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Tiktok Feed b-tiktok-feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Tiktok Feed: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66111 | WordPress Nelio Popups plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66111</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nelio Software Nelio Popups nelio-popups allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Nelio Popups: from n/a through &lt;= 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66112 | WordPress Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66112</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes accessibility-plus allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Accessibility Toolkit by WebYes: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66113 | WordPress Better Chat Support for Messenger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66113</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThemeAtelier Better Chat Support for Messenger better-chat-support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Better Chat Support for Messenger: from n/a through &lt;= 1.2.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66114 | WordPress Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66114</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theme funda Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce woo-show-single-variations-shop-category allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Show Variations as Single Products Woocommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66115 | WordPress Easy Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66115</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in MatrixAddons Easy Invoice easy-invoice allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Easy Invoice: from n/a through &lt;= 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40209 | btrfs: fix memory leak of qgroup_list in btrfs_add_qgroup_relation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40209</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix memory leak of qgroup_list in btrfs_add_qgroup_relation

When btrfs_add_qgroup_relation() is called with invalid qgroup levels
(src &gt;= dst), the function returns -EINVAL directly without freeing the
preallocated qgroup_list structure passed by the caller. This causes a
memory leak because the caller unconditionally sets the pointer to NULL
after the call, preventing any cleanup.

The issue occurs because the level validation check happens before the
mutex is acquired and before any error handling path that would free
the prealloc pointer. On this early return, the cleanup code at the
'out' label (which includes kfree(prealloc)) is never reached.

In btrfs_ioctl_qgroup_assign(), the code pattern is:

    prealloc = kzalloc(sizeof(*prealloc), GFP_KERNEL);
    ret = btrfs_add_qgroup_relation(trans, sa-&gt;src, sa-&gt;dst, prealloc);
    prealloc = NULL;  // Always set to NULL regardless of return value
    ...
    kfree(prealloc);  // This becomes kfree(NULL), does nothing

When the level check fails, 'prealloc' is never freed by either the
callee or the caller, resulting in a 64-byte memory leak per failed
operation. This can be triggered repeatedly by an unprivileged user
with access to a writable btrfs mount, potentially exhausting kernel
memory.

Fix this by freeing prealloc before the early return, ensuring prealloc
is always freed on all error paths.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40210 | Revert &amp;quot;NFSD: Remove the cap on number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40210</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Revert "NFSD: Remove the cap on number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND"

I've found that pynfs COMP6 now leaves the connection or lease in a
strange state, which causes CLOSE9 to hang indefinitely. I've dug
into it a little, but I haven't been able to root-cause it yet.
However, I bisected to commit 48aab1606fa8 ("NFSD: Remove the cap on
number of operations per NFSv4 COMPOUND").

Tianshuo Han also reports a potential vulnerability when decoding
an NFSv4 COMPOUND. An attacker can place an arbitrarily large op
count in the COMPOUND header, which results in:

[   51.410584] nfsd: vmalloc error: size 1209533382144, exceeds total
pages, mode:0xdc0(GFP_KERNEL|__GFP_ZERO),
nodemask=(null),cpuset=/,mems_allowed=0

when NFSD attempts to allocate the COMPOUND op array.

Let's restore the operation-per-COMPOUND limit, but increased to 200
for now.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40211 | ACPI: video: Fix use-after-free in acpi_video_switch_brightness()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40211</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ACPI: video: Fix use-after-free in acpi_video_switch_brightness()

The switch_brightness_work delayed work accesses device-&gt;brightness
and device-&gt;backlight, freed by acpi_video_dev_unregister_backlight()
during device removal.

If the work executes after acpi_video_bus_unregister_backlight()
frees these resources, it causes a use-after-free when
acpi_video_switch_brightness() dereferences device-&gt;brightness or
device-&gt;backlight.

Fix this by calling cancel_delayed_work_sync() for each device's
switch_brightness_work in acpi_video_bus_remove_notify_handler()
after removing the notify handler that queues the work. This ensures
the work completes before the memory is freed.

[ rjw: Changelog edit ]</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 10:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12066 | WP Delete Post Copies &amp;lt;= 6.0.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12066</link><description>The WP Delete Post Copies plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12160 | Simple User Registration &amp;lt;= 6.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12160</link><description>The Simple User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpr_admin_msg' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12750 | Groundhogg &amp;lt;= 4.2.6.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12750</link><description>The Groundhogg — CRM, Newsletters, and Marketing Automation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'term' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12964 | Magical Products Display &amp;lt;= 1.1.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via MPD Pricing Table Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12964</link><description>The Magical Products Display plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mpdpr_title_tag' and 'mpdpr_subtitle_tag' parameters in the MPD Pricing Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied HTML tag names. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13138 | WP Directory Kit &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via select_2_ajax() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13138</link><description>The WP Directory Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'columns_search' parameter of the select_2_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11803 | WPSite Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11803</link><description>The WPSite Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'format' shortcode attribute in the wpsite_y shortcode and the 'before' attribute in the wpsite_postauthor shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping in error messages. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11808 | Shortcode for Google Street View &amp;lt;= 0.5.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11808</link><description>The Shortcode for Google Street View plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'streetview' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.7. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'id' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11826 | WP Company Info &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11826</link><description>The WP Company Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'class' attribute of the 'social-networks' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11973 | 简数采集器 &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11973</link><description>The 简数采集器 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 via the __kds_flag functionality that imports featured images. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Adminstrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12039 | BigBuy Dropshipping Connector for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Unauthenticated IP Spoofing to phpinfo() Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12039</link><description>The BigBuy Dropshipping Connector for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5 due to insufficient IP address validation and use of user-supplied HTTP headers as a primary method for IP retrieval. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to retrieve the output of phpinfo().</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13141 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Tag Attribute Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13141</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Gutenberg blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0 due to insufficient input validation on user-supplied HTML tag names. This is due to the lack of a tag name whitelist allowing dangerous tags like 'script', 'iframe', and 'object' to be injected even though tag_escape() is used for sanitization. While some blocks use esc_html() for content, this can be bypassed using JavaScript encoding techniques (unquoted strings, backticks, String.fromCharCode()). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13149 | Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future: Unpublish, Delete, Change Status, Trash, Change Categories &amp;lt;= 4.9.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Missing Authorization to Post/Page Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13149</link><description>The Schedule Post Changes With PublishPress Future: Unpublish, Delete, Change Status, Trash, Change Categories plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing authorization check on the "saveFutureActionData" function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author level access and above, to change the status of arbitrary posts and pages via the REST API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13156 | Vitepos – Point of Sale (POS) for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13156</link><description>The Vitepos – Point of Sale (POS) for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the insert_media_attachment() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This is due to the save_update_category_img() function accepting user-supplied file types without validation when processing category images. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which makes remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10938 | UiPress lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10938</link><description>The UiPress lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This is due to missing capability checks in the 'uip_process_block_query' AJAX function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive user data including password hashes, emails, and other user information that could be used for account takeover attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11003 | UiPress lite &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11003</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'uip_save_ui_template' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to save templates that contain custom JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11456 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11456</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the eh_crm_new_ticket_post() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11763 | Display Pages Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11763</link><description>The Display Pages Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'column_count' parameter in the [display-pages] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11764 | Shortcodes Bootstrap &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11764</link><description>The Shortcodes Bootstrap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' parameter in the [notification] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to missing input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11765 | Stock Tools &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11765</link><description>The Stock Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'image_height' and 'image_width' shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11767 | Tips Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11767</link><description>The Tips Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tip' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11768 | Islamic Phrases &amp;lt;= 2.12.2015 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11768</link><description>The Islamic Phrases plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'phrases' shortcode attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.2015. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11770 | BrightTALK WordPress Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11770</link><description>The BrightTALK WordPress Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'format' shortcode attribute in the brighttalk-time shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11771 | Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp;amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Presale Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11771</link><description>The Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated and unauthorized modification of data due to missing authentication and capability checks on the 'createSaleRecord' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate presales counters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11773 | Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp;amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Contract Address Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11773</link><description>The Cryptocurrency (Token), Launchpad (Presale), ICO &amp; IDO, Airdrop by TokenICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'saveDeployedContract' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the WordPress option `tokenico_deployed_contracts`, poisoning the smart contract addresses displayed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11799 | Affiliate AI Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11799</link><description>The Affiliate AI Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'asin' shortcode attribute in the affiai_img shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11800 | Surbma | MiniCRM Shortcode &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11800</link><description>The Surbma | MiniCRM Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' shortcode attribute of the 'minicrm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11801 | AudioTube &amp;lt;= 0.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11801</link><description>The AudioTube plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'caption' shortcode attribute of the 'audiotube' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11802 | Bulma Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11802</link><description>The Bulma Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'type' shortcode attribute in the bulma-notification shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11815 | UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.08 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11815</link><description>The UiPress lite | Effortless custom dashboards, admin themes and pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the uip_save_site_option() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary plugin settings. Other AJAX actions are also affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11885 | EchBay Admin Security &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11885</link><description>The EchBay Admin Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_ebnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11985 | Realty Portal &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11985</link><description>The Realty Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'rp_save_property_settings' function in versions 0.1 to 0.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12086 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.5.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Refund Request Cancellation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12086</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.5 via the 'wps_rma_cancel_return_request' AJAX endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete other users refund requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12135 | WPBookit &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12135</link><description>The WPBookit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'css_code' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to a missing capability check on the save_custome_code() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12138 | URL Image Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12138</link><description>The URL Image Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This is due to the plugin relying on a user-controlled Content-Type HTTP header to validate file uploads in the 'uimptr_import_image_from_url()' function which writes the file to the server before performing proper validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible via the uploaded PHP file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12170 | Checkbox &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Log Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12170</link><description>The Checkbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_checkbox_clean_log' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12660 | Padlet Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12660</link><description>The Padlet Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'key' parameter in the 'wallwisher' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12661 | Pollcaster Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12661</link><description>The Pollcaster Shortcode Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' parameter in the 'pollcaster' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12746 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12746</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12881 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.5.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Order Message Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12881</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.5 via the wps_rma_fetch_order_msgs() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read other user's order messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12894 | Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.14.17 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12894</link><description>The Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.17 via the import/export functionality and a lack of .htaccess protection. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from exports stored in /exportwp and import data stored in /importwp.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13134 | AuthorSure &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13134</link><description>The AuthorSure plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'authorsure' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13135 | HotelRunner Booking Widget &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13135</link><description>The HotelRunner Booking Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hotelrunner' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13142 | Custom Post Type &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom Post Type Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13142</link><description>The Custom Post Type plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the custom post type deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete custom post types via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13159 | Flo Forms – Easy Drag &amp;amp; Drop Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.43 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13159</link><description>The Flo Forms – Easy Drag &amp; Drop Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.43. This is due to the plugin allowing SVG file uploads via an unauthenticated AJAX endpoint (`flo_form_submit`) without proper file content validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload malicious SVG files containing JavaScript that executes when an administrator views the uploaded file in the WordPress admin interface, leading to potential full site compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13322 | WP AUDIO GALLERY &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via &amp;#x27;audio_upload&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13322</link><description>The WP AUDIO GALLERY plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to the `wpag_uploadaudio_callback()` AJAX handler not properly validating user-supplied file paths in the `audio_upload` parameter before passing them to `unlink()`. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when critical files like wp-config.php are deleted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 07:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58097 | The installation directory of LogStare Collector is configured with incorrect access permissions. A non-administrative user may manipulate f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58097</link><description>The installation directory of LogStare Collector is configured with incorrect access permissions. A non-administrative user may manipulate files within the installation directory and execute arbitrary code with the administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61949 | LogStare Collector contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in UserManagement. If crafted user information is stored, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61949</link><description>LogStare Collector contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in UserManagement. If crafted user information is stored, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who logs in to the product's management page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62189 | LogStare Collector contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability in UserRegistration. If exploited, a non-administrative user may create...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62189</link><description>LogStare Collector contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability in UserRegistration. If exploited, a non-administrative user may create a new user account by sending a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62687 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in LogStare Collector. If a user views a crafted page while logged, unintended operations ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62687</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in LogStare Collector. If a user views a crafted page while logged, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64299 | LogStare Collector improperly handles the password hash data. An administrative user may obtain the other users' password hashes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64299</link><description>LogStare Collector improperly handles the password hash data. An administrative user may obtain the other users' password hashes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64695 | Uncontrolled search path element issue exists in the installer of LogStare Collector (for Windows). If exploited, arbitrary code may be exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64695</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element issue exists in the installer of LogStare Collector (for Windows). If exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with the privilege of the user invoking the installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13499 | Access of Uninitialized Pointer in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13499</link><description>Kafka dissector crash in Wireshark 4.6.0 and 4.4.0 to 4.4.10 allows denial of service</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 06:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11368 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Callback Execution to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11368</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.9.4. This is due to missing capability checks in the REST endpoint /wp-json/lp/v1/load_content_via_ajax which allows arbitrary callback execution of admin-only template methods. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve admin curriculum HTML, quiz questions with correct answers, course materials, and other sensitive educational content via the REST API endpoint granted they can supply valid numeric IDs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12022 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Trash Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12022</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_settings_restore_trash' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to restore all deleted tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12023 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Ticket Restore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12023</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the eh_crm_restore_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to restore tickets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12085 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Trash Empty</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12085</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eh_crm_settings_empty_trash' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to empty the ticket trash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12169 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenitcated (Subscriber+) to Scheduled Trigger Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12169</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_ajax_eh_crm_settings_empty_scheduled_actions' AJAX Action in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the scheduled triggers option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9825 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9825</link><description>GitLab has remediated an issue in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 13.7 to 18.2.8, 18.3 before 18.3.4, and 18.4 before 18.4.2 that could have allowed authenticated users without project membership to view sensitive manual CI/CD variables by querying the GraphQL API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64310 | EPSON WebConfig and Epson Web Control for SEIKO EPSON Projector Products do not restrict excessive authentication attempts. An administrativ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64310</link><description>EPSON WebConfig and Epson Web Control for SEIKO EPSON Projector Products do not restrict excessive authentication attempts. An administrative user's password may be identified through a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 03:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62164 | VLLM deserialization vulnerability leading to DoS and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62164</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From versions 0.10.2 to before 0.11.1, a memory corruption vulnerability could lead to a crash (denial-of-service) and potentially remote code execution (RCE), exists in the Completions API endpoint. When processing user-supplied prompt embeddings, the endpoint loads serialized tensors using torch.load() without sufficient validation. Due to a change introduced in PyTorch 2.8.0, sparse tensor integrity checks are disabled by default. As a result, maliciously crafted tensors can bypass internal bounds checks and trigger an out-of-bounds memory write during the call to to_dense(). This memory corruption can crash vLLM and potentially lead to code execution on the server hosting vLLM. This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62372 | vLLM vulnerable to DoS with incorrect shape of multimodal embedding inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62372</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From version 0.5.5 to before 0.11.1, users can crash the vLLM engine serving multimodal models by passing multimodal embedding inputs with correct ndim but incorrect shape (e.g. hidden dimension is wrong), regardless of whether the model is intended to support such inputs (as defined in the Supported Models page). This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62426 | vLLM vulnerable to DoS via large Chat Completion or Tokenization requests with specially crafted `chat_template_kwargs`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62426</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). From version 0.5.5 to before 0.11.1, the /v1/chat/completions and /tokenize endpoints allow a chat_template_kwargs request parameter that is used in the code before it is properly validated against the chat template. With the right chat_template_kwargs parameters, it is possible to block processing of the API server for long periods of time, delaying all other requests. This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64751 | OpenFGA Improper Policy Enforcement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64751</link><description>OpenFGA is a high-performance and flexible authorization/permission engine built for developers and inspired by Google Zanzibar. OpenFGA v1.4.0 to v1.11.0 ( openfga-0.1.34 &lt;= Helm chart &lt;= openfga-0.2.48, v.1.4.0 &lt;= docker &lt;= v.1.11.0) are vulnerable to improper policy enforcement when certain Check and ListObject calls are executed. This issue has been patched in version 1.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64755 | @anthropic-ai/claude-code has Sed Command Validation Bypass that Allows Arbitrary File Writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64755</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 2.0.31, due to an error in sed command parsing, it was possible to bypass the Claude Code read-only validation and write to arbitrary files on the host system. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64762 | authkit-nextjs may let session cookies be cached in CDNs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64762</link><description>The AuthKit library for Next.js provides convenient helpers for authentication and session management using WorkOS &amp; AuthKit with Next.js. In authkit-nextjs version 2.11.0 and below, authenticated responses do not defensively apply anti-caching headers. In environments where CDN caching is enabled, this can result in session tokens being included in cached responses and subsequently served to multiple users. Next.js applications deployed on Vercel are unaffected unless they manually enable CDN caching by setting cache headers on authenticated paths. Patched in authkit-nextjs 2.11.1, which applies anti-caching headers to all responses behind authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13485 | itsourcecode Online File Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13485</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Online File Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 01:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13484 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System customer-list.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13484</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/customer-list.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49752 | Azure Bastion Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49752</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59245 | Microsoft SharePoint Online Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59245</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62207 | Azure Monitor Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62207</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62459 | Microsoft Defender Portal Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62459</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64655 | Dynamics OmniChannel SDK Storage Containers Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64655</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64660 | GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio Code Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64660</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36072 | IBM webMethods Integration Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36072</link><description>IBM webMethods Integration 10.11 through 10.11_Core_Fix22, 10.15 through 10.15_Core_Fix22, and 11.1 through 11.1_Core_Fix6 IBM webMethods Integration allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by the deserialization of untrusted object graphs data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13087 | Command Injection in Opto22 Groov REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13087</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the Opto22 Groov Manage REST API on GRV-EPIC and groov RIO Products that allows remote code execution with root privileges. When a POST request is executed against the vulnerable endpoint, the application reads certain header details and unsafely uses these values to build commands, allowing an attacker with administrative privileges to inject arbitrary commands that execute as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36153 | IBM Concert Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36153</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36158 | IBM Concert Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36158</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a local user with specific permission to obtain sensitive information from files due to uncontrolled recursive directory copying.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36159 | IBM Concert Improper Log Neutralization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36159</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a local user to forge log files to impersonate other users or hide their identity due to improper neutralization of output.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61138 | Qlik Sense Enterprise v14.212.13 was discovered to contain an information leak via the /dev-hub/ directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61138</link><description>Qlik Sense Enterprise v14.212.13 was discovered to contain an information leak via the /dev-hub/ directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36160 | IBM Concert Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36160</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could disclose sensitive server information from HTTP response headers that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63685 | Quark Cloud Drive v3.23.2 has a DLL Hijacking vulnerability. This vulnerability stems from the insecure loading of system libraries. Specifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63685</link><description>Quark Cloud Drive v3.23.2 has a DLL Hijacking vulnerability. This vulnerability stems from the insecure loading of system libraries. Specifically, the application does not validate the path or signature of [regsvr32.exe] it loads. An attacker can place a crafted malicious DLL in the application's startup directory, which will be loaded and executed when the user launches the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25613 | FS Inc S3150-8T2F 8-Port Gigabit Ethernet L2+ Switch, 8 x Gigabit RJ45, with 2 x 1Gb SFP, Fanless. All versions before 2.2.0D Build 135103 w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25613</link><description>FS Inc S3150-8T2F 8-Port Gigabit Ethernet L2+ Switch, 8 x Gigabit RJ45, with 2 x 1Gb SFP, Fanless. All versions before 2.2.0D Build 135103 were discovered to transmit cookies for their web based administrative application containing usernames and passwords. These were transmitted in cleartext using simple base64 encoding during every POST request made to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62674 | Missing Authentication for RTSP in iCam Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62674</link><description>The affected product allows unauthenticated access to Real Time Streaming Protocol (RTSP) services, which may allow an attacker unauthorized access to camera configuration information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63807 | An issue was discovered in weijiang1994 university-bbs (aka Blogin) in commit 9e06bab430bfc729f27b4284ba7570db3b11ce84 (2025-01-13). A weak ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63807</link><description>An issue was discovered in weijiang1994 university-bbs (aka Blogin) in commit 9e06bab430bfc729f27b4284ba7570db3b11ce84 (2025-01-13). A weak verification code generation mechanism combined with missing rate limiting allows attackers to perform brute-force attacks on verification codes without authentication. Successful exploitation may result in account takeover via password reset or other authentication bypass methods.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64770 | Missing Authentication for ONVIF in iCam Cameras</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64770</link><description>The affected products allow unauthenticated access to Open Network Video Interface Forum (ONVIF) services, which may allow an attacker unauthorized access to camera configuration information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35029 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health stored cross site scripting via Demographic Information page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35029</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a stored cross site scripting vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to add arbitrary content in the 'Demographic Information' page. This content will be rendered and executed when a victim accesses it. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48986 | Authorization bypass in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an logged in attacker to change other users' email addre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48986</link><description>Authorization bypass in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an logged in attacker to change other users' email address and potentialy take over their accounts using the forgot password functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48987 | Improper Neutralization of Input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes a potential reflected XSS attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes a potential reflected XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52666 | Improper neutralisation of format characters in the settings of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an administrator...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52666</link><description>Improper neutralisation of format characters in the settings of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes an administrator user to disable the admin user console due to a fatal PHP error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52667 | Missing JSON Content-Type header in a script in Revive Adserver 6.0.1 and 5.5.2 and earlier versions causes a stored XSS attack to be possib...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52667</link><description>Missing JSON Content-Type header in a script in Revive Adserver 6.0.1 and 5.5.2 and earlier versions causes a stored XSS attack to be possible for a logged in manager user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52668 | Improper input neutralization in the stats-conversions.php script in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes potential i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52668</link><description>Improper input neutralization in the stats-conversions.php script in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes potential information disclosure and session hijacking via a stored XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52669 | Insecure design policies in the user management system of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to hav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52669</link><description>Insecure design policies in the user management system of Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to have access to the contact name and email address of other users on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52670 | Missing authorization check in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes users on the system to delete banners owned by ot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52670</link><description>Missing authorization check in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes users on the system to delete banners owned by other accounts</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52671 | Debug information disclosure in the SQL error message to in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52671</link><description>Debug information disclosure in the SQL error message to in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes non-admin users to acquire information about the software, PHP and database versions currently in use.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55123 | Improper neutralization of input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes manager accounts to be able to craft XSS att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55123</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Revive Adserver 5.5.2 and 6.0.1 and earlier versions causes manager accounts to be able to craft XSS attacks to their own advertiser users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55124 | Improper neutralisation of input in Revive Adserver 6.0.0+ causes a reflected XSS attack in the banner-zone.php script.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55124</link><description>Improper neutralisation of input in Revive Adserver 6.0.0+ causes a reflected XSS attack in the banner-zone.php script.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55126 | HackerOne community member Dang Hung Vi (vidang04) has reported a stored XSS vulnerability involving the navigation box at the top of advert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55126</link><description>HackerOne community member Dang Hung Vi (vidang04) has reported a stored XSS vulnerability involving the navigation box at the top of advertiser-related pages, with campaign names being the vector for the stored XSS</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55127 | HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an improper neutralization of whitespace in the username when adding new u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55127</link><description>HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an improper neutralization of whitespace in the username when adding new users. A username with leading or trailing whitespace could be virtually indistinguishable from its legitimate counterpart when the username is displayed in the UI, potentially leading to confusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55128 | HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the “userlog-index.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55128</link><description>HackerOne community member Dao Hoang Anh (yoyomiski) has reported an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in the “userlog-index.php”. An attacker with access to the admin interface could request an arbitrarily large number of items per page, potentially leading to a denial of service</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63700 | An issue was discovered in Clerk-js 5.88.0 allowing attackers to bypass the OAuth authentication flow by manipulating the request at the OTP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63700</link><description>An issue was discovered in Clerk-js 5.88.0 allowing attackers to bypass the OAuth authentication flow by manipulating the request at the OTP verification stage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10571 | ABB Ability Edgenius Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10571</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in ABB ABB Ability Edgenius.This issue affects ABB Ability Edgenius: 3.2.0.0, 3.2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64524 | CUPS rastertopclx Filter Vulnerable to Heap Buffer Overflow Leading to Potential Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64524</link><description>cups-filters contains backends, filters, and other software required to get the cups printing service working on operating systems other than macos. In versions 2.0.1 and prior, a heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability in the rastertopclx filter causes the program to crash with a segmentation fault when processing maliciously crafted input data. This issue can be exploited to trigger memory corruption, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution. This issue has been patched via commit 956283c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63888 | The read function in file thinkphp\library\think\template\driver\File.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 contains a remote code execution vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63888</link><description>The read function in file thinkphp\library\think\template\driver\File.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 contains a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63889 | The fetch function in file thinkphp\library\think\Template.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via crafted file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63889</link><description>The fetch function in file thinkphp\library\think\Template.php in ThinkPHP 5.0.24 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via crafted file path in a template value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64428 | DataEase DB2 JNDI Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64428</link><description>Dataease is an open source data visualization analysis tool. Versions prior to 2.10.17 are vulnerable to JNDI injection. A blacklist was added in the patch for version 2.10.14. However, JNDI injection remains possible via the iiop, corbaname, and iiopname schemes. The vulnerability has been fixed in version 2.10.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63848 | Stored cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability in SWISH prolog thru 2.2.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted web IDE ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63848</link><description>Stored cross site scripting (xss) vulnerability in SWISH prolog thru 2.2.0 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted web IDE notebook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64185 | Open OnDemand RPM packages create world writable locations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64185</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16, Open OnDemand packages create world writable locations in the GEM_PATH. Open OnDemand versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16 have been patched for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62709 | ClipBucket v5 is vulnerable to password reset link manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62709</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. In ClipBucket version 5.5.2, a change to network.class.php causes the application to dynamically build the server URL from the incoming HTTP Host header when the configuration base_url is not set. Because Host is a client-controlled header, an attacker can supply an arbitrary Host value. This allows an attacker to cause password-reset links (sent by forget.php) to be generated with the attacker’s domain. If a victim follows that link and enters their activation code on the attacker-controlled domain, the attacker can capture the code and use it to reset the victim’s password and take over the account. This issue has been patched in version 5.5.2#162.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62724 | Open OnDemand allowlist bypass using symlinks in directory downloads (TOCTOU)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62724</link><description>Open OnDemand is an open-source HPC portal. Prior to versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16, users can craft a "Time of Check to Time of Use" (TOCTOU) attack when downloading zip files to access files outside of the OOD_ALLOWLIST. This vulnerability impacts sites that use the file browser allowlists in all current versions of OOD. However, files accessed are still protected by the UNIX permissions. Open OnDemand versions 4.0.8 and 3.1.16 have been patched for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12120 | CVE-2025-12120</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12120</link><description>Lite XL versions 2.1.8 and prior automatically execute the .lite_project.lua file when opening a project directory, without prompting the user for confirmation. The .lite_project.lua file is intended for project-specific configuration but can contain executable Lua logic. This behavior could allow execution of untrusted Lua code if a user opens a malicious project, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the Lite XL process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12121 | CVE-2025-12121</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12121</link><description>Lite XL versions 2.1.8 and prior contain a vulnerability in the system.exec function, which allowed arbitrary command execution through unsanitized shell command construction. This function was used in project directory launching (core.lua), drag-and-drop file handling (rootview.lua), and the “open in system” command in the treeview plugin (treeview.lua). If an attacker could influence input to system.exec, they might execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the Lite XL process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64027 | Snipe-IT v8.3.4 (build 20218) contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CSV Import workflow. When an invalid CSV ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64027</link><description>Snipe-IT v8.3.4 (build 20218) contains a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CSV Import workflow. When an invalid CSV file is uploaded, the application returns a progress_message value that is rendered as raw HTML in the admin interface. An attacker can intercept and modify the POST /livewire/update request to inject arbitrary HTML or JavaScript into the progress_message. Because the server accepts the modified input without sanitization and reflects it back to the user, arbitrary JavaScript executes in the browser of any authenticated admin who views the import page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13437 | Arbitrary node_modules Directory Deletion in Google zx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13437</link><description>When zx is invoked with --prefer-local=, the CLI creates a symlink named ./node_modules pointing to /node_modules. Due to a logic error in src/cli.ts (linkNodeModules / cleanup), the function returns the target path instead of the alias (symlink path). The later cleanup routine removes what it received, which deletes the target directory itself. Result: zx can delete an external /node_modules outside the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52410 | Institute-of-Current-Students v1.0 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The `myds` ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52410</link><description>Institute-of-Current-Students v1.0 contains a time-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The `myds` GET parameter is not adequately sanitized before being used in SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62875 | Local DoS in OpenSMTPD via UNIX domain socket smtpd.sock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62875</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in OpenSMTPD allows local users to crash OpenSMTPD.




This issue affects openSUSE Tumbleweed: from ? before 7.8.0p0-1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62294 | Predictable Generation of Password Recovery Token</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62294</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Predictable Generation of Password Recovery Token. Due to weak mechanism of generating recovery tokens, a malicious attacker is able to brute-force all possible values and takeover any account in reasonable amount of time.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62295 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62295</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /groupe_form endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening editor.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62296 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62296</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /taches endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening editor.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62297 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62297</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /projets endpoint. Malicious attacker with medium privileges can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening edited page.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62729 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62729</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /status endpoint. Malicious attacker with an account can inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening multiple pages.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62730 | Privilege Escalation via Incorrect Authorization in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62730</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in user management tab. Users with user_manage_team role are allowed to modify permissions of users. However, they are able to assign administrative permissions to any user including themselves. This allow a malicious authenticated attacker with this role to escalate to admin privileges. This issue affects both Bulk Update functionality and regular edition of user's right and privileges.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62731 | Stored XSS in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62731</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Stored XSS in /feries endpoint. Malicious attacker with access to public holidays feature is able to inject arbitrary HTML and JS into website, which will be rendered/executed when opening multiple pages. By default only administrators and users with special privileges are able to access this endpoint.

This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62293 | Broken Access Control in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62293</link><description>SOPlanning is vulnerable to Broken Access Control in /status endpoint. Due to lack of permission checks in Project Status functionality an authenticated attacker is able to add, edit and delete any status.


This issue was fixed in version 1.54.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13425 | Denial of Service in OSV-SCALIBR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13425</link><description>A bug in the filesystem traversal fallback path causes fs/diriterate/diriterate.go:Next() to overindex an empty slice when ReadDir returns nil for an empty directory, resulting in a panic (index out of range) and an application crash (denial of service) in OSV-SCALIBR.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34320 | BASIS BBj &amp;lt; 25.00 Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34320</link><description>BASIS BBj versions prior to 25.00 contain a Jetty-served web endpoint that fails to properly validate or canonicalize input path segments. This allows unauthenticated directory traversal sequences to cause the server to read arbitrary system files accessible to the account running the service. Retrieved configuration artifacts may contain account credentials used for BBj Enterprise Manager; possession of these credentials enables administrative access and use of legitimate management functionality that can result in execution of system commands under the service account. Depending on the operating system and the privileges of the BBj service account, this issue may also allow access to other sensitive files on the host, including operating system or application data, potentially exposing additional confidential information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36161 | IBM Concert Software Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36161</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict-Transport-Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60737 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version&lt;= 4.7.18.0.eden:Logic Version&lt;=6.00 - 2025_07_21 allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60737</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version&lt;= 4.7.18.0.eden:Logic Version&lt;=6.00 - 2025_07_21 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /index.php component</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60738 | An issue in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before Logic Version v6.00 - 2025_07_21 and before allows a remote atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60738</link><description>An issue in Ilevia EVE X1 Server Firmware Version v4.7.18.0.eden and before Logic Version v6.00 - 2025_07_21 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the ping.php component does not perform secure filtering on IP parameters</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60798 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in display.php at line 396. The application passes user-controlled inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60798</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in display.php at line 396. The application passes user-controlled input from $_REQUEST['query'] directly to the browseQuery function without proper sanitization. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary SQL commands through malicious query manipulation, potentially leading to complete database compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60799 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains an incorrect access control vulnerability in sql.php at lines 68-76. The application allows unauthori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60799</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains an incorrect access control vulnerability in sql.php at lines 68-76. The application allows unauthorized manipulation of session variables by accepting user-controlled parameters ('subject', 'server', 'database', 'queryid') without proper validation or access control checks. Attackers can exploit this to store arbitrary SQL queries in $_SESSION['sqlquery'] by manipulating these parameters, potentially leading to session poisoning, stored cross-site scripting, or unauthorized access to sensitive session data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65220 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in: /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg via the list parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65220</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in: /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg via the list parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60796 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities across various components. User-supplied input fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60796</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities across various components. User-supplied input from $_REQUEST parameters is reflected in HTML output without proper encoding or sanitization in multiple locations including sequences.php, indexes.php, admin.php, and other unspecified files. An attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers, potentially leading to session hijacking, credential theft, or other malicious actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60797 | phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in dataexport.php at line 118. The application directly executes user-s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60797</link><description>phpPgAdmin 7.13.0 and earlier contains a SQL injection vulnerability in dataexport.php at line 118. The application directly executes user-supplied SQL queries from the $_REQUEST['query'] parameter without any sanitization or parameterization via $data-&gt;conn-&gt;Execute($_REQUEST['query']). An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary SQL commands, potentially leading to complete database compromise, data theft, or privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65221 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter of /goform/setPptpUserList.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65221</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter of /goform/setPptpUserList.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65222 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65222</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65223 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the urls parameter of /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65223</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the urls parameter of /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60794 | Session tokens and passwords in couch-auth 0.21.2 are stored in JavaScript objects and remain in memory without explicit clearing in src/use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60794</link><description>Session tokens and passwords in couch-auth 0.21.2 are stored in JavaScript objects and remain in memory without explicit clearing in src/user.ts lines 700-707. This creates a window of opportunity for sensitive data extraction through memory dumps, debugging tools, or other memory access techniques, potentially leading to session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65226 | Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter in /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65226</link><description>Tenda AC21 V16.03.08.16 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter in /goform/saveParentControlInfo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0645 | Arbitrary File Upload in Narkom Communication Technologies&amp;#x27; Pyxis Signage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0645</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Narkom Communication and Software Technologies Trade Ltd. Co. Pyxis Signage allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Pyxis Signage: through 31012025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13469 | Public Knowledge Project omp/ojs Payment Instructions Setting paymentForm.tpl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13469</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Public Knowledge Project omp and ojs 3.3.0/3.4.0/3.5.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file plugins/paymethod/manual/templates/paymentForm.tpl of the component Payment Instructions Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument manualInstructions leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0643 | XSS in Narkom Communication Technologies&amp;#x27; Pyxis Signage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Narkom Communication and Software Technologies Trade Ltd. Co. Pyxis Signage allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pyxis Signage: through 31012025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13468 | SourceCodester Alumni Management System Delete admin_class.php delete_event authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13468</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Alumni Management System 1.0. This issue affects the function delete_forum/delete_career/delete_comment/delete_gallery/delete_event of the file admin/admin_class.php of the component Delete Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41074 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41074</link><description>Vulnerability in LimeSurvey 6.13.0  in the endpoint /optout that causes infinite HTTP redirects when accessed directly. This behavior can be exploited to generate a Denegation of Service (DoS  attack), by exhausting server or client resources. The system is unable to break the redirect loop, which can cause service degradation or browser instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41075 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41075</link><description>Vulnerability in LimeSurvey 6.13.0 in the endpoint /optin that causes infinite HTTP redirects when accessed directly. This behavior can be exploited to generate a Denegation of Service (DoS  attack), by exhausting server or client resources. The system is unable to break the redirect loop, which can cause service degradation or browser instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41076 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Limesurvey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41076</link><description>In version 6.13.0 of LimeSurvey, any external user can cause a 500 error in the survey system by sending a malformed session cookie. Instead of displaying a generic error message, the system exposes internal backend information, including the use of the Yii framework, the MySQL/MariaDB database engine, the table name 'lime_sessions', primary keys, and fragments of the content that caused the conflict. This information can simplify the collection of data about the internal architecture of the application by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40601 | A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Servic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40601</link><description>A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS), which could cause an impacted firewall to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40604 | Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verify...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40604</link><description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verifying signatures, allowing attackers with VMDK or datastore access to modify system files and gain persistent arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40605 | A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40605</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by injecting crafted directory-traversal sequences (such as ../) and may access files and directories outside the intended restricted path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12414 | Looker account compromise via punycode homograph attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12414</link><description>An attacker could take over a Looker account in a Looker instance configured with OIDC authentication, due to email address string normalization.Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.

This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page   https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.100+
  *  24.18.193+
  *  25.0.69+
  *  25.6.57+
  *  25.8.39+
  *  25.10.22+
  *  25.12.0+</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11676 | UPnP DOS in TL-WR940N V6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11676</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in TP-Link System Inc. TL-WR940N V6 (UPnP modules), which allows unauthenticated adjacent attackers to perform DoS attack. This issue affects TL-WR940N V6 &lt;= Build 220801.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62346 | HCL Glovius Cloud is susceptible to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62346</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability was identified in HCL Glovius Cloud. An attacker can force a user's web browser to execute an unwanted, malicious action on a trusted site where the user is authenticated, specifically on one endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64984 | Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Linux (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), K...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64984</link><description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Linux (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), Kaspersky Industrial CyberSecurity for Linux Nodes (any version with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025), and Kaspersky Endpoint Security for Mac (12.0.0.325, 12.1.0.553, and 12.2.0.694 with anti-virus databases prior to 18.11.2025) that could have allowed a reflected XSS attack to be carried out by an attacker using phishing techniques.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5092 | Multiple Plugins and Themes &amp;lt;= (Various Versions) - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via lightGallery JavaScript Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5092</link><description>Multiple plugins and/or themes for WordPress are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bundled lightGallery library (&lt;= 2.8.3) in various versions due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 06:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12502 | Attention Bar &amp;lt;= 0.7.2.1 - Admin+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12502</link><description>The attention-bar WordPress plugin through 0.7.2.1 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing high privilege users such as administrator to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 06:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12778 | Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12778</link><description>The Ultimate Member Widgets for Elementor – WordPress User Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_filter_users function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract partial metadata of all WordPress users, including their first name, last name and email addresses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13450 | SourceCodester Online Shop Project register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13450</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in SourceCodester Online Shop Project 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /shop/register.php. This manipulation of the argument f_name causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13451 | SourceCodester Online Shop Project action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13451</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Online Shop Project 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /action.php. Such manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13446 | Tenda AC21 SetSysTimeCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13446</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument timeZone/time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13449 | code-projects Online Shop Project login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13449</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shop Project 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Password results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13443 | macrozheng mall delete access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13443</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. Affected by this issue is the function delete of the file /member/readHistory/delete. Performing manipulation of the argument ids results in improper access controls. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13445 | Tenda AC21 SetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13445</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. Executing manipulation of the argument list can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:09:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13435 | Dreampie Resty HttpClient HttpClient.java request path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13435</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Dreampie Resty up to 1.3.1.SNAPSHOT. This affects the function Request of the file /resty-httpclient/src/main/java/cn/dreampie/client/HttpClient.java of the component HttpClient Module. Such manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13442 | UTT 进取 750W formPdbUpConfig system command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13442</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in UTT 进取 750W up to 3.2.2-191225. Affected by this vulnerability is the function system of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Such manipulation of the argument policyNames leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13434 | jameschz Hush Framework HTTP Host Header Util.php http headers for scripting syntax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13434</link><description>A weakness has been identified in jameschz Hush Framework 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file Hush\hush-lib\hush\Util.php of the component HTTP Host Header Handler. This manipulation of the argument $_SERVER['HOST'] causes improper neutralization of http headers for scripting syntax. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13433 | Muse Group MuseHub Windows Service Muse.Updater.exe unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13433</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Muse Group MuseHub 2.1.0.1567. The affected element is an unknown function of the file C:\Program Files\WindowsApps\Muse.MuseHub_2.1.0.1567_x64__rb9pth70m6nz6\Muse.Updater.exe of the component Windows Service. The manipulation results in unquoted search path. The attack is only possible with local access. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is described as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13424 | Campcodes Supplier Management System add_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13424</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_product.php. The manipulation of the argument txtProductName leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13422 | freeprojectscodes Sports Club Management System change_s_pwd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13422</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in freeprojectscodes Sports Club Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/admin/change_s_pwd.php. Performing manipulation of the argument login_id results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13423 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13423</link><description>A flaw has been found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin_product.php. Executing manipulation of the argument product_image can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13421 | itsourcecode Human Resource Management System NoticeStore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13421</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in itsourcecode Human Resource Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /src/store/NoticeStore.php. Such manipulation of the argument noticeDesc leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13420 | itsourcecode Human Resource Management System EventStore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13420</link><description>A weakness has been identified in itsourcecode Human Resource Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/store/EventStore.php. This manipulation of the argument eventSubject causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13415 | icret EasyImages SVG Image upload.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13415</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in icret EasyImages up to 2.8.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /app/upload.php of the component SVG Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11001 | 7-Zip ZIP File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11001</link><description>7-Zip ZIP File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of 7-Zip. Interaction with this product is required to exploit this vulnerability but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of symbolic links in ZIP files. Crafted data in a ZIP file can cause the process to traverse to unintended directories. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of a service account. Was ZDI-CAN-26753.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11884 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability discovered in OpenText™ Universal Discovery and CMDB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11884</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in opentext uCMDB allows Stored XSS. The vulnerability could allow an attacker has high level access to UCMDB to create or update data with malicious scripts

This issue affects uCMDB: 24.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13412 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_running.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13412</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_running.php. Executing manipulation of the argument product_name can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63719 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin/index.php via the parameter username.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63719</link><description>Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /admin/index.php via the parameter username.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63371 | Milos Paripovic OneCommander 3.102.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the ZIP file processing component,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63371</link><description>Milos Paripovic OneCommander 3.102.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The vulnerability resides in the ZIP file processing component, specifically in the functionality responsible for extracting and handling ZIP archive contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13147 | External Service Interaction (DNS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13147</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Progress MOVEit Transfer.This issue affects MOVEit Transfer: before 2024.1.8, from 2025.0.0 before 2025.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47914 | CVE-2025-47914 in golang.org/x/crypto/ssh/agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47914</link><description>SSH Agent servers do not validate the size of messages when processing new identity requests, which may cause the program to panic if the message is malformed due to an out of bounds read.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58181 | CVE-2025-58181 in golang.org/x/crypto/ssh</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58181</link><description>SSH servers parsing GSSAPI authentication requests do not validate the number of mechanisms specified in the request, allowing an attacker to cause unbounded memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13410 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store receipt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13410</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/receipt.php. Such manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13411 | Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store admin_football.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Retro Basketball Shoes Online Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_football.php. Performing manipulation of the argument product_image results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63932 | D-Link Router DIR-868L A1 FW106KRb01.bin has an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the cgibin binary. The HNAP service p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63932</link><description>D-Link Router DIR-868L A1 FW106KRb01.bin has an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability in the cgibin binary. The HNAP service provided by cgibin does not filter the HTTP SOAPAction header field. The unauthenticated remote attacker can execute the shell command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36371 | IBM i Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36371</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 are impacted by obtaining an information vulnerability in the database plan cache implementation.  A user with access to the database plan cache could see information they do not have authority to view.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51661 | A path Traversal vulnerability found in FileCodeBox v2.2 and earlier allows arbitrary file writes when application is configured to use loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51661</link><description>A path Traversal vulnerability found in FileCodeBox v2.2 and earlier allows arbitrary file writes when application is configured to use local filesystem storage. SystemFileStorage.save_file method in core/storage.py uses filenames from user input without validation to construct save_path and save files. This allows remote attackers to perform arbitrary file writes outside the intended directory by sending crafted POST requests with malicious traversal sequences to /share/file/ upload endpoint, which does not require any authorization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51662 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability is found in the text sharing feature of FileCodeBox version 2.2 and earlier. Insufficient ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51662</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability is found in the text sharing feature of FileCodeBox version 2.2 and earlier. Insufficient input validation allows attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into shared text "codeboxes". The xss payload is automatically executed in the browsers of any users who try to access the infected codebox by clicking link or entering share code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51663 | A vulnerability found in IPRateLimit implementation of FileCodeBox up to 2.2 allows remote attackers to bypass ip-based rate limit protectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51663</link><description>A vulnerability found in IPRateLimit implementation of FileCodeBox up to 2.2 allows remote attackers to bypass ip-based rate limit protection and failed attempt restrictions by faking X-Real-IP and X-Forwarded-For HTTP headers. This can enable attackers to perform DoS attacks or brute force share codes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63214 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware version 6.5.0-10 , 6.5.0-9, allowing unauthorized attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63214</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware version 6.5.0-10 , 6.5.0-9, allowing unauthorized attackers to delete and create arbitrary accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63212 | GatesAir Flexiva-LX devices on firmware 1.0.13 and 2.0, including models LX100, LX300, LX600, and LX1000, expose sensitive session identifie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63212</link><description>GatesAir Flexiva-LX devices on firmware 1.0.13 and 2.0, including models LX100, LX300, LX600, and LX1000, expose sensitive session identifiers (sid) in the publicly accessible log file located at /log/Flexiva%20LX.log. An unauthenticated attacker can retrieve valid session IDs and hijack sessions without providing any credentials. This attack requires the legitimate user (admin) to have previously closed the browser window without logging out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:48:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63213 | The QVidium Opera11 device (firmware version 2.9.0-Ax4x-opera11) is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input validati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63213</link><description>The QVidium Opera11 device (firmware version 2.9.0-Ax4x-opera11) is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input validation on the /cgi-bin/net_ping.cgi endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted GET request with a malicious parameter to inject arbitrary commands. These commands are executed with root privileges, allowing attackers to gain full control over the device. This poses a significant security risk to any device running this software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65103 | OpenSTAManager has an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability in API via &amp;#x27;display&amp;#x27; parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65103</link><description>OpenSTAManager is an open source management software for technical assistance and invoicing. Prior to version 2.9.5, an authenticated SQL Injection vulnerability in the API allows any user, regardless of permission level, to execute arbitrary SQL queries. By manipulating the display parameter in an API request, an attacker can exfiltrate, modify, or delete any data in the database, leading to a full system compromise. This issue has been patched in version 2.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65094 | WBCE CMS is Vulnerable to Privilege Escalation via Group ID Manipulation (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65094</link><description>WBCE CMS is a content management system. Prior to version 1.6.4, a low-privileged user in WBCE CMS can escalate their privileges to the Administrators group by manipulating the groups[] parameter in the /admin/users/save.php request. The UI restricts users to assigning only their existing group, but server-side validation is missing, allowing attackers to overwrite their group membership and obtain full administrative access. This results in a complete compromise of the CMS. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65100 | Security Snapshot May Use Unintended Timestamp When Only ISAR_APT_SNAPSHOT_DATE Is Set</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65100</link><description>Isar is an integration system for automated root filesystem generation. In versions 0.11-rc1 and 0.11, defining ISAR_APT_SNAPSHOT_DATE alone does not set the correct timestamp value for security distribution, leading to missed security updates. This issue has been patched via commit 738bcbb.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64759 | Homarr is Vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) and Possible Privilege Escalation via Malicious SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64759</link><description>Homarr is an open-source dashboard. Prior to version 1.43.3, stored XSS vulnerability exists, allowing the execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user's browser, with minimal or no user interaction required, due to the rendering of a malicious uploaded SVG file. This could be abused to add an attacker's account to the "credentials-admin" group, giving them full administrative access, if a user logged in as an administrator was to view the page which renders or redirects to the SVG. This issue has been patched in version 1.43.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63211 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware versions 6.5.0-9 thru 6.5.0-10, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63211</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in bridgetech VBC Server &amp; Element Manager, firmware versions 6.5.0-9 thru 6.5.0-10, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the addName parameter to the /vbc/core/userSetupDoc/userSetupDoc endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13316 | Hard-coded encryption keys in Twonky Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13316</link><description>Twonky Server 8.5.2 on Linux and Windows is vulnerable to a cryptographic flaw, use of hard-coded cryptographic keys. An attacker with knowledge of the encrypted administrator password can decrypt the value with static keys to view the plain text password and gain administrator-level access to Twonky Server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13315 | Unauthenticated log access in Twonky Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13315</link><description>Twonky Server 8.5.2 on Linux and Windows is vulnerable to an access control flaw. An unauthenticated attacker can bypass web service API authentication controls to leak a log file and read the administrator's username and encrypted password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65089 | XWiki view file macro: User can view content of office file without view rights on the attachment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65089</link><description>XWiki Remote Macros provides XWiki rendering macros that are useful when migrating content from Confluence. Prior to version 1.27.0, a user with no view rights on a page may see the content of an office attachment displayed with the view file macro. This issue has been patched in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65095 | Lookyloo is vulnerable due to improper user input sanitization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65095</link><description>Lookyloo is a web interface that allows users to capture a website page and then display a tree of domains that call each other. Prior to version 1.35.1, there is potential cross-site scripting on index and tree page. This issue has been patched in version 1.35.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63210 | The Newtec Celox UHD (models: CELOXA504, CELOXA820) running firmware version celox-21.6.13 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63210</link><description>The Newtec Celox UHD (models: CELOXA504, CELOXA820) running firmware version celox-21.6.13 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass. An attacker can exploit this issue by modifying intercepted responses from the /celoxservice endpoint. By injecting a forged response body during the loginWithUserName flow, the attacker can gain Superuser or Operator access without providing valid credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65025 | esm.sh CDN service has arbitrary file write via tarslip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65025</link><description>esm.sh is a nobuild content delivery network(CDN) for modern web development. Prior to version 136, the esm.sh CDN service is vulnerable to path traversal during NPM package tarball extraction. An attacker can craft a malicious NPM package containing specially crafted file paths (e.g., package/../../tmp/evil.js). When esm.sh downloads and extracts this package, files may be written to arbitrary locations on the server, escaping the intended extraction directory. This issue has been patched in version 136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65026 | esm.sh CDN service has JS Template Literal Injection in CSS-to-JavaScript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65026</link><description>esm.sh is a nobuild content delivery network(CDN) for modern web development. Prior to version 136, The esm.sh CDN service contains a Template Literal Injection vulnerability (CWE-94) in its CSS-to-JavaScript module conversion feature. When a CSS file is requested with the ?module query parameter, esm.sh converts it to a JavaScript module by embedding the CSS content directly into a template literal without proper sanitization. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code using ${...} expressions within CSS files, which will execute when the module is imported by victim applications. This enables Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in browsers and Remote Code Execution (RCE) in Electron applications. This issue has been patched in version 136.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65099 | Claude Code vulnerable to command execution prior to startup trust dialog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65099</link><description>Claude Code is an agentic coding tool. Prior to version 1.0.39, when running on a machine with Yarn 3.0 or above, Claude Code could have been tricked to execute code contained in a project via yarn plugins before the user accepted the startup trust dialog. Exploiting this would have required a user to start Claude Code in an untrusted directory and to be using Yarn 3.0 or above. This issue has been patched in version 1.0.39.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63207 | The R.V.R Elettronica TEX product (firmware TEXL-000400, Web GUI TLAN-000400) is vulnerable to broken access control due to improper authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63207</link><description>The R.V.R Elettronica TEX product (firmware TEXL-000400, Web GUI TLAN-000400) is vulnerable to broken access control due to improper authentication checks on the /_Passwd.html endpoint. An attacker can send an unauthenticated POST request to change the Admin, Operator, and User passwords, resulting in complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63208 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech VB288 Objective QoE Content Extractor, firmware version 5.6.0-8, allowing attackers to gain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63208</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech VB288 Objective QoE Content Extractor, firmware version 5.6.0-8, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information such as administrator passwords via the /probe/core/setup/passwd endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63209 | The ELCA Star Transmitter Remote Control firmware 1.25 for STAR150, BP1000, STAR300, STAR2000, STAR1000, STAR500, and possibly other models,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63209</link><description>The ELCA Star Transmitter Remote Control firmware 1.25 for STAR150, BP1000, STAR300, STAR2000, STAR1000, STAR500, and possibly other models, contains an information disclosure vulnerability allowing unauthenticated attackers to retrieve admin credentials and system settings via an unprotected /setup.xml endpoint. The admin password is stored in plaintext under the  XML tag, potentially leading to remote compromise of the transmitter system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65020 | Rallly Has Unauthorized Poll Duplication via Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65020</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the poll duplication endpoint (/api/trpc/polls.duplicate) allows any authenticated user to duplicate polls they do not own by modifying the pollId parameter. This effectively bypasses access control and lets unauthorized users clone private or administrative polls. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65021 | Rallly Has Unauthorized Poll Finalization via Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65021</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability exists in the poll finalization feature of the application. Any authenticated user can finalize a poll they do not own by manipulating the pollId parameter in the request. This allows unauthorized users to finalize other users’ polls and convert them into events without proper authorization checks, potentially disrupting user workflows and causing data integrity and availability issues. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65028 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Vote Update Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Manipulation of Participant Votes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65028</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to modify other participants’ votes in polls without authorization. The backend relies solely on the participantId parameter to identify which votes to update, without verifying ownership or poll permissions. This allows an attacker to alter poll results in their favor, directly compromising data integrity. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65029 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Participant Deletion Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Removal of Poll Participants</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65029</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to delete arbitrary participants from polls without ownership verification. The endpoint relies solely on a participant ID to authorize deletions, enabling attackers to remove other users (including poll owners) from polls. This impacts the integrity and availability of poll participation data. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65030 | Rallly Improper Authorization in Comment Deletion Endpoint Allows Unauthorized Comment Removal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65030</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an authorization flaw in the comment deletion API allows any authenticated user to delete comments belonging to other users, including poll owners and administrators. The endpoint relies solely on the comment ID for deletion and does not validate whether the requesting user owns the comment or has permission to remove it. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65031 | Rallly Improper Authorization in Comment Endpoint Allows User Impersonation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65031</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an improper authorization flaw in the comment creation endpoint allows authenticated users to impersonate any other user by altering the authorName field in the API request. This enables attackers to post comments under arbitrary usernames, including privileged ones such as administrators, potentially misleading other users and enabling phishing or social engineering attacks. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65032 | Rallly Has an IDOR Vulnerability in Participant Rename Function Allows Unauthorized Modification of Other Users’ Names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65032</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows any authenticated user to change the display names of other participants in polls without being an admin or the poll owner. By manipulating the participantId parameter in a rename request, an attacker can modify another user’s name, violating data integrity and potentially causing confusion or impersonation attacks. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65033 | Rallly Broken Authorization: Any User Can Pause or Resume Any Poll via Poll ID Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65033</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an authorization flaw in the poll management feature allows any authenticated user to pause or resume any poll, regardless of ownership. The system only uses the public pollId to identify polls, and it does not verify whether the user performing the action is the poll owner. As a result, any user can disrupt polls created by others, leading to a loss of integrity and availability across the application. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65034 | Rallly Improper Authorization Allows Reopening of Any Finalized Poll via Public pollId</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65034</link><description>Rallly is an open-source scheduling and collaboration tool. Prior to version 4.5.4, an improper authorization vulnerability allows any authenticated user to reopen finalized polls belonging to other users by manipulating the pollId parameter. This can disrupt events managed by other users and compromise both availability and integrity of poll data. This issue has been patched in version 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63205 | An issue was discovered in bridgetech probes VB220 IP Network Probe,VB120 Embedded IP + RF Probe, VB330 High-Capacity Probe, VB440 ST 2110 P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63205</link><description>An issue was discovered in bridgetech probes VB220 IP Network Probe,VB120 Embedded IP + RF Probe, VB330 High-Capacity Probe, VB440 ST 2110 Production Analytics Probe, and NOMAD, firmware versions 6.5.0-9, allowing attackers to gain sensitive information such as administrator passwords via the /probe/core/setup/passwd endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63206 | An authentication bypass issue was discovered in Dasan Switch DS2924 web based interface, firmware versions 1.01.18 and 1.02.00, allowing at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63206</link><description>An authentication bypass issue was discovered in Dasan Switch DS2924 web based interface, firmware versions 1.01.18 and 1.02.00, allowing attackers to gain escalated privileges via storing crafted cookies in the web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13400 | Tenda CH22 WrlExtraGet formWrlExtraGet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13400</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. Affected is the function formWrlExtraGet of the file /goform/WrlExtraGet. Performing manipulation of the argument chkHz results in buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64521 | authentik deactivated service accounts can authenticate to OAuth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64521</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2, when authenticating with client_id and client_secret to an OAuth provider, authentik creates a service account for the provider. In previous authentik versions, authentication for this account was possible even when the account was deactivated. Other permissions are correctly applied and federation with other providers still take assigned policies correctly into account. authentik versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2 fix this issue. A workaround involves adding a policy to the application that explicitly checks if the service account is still valid, and deny access if not.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64708 | authentik invitation expiry is delayed by at least 5 minutes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64708</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Prior to versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2, in previous authentik versions, invitations were considered valid regardless if they are expired or not, thus relying on background tasks to clean up expired ones. In a normal scenario this can take up to 5 minutes because the cleanup of expired objects is scheduled to run every 5 minutes. However, with a large amount of tasks in the backlog, this might take longer. authentik versions 2025.8.5 and 2025.10.2 fix this issue. A workaround involves creating a policy that explicitly checks whether the invitation is still valid, and then bind it to the invitation stage on the invitation flow, and denying access if the invitation is not valid.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12743 | SQL Injection in Looker Project Generation Endpoint Allows Access to Internal MySQL Database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12743</link><description>The Looker endpoint for generating new projects from database connections allows users to specify "looker" as a connection name, which is a reserved internal name for Looker's internal MySQL database. The schemas parameter is vulnerable to SQL injection, enabling attackers to manipulate SELECT queries that are constructed and executed against the internal MySQL database. This vulnerability allows users with developer permissions to extract data from Looker's internal MySQL database.

Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect against this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.106
  *  24.18.198+
  *  25.0.75
  *  25.6.63+
  *  25.8.45+
  *  25.10.33+
  *  25.12.1+
  *  25.14+</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64757 | Astro Development Server is Vulnerable to Arbitrary Local File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64757</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.14.3, a vulnerability has been identified in the Astro framework's development server that allows arbitrary local file read access through the image optimization endpoint. The vulnerability affects Astro development environments and allows remote attackers to read any image file accessible to the Node.js process on the host system. This issue has been patched in version 5.14.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64764 | Astro is vulnerable to Reflected XSS via the server islands feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64764</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.8, a reflected XSS vulnerability is present when the server islands feature is used in the targeted application, regardless of what was intended by the component template(s). This issue has been patched in version 5.15.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64765 | Astro middleware authentication checks based on url.pathname can be bypassed via url encoded values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64765</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.8, a mismatch exists between how Astro normalizes request paths for routing/rendering and how the application’s middleware reads the path for validation checks. Astro internally applies decodeURI() to determine which route to render, while the middleware uses context.url.pathname without applying the same normalization (decodeURI). This discrepancy may allow attackers to reach protected routes using encoded path variants that pass routing but bypass validation checks. This issue has been patched in version 5.15.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65019 | Astro Cloudflare adapter has a Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in /_image endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65019</link><description>Astro is a web framework. Prior to version 5.15.9, when using Astro's Cloudflare adapter (@astrojs/cloudflare) with output: 'server', the image optimization endpoint (/_image) contains a critical vulnerability in the isRemoteAllowed() function that unconditionally allows data: protocol URLs. This enables Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks through malicious SVG payloads, bypassing domain restrictions and Content Security Policy protections. This issue has been patched in version 5.15.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34328 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated File Upload RCE via ajaxScript.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34328</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component (F2MAdmin) that exposes an unauthenticated script-management endpoint at AudioCodes_files/utils/IVR/diagram/ajaxScript.php. The saveScript action writes attacker-supplied data directly to a server-side file path under the privileges of the web service account, which runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM on Windows deployments. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can write arbitrary files into the product’s web-accessible directory structure and subsequently execute them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34329 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated Backup Upload RCE via ajaxBackupUploadFile.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34329</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 expose an unauthenticated backup upload endpoint at AudioCodes_files/ajaxBackupUploadFile.php in the F2MAdmin web interface. The script derives a backup folder path from application configuration, creates the directory if it does not exist, and then moves an uploaded file to that location using the attacker-controlled filename, without any authentication, authorization, or file-type validation. On default Windows deployments where the backup directory resolves to the system drive, a remote attacker can upload web server or interpreter configuration files that cause a log file or other server-controlled resource to be treated as executable code. This allows subsequent HTTP requests to trigger arbitrary command execution under the web server account, which runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34330 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated Prompt File Upload via ajaxPromptUploadFile.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34330</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component (F2MAdmin) that exposes an unauthenticated prompt upload endpoint at AudioCodes_files/utils/IVR/diagram/ajaxPromptUploadFile.php. The script accepts an uploaded file and writes it into the C:\\F2MAdmin\\tmp directory using a filename derived from application constants, without any authentication, authorization, or file-type validation. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can upload or overwrite prompt- or music-on-hold–related files in this directory, potentially leading to tampering with IVR audio content or preparing files for use in further attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34331 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Unauthenticated File Read via download.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34331</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 contain an unauthenticated file read vulnerability via the download.php script. The endpoint exposes a file download mechanism that lacks access control, allowing remote, unauthenticated users to request files stored on the appliance based solely on attacker-supplied path and filename parameters. While limited to specific file extensions permitted by the application logic, sensitive backup archives can be retrieved, exposing internal databases and credential hashes. Successful exploitation may lead to disclosure of administrative password hashes and other sensitive configuration data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34332 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Insecure Service Control Scripts LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34332</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 include a web administration component that controls back-end Windows services using helper batch scripts located under C:\\F2MAdmin\\F2E\\AudioCodes_files\\utils\\Services. When certain service actions are requested through ajaxPost.php, these scripts are invoked by PHP using system() under the NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM account. The batch files in this directory are writable by any authenticated local user due to overly permissive ACLs, allowing them to replace script contents with arbitrary commands. On the next service start/stop operation, the modified script is executed as SYSTEM, enabling elevation of local privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34333 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 World-Writable Webroot LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34333</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 configure the web document root at C:\\F2MAdmin\\F2E with overly permissive file system permissions. Authenticated local users have modify rights on this directory, while the associated web server process runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM. As a result, any local user can create or alter server-side scripts within the webroot and then trigger them via HTTP requests, causing arbitrary code to execute with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34334 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Authenticated Command Injection via TestFax.php &amp;amp; LPE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34334</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 are vulnerable to an authenticated command injection in the fax test functionality implemented by AudioCodes_files/TestFax.php. When a fax "send" test is requested, the application builds a faxsender command line using attacker-supplied parameters and passes it to GlobalUtils::RunBatchFile without proper validation or shell-argument sanitization. The resulting batch file is written into a temporary run directory and then executed via a backend service that runs as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM. An authenticated attacker with access to the fax test interface can craft parameter values that inject additional shell commands into the generated batch file, leading to arbitrary command execution with SYSTEM privileges. In addition, because the generated batch files reside in a location with overly permissive file system permissions, a local low-privilege user on the server can modify pending batch files to achieve the same elevation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34335 | AudioCodes Fax/IVR Appliance &amp;lt;= 2.6.23 Authenticated Command Injection via ActivateLicense.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34335</link><description>AudioCodes Fax Server and Auto-Attendant IVR appliances versions up to and including 2.6.23 expose an authenticated command injection vulnerability in the license activation workflow handled by AudioCodes_files/ActivateLicense.php. When a license file is uploaded, the application derives a new filename by combining a generated base name with the attacker-controlled extension portion of the original upload name, then constructs a command line for fax_server_lic_cmdline.exe that includes this path. The extension value is incorporated into the command string without input validation, escaping, or proper argument quotation before being passed to exec(). An authenticated user with access to the license upload interface can supply a specially crafted filename whose extension injects additional shell metacharacters, causing arbitrary commands to be executed as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34336 | eGovFramework &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 Unauthenticated File Upload via Web Editor Image Upload Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34336</link><description>eGovFramework/egovframe-common-components versions up to and including 4.3.1 contain an unauthenticated file upload vulnerability via the /utl/wed/insertImage.do and /utl/wed/insertImageCk.do image upload endpoints. These controllers accept multipart requests without authentication, pass the uploaded content to a shared upload helper, and store the file on the server under a framework-controlled path. The framework then returns a download URL that can be used to retrieve the uploaded content, including an attacker-controlled Content-Type within the limits of the image upload functionality. While a filename extension whitelist is enforced, the attacker fully controls the file contents. The response MIME type used is also attacker-controlled when the file is served up to version &lt; 4.1.2. Since version 4.1.2, it is possible to download any image uploaded with any whitelisted content type. But any file uploaded other than an image will be served with the `application/octet-stream` content type (the content type is no longer controlled by the attacker since version 4.1.2). This enables an unauthenticated attacker to use any affected application as a persistent file hosting service for arbitrary content under the application's origin. KISA/KrCERT has identified this unpatched vulnerability as "KVE-2023-5280."</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34337 | eGovFramework &amp;lt;= 4.3.1 Unauthenticated Encryption Oracle via Web Editor Image Upload Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34337</link><description>eGovFramework/egovframe-common-components versions up to and including 4.3.1 includes Web Editor image upload and related file delivery functionality that uses symmetric encryption to protect URL parameters, but exposes an encryption oracle that allows attackers to generate valid ciphertext for chosen values. The image upload endpoints /utl/wed/insertImage.do and /utl/wed/insertImageCk.do encrypt server-side paths, filenames, and MIME types and embed them directly into a download URL that is returned to the client. Because these same encrypted parameters are trusted by other endpoints, such as /utl/web/imageSrc.do and /cmm/fms/getImage.do, an unauthenticated attacker can abuse the upload functionality to obtain encrypted representations of attacker-chosen identifiers and then replay those ciphertext values to file-serving APIs. This design failure allows an attacker to bypass access controls that rely solely on the secrecy of encrypted parameters and retrieve arbitrary stored files that are otherwise expected to require an existing session or specific authorization context. KISA/KrCERT has identified this unpatched vulnerability as "KVE-2023-5281."</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12766 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Management Console of affected versions of BlackBerry AtHoc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12766</link><description>An Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Management Console of BlackBerry® AtHoc® (OnPrem) version 7.21 could allow an attacker to potentially gain unauthorized knowledge about other organizations hosted on the same Interactive Warning System (IWS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63223 | The Axel Technology StreamerMAX MK II devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63223</link><description>The Axel Technology StreamerMAX MK II devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63224 | The Itel DAB Encoder (IDEnc build 25aec8d) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63224</link><description>The Itel DAB Encoder (IDEnc build 25aec8d) is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to improper JWT validation across devices. Attackers can reuse a valid JWT token obtained from one device to authenticate and gain administrative access to any other device running the same firmware, even if the passwords and networks are different. This allows full compromise of affected devices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65022 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `agenda.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65022</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/agenda.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_agenda request parameter, which is directly concatenated into multiple SQL queries without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit b473f92.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65023 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `funcionario_vinculo_cad.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65023</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/funcionario_vinculo_cad.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_funcionario_vinculo GET parameter, which is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit a00dfa3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65024 | i-Educar Authenticated Time-based SQL Injection in `agenda_admin_cad.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65024</link><description>i-Educar is free, fully online school management software. In versions 2.10.0 and prior, an authenticated time-based SQL injection vulnerability exists in the ieducar/intranet/agenda_admin_cad.php script. An attacker with access to an authenticated session can execute arbitrary SQL commands against the application's database. This vulnerability is caused by the improper handling of the cod_agenda GET parameter, which is directly concatenated into an SQL query without proper sanitization. This issue has been patched in commit 3e9763a.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63879 | A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /ecommerce/products.php component of E-commerce Project v1.0 and earlier allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63879</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripted (XSS) vulnerability in the /ecommerce/products.php component of E-commerce Project v1.0 and earlier allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10702 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10702</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect Open Access JDBC driver and Hybrid Data Pipeline allows Remote Code Inclusion.


The SpyAttribute connection option implemented by the DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC driver and the DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC driver supports an undocumented syntax construct for the option value that if discovered can be used by an attacker.  If an application allows an end user to specify a value for the SpyAttributes connection option then an attacker can use the undocumented syntax to cause the driver to load an arbitrary class on the class path and execute a constructor on that class.  


This issue affects:

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Amazon Redshift: through 6.0.0.001392, fixed in 6.0.0.001541

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Cassandra: through 6.0.0.000805, fixed in 6.0.0.000833

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Hive: through 6.0.1.001499, fixed in 6.0.1.001628

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Impala: through 6.0.0.001155, fixed in 6.0.0.001279

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache SparkSQL: through 6.0.1.001222, fixed in 6.0.1.001344

DataDirect Connect for JDBC Autonomous REST Connector: through 6.0.1.006961, fixed in 6.0.1.007063

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for DB2: through 6.0.0.000717, fixed in 6.0.0.000964

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google Analytics 4: through 6.0.0.000454, fixed in 6.0.0.000525

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google BigQuery: through 6.0.0.002279, fixed in 6.0.0.002410
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Greenplum: through 6.0.0.001712, fixed in 6.0.0.001727
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Informix: through 6.0.0.000690, fixed in 6.0.0.0851


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Dynamics 365: through 6.0.0.003161, fixed in 6.0.0.3198

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft SQLServer: through 6.0.0.001936, fixed in 6.0.0.001957

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Sharepoint: through 6.0.0.001559, fixed in 6.0.0.001587

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MongoDB: through 6.1.0.001654, fixed in 6.1.0.001669

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MySQL: through 5.1.4.000330, fixed in 5.1.4.000364

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Database: through 6.0.0.001747, fixed in 6.0.0.001776

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Eloqua: through 6.0.0.001438, fixed in 6.0.0.001458

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Sales Cloud: through 6.0.0.001225, fixed in 6.0.0.001316

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Service Cloud: through 5.1.4.000298, fixed in 5.1.4.000309
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for PostgreSQL: through 6.0.0.001843, fixed in 6.0.0.001856

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Progress OpenEdge: through 5.1.4.000187, fixed in 5.1.4.000189

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Salesforce: through 6.0.0.003020, fixed in 6.0.0.003125
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP HANA: through 6.0.0.000879, product retired

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP S/4 HANA: through 6.0.1.001818, fixed in 6.0.1.001858

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Sybase ASE: through 5.1.4.000161, fixed in 5.1.4.000162

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Snowflake: through 6.0.1.001821, fixed in 6.0.1.001856

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Server: through 4.6.2.3309, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC Driver: through 4.6.2.0607, fixed in 4.6.2.1023

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline On Premises Connector: through 4.6.2.1223, fixed in 4.6.2.1339
DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Docker: through 4.6.2.3316, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 8.1.0.0177, fixed in 8.1.0.0183

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 9.0.0.0019, fixed in 9.0.0.0022</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10703 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10703</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Progress DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, Progress DataDirect Open Access JDBC driver and Hybrid Data Pipeline allows Remote Code Inclusion.

The SpyAttribute connection option implemented by the DataDirect Connect for JDBC drivers, DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC driver and the DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC driver log=(file) construct allows the user to specify an arbitrary file for the JDBC driver to write its log information to.  If an application allows an end user to specify a value for the SpyAttributes connection option then an attacker could cause java script to be written to a log file.  If the log file was in the correct location with the correct extension, an application server could see that log file as a resource to be served.  The attacker could fetch the resource from the server causing the java script to be executed.





This issue affects:



DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Amazon Redshift: through 6.0.0.001392, fixed in 6.0.0.001541

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Cassandra: through 6.0.0.000805, fixed in 6.0.0.000833

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Hive: through 6.0.1.001499, fixed in 6.0.1.001628

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache Impala: through 6.0.0.001155, fixed in 6.0.0.001279

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Apache SparkSQL: through 6.0.1.001222, fixed in 6.0.1.001344

DataDirect Connect for JDBC Autonomous REST Connector: through 6.0.1.006961, fixed in 6.0.1.007063

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for DB2: through 6.0.0.000717, fixed in 6.0.0.000964

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google Analytics 4: through 6.0.0.000454, fixed in 6.0.0.000525

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Google BigQuery: through 6.0.0.002279, fixed in 6.0.0.002410
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Greenplum: through 6.0.0.001712, fixed in 6.0.0.001727
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Informix: through 6.0.0.000690, fixed in 6.0.0.0851


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Dynamics 365: through 6.0.0.003161, fixed in 6.0.0.3198

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft SQLServer: through 6.0.0.001936, fixed in 6.0.0.001957

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Microsoft Sharepoint: through 6.0.0.001559, fixed in 6.0.0.001587

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MongoDB: through 6.1.0.001654, fixed in 6.1.0.001669

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for MySQL: through 5.1.4.000330, fixed in 5.1.4.000364

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Database: through 6.0.0.001747, fixed in 6.0.0.001776

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Eloqua: through 6.0.0.001438, fixed in 6.0.0.001458

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Sales Cloud: through 6.0.0.001225, fixed in 6.0.0.001316

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Oracle Service Cloud: through 5.1.4.000298, fixed in 5.1.4.000309
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for PostgreSQL: through 6.0.0.001843, fixed in 6.0.0.001856


DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Progress OpenEdge: through 5.1.4.000187, fixed in 5.1.4.000189

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Salesforce: through 6.0.0.003020, fixed in 6.0.0.003125
DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP HANA: through 6.0.0.000879, product retired

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for SAP S/4 HANA: through 6.0.1.001818, fixed in 6.0.1.001858

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Sybase ASE: through 5.1.4.000161, fixed in 5.1.4.000162

DataDirect Connect for JDBC for Snowflake: through 6.0.1.001821, fixed in 6.0.1.001856

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Server: through 4.6.2.3309, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline JDBC Driver: through 4.6.2.0607, fixed in 4.6.2.1023

DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline On Premises Connector: through 4.6.2.1223, fixed in 4.6.2.1339
DataDirect Hybrid Data Pipeline Docker: through 4.6.2.3316, fixed in 4.6.2.3430

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 8.1.0.0177, fixed in 8.1.0.0183

DataDirect OpenAccess JDBC Driver: through 9.0.0.0019, fixed in 9.0.0.0022</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63221 | The Axel Technology puma devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63221</link><description>The Axel Technology puma devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63220 | The Sound4 FIRST web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63220</link><description>The Sound4 FIRST web-based management interface is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via a malicious firmware update package. The update mechanism fails to validate the integrity of manual.sh, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by modifying this script and repackaging the firmware.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13396 | code-projects Courier Management System add-office.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13396</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /add-office.php. This manipulation of the argument OfficeName causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13397 | mrubyc alloc.c mrbc_raw_realloc null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13397</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in mrubyc up to 3.4. This impacts the function mrbc_raw_realloc of the file src/alloc.c. Such manipulation of the argument ptr leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The name of the patch is 009111904807b8567262036bf45297c3da8f1c87. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63878 | Github Restaurant Website Restoran v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Contact Form page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63878</link><description>Github Restaurant Website Restoran v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the Contact Form page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63219 | The ITEL ISO FM SFN Adapter (firmware ISO2 2.0.0.0, WebServer 2.0) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper session management on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63219</link><description>The ITEL ISO FM SFN Adapter (firmware ISO2 2.0.0.0, WebServer 2.0) is vulnerable to session hijacking due to improper session management on the /home.html endpoint. An attacker can access an active session without authentication, allowing them to control the device, modify configurations, and compromise system integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63218 | The Axel Technology WOLF1MS and WOLF2MS devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63218</link><description>The Axel Technology WOLF1MS and WOLF2MS devices (firmware versions 0.8.5 to 1.0.3) are vulnerable to Broken Access Control due to missing authentication on the /cgi-bin/gstFcgi.fcgi endpoint. Unauthenticated remote attackers can list user accounts, create new administrative users, delete users, and modify system settings, leading to full compromise of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63243 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the password change functionality of Pixeon WebLaudos 25.1 (01). The sle_sSen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63243</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the password change functionality of Pixeon WebLaudos 25.1 (01). The sle_sSenha parameter to the loginAlterarSenha.asp file. An attacker can craft a malicious URL that, when visited by a victim, causes arbitrary JavaScript code to be executed in the victim's browser within the security context of the vulnerable application. This issue could allow attackers to steal session cookies, disclose sensitive information, perform unauthorized actions on behalf of the user, or conduct phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11963 | Reflected XSS in Saysis&amp;#x27;s StarCities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11963</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saysis Computer Systems Trade Ltd. Co. StarCities allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects StarCities: before 1.1.61.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0421 | iFrame Injection in Mikrogrup&amp;#x27;s Shopside</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0421</link><description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Shopside Software Technologies Inc. Shopside allows iFrame Overlay.This issue affects Shopside: through 05022025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8527 | ALC WebCTRL Carrier i-Vu Open Redirect via URL parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8527</link><description>Open Redirect in URL parameter in Automated Logic WebCTRL and Carrier i-Vu versions 6.0, 6.5, 7.0, 8.0, 8.5, 9.0 may allow attackers to exploit user sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8528 | ALC WebCTRL Carrier i-Vu Reflected XSS due to unsanitized parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8528</link><description>Reflected XSS using a specific URL in Automated Logic WebCTRL and Carrier i-VU can allow delivery of malicious payload due to a specific GET parameter not being sanitized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12592 | Use of default login credentials in Legacy Vivotek Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12592</link><description>Legacy Vivotek Device firmware uses default credetials for the root and user login accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10437 | SQLi in Exagate&amp;#x27;s Webpack Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10437</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eksagate Electronic Engineering and Computer Industry Trade Inc. Webpack Management System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Webpack Management System: through 20251119.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13395 | codehub666 94list function.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13395</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in codehub666 94list up to 5831c8240e99a72b7d3508c79ef46ae4b96befe8. The impacted element is the function Login of the file /function.php. The manipulation results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12472 | Remote Code Execution in Looker due to Improperly Validated Directory Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12472</link><description>An attacker with a Looker Developer role could manipulate a LookML project to exploit a race condition during Git directory deletion, leading to arbitrary command execution on the Looker instance.



Looker-hosted and Self-hosted were found to be vulnerable.
This issue has already been mitigated for Looker-hosted instances. No user action is required for these.


Self-hosted instances must be upgraded as soon as possible. This vulnerability has been patched in all supported versions of Self-hosted.
The versions below have all been updated to protect from this vulnerability. You can download these versions at the Looker download page  https://download.looker.com/ :
  *  24.12.103+
  *  24.18.195+
  *  25.0.72+
  *  25.6.60+
  *  25.8.42+
  *  25.10.22+</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 10:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64408 | Apache Causeway: Java deserialization vulnerability to authenticated attackers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64408</link><description>Apache Causeway faces Java deserialization vulnerabilities that allow remote code execution (RCE) through user-controllable URL parameters. These vulnerabilities affect all applications using Causeway's ViewModel functionality and can be exploited by authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code with application privileges. 

This issue affects all current versions.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.5.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 10:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58412 | A improper neutralization of script-related html tags in a web page (basic xss) vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 8.0.0, FortiADC 7.6.0 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58412</link><description>A improper neutralization of script-related html tags in a web page (basic xss) vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 8.0.0, FortiADC 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, FortiADC 7.4 all versions, FortiADC 7.2 all versions may allow attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 09:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11230 | Denial of service vulnerability in HAProxy mjson library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11230</link><description>Inefficient algorithm complexity in mjson in HAProxy allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via specially crafted JSON requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11446 | Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11446</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in upKeeper Solutions upKeeper Manager allows Use of Known Domain Credentials.This issue affects upKeeper Manager: from 5.2.0 before 5.2.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 08:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12484 | Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers &amp;lt;= 1.12.19 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12484</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress – Get More Website Traffic, Email Subscribers, and Social Followers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple social media username parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13035 | Code Snippets &amp;lt;= 3.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Code Injection via extract() and PHP Filter Chains</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13035</link><description>The Code Snippets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.1. This is due to the plugin's use of extract() on attacker-controlled shortcode attributes within the `evaluate_shortcode_from_flat_file` method, which can be used to overwrite the `$filepath` variable and subsequently passed to require_once. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute arbitrary PHP code on the server via the `[code_snippet]` shortcode using PHP filter chains granted they can trick an administrator into enabling the "Enable file-based execution" setting and creating at least one active Content snippet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13206 | GiveWP - Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 4.13.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;name&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13206</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.13.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Avatars must be enabled in the WordPress install in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11243 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in Shelly Pro 4PM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11243</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Shelly Pro 4PM (before v1.6) allows Excessive Allocation via network.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12056 | Out-of-bounds Read in Shelly Pro 3EM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12056</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in Shelly Pro 3EM (before v1.4.4) allows Overread Buffers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12535 | SureForms &amp;lt;= 1.13.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery Protection Bypass via Improper Nonce Distribution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12535</link><description>The SureForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.1. This is due to the plugin distributing generic WordPress REST API nonces (wp_rest) to unauthenticated users via the 'wp_ajax_nopriv_rest-nonce' action. While the plugin legitimately needs to support unauthenticated form submissions, it incorrectly uses generic REST nonces instead of form-specific nonces. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass CSRF protection on REST API endpoints that rely solely on nonce verification without additional authentication checks, allowing them to trigger unauthorized actions such as the plugin's own post-submission hooks and potentially other plugins' REST endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13085 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Post Meta Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13085</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Authorization leading to Sensitive Post Meta Disclosure in versions up to and including 1.3.2. This is due to missing object-level authorization checks in the resolve_variables() AJAX handler. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the siteseo_manage capability (e.g., Author-level users who have been granted SiteSEO access by an administrator) to read arbitrary post metadata from any post, page, attachment, or WooCommerce order they cannot edit, via the custom field variable resolution feature granted they have been given access to SiteSEO by an administrator and legacy storage is enabled. In affected WooCommerce installations, this exposes sensitive customer billing information including names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, and payment methods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12057 | WavePlayer &amp;lt; 3.8.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12057</link><description>The WavePlayer WordPress plugin before 3.8.0 does not have authorization in an AJAX action as well as does not validate the file to be copied locally, allowing unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary file on the server and lead to RCE</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12174 | Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings &amp;lt;= 8.5.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Data Export and Slug Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12174</link><description>The Directorist: AI-Powered Business Directory Plugin with Classified Ads Listings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'directorist_prepare_listings_export_file' and 'directorist_type_slug_change' AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 8.5.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to export listing details and change the directorist slug.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12359 | Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12359</link><description>The Responsive Lightbox &amp; Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3 via the 'get_image_size_by_url' function. This is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied URLs when determining image dimensions for gallery items. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application which can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12646 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12646</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dayofyear' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12710 | Pet-Manager – Petfinder &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via kwm-petfinder Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12710</link><description>The Pet-Manager – Petfinder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the kwm-petfinder shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12751 | WSChat – WordPress Live Chat &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12751</link><description>The WSChat – WordPress Live Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'reset_settings' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12814 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12814</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to n incorrect capability check on the siteseo_reset_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, who have been granted access to at least on SiteSEO setting capability, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12822 | WP Login and Register using JWT &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) API Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12822</link><description>The WP Login and Register using JWT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mo_jwt_generate_new_api_key' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to generate a new API key on site's that do not have an API key configured and subsequently use that to access restricted endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12842 | Booking Plugin for WordPress Appointments – Time Slot &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12842</link><description>The Booking Plugin for WordPress Appointments – Time Slot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized email sending in versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to missing validation on the tslot_appt_email AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send appointment notification emails to arbitrary recipients with attacker-controlled text content in certain email fields, potentially enabling the site to be abused for phishing campaigns or spam distribution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12878 | FunnelKit – Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout &amp;lt;= 3.13.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wfop_phone Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12878</link><description>The FunnelKit – Funnel Builder for WooCommerce Checkout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `wfop_phone` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user-supplied `default` attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13054 | User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp;amp; User Role Editor &amp;lt;= 3.14.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13054</link><description>The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wppb-embed shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13145 | WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.33.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection via CSV Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13145</link><description>The WP Import – Ultimate CSV XML Importer for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.33.1. This is due to deserialization of untrusted data supplied via CSV file imports in the import_single_post_as_csv function within SingleImportExport.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access or higher, to inject a PHP object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12349 | Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters &amp;lt;= 5.9.10 - Missing Authentication to Unauthenticated Mailing Queue Trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12349</link><description>The Icegram Express - Email Subscribers, Newsletters and Marketing Automation Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authorization in versions up to, and including, 5.9.10. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action in the `trigger_mailing_queue_sending` function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to force immediate email sending, bypass the schedule, increase server load, and change plugin state (e.g., last-cron-hit), enabling abuse or DoS-like effects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12426 | Quiz Maker &amp;lt;= 6.7.0.80 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12426</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.0.80. This is due to the plugin exposing quiz answers through the ays_quiz_check_answer AJAX action without proper authorization checks. The endpoint only validates a nonce, but that same nonce is publicly available to all site visitors via the quiz_maker_ajax_public localized script data. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including quiz answers for any quiz question.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12427 | YITH WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Wishlist Rename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12427</link><description>The YITH WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0 via the REST API endpoint and AJAX handler due to missing validation on user-controlled keys. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to discover any user's wishlist token ID, and subsequently rename the victim's wishlist without authorization (integrity impact). This can be exploited to target multi-user stores for defacement, social engineering attacks, mass tampering, and profiling at scale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12770 | New User Approve &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure via Type Juggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12770</link><description>The New User Approve plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.9 due to insufficient API key validation using loose equality comparison. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve personally identifiable information (PII), including usernames and email addresses of users with various approval statuses via the Zapier REST API endpoints, by exploiting PHP type juggling with the api_key parameter set to "0" on sites where the Zapier API key has not been configured.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12777 | YITH WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 4.10.0 - Unauthenticated Wishlist Token Disclosure to Wishlist Item Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12777</link><description>The YITH WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform actions on the REST API /wp-json/yith/wishlist/v1/lists endpoint (which uses permission_callback =&gt; '__return_true') and the AJAX delete_item handler (which only checks nonce validity without verifying object-level authorization). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disclose wishlist tokens for any user and subsequently delete wishlist items by chaining the REST API authorization bypass with the exposed delete_item nonce on shared wishlist pages and the AJAX handler's missing object-level authorization check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6251 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1036 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6251</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via $item['field_id'] in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1036 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13051 | Windows service used an uncontrolled search path element will cause unauthorized code execution with localsystem privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13051</link><description>When the service of ABP and AES is installed in a directory writable by non-administrative users, an attacker can replace or plant a DLL with the same name as one loaded by the service. Upon service restart, the malicious DLL is loaded and executed under the LocalSystem account, resulting in unauthorized code execution with elevated privileges.
This issue affects ABP and AES: from ABP 2.0 through 2.0.7.9050, from AES 1.0 through 1.0.6.8290.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13225 | Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in TanOS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13225</link><description>Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in TanOS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 03:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12852 | DLL Loading vulnerability in NEC Corporation RakurakuMusen Start EX All Verisons allows a attacker to manipulate the PC environment to cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12852</link><description>DLL Loading vulnerability in NEC Corporation RakurakuMusen Start EX All Verisons allows a attacker to manipulate the PC environment to cause unintended operations on the user's device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>