<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12917 | Improper Access Control in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Health4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12917</link><description>Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in Agito Computer Health4All allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels, Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Health4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12918 | SQLi in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Health4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12918</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Agito Computer Health4All allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Health4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12916 | SQLi in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Life4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12916</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Agito Computer Life4All allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Life4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0545 | XSS in Tekrom Technology&amp;#x27;s T-Soft E-Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tekrom Technology T-Soft E-Commerce allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects T-Soft E-Commerce: before v5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5174 | Broken Authentication in Gliffy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5174</link><description>A flaw in Gliffy results in broken authentication through the reset functionality of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1632 | libarchive bsdunzip.c list null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1632</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libarchive up to 3.7.7. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function list of the file bsdunzip.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1488 | WPO365 | MICROSOFT 365 GRAPH MAILER &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect_to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1488</link><description>The WPO365 | MICROSOFT 365 GRAPH MAILER plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 3.2. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the 'redirect_to' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if 1. they can successfully trick them into performing an action and 2. the plugin is activated but not configured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 11:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52926 | io_uring/rw: split io_read() into a helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52926</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

IORING_OP_READ did not correctly consume the provided buffer list when
read i/o returned &lt; 0 (except for -EAGAIN and -EIOCBQUEUED return).
This can lead to a potential use-after-free when the completion via
io_rw_done runs at separate context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 09:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0690 | Grub2: read: integer overflow may lead to out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0690</link><description>The read command is used to read the keyboard input from the user, while reads it keeps the input length in a 32-bit integer value which is further used to reallocate the line buffer to accept the next character. During this process, with a line big enough it's possible to make this variable to overflow leading to a out-of-bounds write in the heap based buffer. This flaw may be leveraged to corrupt grub's internal critical data and secure boot bypass is not discarded as consequence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20051 | Arbitrary file read via block duplication in Mattermost Boards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20051</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to properly validate input when patching and duplicating a board, which allows a user to read any arbitrary file on the system via duplicating a specially crafted block in Boards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24490 | SQL Injection in Mattermost Boards via board category ID reordering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24490</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to use prepared statements in the SQL query of boards reordering which allows an attacker to retrieve data from the database, via a SQL injection when reordering specially crafted boards categories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25279 | Arbitrary file read in Mattermost Boards via import &amp;amp; export board archive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25279</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to properly validate board blocks when importing boards which allows an attacker could read any arbitrary file on the system via importing and exporting a specially crafted import archive in Boards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1412 | Session Persistence After User-to-Bot Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1412</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.6, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1 fail to invalidate all active sessions when converting a user to a bot, with allows the converted user to escalate their privileges depending on the permissions granted to the bot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24526 | Channel export permitted on archived channel when viewing archived channels is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24526</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.3, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to restrict channel export of archived channels when the "Allow users to view archived channels" is disabled which allows a user to export channel contents when they shouldn't have access to it</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12308 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.6.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12308</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.6.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13605 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.33 -  Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13605</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13822 | Total Contest Lite &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13822</link><description>The Photo Contest  | Competition | Video Contest WordPress plugin through 2.8.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1629 | Excitel Broadband Private my Excitel App One-Time Password excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1629</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Excitel Broadband Private my Excitel App 3.13.0 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component One-Time Password Handler. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 05:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1618 | vTiger CRM index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1618</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in vTiger CRM 6.4.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /modules/Mobile/index.php. The manipulation of the argument _operation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1616 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON Diagnosis os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1616</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Diagnosis. The manipulation of the argument Destination Address leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1617 | Netis WF2780 Wireless 2.4G Menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1617</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netis WF2780 2.1.41925. This affects an unknown part of the component Wireless 2.4G Menu. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1615 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON NAT Submenu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1615</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component NAT Submenu. The manipulation of the argument Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1613 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON URL Filtering Submenu URL_filterCfg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/URL_filterCfg of the component URL Filtering Submenu. The manipulation of the argument url_IP leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1614 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON Port Forwarding Submenu portForwardingCfg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1614</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/portForwardingCfg of the component Port Forwarding Submenu. The manipulation of the argument pf_Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1612 | Edimax BR-6288ACL wireless5g_basic.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1612</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Edimax BR-6288ACL 1.30. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file wireless5g_basic.asp. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:06:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55898 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55898</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 could allow a user with the capability to compile or restore a program to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call. A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1611 | ShopXO Template ThemeAdminService.php injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1611</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ShopXO up to 6.4.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file app/service/ThemeAdminService.php of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1609 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_cmd websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1609</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_cmd. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1610 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_blacklist websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1610</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_blacklist. The manipulation of the argument mac/enable leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1607 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System salary_slip.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1607</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/salary_slip.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1608 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_manpwd websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1608</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2. Affected is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_manpwd. The manipulation of the argument routepwd  leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1599 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software profile_crud.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1599</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/profile_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument old_cat_img leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1606 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System backups.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1606</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/backup/backups.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1598 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software asset_crud.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1598</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/asset_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument photo1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1596 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software fpassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /fpassword.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1597 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software redirect.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1597</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/redirect.php. The manipulation of the argument a leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22631 | WordPress Marketing Automation Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vbout Marketing Automation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Marketing Automation: from n/a through 1.2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22632 | WordPress WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in totalsoft WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22633 | WordPress Give – Divi Donation Modules plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22633</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Matt Cromwell Give – Divi Donation Modules allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Give – Divi Donation Modules: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22635 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt; 3.9.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jyothis Joy Eventer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1595 | Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR getbaseconfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR up to 2.7.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/v1/getbaseconfig. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 22:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1594 | FFmpeg AAC Encoder aacenc_tns.c ff_aac_search_for_tns stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1594</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FFmpeg up to 7.1. This affects the function ff_aac_search_for_tns of the file libavcodec/aacenc_tns.c of the component AAC Encoder. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 21:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1593 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Profile Picture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1593</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /_hr_soft/assets/uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1592 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Add Role Page Role.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1592</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/Operations/Role.php of the component Add Role Page. The manipulation of the argument assign_name/description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1591 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Department Page department.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1591</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /department.php of the component Department Page. The manipulation of the argument Department Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1590 | SourceCodester E-Learning System List of Lessons Page index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/lesson/index.php of the component List of Lessons Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1589 | SourceCodester E-Learning System User Registration register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /register.php of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1588 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System manage-nurse.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1588</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/manage-nurse.php. The manipulation of the argument profilepic leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting vulnerability classes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1467 | Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1467</link><description>Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(). This is related to [SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541)</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1587 | SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System Add New Record main.cpp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file main.cpp of the component Add New Record. The manipulation of the argument name leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1586 | code-projects Blood Bank System A-.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1586</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Blood/A-.php. The manipulation of the argument Bloodname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1585 | otale header.html OptionsService cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1585</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in otale tale up to 2.0.5. This issue affects the function OptionsService of the file src/main/resources/templates/themes/default/partial/header.html. The manipulation of the argument logo_url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1584 | opensolon Solon StaticMappings.java path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1584</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in opensolon Solon up to 3.0.8. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file solon-projects/solon-web/solon-web-staticfiles/src/main/java/org/noear/solon/web/staticfiles/StaticMappings.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.9 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is f46e47fd1f8455b9467d7ead3cdb0509115b2ef1. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1583 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System search-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/search-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1582 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System all-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/all-request.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1581 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System book-nurse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /book-nurse.php?bookid=1. The manipulation of the argument contactname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1580 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting parameter names to be affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1579 | code-projects Blood Bank System user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1578 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal search-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1578</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument product leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1577 | code-projects Blood Bank System prostatus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1577</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /prostatus.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 07:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13728 | Accept Donations with PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13728</link><description>The Accept Donations with PayPal &amp; Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the rf parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1576 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System ajax_state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1576</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax_state.php. The manipulation of the argument StateName as part of String leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1575 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1575</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. Affected is an unknown function of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument cod/codexame leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28339 | Trend Micro HouseCall for Home Networks version 5.3.1302 and below contains an uncontrolled search patch element vulnerability that could al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28339</link><description>Trend Micro HouseCall for Home Networks version 5.3.1302 and below contains an uncontrolled search patch element vulnerability that could allow an attacker with low user privileges to create a malicious DLL that could lead to escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 21:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26750 | WordPress Vitepos Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26750</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in appsbd Vitepos allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Vitepos: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26756 | WordPress Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26756</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in grimdonkey Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips: from n/a through 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26757 | WordPress FULL – Cliente plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.26 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26757</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in FULL SERVICES FULL Customer allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects FULL Customer: from n/a through 3.1.26.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26760 | WordPress Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26760</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Wow-Company Calculator Builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Calculator Builder: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26763 | WordPress Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider – Image Slider, Video Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.94.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26763</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MetaSlider Responsive Slider by MetaSlider allows Object Injection. This issue affects Responsive Slider by MetaSlider: from n/a through 3.94.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26764 | WordPress Distance Based Shipping Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.22 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26764</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Distance Based Shipping Calculator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Distance Based Shipping Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26774 | WordPress Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26774</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rock Solid Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Responsive Modal Builder for High Conversion – Easy Popups: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26776 | WordPress Chaty Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26776</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Chaty Pro allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Chaty Pro: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26973 | WordPress Social Warfare Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26973</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WarfarePlugins Social Warfare allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Social Warfare: from n/a through 4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27012 | WordPress A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27012</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in a1post A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects A1POST.BG Shipping for Woo: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12577 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_pcset_ungrab OOB write via psFWMemContext-&amp;gt;uiPageCatBaseRegSet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12577</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52939 | GPU DDK - RGXFWIF_HWPERF_CTL_BLK.uiNumCounters OOB write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52939</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may post improper commands to the GPU Firmware to trigger a write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47896 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_hwr_log_info OOB write via psHWRInfoBuf-&amp;gt;ui32WriteIndex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47896</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46975 | GPU DDK - rgxfw_write_robustness_buffer allows arbitrary catreg set mapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46975</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to write data into another Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0957 | Vulnerability: SMTP for Amazon SES &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0957</link><description>The SMTP for Amazon SES – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1557 | OFCMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1557</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in OFCMS 1.1.3. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 13:03:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13869 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid &amp;lt;= 0.9.112 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload via wpvivid_upload_file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13869</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.112. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. NOTE: Uploaded files are only accessible on WordPress instances running on the NGINX web server as the existing .htaccess within the target file upload folder prevents access on Apache servers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0918 | SMTP for SendGrid – YaySMTP &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0918</link><description>The SMTP for SendGrid – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0953 | SMTP for Sendinblue – YaySMTP &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0953</link><description>The SMTP for Sendinblue – YaySMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1556 | westboy CicadasCMS Template Management system deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1556</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /system of the component Template Management. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 12:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21704 | usb: cdc-acm: Check control transfer buffer size before access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21704</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: cdc-acm: Check control transfer buffer size before access

If the first fragment is shorter than struct usb_cdc_notification, we can't
calculate an expected_size. Log an error and discard the notification
instead of reading lengths from memory outside the received data, which can
lead to memory corruption when the expected_size decreases between
fragments, causing `expected_size - acm-&gt;nb_index` to wrap.

This issue has been present since the beginning of git history; however,
it only leads to memory corruption since commit ea2583529cd1
("cdc-acm: reassemble fragmented notifications").

A mitigating factor is that acm_ctrl_irq() can only execute after userspace
has opened /dev/ttyACM*; but if ModemManager is running, ModemManager will
do that automatically depending on the USB device's vendor/product IDs and
its other interfaces.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 09:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1553 | pankajindevops scale project cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1553</link><description>A vulnerability was found in pankajindevops scale up to 3633544a00245d3df88b6d13d9b3dd0f411be7f6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /scale/project. The manipulation of the argument goal leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 09:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13564 | Rife Elementor Extensions &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Writing Effect Headline Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13564</link><description>The Rife Elementor Extensions &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Writing Effect Headline shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1361 | IP2Location Country Blocker &amp;lt;= 2.38.8 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure via admin_init Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1361</link><description>The IP2Location Country Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.38.8 due to missing capability checks on the admin_init() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12038 | Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;buddyforms_nav&amp;#x27; Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12038</link><description>The Post Form – Registration Form – Profile Form for User Profiles – Frontend Content Forms for User Submissions (UGC) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buddyforms_nav' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12467 | Pago por Redsys &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12467</link><description>The Pago por Redsys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Ds_MerchantParameters' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13474 | LTL Freight Quotes – Purolator Edition &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13474</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Purolator Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13798 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Unauthenticated Paid Order Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13798</link><description>The Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks – ComboBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized order creation in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This is due to insufficient verification on form fields. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new orders for products and mark them as paid without actually completing a payment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 04:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13873 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Photo Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13873</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.8 via the deleteUserPhoto() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove profile photos from users accounts. Please note that this does not officially delete the file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13899 | Mambo Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13899</link><description>The Mambo Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 via deserialization of untrusted input via the $data parameter in the fImportMenu function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1509 | Show Me The Cookies &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1509</link><description>The The Show Me The Cookies plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1510 | Custom Post Type Date Archives &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1510</link><description>The The Custom Post Type Date Archives plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 03:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22341 | IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22341</link><description>IBM Watson Query on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.0 through 4.0.9, 4.5.0 through 4.5.3, 4.6.0 through 4.6.6, 4.7.0 through 4.7.4, and 4.8.0 through 4.8.7 could allow unauthorized data access from a remote data source object due to improper privilege management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 02:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>