<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 05:45:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-5431 | WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.25 - Authenticated (Contributor+) File inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5431</link><description>The WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.25 via the reservation_extra_field shortcode parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include remote files on the server, potentially resulting in code execution</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 05:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32855 | Dell Client Platform BIOS contains an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32855</link><description>Dell Client Platform BIOS contains an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in an externally developed component. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4197 | Avaya IP Office One-X Portal File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4197</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Avaya IP Office was discovered that could allow remote command or code execution via the One-X component. Affected versions include all versions prior to 11.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4196 | Avaya IP Office Web Control RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4196</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability  was discovered in Avaya IP Office that could allow remote command or code execution via a specially crafted web request to the Web Control component. Affected versions include all versions prior to 11.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23156 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23156</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23157 | A maliciously crafted SLDASM or SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23157</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDASM or SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23158 | A maliciously crafted IGES file, when parsed in ASMImport229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a use-after-free vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23158</link><description>A maliciously crafted IGES file, when parsed in ASMImport229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a use-after-free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23159 | A maliciously crafted STP file, when parsed in stp_aim_x64_vc15d.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23159</link><description>A maliciously crafted STP file, when parsed in stp_aim_x64_vc15d.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36999 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36999</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37007 | A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37007</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6297 | Several WordPress.org Plugins &amp;lt;= Various Versions  - Injected Backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6297</link><description>Several plugins for WordPress hosted on WordPress.org have been compromised and injected with malicious PHP scripts. A malicious threat actor compromised the source code of various plugins and injected code that exfiltrates database credentials and is used to create new, malicious, administrator users and send that data back to a server. Currently, not all plugins have been patched and we strongly recommend uninstalling the plugins for the time being and running a complete malware scan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23151 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23151</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23152 | A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23152</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23153 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodx.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23153</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodx.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23154 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23154</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23155 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in atf_asm_interface.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Buff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23155</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in atf_asm_interface.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23150 | A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in odxug_dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23150</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in odxug_dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37003 | A maliciously crafted DWG and SLDPRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37003</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWG and SLDPRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Stack-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37004 | A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37004</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed in ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37005 | A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37005</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37006 | A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37006</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37000 | A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37000</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37001 | [A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37001</link><description>[A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can be used to cause a Heap-based Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37002 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dllthrough Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37002</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dllthrough Autodesk applications, can be used to uninitialized variables. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, could lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23148 | A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23148</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23149 | A maliciously crafted SLDDRW file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23149</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDDRW file, when parsed in ODXSW_DLL.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23145 | A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious acto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23145</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23146 | A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malici...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23146</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_B and X_T file, when parsed in pskernel.DLL through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23147 | A maliciously crafted CATPART, X_B and STEP, when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll and ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23147</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART, X_B and STEP, when parsed in ASMKERN228A.dll and ASMKERN229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can lead to a memory corruption vulnerability by write access violation. This vulnerability, in conjunction with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:50:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5038 | Unauthenticated DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5038</link><description>badmonkey, a Security Researcher has found a flaw that allows for a unauthenticated DoS attack on the camera. An attacker runs a crafted URL, nobody can access the web management page of the camera. and must manually restart the device or re-power it. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6295 | udn News App - Insecure Data Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6295</link><description>udn News Android APP stores the unencrypted user session in the local database when user log into the application. A malicious APP or an attacker with physical access to the Android device can retrieve this session and use it to log into the news APP and other services provided by udn.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23143 | A maliciously crafted 3DM, MODEL and X_B file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll and ASMBASE229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23143</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM, MODEL and X_B file, when parsed in ASMkern229A.dll and ASMBASE229A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read and/or Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23144 | A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23144</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed in CC5Dll.dll and ASMBASE228A.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6294 | udn News App - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6294</link><description>udn News Android APP stores the user session in logcat file when user log into the APP. A malicious APP or an attacker with physical access to the Android device can retrieve this session and use it to log into the news APP and other services provided by udn.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6198 | Hard Coded Credential</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6198</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Baicells Snap Router BaiCE_BMI on EP3011 (User Passwords modules) allows unauthorized access to the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22385 | File and Directory Permission Vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22385</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter allows local users to read and write specific files.This issue affects Hitachi Storage Provider for VMware vCenter: from 3.1.0 before 3.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23141 | A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a double free. This vulnerability, along...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23141</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed in libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a double free. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23142 | A maliciously crafted CATPART, STP, and MODEL file, when parsed in atf_dwg_consumer.dll, rose_x64_vc15.dll and libodxdll through Autodesk ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23142</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART, STP, and MODEL file, when parsed in atf_dwg_consumer.dll, rose_x64_vc15.dll and libodxdll through Autodesk applications, can cause a use-after-free vulnerability. This vulnerability, along with other vulnerabilities, can lead to code execution in the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23140 | A maliciously crafted 3DM and MODEL file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and atf_api.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23140</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM and MODEL file, when parsed in opennurbs.dll and atf_api.dll through Autodesk applications, can force an Out-of-Bound Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22168 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on Western Digital My Cloud and SanDisk ibi Web Apps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22168</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the My Cloud, My Cloud Home, SanDisk ibi, and WD Cloud web apps was found which could allow an attacker to redirect the user to a crafted domain and reset their credentials, or to execute arbitrary client-side code in the user’s browser session to carry out malicious activities.The web apps for these devices have been automatically updated to resolve this vulnerability and improve the security of your devices and data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36683 | SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Products Alert" (productsalert) before 1.7.4 from Smart Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36683</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Products Alert" (productsalert) before 1.7.4 from Smart Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via the ProductsAlertAjaxProcessModuleFrontController::initContent method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36681 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Isotope" (pk_isotope) &lt;=1.7.3 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36681</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Isotope" (pk_isotope) &lt;=1.7.3 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via `pk_isotope::saveData` and `pk_isotope::removeData` methods.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50029 | PHP Injection vulnerability in the module "M4 PDF Extensions" (m4pdf) up to version 3.3.2 from PrestaAddons for PrestaShop allows attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50029</link><description>PHP Injection vulnerability in the module "M4 PDF Extensions" (m4pdf) up to version 3.3.2 from PrestaAddons for PrestaShop allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the M4PDF::saveTemplate() method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34992 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Help Desk - Customer Support Management System" (helpdesk) up to version 2.4.0 from FME Modules f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34992</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the module "Help Desk - Customer Support Management System" (helpdesk) up to version 2.4.0 from FME Modules for PrestaShop allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and cause other impacts via 'Tickets::getsearchedtickets()'</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34988 | SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Complete for Create a Quote in Frontend + Backend Pro" (askforaquotemodul) &lt;= 1.0.51 from Buy Add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34988</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the module "Complete for Create a Quote in Frontend + Backend Pro" (askforaquotemodul) &lt;= 1.0.51 from Buy Addons for PrestaShop allows attackers to view sensitive information and cause other impacts via methods `AskforaquotemodulcustomernewquoteModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemoduladdproductnewquoteModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulCouponcodeModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulgetshippingcostModuleFrontController::run()`, `AskforaquotemodulgetstateModuleFrontController::run().`</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36682 | In the module "Theme settings" (pk_themesettings) &lt;= 1.8.8 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can download all email collected while S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36682</link><description>In the module "Theme settings" (pk_themesettings) &lt;= 1.8.8 from Promokit.eu for PrestaShop, a guest can download all email collected while SHOP is in maintenance mode. Due to a lack of permissions control, a guest can access the txt file which collect email when maintenance is enable which can lead to leak of personal information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34991 | In the module "Axepta" (axepta) before 1.3.4 from Quadra Informatique for PrestaShop, a guest can download partial credit card information (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34991</link><description>In the module "Axepta" (axepta) before 1.3.4 from Quadra Informatique for PrestaShop, a guest can download partial credit card information (expiry date) / postal address / email / etc. without restriction due to a lack of permissions control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6290 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6290</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6291 | Use after free in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6291</link><description>Use after free in Swiftshader in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6292 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6292</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6293 | Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6293</link><description>Use after free in Dawn in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.126 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33898 | Axiros AXESS Auto Configuration Server (ACS) 4.x and 5.0.0 has Incorrect Access Control. An authorization bypass allows remote attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33898</link><description>Axiros AXESS Auto Configuration Server (ACS) 4.x and 5.0.0 has Incorrect Access Control. An authorization bypass allows remote attackers to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45195 | Adminer and AdminerEvo SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45195</link><description>Adminer and AdminerEvo are vulnerable to SSRF via database connection fields. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to enumerate or access systems the attacker would not otherwise have access to. Adminer is no longer supported, but this issue was fixed in AdminerEvo version 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45196 | Adminer and AdminerEvo denial of service via HTTP redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45196</link><description>Adminer and AdminerEvo allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service by connecting to an attacker-controlled service that responds with HTTP redirects. The denial of service is subject to PHP configuration limits. Adminer is no longer supported, but this issue was fixed in AdminerEvo version 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38897 | WAVLINK WN551K1'live_check.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38897</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1'live_check.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38902 | H3C Magic R230 V100R002 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as roo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38902</link><description>H3C Magic R230 V100R002 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38903 | H3C Magic R230 V100R002's udpserver opens port 9034, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38903</link><description>H3C Magic R230 V100R002's udpserver opens port 9034, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38895 | WAVLINK WN551K1'live_mfg.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38895</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1'live_mfg.shtml enables attackers to obtain sensitive router information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38896 | WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the start_hour parameter of /cgi-bin/nightled.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38896</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the start_hour parameter of /cgi-bin/nightled.cgi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38894 | WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the IP parameter of /cgi-bin/touchlist_sync.cgi.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38894</link><description>WAVLINK WN551K1 found a command injection vulnerability through the IP parameter of /cgi-bin/touchlist_sync.cgi.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37759 | DataGear v5.0.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a SpEL (Spring Expression Language) expression injection vulnerability via the Data Vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37759</link><description>DataGear v5.0.0 and earlier was discovered to contain a SpEL (Spring Expression Language) expression injection vulnerability via the Data Viewing interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38892 | An issue in Wavlink WN551K1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ExportAllSettings.sh component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38892</link><description>An issue in Wavlink WN551K1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ExportAllSettings.sh component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34312 | Virtual Programming Lab for Moodle up to v4.2.3 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component vplid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34312</link><description>Virtual Programming Lab for Moodle up to v4.2.3 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component vplide.js.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34313 | An issue in VPL Jail System up to v4.0.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted request to a public endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34313</link><description>An issue in VPL Jail System up to v4.0.2 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted request to a public endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37678 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. Finesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37678</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. Finesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37681 | An issue the background management system of Shanxi Internet Chuangxiang Technology Co., Ltd v1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to cause a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37681</link><description>An issue the background management system of Shanxi Internet Chuangxiang Technology Co., Ltd v1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the index.html component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-45785 | TruDesk Help Desk/Ticketing Solution v1.1.11 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack which would allow an attacker to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45785</link><description>TruDesk Help Desk/Ticketing Solution v1.1.11 is vulnerable to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack which would allow an attacker to restart the server, causing a DoS attack. The attacker must craft a webpage that would perform a GET request to the /api/v1/admin/restart endpoint, then the victim (who has sufficient privileges), would visit the page and the server restart would begin. The attacker must know the full URL that TruDesk is on in order to craft the webpage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37677 | An issue in Shenzhen Weitillage Industrial Co., Ltd the access management specialist V6.62.51215 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37677</link><description>An issue in Shenzhen Weitillage Industrial Co., Ltd the access management specialist V6.62.51215 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37679 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., LTd Finnesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37679</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., LTd Finnesoft v.8.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the login.jsp parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37680 | Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. FineSoft &lt;=8.0 is affected by Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows remote attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37680</link><description>Hangzhou Meisoft Information Technology Co., Ltd. FineSoft &lt;=8.0 is affected by Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Enter any account and password, click Login, the page will report an error, and a controllable parameter will appear at the URL:weburl.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37732 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anchor CMS v.0.12.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .pdf file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37732</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Anchor CMS v.0.12.7 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted .pdf file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49793 | Path traversal in `CodeChecker server` in the endpoint of `CodeChecker store`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49793</link><description>CodeChecker is an analyzer tooling, defect database and viewer extension for the Clang Static Analyzer and Clang Tidy. Zip files uploaded to the server endpoint of `CodeChecker store` are not properly sanitized. An attacker, using a path traversal attack, can load and display files on the machine of `CodeChecker server`. The vulnerable endpoint is `/Default/v6.53/CodeCheckerService@massStoreRun`. The path traversal vulnerability allows reading data on the machine of the `CodeChecker server`, with the same permission level as the `CodeChecker server`.
The attack requires a user account on the `CodeChecker server`, with permission to store to a server, and view the stored report. This vulnerability has been patched in version 6.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6104 | go-retryablehttp can leak basic auth credentials to log files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6104</link><description>go-retryablehttp prior to 0.7.7 did not sanitize urls when writing them to its log file. This could lead to go-retryablehttp writing sensitive HTTP basic auth credentials to its log file. This vulnerability, CVE-2024-6104, was fixed in go-retryablehttp 0.7.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38369 | XWiki programming rights may be inherited by inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38369</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. The content of a document included using `{{include reference="targetdocument"/}}` is executed with the right of the includer and not with the right of its author. This means that any user able to modify the target document can impersonate the author of the content which used the `include` macro. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 15.0 RC1 by making the default behavior safe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33879 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Downlo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33879</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx isCompleted method allows arbitrary file download and deletion via absolute path traversal in the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33880 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. It discloses full pathnames via Virto.SharePoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33880</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. It discloses full pathnames via Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx?action=archive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33881 | An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Downlo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33881</link><description>An issue was discovered in VirtoSoftware Virto Bulk File Download 5.5.44 for SharePoint 2019. The Virto.SharePoint.FileDownloader/Api/Download.ashx isCompleted method allows an NTLMv2 hash leak via a UNC share pathname in the path parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38373 | FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP Buffer Over-Read in DNS Response Parser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38373</link><description>FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP is a lightweight TCP/IP stack for FreeRTOS. FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP versions 4.0.0 through 4.1.0 contain a buffer over-read issue in the DNS Response Parser when parsing domain names in a DNS response. A carefully crafted DNS response with domain name length value greater than the actual domain name length, could cause the parser to read beyond the DNS response buffer. This issue affects applications using DNS functionality of the FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP stack. Applications that do not use DNS functionality are not affected, even when the DNS functionality is enabled. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6285 | Integer Underflow in Memory Range Check in Renesas RCAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6285</link><description>Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability in Renesas arm-trusted-firmware.
An integer underflow in image range check calculations could lead to bypassing address restrictions and loading of images to unallowed addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6287 | Incorrect Address Range Calculations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6287</link><description>Incorrect Calculation vulnerability in Renesas arm-trusted-firmware allows Local Execution of Code.


When checking whether a new image invades/overlaps with a previously loaded image the code neglects to consider a few cases. that could An attacker to bypass memory range restriction and overwrite an already loaded image partly or completely, which could result in code execution and bypass of secure boot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33687 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity issue exists in NJ Series CPU Unit all versions and NX Series CPU Unit all versions. If a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33687</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity issue exists in NJ Series CPU Unit all versions and NX Series CPU Unit all versions. If a user program in the affected product is altered, the product may not be able to detect the alteration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33278 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ASUS router RT-AX88U with firmware versions v3.0.0.4.388_24198 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33278</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ASUS router RT-AX88U with firmware versions v3.0.0.4.388_24198 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the connection_state_machine due to improper length validation for the cookie field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37825 | An issue in EnvisionWare Computer Access &amp; Reservation Control SelfCheck v1.0 (fixed in OneStop 3.2.0.27184 Hotfix May 2024) allows unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37825</link><description>An issue in EnvisionWare Computer Access &amp; Reservation Control SelfCheck v1.0 (fixed in OneStop 3.2.0.27184 Hotfix May 2024) allows unauthenticated attackers on the same network to perform a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32936 | media: ti: j721e-csi2rx: Fix races while restarting DMA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32936</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: ti: j721e-csi2rx: Fix races while restarting DMA

After the frame is submitted to DMA, it may happen that the submitted
list is not updated soon enough, and the DMA callback is triggered
before that.

This can lead to kernel crashes, so move everything in a single
lock/unlock section to prevent such races.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33847 | f2fs: compress: don&amp;#x27;t allow unaligned truncation on released compress inode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33847</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: compress: don't allow unaligned truncation on released compress inode

f2fs image may be corrupted after below testcase:
- mkfs.f2fs -O extra_attr,compression -f /dev/vdb
- mount /dev/vdb /mnt/f2fs
- touch /mnt/f2fs/file
- f2fs_io setflags compression /mnt/f2fs/file
- dd if=/dev/zero of=/mnt/f2fs/file bs=4k count=4
- f2fs_io release_cblocks /mnt/f2fs/file
- truncate -s 8192 /mnt/f2fs/file
- umount /mnt/f2fs
- fsck.f2fs /dev/vdb

[ASSERT] (fsck_chk_inode_blk:1256)  --&gt; ino: 0x5 has i_blocks: 0x00000002, but has 0x3 blocks
[FSCK] valid_block_count matching with CP             [Fail] [0x4, 0x5]
[FSCK] other corrupted bugs                           [Fail]

The reason is: partial truncation assume compressed inode has reserved
blocks, after partial truncation, valid block count may change w/o
.i_blocks and .total_valid_block_count update, result in corruption.

This patch only allow cluster size aligned truncation on released
compress inode for fixing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34027 | f2fs: compress: fix to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34027</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

f2fs: compress: fix to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock

It needs to cover {reserve,release}_compress_blocks() w/ cp_rwsem lock
to avoid racing with checkpoint, otherwise, filesystem metadata including
blkaddr in dnode, inode fields and .total_valid_block_count may be
corrupted after SPO case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34030 | PCI: of_property: Return error for int_map allocation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34030</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: of_property: Return error for int_map allocation failure

Return -ENOMEM from of_pci_prop_intr_map() if kcalloc() fails to prevent a
NULL pointer dereference in this case.

[bhelgaas: commit log]</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35247 | fpga: region: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35247</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: region: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga region assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the region
during programming if the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_region
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the functions for
registering a region to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename them to avoid conflicts. Use the old function names for helper
macros that automatically set the module that registers the region as the
owner. This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules
and reduces the chances of registering a region without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga region.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36479 | fpga: bridge: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36479</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: bridge: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga bridge assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the bridge if
the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_bridge
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the function for
registering a bridge to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename it to avoid conflicts. Use the old function name for a helper macro
that automatically sets the module that registers the bridge as the owner.
This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules and
reduces the chances of registering a bridge without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga bridge.

Other changes: opportunistically move put_device() from __fpga_bridge_get()
to fpga_bridge_get() and of_fpga_bridge_get() to improve code clarity since
the bridge device is taken in these functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37021 | fpga: manager: add owner module and take its refcount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37021</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fpga: manager: add owner module and take its refcount

The current implementation of the fpga manager assumes that the low-level
module registers a driver for the parent device and uses its owner pointer
to take the module's refcount. This approach is problematic since it can
lead to a null pointer dereference while attempting to get the manager if
the parent device does not have a driver.

To address this problem, add a module owner pointer to the fpga_manager
struct and use it to take the module's refcount. Modify the functions for
registering the manager to take an additional owner module parameter and
rename them to avoid conflicts. Use the old function names for helper
macros that automatically set the module that registers the manager as the
owner. This ensures compatibility with existing low-level control modules
and reduces the chances of registering a manager without setting the owner.

Also, update the documentation to keep it consistent with the new interface
for registering an fpga manager.

Other changes: opportunistically move put_device() from __fpga_mgr_get() to
fpga_mgr_get() and of_fpga_mgr_get() to improve code clarity since the
manager device is taken in these functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37026 | drm/xe: Only use reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37026</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe: Only use reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue

The GuC context scheduling queue is 2 entires deep, thus it is possible
for a migration job to be stuck behind a fault if migration exec queue
shares engines with user jobs. This can deadlock as the migrate exec
queue is required to service page faults. Avoid deadlock by only using
reserved BCS instances for usm migrate exec queue.

(cherry picked from commit 04f4a70a183a688a60fe3882d6e4236ea02cfc67)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38667 | riscv: prevent pt_regs corruption for secondary idle threads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

riscv: prevent pt_regs corruption for secondary idle threads

Top of the kernel thread stack should be reserved for pt_regs. However
this is not the case for the idle threads of the secondary boot harts.
Their stacks overlap with their pt_regs, so both may get corrupted.

Similar issue has been fixed for the primary hart, see c7cdd96eca28
("riscv: prevent stack corruption by reserving task_pt_regs(p) early").
However that fix was not propagated to the secondary harts. The problem
has been noticed in some CPU hotplug tests with V enabled. The function
smp_callin stored several registers on stack, corrupting top of pt_regs
structure including status field. As a result, kernel attempted to save
or restore inexistent V context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39291 | drm/amdgpu: Fix buffer size in gfx_v9_4_3_init_ cp_compute_microcode() and rlc_microcode()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39291</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix buffer size in gfx_v9_4_3_init_ cp_compute_microcode() and rlc_microcode()

The function gfx_v9_4_3_init_microcode in gfx_v9_4_3.c was generating
about potential truncation of output when using the snprintf function.
The issue was due to the size of the buffer 'ucode_prefix' being too
small to accommodate the maximum possible length of the string being
written into it.

The string being written is "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin" or "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin",
where %s is replaced by the value of 'chip_name'. The length of this
string without the %s is 16 characters. The warning message indicated
that 'chip_name' could be up to 29 characters long, resulting in a total
of 45 characters, which exceeds the buffer size of 30 characters.

To resolve this issue, the size of the 'ucode_prefix' buffer has been
reduced from 30 to 15. This ensures that the maximum possible length of
the string being written into the buffer will not exceed its size, thus
preventing potential buffer overflow and truncation issues.

Fixes the below with gcc W=1:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c: In function ‘gfx_v9_4_3_early_init’:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:379:52: warning: ‘%s’ directive output may be truncated writing up to 29 bytes into a region of size 23 [-Wformat-truncation=]
  379 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin", chip_name);
      |                                                    ^~
......
  439 |         r = gfx_v9_4_3_init_rlc_microcode(adev, ucode_prefix);
      |                                                 ~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:379:9: note: ‘snprintf’ output between 16 and 45 bytes into a destination of size 30
  379 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_rlc.bin", chip_name);
      |         ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:413:52: warning: ‘%s’ directive output may be truncated writing up to 29 bytes into a region of size 23 [-Wformat-truncation=]
  413 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin", chip_name);
      |                                                    ^~
......
  443 |         r = gfx_v9_4_3_init_cp_compute_microcode(adev, ucode_prefix);
      |                                                        ~~~~~~~~~~~~
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/gfx_v9_4_3.c:413:9: note: ‘snprintf’ output between 16 and 45 bytes into a destination of size 30
  413 |         snprintf(fw_name, sizeof(fw_name), "amdgpu/%s_mec.bin", chip_name);
      |         ^~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39292 | um: Add winch to winch_handlers before registering winch IRQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39292</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

um: Add winch to winch_handlers before registering winch IRQ

Registering a winch IRQ is racy, an interrupt may occur before the winch is
added to the winch_handlers list.

If that happens, register_winch_irq() adds to that list a winch that is
scheduled to be (or has already been) freed, causing a panic later in
winch_cleanup().

Avoid the race by adding the winch to the winch_handlers list before
registering the IRQ, and rolling back if um_request_irq() fails.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4748 | RCE in Cruddiy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4748</link><description>The CRUDDIY project is vulnerable to shell command injection via sending a crafted POST request to the application server. 
The exploitation risk is limited since CRUDDIY is meant to be launched locally. Nevertheless, a user with the project running on their computer might visit a website which would send such a malicious request to the locally launched server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38384 | blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from reorder of WRITE -&amp;gt;lqueued</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38384</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from reorder of WRITE -&gt;lqueued

__blkcg_rstat_flush() can be run anytime, especially when blk_cgroup_bio_start
is being executed.

If WRITE of `-&gt;lqueued` is re-ordered with READ of 'bisc-&gt;lnode.next' in
the loop of __blkcg_rstat_flush(), `next_bisc` can be assigned with one
stat instance being added in blk_cgroup_bio_start(), then the local
list in __blkcg_rstat_flush() could be corrupted.

Fix the issue by adding one barrier.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38663 | blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from resetting io stat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-cgroup: fix list corruption from resetting io stat

Since commit 3b8cc6298724 ("blk-cgroup: Optimize blkcg_rstat_flush()"),
each iostat instance is added to blkcg percpu list, so blkcg_reset_stats()
can't reset the stat instance by memset(), otherwise the llist may be
corrupted.

Fix the issue by only resetting the counter part.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38664 | drm: zynqmp_dpsub: Always register bridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm: zynqmp_dpsub: Always register bridge

We must always register the DRM bridge, since zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func
calls drm_bridge_hpd_notify, which in turn expects hpd_mutex to be
initialized. We do this before zynqmp_dpsub_drm_init since that calls
drm_bridge_attach. This fixes the following lockdep warning:

[   19.217084] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   19.227530] DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
[   19.227768] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 140 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:582 __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.241696] Modules linked in:
[   19.244937] CPU: 0 PID: 140 Comm: kworker/0:4 Not tainted 6.6.20+ #96
[   19.252046] Hardware name: xlnx,zynqmp (DT)
[   19.256421] Workqueue: events zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func
[   19.261795] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[   19.269104] pc : __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.273364] lr : __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.277592] sp : ffffffc085c5bbe0
[   19.281066] x29: ffffffc085c5bbe0 x28: 0000000000000000 x27: ffffff88009417f8
[   19.288624] x26: ffffff8800941788 x25: ffffff8800020008 x24: ffffffc082aa3000
[   19.296227] x23: ffffffc080d90e3c x22: 0000000000000002 x21: 0000000000000000
[   19.303744] x20: 0000000000000000 x19: ffffff88002f5210 x18: 0000000000000000
[   19.311295] x17: 6c707369642e3030 x16: 3030613464662072 x15: 0720072007200720
[   19.318922] x14: 0000000000000000 x13: 284e4f5f4e524157 x12: 0000000000000001
[   19.326442] x11: 0001ffc085c5b940 x10: 0001ff88003f388b x9 : 0001ff88003f3888
[   19.334003] x8 : 0001ff88003f3888 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 0000000000000000
[   19.341537] x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : 0000000000001668 x3 : 0000000000000000
[   19.349054] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffffff88003f3880
[   19.356581] Call trace:
[   19.359160]  __mutex_lock+0x4bc/0x550
[   19.363032]  mutex_lock_nested+0x24/0x30
[   19.367187]  drm_bridge_hpd_notify+0x2c/0x6c
[   19.371698]  zynqmp_dp_hpd_work_func+0x44/0x54
[   19.376364]  process_one_work+0x3ac/0x988
[   19.380660]  worker_thread+0x398/0x694
[   19.384736]  kthread+0x1bc/0x1c0
[   19.388241]  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
[   19.392031] irq event stamp: 183
[   19.395450] hardirqs last  enabled at (183): [] finish_task_switch.isra.0+0xa8/0x2d4
[   19.405140] hardirqs last disabled at (182): [] __schedule+0x714/0xd04
[   19.413612] softirqs last  enabled at (114): [] srcu_invoke_callbacks+0x158/0x23c
[   19.423128] softirqs last disabled at (110): [] srcu_invoke_callbacks+0x158/0x23c
[   19.432614] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

(cherry picked from commit 61ba791c4a7a09a370c45b70a81b8c7d4cf6b2ae)</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37233 | WordPress Play.ht plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37233</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Play.Ht allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Play.Ht: from n/a through 3.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3264 | Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med Health Aplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3264</link><description>Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. Mia-Med Health Aplication allows Signature Spoofing by Improper Validation.This issue affects Mia-Med Health Aplication: before 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4839 | CSRF in Servers Configurations in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4839</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the 'Servers Configurations' function of the parisneo/lollms-webui, versions 9.6 to the latest. The affected functions include Elastic search Service (under construction), XTTS service, Petals service, vLLM service, and Motion Ctrl service, which lack CSRF protection. This vulnerability allows attackers to deceive users into unwittingly installing the XTTS service among other packages by submitting a malicious installation request. Successful exploitation results in attackers tricking users into performing actions without their consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37107 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Authenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37107</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37109 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Authenticated Arbitrary PHP Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37109</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X allows Code Injection.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37111 | WordPress WishList Member X plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Unauthenticated Denial of Service Attack vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37111</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Membership Software WishList Member X.This issue affects WishList Member X: from n/a through 3.25.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37228 | WordPress InstaWP Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.38 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37228</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in InstaWP Team InstaWP Connect allows Code Injection.This issue affects InstaWP Connect: from n/a through 0.1.0.38.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37231 | WordPress Salon booking system plugin &amp;lt;= 9.9 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37231</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Salon Booking System Salon booking system allows File Manipulation.This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 9.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5862 | User Enumeration in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med Health Aplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5862</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. Mia-Med Health Aplication allows Interface Manipulation.This issue affects Mia-Med Health Aplication: before 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37092 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37092</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37089 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37089</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37091 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36038 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36038</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ITOM products versions from 128234 to 128248 are affected by the stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the proxy server option.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29868 | Apache StreamPipes, Apache StreamPipes: Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) in Recovery Token Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29868</link><description>Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes user self-registration and password recovery mechanism.
This allows an attacker to guess the recovery token in a reasonable time and thereby to take over the attacked user's account.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: from 0.69.0 through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 10:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6160 | SQL Injection in MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6160</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in MegaBIP software allows attacker to disclose the contents of the database, obtain session cookies or modify the content of pages. This issue affects MegaBIP software versions through 5.12.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36496 | Hardcoded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36496</link><description>The configuration file is encrypted with a static key derived from a 
static five-character password which allows an attacker to decrypt this 
file. The application hashes this five-character password with 
the outdated and broken MD5 algorithm (no salt) and uses the first five 
bytes as the key for RC4. The configuration file is then encrypted with 
these parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36497 | Unhashed Storage of Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36497</link><description>The decrypted configuration file contains the password in cleartext 
which is used to configure WINSelect. It can be used to remove the 
existing restrictions and disable WINSelect entirely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4754 | Stored XSS in Next4Biz&amp;#x27;s BPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4754</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Next4Biz CRM &amp; BPM Software Business Process Manangement (BPM) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Business Process Manangement (BPM): from 6.6.4.4 before 6.6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5683 | Remote Code Execution in Next4Biz&amp;#x27;s BPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5683</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Next4Biz CRM &amp; BPM Software Business Process Manangement (BPM) allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Business Process Manangement (BPM): from 6.6.4.4 before 6.6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36495 | Read/Write Permissions for Everyone on Configuration File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36495</link><description>The application Faronics WINSelect (Standard + Enterprise) saves its configuration in an encrypted file on the file system which "Everyone" has read and write access to, path to file:



C:\ProgramData\WINSelect\WINSelect.wsd

The path for the affected WINSelect Enterprise configuration file is:

C:\ProgramData\Faronics\StorageSpace\WS\WINSelect.wsd</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27136 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-site scripting vulnerability on upload page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27136</link><description>XSS in Upload page in Apache JSPWiki 2.12.1 and priors allows the attacker to execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the victim.  Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.2 or later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24554 | Bludit - Insecure Token Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24554</link><description>Bludit uses predictable methods in combination with the MD5 hashing algorithm to generate sensitive tokens such as the API token and the user token. This allows attackers to authenticate against the Bludit API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24550 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through File API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24550</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing attackers with knowledge of the API token to upload arbitrary files through the File API which leads to arbitrary code execution on the server. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24551 | Bludit - Remote Code Execution (RCE) through Image API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24551</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in Bludit, allowing authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code through the Image API. This vulnerability arises from improper handling of file uploads, enabling malicious actors to upload and execute PHP files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24552 | Bludit is Vulnerable to Session Fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24552</link><description>A session fixation vulnerability in Bludit allows an attacker to bypass the server's authentication if they can trick an administrator or any other user into authorizing a session ID of their choosing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24553 | Bludit uses SHA1 as Password Hashing Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24553</link><description>Bludit uses the SHA-1 hashing algorithm to compute password hashes. Thus, attackers could determine cleartext passwords with brute-force attacks due to the inherent speed of SHA-1. In addition, the salt that is computed by Bludit is generated with a non-cryptographically secure function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4460 | DoS Vulnerability in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4460</link><description>A denial of service (DoS) vulnerability exists in zenml-io/zenml version 0.56.3 due to improper handling of line feed (`\n`) characters in component names. When a low-privileged user adds a component through the API endpoint `api/v1/workspaces/default/components` with a name containing a `\n` character, it leads to uncontrolled resource consumption. This vulnerability results in the inability of users to add new components in certain categories (e.g., 'Image Builder') and to register new stacks through the UI, thereby degrading the user experience and potentially rendering the ZenML Dashboard unusable. The issue does not affect component addition through the Web UI, as `\n` characters are properly escaped in that context. The vulnerability was tested on ZenML running in Docker, and it was observed in both Firefox and Chrome browsers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4899 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4899</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its Post settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4900 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.8 - Contributor+ Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4900</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.8 does not validate and escape one of its Post settings, which could allow contributor and above role to perform Open redirect attacks against any user viewing a malicious post</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4499 | CSRF Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms XTTS Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4499</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of parisneo/lollms version 9.6 due to a lax CORS policy. The vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions by tricking a user into visiting a malicious webpage, which can then trigger arbitrary LoLLMS-XTTS API requests. This issue can lead to the reading and writing of audio files and, when combined with other vulnerabilities, could allow for the reading of arbitrary files on the system and writing files outside the permitted audio file location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6280 | SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Online Bidding System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269493 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6278 | lahirudanushka School Management System Subject Page subject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6278</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file subject.php of the component Subject Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6279 | lahirudanushka School Management System Exam Results Page examresults-par.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file examresults-par.php of the component Exam Results Page. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269492.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6277 | lahirudanushka School Management System Student Page student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6277</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file student.php of the component Student Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6276 | lahirudanushka School Management System Teacher Page teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6276</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file teacher.php of the component Teacher Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269489 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6274 | lahirudanushka School Management System Attendance Report Page attendancelist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6274</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /attendancelist.php of the component Attendance Report Page. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269487.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6275 | lahirudanushka School Management System Parent Page parent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6275</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file parent.php of the component Parent Page. The manipulation of the argument update leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269488.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3121 | Remote Code Execution in create_conda_env function in parisneo/lollms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3121</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the create_conda_env function of the parisneo/lollms repository, version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises from the use of shell=True in the subprocess.Popen function, which allows an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by manipulating the env_name and python_version parameters. This issue could lead to a serious security breach as demonstrated by the ability to execute the 'whoami' command among potentially other harmful commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 01:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39337 | Click Studios Passwordstate Core before 9.8 build 9858 allows Authentication Bypass.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39337</link><description>Click Studios Passwordstate Core before 9.8 build 9858 allows Authentication Bypass.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 23:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39334 | MENDELSON AS4 before 2024 B376 has a client-side vulnerability when a trading partner provides prepared XML data. When a victim opens the de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39334</link><description>MENDELSON AS4 before 2024 B376 has a client-side vulnerability when a trading partner provides prepared XML data. When a victim opens the details of this transaction in the client, files can be written to the computer on which the client process is running. (The server process is not affected.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6273 | SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System patient_side.php save_patient cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6273</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinic Queuing System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function save_patient of the file patient_side.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name/Contact/Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269485 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39331 | In Emacs before 29.4, org-link-expand-abbrev in lisp/ol.el expands a %(...) link abbrev even when it specifies an unsafe function, such as s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39331</link><description>In Emacs before 29.4, org-link-expand-abbrev in lisp/ol.el expands a %(...) link abbrev even when it specifies an unsafe function, such as shell-command-to-string. This affects Org Mode before 9.7.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4841 | Path Traversal in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4841</link><description>A Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'add_reference_to_local_mode' function due to the lack of input sanitization. This vulnerability affects versions v9.6 to the latest. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can predict the folders, subfolders, and files present on the victim's computer. The vulnerability is present in the way the application handles the 'path' parameter in HTTP requests to the '/add_reference_to_local_model' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6269 | Ruijie RG-UAC HTTP POST Request sxh_vpnlic.php get_ip.addr_details command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6269</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Ruijie RG-UAC 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_ip.addr_details of the file /view/vpn/autovpn/sxh_vpnlic.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument indevice leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269482 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6268 | lahirudanushka School Management System Login Page login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lahirudanushka School Management System 1.0.0/1.0.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269480.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6267 | SourceCodester Service Provider Management System System Info Page index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6267</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Service Provider Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file system_info/index.php of the component System Info Page. The manipulation of the argument System Name/System Short Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269479.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 06:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6266 | Pear Admin Boot loadDictItem sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Pear Admin Boot up to 2.0.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /system/dictData/loadDictItem. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269478 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 02:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>