<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-37555 | WordPress Generate PDF using Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.6 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37555</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ZealousWeb Generate PDF using Contact Form 7.This issue affects Generate PDF using Contact Form 7: from n/a through 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28747 | ifm: Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28747</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can use the hard-coded credentials to access the SmartSPS devices with high privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28748 | ifm: Reading function in Smart PLC allows command injections </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28748</link><description>A remote attacker with high privileges may use a reading file function to inject OS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28749 | ifm: Writing file function in Smart PLC allows command injections </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28749</link><description>A remote attacker with high privileges may use a writing file function to inject OS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28750 | ifm: Deleting function in Smart PLC allows command injections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28750</link><description>A remote attacker with high privileges may use a deleting file function to inject OS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28751 | ifm: Hardcoded telnet credentials in Smart PLC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28751</link><description>An high privileged remote attacker can enable telnet access that accepts hardcoded credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22062 | Permissions and Access Control Vulnerability in  ZTE ZXCLOUD IRAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22062</link><description>There is a permissions and access control vulnerability in ZXCLOUD IRAI.An attacker can elevate non-administrator permissions to administrator permissions by modifying the configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3410 | DN Footer Contacts &amp;lt; 1.6.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3410</link><description>The DN Footer Contacts WordPress plugin before 1.6.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5488 | SEOPress &amp;lt; 7.9 - Unauthenticated Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5488</link><description>The SEOPress  WordPress plugin before 7.9 does not properly protect some of its REST API routes, which combined with another Object Injection vulnerability can allow unauthenticated attackers to unserialize malicious gadget chains, compromising the site if a suitable chain is present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5802 | URL Shortener by MyThemeShop &amp;lt;= 1.0.17 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5802</link><description>The URL Shortener by Myhop WordPress plugin through 1.0.17 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6334 |  Easy Table of Contents &amp;lt; 2.0.67 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6334</link><description>The Easy Table of Contents WordPress plugin before 2.0.67.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5441 | Modern Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 7.11.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5441</link><description>The Modern Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the set_featured_image function in all versions up to, and including, 7.11.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The plugin allows administrators (via its settings) to extend the ability to submit events to unauthenticated users, which would allow unauthenticated attackers to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 05:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34692 | [CVE-2024-34692] Unrestricted File upload vulnerability in SAP Enable Now</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34692</link><description>Due to missing verification of file type or
content, SAP Enable Now allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary
files. These files include executables which might be downloaded and executed
by the user which could host malware. On successful exploitation an attacker
can cause limited impact on confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37180 | [CVE-2024-37180] Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37180</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver
Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an attacker to access
remote-enabled function module with no further authorization which would
otherwise be restricted, the function can be used to read non-sensitive
information with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4667 | Blog, Posts and Category Filter for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post and Category Filter Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4667</link><description>The Blog, Posts and Category Filter for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post and Category Filter widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'post_types' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6166 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.112 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6166</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘addons_order’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.112 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above and granted plugin setting edit permissions by an administrator, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6169 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.112 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;username&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6169</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘username’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.112 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above and granted plugin setting edit permissions by an administrator, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6170 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.112 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;email&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6170</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘email’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.112 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6171 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) &amp;lt;= 1.5.112 - IP Address Spoofing to Antispam Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6171</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.112 due to insufficient IP address validation and/or use of user-supplied HTTP headers as a primary method for IP retrieval. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to bypass antispam functionality in the Form Builder widgets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34689 | [CVE-2024-34689] Server-Side Request Forgery in SAP Business Workflow (WebFlow Services)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34689</link><description>WebFlow Services of SAP Business Workflow allows
an authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37171 | [CVE-2024-37171] Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SAP Transportation Management (Collaboration Portal)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37171</link><description>SAP Transportation Management (Collaboration
Portal) allows an attacker with non-administrative privileges to send a crafted
request from a vulnerable web application. This will trigger the application
handler to send a request to an unintended service, which may reveal
information about that service. The information obtained could be used to
target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an
attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery
vulnerability. There is no effect on integrity or availability of the
application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39596 | [CVE-2024-39596] Missing Authorization check vulnerability in SAP Enable Now</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39596</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP Enable
Now allows an author to escalate privileges to access information which should
otherwise be restricted. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39599 | [CVE-2024-39599] Protection Mechanism Failure in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39599</link><description>Due to a Protection Mechanism Failure in SAP
NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform, a developer can bypass
the configured malware scanner API because of a programming error. This leads
to a low impact on the application's confidentiality, integrity, and
availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39600 | [CVE-2024-39600] Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP GUI for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39600</link><description>Under certain conditions, the memory of SAP GUI
for Windows contains the password used to log on to an SAP system, which might
allow an attacker to get hold of the password and impersonate the affected
user. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality but there is no
impact on the integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37172 | [CVE-2024-37172] Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment Management)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37172</link><description>SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment
Management) does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact
to confidentiality and availability but there is no impact on the integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37175 | [Multiple CVEs] Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37175</link><description>SAP CRM WebClient does not
perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in
escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to access some sensitive
information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39594 | [CVE-2024-39594] Multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and Simulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39594</link><description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs,
resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact on the confidentiality
and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39595 | [CVE-2024-39594] Multiple Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and Simulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39595</link><description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs,
resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This
vulnerability allows users to modify website content and on successful
exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact to the confidentiality and
integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37173 | [Multiple CVEs] Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37173</link><description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP
  CRM WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
  embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
  be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
  and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37174 | [Multiple CVEs] Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37174</link><description>Custom CSS support option in SAP CRM WebClient
UI does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs resulting in Cross-Site
Scripting vulnerability. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39598 | [Multiple CVEs] Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP CRM (WebClient UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39598</link><description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI Framework) allows an
authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the internal
network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful exploitation this
can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on integrity and
availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34685 | [CVE-2024-34685] Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XMLEditor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34685</link><description>Due to weak encoding of user-controlled input in
SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XMLEditor which allows malicious scripts can
be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application
but it has a low impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39593 | [CVE-2024-39593] Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Landscape Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39593</link><description>SAP Landscape Management allows an authenticated
user to read confidential data disclosed by the REST Provider Definition
response. Successful exploitation can cause high impact on confidentiality of
the managed entities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39597 | [CVE-2024-39597] Improper Authorization Checks on Early Login Composable Storefront B2B sites of SAP Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39597</link><description>In SAP Commerce, a user can misuse the forgotten
password functionality to gain access to a Composable Storefront B2B site for
which early login and registration is activated, without requiring the merchant
to approve the account beforehand. If the site is not configured as isolated
site, this can also grant access to other non-isolated early login sites, even
if registration is not enabled for those other sites.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39592 | [CVE-2024-39592] Missing Authorization check in SAP PDCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39592</link><description>Elements of PDCE does not perform necessary
authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges.



This
allows an attacker to read sensitive information causing high impact on the
confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6365 | Product Table by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6365</link><description>The Product Table by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 via the 'saveCustomTitle' function. This is due to missing authorization and lack of sanitization of appended data in the languages/customTitle.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4944 | Mobile VPN with SSL Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4944</link><description>A local privilege escalation vlnerability in the WatchGuard Mobile VPN with SSL client on Windows enables a local user to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5974 | Firebox Authenticated Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5974</link><description>A buffer overflow in WatchGuard Fireware OS could may allow an authenticated remote attacker with privileged management access to execute arbitrary code with system privileges on the firewall.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 11.9.6 through 12.10.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5793 | Houzez Theme - Functionality &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Authenticated (Seller+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5793</link><description>The Houzez Theme - Functionality plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘currency_code’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level (seller) access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5855 | Media Hygiene &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Attachment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5855</link><description>The Media Hygiene: Remove or Delete Unused Images and More! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the bulk_action_delete and delete_single_image_call AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachments. A nonce check was added in version 3.0.1, however, it wasn't until version 3.0.2 that a capability check was added.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22020 | A security flaw in Node.js  allows a bypass of network import restrictions.
By embedding non-network imports in data URLs, an attacker can e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22020</link><description>A security flaw in Node.js  allows a bypass of network import restrictions.
By embedding non-network imports in data URLs, an attacker can execute arbitrary code, compromising system security.
Verified on various platforms, the vulnerability is mitigated by forbidding data URLs in network imports.
Exploiting this flaw can violate network import security, posing a risk to developers and servers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34786 | UniFi iOS app 10.15.0 introduces a misconfiguration on 2nd Generation UniFi Access Points configured as standalone (not using UniFi Network ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34786</link><description>UniFi iOS app 10.15.0 introduces a misconfiguration on 2nd Generation UniFi Access Points configured as standalone (not using UniFi Network Application) that could cause the SSID name to change and/or the WiFi Password to be removed on the 5GHz Radio.

This vulnerability is fixed in UniFi iOS app 10.15.2 and later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5549 | Origin Validation Error in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5549</link><description>Origin Validation Error in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5569 | Denial of Service via crafted zip file in jaraco/zipp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5569</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the jaraco/zipp library, affecting all versions prior to 3.19.1. The vulnerability is triggered when processing a specially crafted zip file that leads to an infinite loop. This issue also impacts the zipfile module of CPython, as features from the third-party zipp library are later merged into CPython, and the affected code is identical in both projects. The infinite loop can be initiated through the use of functions affecting the `Path` module in both zipp and zipfile, such as `joinpath`, the overloaded division operator, and `iterdir`. Although the infinite loop is not resource exhaustive, it prevents the application from responding. The vulnerability was addressed in version 3.19.1 of jaraco/zipp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28882 | OpenVPN 2.6.10 and earlier in a server role accepts multiple exit notifications from authenticated clients which will extend the validity of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28882</link><description>OpenVPN 2.6.10 and earlier in a server role accepts multiple exit notifications from authenticated clients which will extend the validity of a closing session</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3653 | Undertow: learningpushhandler can lead to remote memory dos attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow. This issue requires enabling the learning-push handler in the server's config, which is disabled by default, leaving the maxAge config in the handler unconfigured. The default is -1, which makes the handler vulnerable. If someone overwrites that config, the server is not subject to the attack. The attacker needs to be able to reach the server with a normal HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5971 | Undertow: response write hangs in case of java 17 tlsv1.3 newsessionticket</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow, where the chunked response hangs after the body was flushed. The response headers and body were sent but the client would continue waiting as Undertow does not send the expected 0\r\n termination of the chunked response. This results in uncontrolled resource consumption, leaving the server side to a denial of service attack. This happens only with Java 17 TLSv1.3 scenarios.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38372 | Undici vulnerable to data leak when using response.arrayBuffer()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38372</link><description>Undici is an HTTP/1.1 client, written from scratch for Node.js. Depending on network and process conditions of a `fetch()` request, `response.arrayBuffer()` might include portion of memory from the Node.js process. This has been patched in v6.19.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6227 | Denial of Service in aimhubio/aim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6227</link><description>A vulnerability in aimhubio/aim version 3.19.3 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service by configuring the remote tracking server to point at itself. This results in the server endlessly connecting to itself, rendering it unable to respond to other connections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 19:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6580 | /n software IPWorks SSH insufficient file access verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6580</link><description>The /n software IPWorks SSH library SFTPServer component can be induced to make unintended filesystem or network path requests when loading a SSH public key or certificate. To be exploitable, an application calling the SFTPServer component must grant user access without verifying the SSH public key or certificate (which would most likely be a separate vulnerability in the calling application). IPWorks SSH versions 22.0.8945 and 24.0.8945 were released to address this condition by blocking all filesystem and network path requests for SSH public keys or certificates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 19:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6409 | Openssh: possible remote code execution due to a race condition in signal handling affecting red hat enterprise linux 9</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6409</link><description>A signal handler race condition vulnerability was found in OpenSSH's server (sshd), where a client does not authenticate within LoginGraceTime seconds (120 by default, 600 in old OpenSSH versions), then sshd's SIGALRM handler is called asynchronously. However, this signal handler calls various functions that are not async-signal-safe, for example, syslog(). This issue leaves it vulnerable to a signal handler race condition on the cleanup_exit() function, which introduces the same vulnerability as CVE-2024-6387 in the unprivileged child of the SSHD server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1305 | tap-windows6 driver version 9.26 and earlier does not properly 
check the size data of incomming write operations which an attacker can 
use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1305</link><description>tap-windows6 driver version 9.26 and earlier does not properly 
check the size data of incomming write operations which an attacker can 
use to overflow memory buffers, resulting in a bug check and potentially
 arbitrary code execution in kernel space</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39896 | Directus allows SSO User Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39896</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. When relying on SSO providers in combination with local authentication it can be possible to enumerate existing SSO users in the instance. This is possible because if an email address exists in Directus and belongs to a known SSO provider then it will throw a "helpful" error that the user belongs to another provider. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.13.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4882 | URL Redirection to Arbitrary Site Exists in Sitefinity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4882</link><description>The user may be redirected to an arbitrary site in Sitefinity 15.1.8321.0 and previous versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39895 | Directus GraphQL Field Duplication Denial of Service (DoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39895</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. A denial of service (DoS) attack by field duplication in GraphQL is a type of attack where an attacker exploits the flexibility of GraphQL to overwhelm a server by requesting the same field multiple times in a single query. This can cause the server to perform redundant computations and consume excessive resources, leading to a denial of service for legitimate users. Request to the endpoint /graphql are sent when visualizing graphs generated at a dashboard. By modifying the data sent and duplicating many times the fields a DoS attack is possible. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.12.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39701 | Directus Incorrectly handles _in` filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39701</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Directus &gt;=9.23.0, &lt;=v10.5.3 improperly handles _in, _nin operators. It evaluates empty arrays as valid so expressions like {"role": {"_in": $CURRENT_USER.some_field}} would evaluate to true allowing the request to pass. This results in Broken Access Control because the rule fails to do what it was intended to do: Pass rule if **field** matches any of the **values**. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39312 | Botan has an Authorization Error due to Name Constraint Decoding Bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39312</link><description>Botan is a C++ cryptography library. X.509 certificates can identify elliptic curves using either an object identifier or using explicit encoding of the parameters. A bug in the parsing of name constraint extensions in X.509 certificates meant that if the extension included both permitted subtrees and excluded subtrees, only the permitted subtree would be checked. If a certificate included a name which was permitted by the permitted subtree but also excluded by excluded subtree, it would be accepted. Fixed in versions 3.5.0 and 2.19.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34702 | Botan has a Denial of Service Due to Excessive Name Constraints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34702</link><description>Botan is a C++ cryptography library. X.509 certificates can identify elliptic curves using either an object identifier or using explicit encoding of the parameters.  Prior to 3.5.0 and 2.19.5, checking name constraints in X.509 certificates is quadratic in the number of names and name constraints. An attacker who presented a certificate chain which contained a very large number of names in the SubjectAlternativeName, signed by a CA certificate which contained a large number of name constraints, could cause a denial of service. The problem has been addressed in Botan 3.5.0 and a partial backport has also been applied and is included in Botan 2.19.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23562 | HCL Domino is susceptible to an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23562</link><description>A security vulnerability in HCL Domino could allow disclosure of sensitive configuration information.  A remote unauthenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain information to launch further attacks against the affected system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39202 | D-Link DIR-823X firmware - 240126 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the dhcpd_startip parameter a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39202</link><description>D-Link DIR-823X firmware - 240126 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the dhcpd_startip parameter at /goform/set_lan_settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34435 | A firmware update vulnerability exists in the boa formUpload functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted networ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34435</link><description>A firmware update vulnerability exists in the boa formUpload functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted network packets can lead to arbitrary firmware update. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47677 | A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the boa CSRF protection functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47677</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (csrf) vulnerability exists in the boa CSRF protection functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted network request can lead to CSRF. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21778 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the configuration file mib_init_value_array functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21778</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the configuration file mib_init_value_array functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted .dat file can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can upload a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39699 | Directus has a Blind SSRF On File Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39699</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. There was already a reported SSRF vulnerability via file import. It was fixed by resolving all DNS names and checking if the requested IP is an internal IP address. However it is possible to bypass this security measure and execute a SSRF using redirects. Directus allows redirects when importing file from the URL and does not check the result URL. Thus, it is possible to execute a request to an internal IP, for example to 127.0.0.1. However, it is blind SSRF, because Directus also uses response interception technique to get the information about the connect from the socket directly and it does not show a response if the IP address is internal. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.9.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41251 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formRoute functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41251</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formRoute functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45215 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa setRepeaterSsid functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45215</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa setRepeaterSsid functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45742 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa updateConfigIntoFlash functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45742</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa updateConfigIntoFlash functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46685 | A hard-coded password vulnerability exists in the telnetd functionality of LevelOne WBR-6013 RER4_A_v3411b_2T2R_LEV_09_170623. A set of spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46685</link><description>A hard-coded password vulnerability exists in the telnetd functionality of LevelOne WBR-6013 RER4_A_v3411b_2T2R_LEV_09_170623. A set of specially crafted network packets can lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47856 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa set_RadvdPrefixParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47856</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa set_RadvdPrefixParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48270 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formDnsv6 functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48270</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formDnsv6 functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49073 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formFilter functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49073</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formFilter functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49593 | Leftover debug code exists in the boa formSysCmd functionality of LevelOne WBR-6013 RER4_A_v3411b_2T2R_LEV_09_170623. A specially crafted ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49593</link><description>Leftover debug code exists in the boa formSysCmd functionality of LevelOne WBR-6013 RER4_A_v3411b_2T2R_LEV_09_170623. A specially crafted network request can lead to arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49595 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa rollback_control_code functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49595</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa rollback_control_code functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49867 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49867</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50239 | Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa set_RadvdInterfaceParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50239</link><description>Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa set_RadvdInterfaceParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This stack-based buffer overflow is related to the `interfacename` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50240 | Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa set_RadvdInterfaceParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50240</link><description>Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa set_RadvdInterfaceParam functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of network requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a sequence of requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This stack-based buffer overflow is related to the `AdvDefaultPreference` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50243 | Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa formIpQoS functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50243</link><description>Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa formIpQoS functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This stack-based buffer overflow is related to the `comment` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50244 | Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa formIpQoS functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50244</link><description>Two stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the boa formIpQoS functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This stack-based buffer overflow is related to the `entry_name` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50330 | A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa getInfo functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50330</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the boa getInfo functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50381 | Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50381</link><description>Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This command injection is related to the `targetAPSsid` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50382 | Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50382</link><description>Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This command injection is related to the `peerPin` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50383 | Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50383</link><description>Three os command injection vulnerabilities exist in the boa formWsc functionality of Realtek rtl819x Jungle SDK v3.4.11. A specially crafted series of HTTP requests can lead to arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.This command injection is related to the `localPin` request's parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39203 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Backend Theme Management module of Z-BlogPHP v1.7.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39203</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Backend Theme Management module of Z-BlogPHP v1.7.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6564 | Buffer overflow in Rensas RCAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6564</link><description>Buffer overflow in "rcar_dev_init"  due to using due to using untrusted data (rcar_image_number) as a loop counter before verifying it against RCAR_MAX_BL3X_IMAGE. This could lead to a full bypass of secure boot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31504 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SILA Embedded Solutions GmbH freemodbus v.2018-09-12 allows a remtoe attacker to cause a denial of service ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31504</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in SILA Embedded Solutions GmbH freemodbus v.2018-09-12 allows a remtoe attacker to cause a denial of service via the LINUXTCP server component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39695 | Exiv2 has an out-of-bounds read in AsfVideo::streamProperties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39695</link><description>Exiv2 is a command-line utility and C++ library for reading, writing, deleting, and modifying the metadata of image files. An out-of-bounds read was found in Exiv2 version v0.28.2. The vulnerability is in the parser for the ASF video format, which was a new feature in v0.28.0. The out-of-bounds read is triggered when Exiv2 is used to read the metadata of a crafted video file. The bug is fixed in version v0.28.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6563 | Buffer Overflow Arbitrary Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6563</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Renesas arm-trusted-firmware allows Local Execution of Code. This vulnerability is associated with program files  https://github.Com/renesas-rcar/arm-trusted-firmware/blob/rcar_gen3_v2.5/drivers/renesas/common/io/i... https://github.Com/renesas-rcar/arm-trusted-firmware/blob/rcar_gen3_v2.5/drivers/renesas/common/io/io_rcar.C .




In line 313 "addr_loaded_cnt" is checked not to be "CHECK_IMAGE_AREA_CNT" (5) or larger, this check does not halt the function. Immediately after (line 317) there will be an overflow in the buffer and the value of "dst" will be written to the area immediately after the buffer, which is "addr_loaded_cnt". This will allow an attacker to freely control the value of "addr_loaded_cnt" and thus control the destination of the write immediately after (line 318). The write in line 318 will then be fully controlled by said attacker, with whichever address and whichever value ("len") they desire.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:23:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39677 | NHibernate SQL injection vulnerability in discriminator mappings, static fields referenced in HQL, and some utilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39677</link><description>NHibernate is an object-relational mapper for the .NET framework. A SQL injection vulnerability exists in some types implementing ILiteralType.ObjectToSQLString. Callers of these methods are exposed to the vulnerability, which includes mappings using inheritance with discriminator values; HQL queries referencing a static field of the application; users of the SqlInsertBuilder and SqlUpdateBuilder utilities, calling their AddColumn overload taking a literal value; and any direct use of the ObjectToSQLString methods for building SQL queries on the user side. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.4.9 and 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39308 | RailsAdmin Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in the list view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39308</link><description>RailsAdmin is a Rails engine that provides an interface for managing data. RailsAdmin list view has the XSS vulnerability, caused by improperly-escaped HTML title attribute. Upgrade to 3.1.3 or 2.2.2 (to be released).</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25639 | Prompt Injection triggered XSS vulnerability in Khoj Obsidian, Desktop and Web clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25639</link><description>Khoj is an application that creates personal AI agents. The Khoj Obsidian, Desktop and Web clients inadequately sanitize the AI model's response and user inputs. This can trigger Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via Prompt Injection from untrusted documents either indexed by the user on Khoj or read by Khoj from the internet when the user invokes the /online command. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4341 | Information Disclosure in ExtremePacs&amp;#x27;s Extreme XDS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4341</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Ekstrem Bir Bilgisayar Danismanlik Ic Ve Dis Ticaret Ltd. Sti. Extreme XDS allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects Extreme XDS: before 3928.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39742 | IBM MQ Container authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39742</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 3.2.2 and IBM MQ Operator 2.0.24 could allow a user to bypass authentication under certain configurations due to a partial string comparison vulnerability.  IBM X-Force ID:  297169.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39743 | IBM MQ Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39743</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 3.2.2 and IBM MQ Operator 2.0.24 could allow a user to cause a denial of service under certain configurations due to a partial string comparison vulnerability.  IBM X-Force ID:  297172.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6163 | local IP restriction of internal HTTP endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6163</link><description>Certain http endpoints of Checkmk in Checkmk &lt; 2.3.0p10 &lt; 2.2.0p31, &lt; 2.1.0p46, &lt;= 2.0.0p39 allows remote attacker to bypass authentication and access data</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27903 | OpenVPN plug-ins on Windows with OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier could be loaded from any directory, which allows an attacker to load an arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27903</link><description>OpenVPN plug-ins on Windows with OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier could be loaded from any directory, which allows an attacker to load an arbitrary plug-in which can be used to interact with the privileged OpenVPN interactive service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37999 | A vulnerability has been identified in Medicalis Workflow Orchestrator (All versions). The affected application executes as a trusted accoun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37999</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Medicalis Workflow Orchestrator (All versions). The affected application executes as a trusted account with high privileges and network access. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24974 | The interactive service in OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier allows the OpenVPN service pipe to be accessed remotely, which allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24974</link><description>The interactive service in OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier allows the OpenVPN service pipe to be accessed remotely, which allows a remote attacker to interact with the privileged OpenVPN interactive service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27459 | The interactive service in OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier allows an attacker to send data causing a stack overflow which can be used to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27459</link><description>The interactive service in OpenVPN 2.6.9 and earlier allows an attacker to send data causing a stack overflow which can be used to execute arbitrary code with more privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37389 | Apache NiFi: Improper Neutralization of Input in Parameter Context Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34602 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Messages prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34602</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Samsung Messages prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 06:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34603 | Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access location data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34603</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jul-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access location data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 06:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37528 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37528</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, 22.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  294293.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31897 | IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31897</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Business Automation 18.0.0, 18.0.1, 18.0.2, 19.0.1, 19.0.2, 19.0.3, 20.0.1, 20.0.2, 20.0.3, 21.0.1, 21.0.2, 21.0.3, 22.0.1, 22.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.  IBM X-Force ID:  288178.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38330 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38330</link><description>IBM System Management for i 7.2, 7.3, and 7.4 could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library program call.  A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.  IBM X-Force ID:  295227.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39723 | IBM FlashSystem denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39723</link><description>IBM FlashSystem 5300 USB ports may be usable even if the port has been disabled by the administrator. A user with physical access to the system could use the USB port to cause loss of access to data.  IBM X-Force ID:  295935.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5711 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5711</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6539 | heyewei SpringBootCMS Guestbook guestbook cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6539</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in heyewei SpringBootCMS up to 2024-05-28. Affected is an unknown function of the file /guestbook of the component Guestbook Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3651 | Denial of Service via Quadratic Complexity in kjd/idna</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3651</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the kjd/idna library, specifically within the `idna.encode()` function, affecting version 3.6. The issue arises from the function's handling of crafted input strings, which can lead to quadratic complexity and consequently, a denial of service condition. This vulnerability is triggered by a crafted input that causes the `idna.encode()` function to process the input with considerable computational load, significantly increasing the processing time in a quadratic manner relative to the input size.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6229 | Stored XSS in stangirard/quivr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6229</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 'Upload Knowledge' feature of stangirard/quivr, affecting the latest version. Users can upload files via URL, which allows the insertion of malicious JavaScript payloads. These payloads are stored on the server and executed whenever any user clicks on a link containing the payload, leading to potential data theft, session hijacking, and reputation damage.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40614 | EGroupware before 23.1.20240624 mishandles an ORDER BY clause.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40614</link><description>EGroupware before 23.1.20240624 mishandles an ORDER BY clause.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>