<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:42:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2371 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System Registered Mobile Number Search registered-user-testing.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2371</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registered-user-testing.php of the component Registered Mobile Number Search. The manipulation of the argument regmobilenumber leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12971 | QuickShell Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12971</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command vulnerability allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Pandora FMS from 700 to 777.6</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12992 | Remote Code Execution leads to Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12992</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command vulnerability allows OS Command Injection via RCE. 

This issue affects Pandora FMS from 700 to 777.6

.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2370 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setWiFiExtenderConfig stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T up to 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setWiFiExtenderConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument apcliSsid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 09:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2369 | TOTOLINK EX1800T cstecgi.cgi setPasswordCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK EX1800T up to 9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setPasswordCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument admpass leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2368 | WebAssembly wabt Malformed File binary-reader-interp.cc OnExport heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in WebAssembly wabt 1.0.36 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function wabt::interp::(anonymous namespace)::BinaryReaderInterp::OnExport of the file wabt/src/interp/binary-reader-interp.cc of the component Malformed File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2367 | Oiwtech OIW-2431APGN-HP Personal Script Submenu formScript os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2367</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Oiwtech OIW-2431APGN-HP 2.5.3-B20131128 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formScript of the component Personal Script Submenu. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1724 | Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1724</link><description>Zohocorp's ManageEngine Analytics Plus and Zoho Analytics on-premise versions older than 6130 are vulnerable to an AD only account takeover because of a hardcoded sensitive token.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2366 | gougucms Add Department Page add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2366</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in gougucms 4.08.18. This affects the function add of the file /admin/department/add of the component Add Department Page. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 07:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2365 | crmeb_java WeChatMessageController.java webHook xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2365</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in crmeb_java up to 1.3.4. Affected by this issue is the function webHook of the file WeChatMessageController.java. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2364 | lenve VBlog ArticleService.java addNewArticle cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2364</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in lenve VBlog up to 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function addNewArticle of the file blogserver/src/main/java/org/sang/service/ArticleService.java. The manipulation of the argument mdContent/htmlContent leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2396 | e-Excellence U-Office Force - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2396</link><description>The U-Office Force from e-Excellence has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 06:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2395 | e-Excellence U-Office Force - Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2395</link><description>The U-Office Force from e-Excellence has an Improper Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to use a particular API and alter cookies to log in as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2363 | lenve VBlog ArticleController.java uploadImg path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2363</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lenve VBlog up to 1.0.0. Affected is the function uploadImg of the file blogserver/src/main/java/org/sang/controller/ArticleController.java. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2362 | PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnum leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 05:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2361 | Mercurial SCM Web Interface cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2361</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mercurial SCM 4.5.3/71.19.145.211. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2360 | D-Link DIR-823G UPnP Service HNAP1 SetUpnpSettings improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2360</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-823G 1.0.2B05_20181207. Affected by this vulnerability is the function SetUpnpSettings of the file /HNAP1/ of the component UPnP Service. The manipulation of the argument SOAPAction leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 04:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2359 | D-Link DIR-823G DDNS Service HNAP1 SetDDNSSettings improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2359</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DIR-823G 1.0.2B05_20181207. Affected is the function SetDDNSSettings of the file /HNAP1/ of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument SOAPAction leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2358 | Shenzhen Mingyuan Cloud Technology Mingyuan Real Estate ERP System HTTP Header Service.asmx sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Mingyuan Cloud Technology Mingyuan Real Estate ERP System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Kfxt/Service.asmx of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2357 | DCMTK dcmjpls JPEG-LS Decoder memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2357</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DCMTK 3.6.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component dcmjpls JPEG-LS Decoder. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 3239a7915. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2356 | BlackVue App API deviceDelete get request method with sensitive query strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlackVue App 3.65 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function deviceDelete of the component API Handler. The manipulation leads to use of get request method with sensitive query strings. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2355 | BlackVue App API Endpoint credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlackVue App 3.65 on Android and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component API Endpoint Handler. The manipulation of the argument BCS_TOKEN/SECRET_KEY leads to unprotected storage of credentials. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2354 | VAM Virtual Airlines Manager index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2354</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in VAM Virtual Airlines Manager 2.6.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /vam/index.php. The manipulation of the argument registry_id/plane_icao/hub_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30089 | gurk (aka gurk-rs) through 0.6.3 mishandles ANSI escape sequences.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30089</link><description>gurk (aka gurk-rs) through 0.6.3 mishandles ANSI escape sequences.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2353 | VAM Virtual Airlines Manager HTTP GET Parameter index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in VAM Virtual Airlines Manager up to 2.6.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /vam/index.php of the component HTTP GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID/registry_id/plane_icao leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2352 | StarSea99 starsea-mall Backend save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2352</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in StarSea99 starsea-mall 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/indexConfigs/save of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument categoryName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 23:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2351 | DayCloud StudentManage Login Endpoint adminScoreUrl sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in DayCloud StudentManage 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/adminScoreUrl of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument query leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 22:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2350 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 upload_file unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /action/upload_file. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2349 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 Password Hash passwd weak password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /etc/passwd of the component Password Hash Handler. The manipulation leads to password hash with insufficient computational effort. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2348 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 HTTP/RTSP event information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /mnt/extsd/event/ of the component HTTP/RTSP. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2347 | IROAD Dash Cam FX2 Device Registration default password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam FX2 up to 20250308 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Device Registration. The manipulation of the argument Password with the input qwertyuiop leads to use of default password. The attack needs to be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2346 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 Domain origin validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2346</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Domain Handler. The manipulation of the argument Domain Name leads to origin validation error. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 20:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2345 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2345</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as very critical, was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2344 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 API Endpoint missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2344</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2343 | IROAD Dash Cam X5/Dash Cam X6 Device Pairing hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2343</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 and Dash Cam X6 up to 20250308. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Device Pairing. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. Access to the local network is required for this attack to succeed. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2342 | IROAD X5 Mobile App API Endpoint hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2342</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in IROAD X5 Mobile App up to 5.2.5 on Android. Affected is an unknown function of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2341 | IROAD Dash Cam X5 SSID default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2341</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IROAD Dash Cam X5 up to 20250203. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component SSID. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 14:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2340 | otale Tale Blog Site Settings save saveOptions cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in otale Tale Blog 2.0.5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function saveOptions of the file /options/save of the component Site Settings. The manipulation of the argument Site Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2339 | otale Tale Blog logs improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in otale Tale Blog 2.0.5. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /%61dmin/api/logs. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2338 | tbeu matio io.c strdup_vprintf heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2338</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in tbeu matio 1.5.28. Affected is the function strdup_vprintf of the file src/io.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 12:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2337 | tbeu matio mat.c Mat_VarPrint heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in tbeu matio 1.5.28. This issue affects the function Mat_VarPrint of the file src/mat.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 09:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13126 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.3.07 - Unauthenticated Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13126</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.3.07 doesn't prevent directory listing on web servers that don't use htaccess, allowing unauthorized access of files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13602 | Poll Maker &amp;lt; 5.5.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13602</link><description>The Poll Maker  WordPress plugin before 5.5.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1619 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1619</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1620 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1620</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1621 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1621</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1622 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1622</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1623 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1623</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1624 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt; 4.15.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1624</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance  WordPress plugin before 4.15.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24856 | An issue was discovered in the oidc (aka OpenID Connect Authentication) extension before 4.0.0 for TYPO3. The account linking logic allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24856</link><description>An issue was discovered in the oidc (aka OpenID Connect Authentication) extension before 4.0.0 for TYPO3. The account linking logic allows a pre-hijacking attack, leading to Account Takeover. The attack can only be exploited if the following requirements are met: (1) an attacker can anticipate the e-mail address of the user, (2) an attacker can register a public frontend user account using that e-mail address before the user's first OIDC login, and (3) the IDP returns an email field containing the e-mail address of the user,</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58103 | Square Wire before 5.2.0 does not enforce a recursion limit on nested groups in ByteArrayProtoReader32.kt and ProtoReader.kt.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58103</link><description>Square Wire before 5.2.0 does not enforce a recursion limit on nested groups in ByteArrayProtoReader32.kt and ProtoReader.kt.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30077 | Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.28 allows an index out-of-range panic in asn1/aper GetBitString via a zero value of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30077</link><description>Open Networking Foundation SD-RAN ONOS onos-lib-go 0.10.28 allows an index out-of-range panic in asn1/aper GetBitString via a zero value of numBits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2335 | Drivin Soluções API registerSchool cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Drivin Soluções up to 20250226. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/school/registerSchool of the component API Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30076 | Koha before 24.11.02 allows admins to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tools/scheduler.pl report parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30076</link><description>Koha before 24.11.02 allows admins to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tools/scheduler.pl report parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 03:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30074 | Alludo Parallels Desktop before 19.4.2 and 20.x before 20.2.2 for macOS on Intel platforms allows privilege escalation to root via the VM cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30074</link><description>Alludo Parallels Desktop before 19.4.2 and 20.x before 20.2.2 for macOS on Intel platforms allows privilege escalation to root via the VM creation routine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 02:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49737 | In X.Org X server 20.11 through 21.1.16, when a client application uses easystroke for mouse gestures, the main thread modifies various data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49737</link><description>In X.Org X server 20.11 through 21.1.16, when a client application uses easystroke for mouse gestures, the main thread modifies various data structures used by the input thread without acquiring a lock, aka a race condition. In particular, AttachDevice in dix/devices.c does not acquire an input lock.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 01:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2334 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt Chat History chat deleteChat access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2334</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5. This affects the function deleteChat of the file /api/mjkj-chat/chat/ai/delete/chat of the component Chat History Handler. The manipulation of the argument chatListId leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 23:07:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23744 | WordPress Random Posts, Mp3 Player + ShareButton plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23744</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in dvs11 Random Posts, Mp3 Player + ShareButton allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Random Posts, Mp3 Player + ShareButton: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26548 | WordPress Random Image Selector plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Random Image Selector allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Random Image Selector: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26553 | WordPress Pre Order Addon for WooCommerce plugin&amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spring Devs Pre Order Addon for WooCommerce – Advance Order/Backorder Plugin allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Pre Order Addon for WooCommerce – Advance Order/Backorder Plugin: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26554 | WordPress WP Discord Post Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Discord Post allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Discord Post: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26555 | WordPress Debug-Bar-Extender Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26555</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Debug-Bar-Extender allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Debug-Bar-Extender: from n/a through 0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26556 | WordPress WP AntiDDOS Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26556</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zzmaster WP AntiDDOS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP AntiDDOS: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26875 | WordPress Multiple Shipping And Billing Address For Woocommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in silverplugins217 Multiple Shipping And Billing Address For Woocommerce allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Multiple Shipping And Billing Address For Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26886 | WordPress PublishPress Authors plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26886</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PublishPress PublishPress Authors allows SQL Injection. This issue affects PublishPress Authors: from n/a through 4.7.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26895 | WordPress m1.DownloadList plugin &amp;lt;= 0.19 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26895</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in maennchen1.de m1.DownloadList allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects m1.DownloadList: from n/a through 0.19.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26899 | WordPress Recapture for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.43 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26899</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Recapture Cart Recovery and Email Marketing Recapture for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Recapture for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.43.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26921 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.6 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26921</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in magepeopleteam Booking and Rental Manager allows Object Injection. This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through 2.2.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26924 | WordPress Ohio Theme Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Shortcode Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26924</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Ohio Extra allows Code Injection. This issue affects Ohio Extra: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26940 | WordPress Pie Register Premium plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.2 - Path Traversal to Non-Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26940</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in NotFound Pie Register Premium. This issue affects Pie Register Premium: from n/a through 3.8.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26961 | WordPress Fresh Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.70.0 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26961</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Fresh Framework allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Fresh Framework: from n/a through 1.70.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26969 | WordPress PrivateContent plugin &amp;lt;= 8.11.5 - Subscriber+ Site Wide Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26969</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aldo Latino PrivateContent. This issue affects PrivateContent: from n/a through 8.11.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26972 | WordPress PrivateContent plugin &amp;lt;= 8.11.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26972</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound PrivateContent. This issue affects PrivateContent: from n/a through 8.11.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26976 | WordPress PrivateContent plugin &amp;lt;= 8.11.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26976</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Aldo Latino PrivateContent. This issue affects PrivateContent: from n/a through 8.11.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26978 | WordPress FS Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26978</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound FS Poster. This issue affects FS Poster: from n/a through 6.5.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27281 | WordPress All In Menu Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in cookforweb All In Menu allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects All In Menu: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 22:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25225 | Extension - hikashop.com - Privilege escalation vulnerability Hikashop component version 1.0.0 - 5.1.3 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25225</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in the Hikashop component versions 1.0.0-5.1.3 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to escalate their privileges to Super Admin Permissions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2323 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt Number of Question questionCou updateQuestionCou behavioral workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2323</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function updateQuestionCou of the file /api/mjkj-chat/chat/mng/update/questionCou of the component Number of Question Handler. The manipulation leads to enforcement of behavioral workflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2322 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt OpenController.java hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2322</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /chatgpt-boot/src/main/java/org/springblade/modules/mjkj/controller/OpenController.java. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2321 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt addData logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2321</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/mjkj-chat/cgform-api/addData/. The manipulation of the argument chatUserID leads to business logic errors. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1530 | Tripetto &amp;lt;= 8.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Results Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1530</link><description>The Tripetto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.9. This is due to missing nonce validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary results via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 11:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2025 | Give &amp;lt;= 3.22.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Earning Reports Disclosure via give_reports_earnings Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2025</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the give_reports_earnings() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.22.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disclose sensitive information included within earnings reports.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 11:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1057 | Keylime: keylime registrar dos due to incompatible database entry handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1057</link><description>A flaw was found in Keylime, a remote attestation solution, where strict type checking introduced in version 7.12.0 prevents the registrar from reading database entries created by previous versions, for example, 7.11.0. Specifically, older versions store agent registration data as bytes, whereas the updated registrar expects str. This issue leads to an exception when processing agent registration requests, causing the agent to fail.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 08:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25222 | Thumbnail carousel slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25222</link><description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2157 | Foreman: disclosure of executed commands and outputs in foreman / red hat satellite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2157</link><description>A flaw was found in Foreman/Red Hat Satellite. Improper file permissions allow low-privileged OS users to monitor and access temporary files under /var/tmp, exposing sensitive command outputs, such as /etc/shadow. This issue can lead to information disclosure and privilege escalation if exploited effectively.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2325 | WP Test Email &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2325</link><description>The WP Test Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Email Logs in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30066 | tj-actions changed-files through 45.0.7 allows remote attackers to discover secrets by reading actions logs. (The tags v1 through v45.0.7 we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30066</link><description>tj-actions changed-files through 45.0.7 allows remote attackers to discover secrets by reading actions logs. (The tags v1 through v45.0.7 were not originally affected, but were modified by a threat actor to point at commit 0e58ed8, which contains the malicious updateFeatures code.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13497 | WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto &amp;lt;= 8.0.9 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13497</link><description>The WordPress form builder plugin for contact forms, surveys and quizzes – Tripetto plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via attachment uploads in all versions up to, and including, 8.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1771 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.8 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion via hotel_alone_load_more_post</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1771</link><description>The Traveler theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 via the 'hotel_alone_load_more_post' function 'style' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1773 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.8  - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1773</link><description>The Traveler theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via multiple parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 04:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12336 | WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure via wf-export-all</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12336</link><description>The WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'export_all_data' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose sensitive affiliate data, including personally identifiable information (PII).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13847 | Portfolio and Projects &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13847</link><description>The Portfolio and Projects plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1667 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1667</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the wpsp_UpdateTeacher() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to update arbitrary user details including email which makes it possible to request a password reset and access arbitrary user accounts, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1668 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1668</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary user deletion due to a missing capability check on the wpsp_DeleteUser() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to delete arbitrary user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1669 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Authenticated (Teacher+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1669</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'addNotify' action in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with teacher-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1670 | School Management System – WPSchoolPress &amp;lt;= 2.2.16 - Authenticated (Parent+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1670</link><description>The School Management System – WPSchoolPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'cid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Custom-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2163 | Zoorum Comments &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2163</link><description>The Zoorum Comments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on  the zoorum_set_options() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2164 | pixelstats &amp;lt;= 0.8.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2164</link><description>The pixelstats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'post_id' and 'sortby' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2267 | WP01 – Speed, Security, SEO consultant &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2267</link><description>The WP01 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Download in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to a missing capability check and insufficient restrictions on the make_archive() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download and read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1653 | Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1653</link><description>The Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7. This is due to the stm_listing_profile_edit AJAX action not having enough restriction on the user meta that can be updated. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1657 | Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Meta Update and PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1657</link><description>The Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and PHP Object Injection due to a missing capability check on the stm_listing_ajax AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update post meta data and inject PHP Objects that may be unserialized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 03:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>