<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-0657 | The Internal Link Juicer: SEO Auto Linker for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0657</link><description>The Internal Link Juicer: SEO Auto Linker for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings such as 'ilj_settings_field_links_per_page'  in all versions up to, and including, 2.23.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0842 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Denial of Service in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0842</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Denial of Service in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to direct access of the backuply/restore_ins.php file and. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make excessive requests that result in the server running out of resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1122 | The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1122</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.50. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export event data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43609 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43609</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could obtain access to sensitive information or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46687 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46687</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could execute arbitrary commands in root context from a remote computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49716 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49716</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an authenticated user with network access could run arbitrary commands from a remote computer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51761 | Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, GC1500XA Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51761</link><description>In Emerson Rosemount GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA products, an unauthenticated user with network access could bypass authentication and acquire admin capabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32341 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32341</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  255827.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42016 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42016</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.8 and 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.2.3 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.  IBM X-Force ID:  265559.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22332 | IBM Integration Bus for z/OS denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22332</link><description>The IBM Integration Bus for z/OS 10.1 through 10.1.0.2 AdminAPI is vulnerable to a denial of service due to file system exhaustion.  IBM X-Force ID:  279972.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45187 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45187</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  268749.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45190 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization HTTP header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45190</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  268754.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45191 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45191</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  268755.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1353 | PHPEMS index.api.php index deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1353</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPEMS up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function index of the file app/weixin/controller/index.api.php. The manipulation of the argument picurl leads to deserialization. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253226 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22318 | IBM i Access Client Solutions information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22318</link><description>IBM i Access Client Solutions (ACS) 1.1.2 through 1.1.4 and 1.1.4.3 through 1.1.9.4 is vulnerable to NT LAN Manager (NTLM) hash disclosure by an attacker modifying UNC capable paths within ACS configuration files to point to a hostile server. If NTLM is enabled, the Windows operating system will try to authenticate using the current user's session. The hostile server could capture the NTLM hash information to obtain the user's credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  279091.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23639 | micronaut-core  management endpoints vulnerable to drive-by localhost attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23639</link><description>Micronaut Framework is a modern, JVM-based, full stack Java framework designed for building modular, easily testable JVM applications with support for Java, Kotlin and the Groovy language. Enabled but unsecured management endpoints are susceptible to drive-by localhost attacks. While not typical of a production application, these attacks may have more impact on a development environment where such endpoints may be flipped on without much thought. A malicious/compromised website can make HTTP requests to `localhost`. Normally, such requests would trigger a CORS preflight check which would prevent the request; however, some requests are "simple" and do not require a preflight check. These endpoints, if enabled and not secured, are vulnerable to being triggered. Production environments typically disable unused endpoints and secure/restrict access to needed endpoints. A more likely victim is the developer in their local development host, who has enabled endpoints without security for the sake of easing development. This issue has been addressed in version 3.8.3. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24819 | icingaweb2-module-incubator base implementation for HTML forms is susceptible to CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24819</link><description>icingaweb2-module-incubator is a working project of bleeding edge Icinga Web 2 libraries. In affected versions the class `gipfl\Web\Form` is the base for various concrete form implementations [1] and provides protection against cross site request forgery (CSRF) by default. This is done by automatically adding an element with a CSRF token to any form, unless explicitly disabled, but even if enabled, the CSRF token (sent during a client's submission of a form relying on it) is not validated. This enables attackers to perform changes on behalf of a user which, unknowingly, interacts with a prepared link or website. The version 0.22.0 is available to remedy this issue. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24820 | Icinga Director configuration is susceptible to Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24820</link><description>Icinga Director is a tool designed to make Icinga 2 configuration handling easy. Not any of Icinga Director's configuration forms used to manipulate the monitoring environment are protected against cross site request forgery (CSRF). It enables attackers to perform changes in the monitoring environment managed by Icinga Director without the awareness of the victim. Users of the map module in version 1.x, should immediately upgrade to v2.0. The mentioned XSS vulnerabilities in Icinga Web are already fixed as well and upgrades to the most recent release of the 2.9, 2.10 or 2.11 branch must be performed if not done yet. Any later major release is also suitable. Icinga Director will receive minor updates to the 1.8, 1.9, 1.10 and 1.11 branches to remedy this issue. Upgrade immediately to a patched release. If that is not feasible, disable the director module for the time being.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24821 | Code execution and possible privilege escalation via compromised InstalledVersions.php or installed.php in Composer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24821</link><description>Composer is a dependency Manager for the PHP language. In affected versions several files within the local working directory are included during the invocation of Composer and in the context of the executing user. As such, under certain conditions arbitrary code execution may lead to local privilege escalation, provide lateral user movement or malicious code execution when Composer is invoked within a directory with tampered files. All Composer CLI commands are affected, including composer.phar's self-update. The following scenarios are of high risk: Composer being run with sudo, Pipelines which may execute Composer on untrusted projects, Shared environments with developers who run Composer individually on the same project. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 2.7.0 and 2.2.23. It is advised that the patched versions are applied at the earliest convenience. Where not possible, the following should be addressed: Remove all sudo composer privileges for all users to mitigate root privilege escalation, and avoid running Composer within an untrusted directory, or if needed, verify that the contents of `vendor/composer/InstalledVersions.php` and `vendor/composer/installed.php` do not include untrusted code.  A reset can also be done on these files by the following:```sh
rm vendor/composer/installed.php vendor/composer/InstalledVersions.php
composer install --no-scripts --no-plugins
```</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24829 | SSRF in Sentry via Phabricator integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24829</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Sentry’s integration platform provides a way for external services to interact with Sentry. One of such integrations, the Phabricator integration (maintained by Sentry) with version &lt;=24.1.1 contains a constrained SSRF vulnerability. An attacker could make Sentry send POST HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs (including internal IP addresses) by providing an unsanitized input to the Phabricator integration. However, the body payload is constrained to a specific format. If an attacker has access to a Sentry instance, this allows them to: 1. interact with internal network; 2. scan local/remote ports. This issue has been fixed in Sentry self-hosted release 24.1.2, and has already been mitigated on sentry.io on February 8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24825 | TokenManager not checking permissions on cached tokens in DIRAC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24825</link><description>DIRAC is a distributed resource framework. In affected versions any user could get a token that has been requested by another user/agent. This may expose resources to unintended parties. This issue has been addressed in release version 8.0.37. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24830 | OpenObserve Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in Users API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24830</link><description>OpenObserve is a observability platform built specifically for logs, metrics, traces, analytics, designed to work at petabyte scale. A vulnerability has been identified in the "/api/{org_id}/users" endpoint. This vulnerability allows any authenticated regular user ('member') to add new users with elevated privileges, including the 'root' role, to an organization. This issue circumvents the intended security controls for role assignments. The vulnerability resides in the user creation process, where the payload does not validate the user roles. A regular user can manipulate the payload to assign root-level privileges. This vulnerability leads to Unauthorized Privilege Escalation and significantly compromises the application's role-based access control system. It allows unauthorized control over application resources and poses a risk to data security. All users, particularly those in administrative roles, are impacted. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25106 | OpenObserve Unauthorized Access Vulnerability in Users API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25106</link><description>OpenObserve is a observability platform built specifically for logs, metrics, traces, analytics, designed to work at petabyte scale. A critical vulnerability has been identified in the "/api/{org_id}/users/{email_id}" endpoint. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user within an organization to remove any other user from that same organization, irrespective of their respective roles. This includes the ability to remove users with "Admin" and "Root" roles. By enabling any organizational member to unilaterally alter the user base, it opens the door to unauthorized access and can cause considerable disruptions in operations. The core of the vulnerability lies in the `remove_user_from_org` function in the user management system. This function is designed to allow organizational users to remove members from their organization. The function does not check if the user initiating the request has the appropriate administrative privileges to remove a user. Any user who is part of the organization, irrespective of their role, can remove any other user, including those with higher privileges. This vulnerability is categorized as an Authorization issue leading to Unauthorized User Removal. The impact is severe, as it compromises the integrity of user management within organizations. By exploiting this vulnerability, any user within an organization, without the need for administrative privileges, can remove critical users, including "Admins" and "Root" users. This could result in unauthorized system access, administrative lockout, or operational disruptions. Given that user accounts are typically created by "Admins" or "Root" users, this vulnerability can be exploited by any user who has been granted access to an organization, thereby posing a critical risk to the security and operational stability of the application. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.8.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25107 | Cross-Site Scripting in WikiDiscover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25107</link><description>WikiDiscover is an extension designed for use with a CreateWiki managed farm to display wikis. On Special:WikiDiscover, the `Language::date` function is used when making the human-readable timestamp for inclusion on the wiki_creation column. This function uses interface messages to translate the names of months and days. It uses the `-&gt;text()` output mode, returning unescaped interface messages. Since the output is not escaped later, the unescaped interface message is included on the output, resulting in an XSS vulnerability. Exploiting this on-wiki requires the `(editinterface)` right. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `267e763a0`. Users are advised to update their installations. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47132 | An issue discovered in N-able N-central before 2023.6 and earlier allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via API calls.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47132</link><description>An issue discovered in N-able N-central before 2023.6 and earlier allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via API calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47131 | The N-able PassPortal extension before 3.29.2 for Chrome inserts sensitive information into a log file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47131</link><description>The N-able PassPortal extension before 3.29.2 for Chrome inserts sensitive information into a log file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40262 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40262</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the administration component via Access Request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40263 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated command injection via ftp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40263</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated command injection via ftp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40264 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated path traversal in the user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40264</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice Trace Manager V8 before V8 R0.9.11. It allows authenticated path traversal in the user interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51630 | Paessler PRTG Network Monitor Cross-Site Scripting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51630</link><description>Paessler PRTG Network Monitor Cross-Site Scripting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Paessler PRTG Network Monitor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the web console. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21182.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49101 | WebAdmin in Axigen 10.3.x before 10.3.3.61, 10.4.x before 10.4.24, and 10.5.x before 10.5.10 allows XSS attacks against admins because of mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49101</link><description>WebAdmin in Axigen 10.3.x before 10.3.3.61, 10.4.x before 10.4.24, and 10.5.x before 10.5.10 allows XSS attacks against admins because of mishandling of viewing the usage of SSL certificates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 22:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40265 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows authenticated remote code ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40265</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows authenticated remote code execution via file upload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40266 | An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows path traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40266</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Unify OpenScape Xpressions WebAssistant V7 before V7R1 FR5 HF42 P911. It allows path traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24393 | File Upload vulnerability index.php in Pichome v.1.1.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted POST request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24393</link><description>File Upload vulnerability index.php in Pichome v.1.1.01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25365 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in October CMS v.3.2.0 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file type .mp3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25365</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability found in October CMS v.3.2.0 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file type .mp3</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27001 | An issue discovered in Egerie Risk Manager v4.0.5 allows attackers to bypass the signature mechanism and tamper with the values inside the J...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27001</link><description>An issue discovered in Egerie Risk Manager v4.0.5 allows attackers to bypass the signature mechanism and tamper with the values inside the JWT payload resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24498 | Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Employee Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the edit-pho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24498</link><description>Unrestricted File Upload vulnerability in Employee Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the edit-photo.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24499 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtfullna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24499</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtfullname and txtphone parameters in the edit_profile.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24496 | An issue in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to manipulate trackers via the home.php, add-tracker.php, delete-tracker.php,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24496</link><description>An issue in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to manipulate trackers via the home.php, add-tracker.php, delete-tracker.php, update-tracker.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24497 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtuserna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24497</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Employee Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the txtusername and txtpassword parameters in the login.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24495 | SQL Injection vulnerability in delete-tracker.php in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24495</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in delete-tracker.php in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24494 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the day, exercise, pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24494</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Daily Habit Tracker v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the day, exercise, pray, read_book, vitamins, laundry, alcohol and meat parameters in the add-tracker.php and update-tracker.php components.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23756 | The HTTP PUT and DELETE methods are enabled in the Plone official Docker version 5.2.13 (5221), allowing unauthenticated attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23756</link><description>The HTTP PUT and DELETE methods are enabled in the Plone official Docker version 5.2.13 (5221), allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute dangerous actions such as uploading files to the server or deleting them.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23660 | The Binance Trust Wallet app for iOS in commit 3cd6e8f647fbba8b5d8844fcd144365a086b629f, git tag 0.0.4 misuses the trezor-crypto library and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23660</link><description>The Binance Trust Wallet app for iOS in commit 3cd6e8f647fbba8b5d8844fcd144365a086b629f, git tag 0.0.4 misuses the trezor-crypto library and consequently generates mnemonic words for which the device time is the only entropy source, leading to economic losses, as exploited in the wild in July 2023. An attacker can systematically generate mnemonics for each timestamp within an applicable timeframe, and link them to specific wallet addresses in order to steal funds from those wallets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24115 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Page function of Cotonti CMS v0.9.24 allows authenticated attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24115</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Edit Page function of Cotonti CMS v0.9.24 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0242 | Unauthorized access to settings in Qolsys IQ Panel 4 and IQ4 Hub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0242</link><description>Under certain circumstances IQ Panel4 and IQ4 Hub panel software prior to version 4.4.2 could allow unauthorized access to settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22836 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Akaunting v3.1.3 and earlier. An attacker can manipulate the company locale when installing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22836</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Akaunting v3.1.3 and earlier. An attacker can manipulate the company locale when installing an app to execute system commands on the hosting server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1329 | Nomad Vulnerable to Arbitrary Write Through Symlink Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1329</link><description>HashiCorp Nomad and Nomad Enterprise 1.5.13 up to 1.6.6, and 1.7.3 template renderer is vulnerable to arbitrary file write on the host as the Nomad client user through symlink attacks. Fixed in Nomad 1.7.4, 1.6.7, 1.5.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22795 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Rechec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22795</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v.11.3.06.0063 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Recheck Compliance Status component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23764 | Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Securi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23764</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow Local Privilege Escalation. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15 and later, WithSecure Server Security 15 and later, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15 and later, and WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24215 | An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24215</link><description>An issue in the component /cgi-bin/GetJsonValue.cgi of Cellinx NVT Web Server 5.0.0.014 allows attackers to leak configuration information via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24213 | Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24213</link><description>Supabase PostgreSQL v15.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component /pg_meta/default/query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:27:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24321 | An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24321</link><description>An issue in Dlink DIR-816A2 v.1.10CNB05 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the wizardstep4_ssid_2 parameter in the sub_42DA54 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50061 | PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50061</link><description>PrestaShop Op'art Easy Redirect &gt;= 1.3.8 and &lt;= 1.3.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via Oparteasyredirect::hookActionDispatcher().</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:09:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25190 | l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25190</link><description>l8w8jwt 2.2.1 uses memcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25189 | libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25189</link><description>libjwt 1.15.3 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25191 | php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25191</link><description>php-jwt 1.0.0 uses strcmp (which is not constant time) to verify authentication, which makes it easier to bypass authentication via a timing side channel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42282 | An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42282</link><description>An issue in NPM IP Package v.1.1.8 and before allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the isPublic() function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47020 | Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47020</link><description>Multiple Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) chaining in NCR Terminal Handler v.1.5.1 allows privileges to be escalated by an attacker through a crafted request involving user account creation and adding the user to an administrator group. This is exploited by an undisclosed function in the WSDL that lacks security controls and can accept custom content types.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 16:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24834 | WordPress BEAR Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net allows Stored XSS.This issue affects BEAR – Bulk Editor and Products Manager Professional for WooCommerce by Pluginus.Net: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1150 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1150</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on Unix allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 7.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24836 | WordPress GDPR Data Request Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24836</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Audrasjb GDPR Data Request Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GDPR Data Request Form: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24871 | WordPress Blocksy Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.19 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24871</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative Themes Blocksy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7169 | Impersonate vendor signed Powershell scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7169</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Snow Software Snow Inventory Agent on Windows allows Signature Spoof.This issue affects Snow Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5. Customers advised to upgrade to version 7.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0985 | PostgreSQL non-owner REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY executes arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0985</link><description>Late privilege drop in REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY in PostgreSQL allows an object creator to execute arbitrary SQL functions as the command issuer. The command intends to run SQL functions as the owner of the materialized view, enabling safe refresh of untrusted materialized views. The victim is a superuser or member of one of the attacker's roles. The attack requires luring the victim into running REFRESH MATERIALIZED VIEW CONCURRENTLY on the attacker's materialized view. As part of exploiting this vulnerability, the attacker creates functions that use CREATE RULE to convert the internally-built temporary table to a view. Versions before PostgreSQL 15.6, 14.11, 13.14, and 12.18 are affected. The only known exploit does not work in PostgreSQL 16 and later. For defense in depth, PostgreSQL 16.2 adds the protections that older branches are using to fix their vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1149 | Improper validation of update packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1149</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in Snow Software Inventory Agent on MacOS, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Windows, Snow Software Inventory Agent on Linux allows File Manipulation through Snow Update Packages.This issue affects Inventory Agent: through 6.12.0; Inventory Agent: through 6.14.5; Inventory Agent: through 6.7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24877 | WordPress Wonder Slider Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 13.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Magic Hills Pty Ltd Wonder Slider Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Wonder Slider Lite: from n/a through 13.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24878 | WordPress Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PT Woo Plugins (by Webdados) Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Portugal CTT Tracking for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1312 | Kernel: race condition leads to use after free during vma lock in lock_vma_under_rcu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1312</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the Linux kernel's Memory Management subsystem when a user wins two races at the same time with a fail in the mas_prev_slot function. This issue could allow a local user to crash the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24113 | xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24113</link><description>xxl-job =&lt; 2.4.1 has a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability, which causes low-privileged users to control executor to RCE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24879 | WordPress Link Library Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.5.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24880 | WordPress Apollo13 Framework Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24880</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apollo13Themes Apollo13 Framework Extensions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Apollo13 Framework Extensions: from n/a through 1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6519 | Seeing admin password hash value in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6519</link><description>Exposure of Data Element to Wrong Session vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6518 | Password Disclosure in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6518</link><description>Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6517 | Seeing the SMS Verification Code in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6517</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6564 | Improper Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6564</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE Premium and Ultimate affecting versions 16.4.3, 16.5.3, and 16.6.1. In projects using subgroups to define who can push and/or merge to protected branches, there may have been instances in which subgroup members with the Developer role were able to push or merge to protected branches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24881 | WordPress WP SMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24881</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VeronaLabs WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP SMS – Messaging &amp; SMS Notification for WordPress, WooCommerce, GravityForms, etc: from n/a through 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24885 | WordPress Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lê Văn Toản Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Woocommerce Vietnam Checkout: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24886 | WordPress Product Labels For Woocommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24886</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Acowebs Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Product Labels For Woocommerce (Sale Badges): from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6515 | IDOR in Mia Technology&amp;#x27;s Mia-Med</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6515</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Mia Technology Inc. MİA-MED allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects MİA-MED: before 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22464 | Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22464</link><description>Dell EMC AppSync, versions from 4.2.0.0 to 4.6.0.0 including all Service Pack releases, contain an exposure of sensitive information vulnerability in AppSync server logs. A high privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable system with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23452 | Apache bRPC: HTTP request smuggling vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23452</link><description>Request smuggling vulnerability in HTTP server in Apache bRPC 0.9.5~1.7.0 on all platforms allows attacker to smuggle request.

Vulnerability Cause Description：

The http_parser does not comply with the RFC-7230 HTTP 1.1 specification.

Attack scenario:
If a message is received with both a Transfer-Encoding and a Content-Length header field, such a message might indicate an attempt to perform request smuggling or response splitting.
One particular attack scenario is that a bRPC made http server on the backend receiving requests in one persistent connection from frontend server that uses TE to parse request with the logic that 'chunk' is contained in the TE field. in that case an attacker can smuggle a request into the connection to the backend server. 

Solution:
You can choose one solution from below:
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.8.0, which fixes this issue. Download link:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/releases/tag/1.8.0
 2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/2518</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0965 | The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0965</link><description>The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's page restriction and view page content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1207 | The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1207</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'calendar_request_params[dates_ddmmyy_csv]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24034 | Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24034</link><description>Setor Informatica S.I.L version 3.0 is vulnerable to Open Redirect via the hprinter parameter, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24091 | Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24091</link><description>Yealink Meeting Server before v26.0.0.66 was discovered to contain an OS command injection vulnerability via the file upload interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0511 | The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0511</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.87. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpr_update_form_action_meta function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to post metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24216 | Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24216</link><description>Zentao v18.0 to v18.10 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the checkConnection method of /app/zentao/module/repo/model.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24202 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24202</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /upgrade/control.php of ZenTao Community Edition v18.10, ZenTao Biz v8.10, and ZenTao Max v4.10 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted .txt file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 04:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25148 | In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25148</link><description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions the `doAsUserId` URL parameter may get leaked when creating linked content using the WYSIWYG editor and while impersonating a user. This may allow remote authenticated users to impersonate a user after accessing the linked content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25146 | Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25146</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 18, and older unsupported versions returns with different responses depending on whether a site does not exist or if the user does not have permission to access the site, which allows remote attackers to discover the existence of sites by enumerating URLs. This vulnerability occurs if locale.prepend.friendly.url.style=2 and if a custom 404 page is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5665 | The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5665</link><description>The Payment Forms for Paystack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25144 | The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25144</link><description>The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before update 6, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions does not check the URL of the IFrame, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) via a self referencing IFrame.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47798 | Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47798</link><description>Account lockout in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.0, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.2 before fix pack 5, and older unsupported versions does not invalidate existing user sessions, which allows remote authenticated users to remain authenticated after an account has been locked.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22394 | An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22394</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been identified in SonicWall SonicOS SSL-VPN feature, which in specific conditions could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication. 

This issue affects only firmware version SonicOS 7.1.1-7040.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24003 | jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24003</link><description>jshERP v3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection. The com.jsh.erp.controller.DepotHeadController: com.jsh.erp.utils.BaseResponseInfo findInOutMaterialCount() function of jshERP does not filter `column` and `order` parameters well enough, and an attacker can construct malicious payload to bypass jshERP's protection mechanism in `safeSqlParse` method for sql injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24014 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24014</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/author/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24017 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24017</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /common/dict/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24021 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24021</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/userFeedback/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48974 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48974</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Axigen WebMail v.10.5.7 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the serverName_input parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24018 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24018</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /system/dataPerm/list</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24025 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24025</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: upload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24350 | File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24350</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Software Publico e-Sic Livre v.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the extension filtering component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24023 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24023</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior. An attacker can pass specially crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /novel/bookContent/list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24024 | An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDown...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24024</link><description>An arbitrary File download vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior at com.java2nb.common.controller.FileController: fileDownload(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filePath and fieName parameters to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24026 | An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24026</link><description>An arbitrary File upload vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions at com.java2nb.system.controller.SysUserController: uploadImg(). An attacker can pass in specially crafted filename parameter to perform arbitrary File download.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6736 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6736</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.3 before 16.6.7, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.5, all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. It was possible for an attacker to cause a client-side denial of service using malicious crafted content in the CODEOWNERS file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6840 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6840</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.4 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows a maintainer to change the name of a protected branch that bypasses the security policy added to block MR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1066 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1066</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 13.3.0 prior to 16.6.7, 16.7 prior to 16.7.5, and 16.8 prior to 16.8.2 which allows an attacker to do a resource exhaustion using GraphQL `vulnerabilitiesCountByDay`</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 22:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24806 | Improper Domain Lookup that potentially leads to SSRF attacks in libuv</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24806</link><description>libuv is a multi-platform support library with a focus on asynchronous I/O. The `uv_getaddrinfo` function in `src/unix/getaddrinfo.c` (and its windows counterpart `src/win/getaddrinfo.c`), truncates hostnames to 256 characters before calling `getaddrinfo`. This behavior can be exploited to create addresses like `0x00007f000001`, which are considered valid by `getaddrinfo` and could allow an attacker to craft payloads that resolve to unintended IP addresses, bypassing developer checks. The vulnerability arises due to how the `hostname_ascii` variable (with a length of 256 bytes) is handled in `uv_getaddrinfo` and subsequently in `uv__idna_toascii`. When the hostname exceeds 256 characters, it gets truncated without a terminating null byte. As a result attackers may be able to access internal APIs or for websites (similar to MySpace) that allows users to have `username.example.com` pages. Internal services that crawl or cache these user pages can be exposed to SSRF attacks if a malicious user chooses a long vulnerable username. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.48.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:53:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23448 | APM Server Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23448</link><description>An issue was discovered whereby APM Server could log at ERROR level, a response from Elasticsearch indicating that indexing the document failed and that response would contain parts of the original document. Depending on the nature of the document that the APM Server attempted to ingest, this could lead to the insertion of sensitive or private information in the APM Server logs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:46:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6356 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in nvmet_tcp_build_iovec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6356</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver and causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6535 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in nvmet_tcp_execute_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6535</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6536 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in __nvmet_req_complete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6536</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's NVMe driver. This issue may allow an unauthenticated malicious actor to send a set of crafted TCP packages when using NVMe over TCP, leading the NVMe driver to a NULL pointer dereference in the NVMe driver, causing kernel panic and a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38995 | An issue in SCHUHFRIED v.8.22.00 allows remote attacker to obtain the database password via crafted curl command.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38995</link><description>An issue in SCHUHFRIED v.8.22.00 allows remote attacker to obtain the database password via crafted curl command.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24488 | An issue in Shenzen Tenda Technology CP3V2.0 V11.10.00.2311090948 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the password c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24488</link><description>An issue in Shenzen Tenda Technology CP3V2.0 V11.10.00.2311090948 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the password component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23769 | Improper privilege control for the named pipe in Samsung Magician PC Software 8.0.0 (for Windows) allows a local attacker to read privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23769</link><description>Improper privilege control for the named pipe in Samsung Magician PC Software 8.0.0 (for Windows) allows a local attacker to read privileged data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24823 | graylog2-server Session Fixation vulnerability through cookie injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24823</link><description>Graylog is a free and open log management platform. Starting in version 4.3.0 and prior to versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, reauthenticating with an existing session cookie would re-use that session id, even if for different user credentials. In this case, the pre-existing session could be used to gain elevated access to an existing Graylog login session, provided the malicious user could successfully inject their session cookie into someone else's browser. The complexity of such an attack is high, because it requires presenting a spoofed login screen and injection of a session cookie into an existing browser, potentially through a cross-site scripting attack. No such attack has been discovered. Graylog 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, and any versions of the 6.0 development branch, contain patches to not re-use sessions under any circumstances. Some workarounds are available. Using short session expiration and explicit log outs of unused sessions can help limiting the attack vector. Unpatched this vulnerability exists, but is relatively hard to exploit. A proxy could be leveraged to clear the `authentication` cookie for the Graylog server URL for the `/api/system/sessions` endpoint, as that is the only one vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24824 | graylog2-server vulnerable to instantiation of arbitrary classes triggered by API request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24824</link><description>Graylog is a free and open log management platform. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4, arbitrary classes can be loaded and instantiated using a HTTP PUT request to the `/api/system/cluster_config/` endpoint. Graylog's cluster config system uses fully qualified class names as config keys. To validate the existence of the requested class before using them, Graylog loads the class using the class loader. If a user with the appropriate permissions performs the request, arbitrary classes with 1-arg String constructors can be instantiated. This will execute arbitrary code that is run during class instantiation. In the specific use case of `java.io.File`, the behavior of the internal web-server stack will lead to information exposure by including the entire file content in the response to the REST request. Versions 5.1.11 and 5.2.4 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24822 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle permissions are not getting checked when working with tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24822</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend user interface for Pimcore. Prior to version 1.3.3, an attacker can create, delete etc. tags without having the permission to do so. A fix is available in version 1.3.3. As a workaround, one may apply the patch manually.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24563 | Vyper array negative index vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24563</link><description>Vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. Arrays can be keyed by a signed integer, while they are defined for unsigned integers only. The typechecker doesn't throw when spotting the usage of an `int` as an index for an array. The typechecker allows the usage of signed integers to be used as indexes to arrays. The vulnerability is present in different forms in all versions, including `0.3.10`. For ints, the 2's complement representation is used. Because the array was declared very large, the bounds checking will pass Negative values will simply be represented as very large numbers. As of time of publication, a fixed version does not exist.

There are three potential vulnerability classes: unpredictable behavior, accessing inaccessible elements and denial of service. Class 1: If it is possible to index an array with a negative integer without reverting, this is most likely not anticipated by the developer and such accesses can cause unpredictable behavior for the contract. Class 2: If a contract has an invariant in the form `assert index &lt; x`, the developer will suppose that no elements on indexes `y | y &gt;= x` are accessible. However, by using negative indexes, this can be bypassed. Class 3: If the index is dependent on the state of the contract, this poses a risk of denial of service. If the state of the contract can be manipulated in such way that the index will be forced to be negative, the array access can always revert (because most likely the array won't be declared extremely large). However, all these the scenarios are highly unlikely. Most likely behavior is a revert on the bounds check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24816 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in samples with enabled the preview feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24816</link><description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability vulnerability has been discovered in versions prior to 4.24.0-lts in samples that use the `preview` feature. All integrators that use these samples in the production code can be affected. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code by abusing the misconfigured preview feature. It affects all users using the CKEditor 4 at version &lt; 4.24.0-lts with affected samples used in a production environment. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24706 | WordPress WP-CFM Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24706</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Forum One WP-CFM wp-cfm.This issue affects WP-CFM: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47700 | IBM Storage Virtualize improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47700</link><description>IBM SAN Volume Controller, IBM Storwize, IBM FlashSystem and IBM Storage Virtualize 8.6 products could allow a remote attacker to spoof a trusted system that would not be correctly validated by the Storwize server.  This could lead to a user connecting to a malicious host, believing that it was a trusted system and deceived into accepting spoofed data.  IBM X-Force ID:  271016.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20290 | A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20290</link><description>A vulnerability in the OLE2 file format parser of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an incorrect check for end-of-string values during scanning, which may result in a heap buffer over-read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the ClamAV scanning process to terminate, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software and consuming available system resources.&#13;
&#13; For a description of this vulnerability, see the ClamAV blog .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23806 | HID Global Reader Configuration Cards Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23806</link><description>Sensitive data can be extracted from HID iCLASS SE reader configuration cards. This could include credential and device administrator keys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31002 | IBM Security Access Manager Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31002</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 temporarily stores sensitive information in files that could be accessed by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  254657.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32328 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32328</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 uses insecure protocols in some instances that could allow an attacker on the network to take control of the server.  IBM X-Force Id:  254957.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32330 | IBM Security Verify Access man in the middle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32330</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 uses insecure calls that could allow an attacker on the network to take control of the server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254977.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38369 | IBM Security Access Manager Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38369</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 does not require that docker images should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  261196.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43017 | IBM Security Verify Access man in the middle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43017</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 could allow a privileged user to install a configuration file that could allow remote access.  IBM X-Force ID:  266155.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20252 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20252</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20254 | Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20254</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server (VCS) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks that perform arbitrary actions on an affected device. &#13;
&#13; Note: "Cisco Expressway Series" refers to Cisco Expressway Control (Expressway-C) devices and Cisco Expressway Edge (Expressway-E) devices.&#13;
&#13; For more information about these vulnerabilities, see the Details ["#details"] section of this advisory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20255 | A vulnerability in the SOAP API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server could allow an unauthenticated,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20255</link><description>A vulnerability in the SOAP API of Cisco Expressway Series and Cisco TelePresence Video Communication Server could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attack on an affected system.&#13;
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protections for the web-based management interface of an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the REST API to follow a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected system to reload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22012 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22012</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24815 | CKEditor4 Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability caused by incorrect CDATA detection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24815</link><description>CKEditor4 is an open source what-you-see-is-what-you-get HTML editor. A cross-site scripting vulnerability has been discovered in the core HTML parsing module in versions of CKEditor4 prior to 4.24.0-lts. It may affect all editor instances that enabled full-page editing mode or enabled CDATA elements in Advanced Content Filtering configuration (defaults to `script` and `style` elements). The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malformed HTML content bypassing Advanced Content Filtering mechanism, which could result in executing JavaScript code. An attacker could abuse faulty CDATA content detection and use it to prepare an intentional attack on the editor. A fix is available in version 4.24.0-lts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24812 | Frappe Authenticated Reflected Cross site scripting (XSS) in portal pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24812</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework that uses Python and MariaDB on the server side and a tightly integrated client side library. Prior to versions 14.59.0 and 15.5.0, portal pages are susceptible to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) which can be used to inject malicious JS code if user clicks on a malicious link. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 14.59.0 and 15.5.0. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25145 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Portal Search module's Search Result app in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.11, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25145</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Portal Search module's Search Result app in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.11, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 8, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 17, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML into the Search Result app's search result if highlighting is disabled by adding any searchable content (e.g., blog, message board message, web content article) to the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24771 | Open Forms potential multi-factor authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24771</link><description>Open Forms allows users create and publish smart forms. Versions prior to 2.2.9, 2.3.7, 2.4.5, and 2.5.2 contain a non-exploitable multi-factor authentication weakness. Superusers who have their credentials (username + password) compromised could potentially have the second-factor authentication bypassed if an attacker somehow managed to authenticate to Open Forms. The maintainers of Open Forms do not believe it is or has been possible to perform this login. However, if this were possible, the victim's account may be abused to view (potentially sensitive) submission data or have been used to impersonate other staff accounts to view and/or modify data. Three mitigating factors to help prevent exploitation include: the usual login page (at `/admin/login/`) does not fully log in the user until the second factor was succesfully provided; the additional non-MFA protected login page at `/api/v2/api-authlogin/` was misconfigured and could not be used to log in; and there are no additional ways to log in. This also requires credentials of a superuser to be compromised to be exploitable. Versions 2.2.9, 2.3.7, 2.4.5, and 2.5.2 contain the following patches to address these weaknesses: Move and only enable the API auth endpoints (`/api/v2/api-auth/login/`) with `settings.DEBUG = True`. `settings.DEBUG = True` is insecure and should never be applied in production settings. Additionally, apply a custom permission check to the hijack flow to only allow second-factor-verified superusers to perform user hijacking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24811 | Products.SQLAlchemyDA  vulnerable to unauthenticated arbitrary SQL query execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24811</link><description>SQLAlchemyDA is a generic database adapter for ZSQL methods. A vulnerability found in versions prior to 2.2 allows unauthenticated execution of arbitrary SQL statements on the database to which the SQLAlchemyDA instance is connected. All users are affected. The problem has been patched in version 2.2. There is no workaround for the problem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25143 | The Document and Media widget In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.6, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25143</link><description>The Document and Media widget In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.6, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 13, and older unsupported versions, does not limit resource consumption when generating a preview image, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via crafted PNG images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24130 | Mail2World v12 Business Control Center was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Usr parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24130</link><description>Mail2World v12 Business Control Center was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Usr parameter at resellercenter/login.asp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24131 | SuperWebMailer v9.31.0.01799 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulenrability via the component api.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24131</link><description>SuperWebMailer v9.31.0.01799 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulenrability via the component api.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24133 | Atmail v6.6.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter on the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24133</link><description>Atmail v6.6.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the username parameter on the login page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25200 | Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain a Stack Overflow via the jspeFactorFunctionCall at src/jsparse.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25200</link><description>Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain a Stack Overflow via the jspeFactorFunctionCall at src/jsparse.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25201 | Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read via jsvStringIteratorPrintfCallback at src/jsvar.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25201</link><description>Espruino 2v20 (commit fcc9ba4) was discovered to contain an Out-of-bounds Read via jsvStringIteratorPrintfCallback at src/jsvar.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24186 | Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a stack-overflow via the component IterGetKeysCallback at /jsish/src/jsiValue.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24186</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a stack-overflow via the component IterGetKeysCallback at /jsish/src/jsiValue.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24188 | Jsish v3.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow in ./src/jsiUtils.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24188</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap-buffer-overflow in ./src/jsiUtils.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24189 | Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the SplitChar at ./src/jsiUtils.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24189</link><description>Jsish v3.5.0 (commit 42c694c) was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the SplitChar at ./src/jsiUtils.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39196 | Apache Ozone: Missing mutual TLS authentication in one of the service internal Ozone Storage Container Manager endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39196</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Ozone.

The vulnerability allows an attacker to download metadata internal to the Storage Container Manager service without proper authentication.
The attacker is not allowed to do any modification within the Ozone Storage Container Manager service using this vulnerability.
The accessible metadata does not contain sensitive information that can be used to exploit the system later on, and the accessible data does not make it possible to gain access to actual user data within Ozone.
This issue affects Apache Ozone: 1.2.0 and subsequent releases up until 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 13:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1109 | The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ini...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1109</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the init_download() and init() functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export the plugin's tracking data and podcast information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1110 | The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1110</link><description>The Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the init() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.11. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1118 | The Podlove Subscribe button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to UNION-based SQL Injection via the 'button' attribute of the podlove-subsc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1118</link><description>The Podlove Subscribe button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to UNION-based SQL Injection via the 'button' attribute of the podlove-subscribe-button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51437 | Apache Pulsar: Timing attack in SASL token signature verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51437</link><description>Observable timing discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Pulsar SASL Authentication Provider can allow an attacker to forge a SASL Role Token that will pass signature verification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.3, 3.0.2, or 3.1.1 which fixes the issue. Users should also consider updating the configured secret in the `saslJaasServerRoleTokenSignerSecretPath` file.

Any component matching an above version running the SASL Authentication Provider is affected. That includes the Pulsar Broker, Proxy, Websocket Proxy, or Function Worker.

2.11 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.3.
3.0 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.2.
3.1 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.1.
Any users running Pulsar 2.8, 2.9, 2.10, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.

For additional details on this attack vector, please refer to  https://codahale.com/a-lesson-in-timing-attacks/ .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24303 | SQL Injection vulnerability in HiPresta "Gift Wrapping Pro" (hiadvancedgiftwrapping) module for PrestaShop before version 1.4.1, allows remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24303</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in HiPresta "Gift Wrapping Pro" (hiadvancedgiftwrapping) module for PrestaShop before version 1.4.1, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the HiAdvancedGiftWrappingGiftWrappingModuleFrontController::addGiftWrappingCartValue() method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24311 | Path Traversal vulnerability in Linea Grafica "Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro - SEO" (lgsitemaps) module for PrestaShop before vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24311</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in Linea Grafica "Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro - SEO" (lgsitemaps) module for PrestaShop before version 1.6.6, a guest can download personal information without restriction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46914 | SQL Injection vulnerability in RM bookingcalendar module for PrestaShop versions 2.7.9 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46914</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in RM bookingcalendar module for PrestaShop versions 2.7.9 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via ics_export.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24304 | In the module "Mailjet" (mailjet) from Mailjet for PrestaShop before versions 3.5.1, a guest can download technical information without rest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24304</link><description>In the module "Mailjet" (mailjet) from Mailjet for PrestaShop before versions 3.5.1, a guest can download technical information without restriction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 08:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40355 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Axigen versions 10.3.3.0 before 10.3.3.59, 10.4.0 before 10.4.19, and 10.5.0 before 10.5.5, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40355</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Axigen versions 10.3.3.0 before 10.3.3.59, 10.4.0 before 10.4.19, and 10.5.0 before 10.5.5, allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the logic for switching between the Standard and Ajax versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0977 | The Timeline Widget For Elementor (Elementor Timeline, Vertical &amp; Horizontal Timeline) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Si...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0977</link><description>The Timeline Widget For Elementor (Elementor Timeline, Vertical &amp; Horizontal Timeline) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image URLs in the plugin's timeline widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, changes the slideshow type, and then changes it back to an image.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1078 | The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_quick_st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1078</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_quick_start() and add_question_rows() functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary quizzes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1079 | The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_show_results()...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1079</link><description>The Quiz Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ays_show_results() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to fetch arbitrary quiz results which can contain PII.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0628 | The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.5 via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0628</link><description>The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.5 via the RSS feed source in admin settings. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1037 | The All-In-One Security (AIOS) – Security and Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1037</link><description>The All-In-One Security (AIOS) – Security and Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1055 | The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scriptin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1055</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's buttons in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URL values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0256 | The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Profile Display Name and Social Settings in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0256</link><description>The Starbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Profile Display Name and Social Settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 04:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23447 | Elastic Network Drive Connector Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23447</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Windows Network Drive Connector when using Document Level Security to assign permissions to a file, with explicit allow write and deny read. Although the document is not accessible to the user in Network Drive it is visible in search applications to the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 03:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23446 | Kibana Broken Access Control issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23446</link><description>An issue was discovered by Elastic, whereby the Detection Engine Search API does not respect Document-level security (DLS) or Field-level security (FLS) when querying the .alerts-security.alerts-{space_id} indices. Users who are authorized to call this API may obtain unauthorized access to documents if their roles are configured with DLS or FLS against the aforementioned index.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 03:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6388 | Suite CRM v7.14.2 - SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6388</link><description>Suite CRM version 7.14.2 allows making arbitrary HTTP requests through

the vulnerable server. This is possible because the application is vulnerable

to SSRF.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0849 | Leanote 2.7.0 - Local File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0849</link><description>Leanote version 2.7.0 allows obtaining arbitrary local files. This is possible

because the application is vulnerable to LFR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24810 | WiX is vulnerable to DLL redirection attacks that allow the attacker to escalate privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24810</link><description>WiX toolset lets developers create installers for Windows Installer, the Windows installation engine. The .be TEMP folder is vulnerable to DLL redirection attacks that allow the attacker to escalate privileges. This impacts any installer built with the WiX installer framework. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1269 | SourceCodester Product Management System supplier.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1269</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Product Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument supplier_name/supplier_contact leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253012.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1268 | CodeAstro Restaurant POS System update_product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Restaurant POS System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file update_product.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253011.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 02:03:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1267 | CodeAstro Restaurant POS System create_account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1267</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in CodeAstro Restaurant POS System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file create_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Full Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253010 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22021 | Vulnerability CVE-2024-22021 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user with a low privileged role (Plan Author) to retrieve plans from a Sco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22021</link><description>Vulnerability CVE-2024-22021 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user with a low privileged role (Plan Author) to retrieve plans from a Scope other than the one they are assigned to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22022 | Vulnerability CVE-2024-22022 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user that has been assigned a low-privileged role to access the NTLM hash ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22022</link><description>Vulnerability CVE-2024-22022 allows a Veeam Recovery Orchestrator user that has been assigned a low-privileged role to access the NTLM hash of the service account used by the Veeam Orchestrator Server Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1266 | CodeAstro University Management System Student Registration Form st_reg.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1266</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CodeAstro University Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /st_reg.php of the component Student Registration Form. The manipulation of the argument Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253009 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 01:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24019 | A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24019</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability exists in Novel-Plus v4.3.0-RC1 and prior versions. An attacker can pass in crafted offset, limit, and sort parameters to perform SQL injection via /system/roleDataPerm/list</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1265 | CodeAstro University Management System Attendance Management att_add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in CodeAstro University Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /att_add.php of the component Attendance Management. The manipulation of the argument Student Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253008.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>