<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-36647 | A hard-coded cryptographic private key used to sign JWT authentication tokens in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote attackers to imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36647</link><description>A hard-coded cryptographic private key used to sign JWT authentication tokens in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote attackers to impersonate arbitrary users and roles in web management and REST API endpoints via crafted JWT tokens.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36648 | Missing authentication in the internal data streaming system in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote unauthenticated users to read pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36648</link><description>Missing authentication in the internal data streaming system in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote unauthenticated users to read potentially sensitive information and deny service to users by directly reading and writing data in Apache Kafka (as consumer and producer).</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36649 | Insertion of sensitive information in the centralized (Grafana) logging system in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote attackers to im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36649</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information in the centralized (Grafana) logging system in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows remote attackers to impersonate other users in web management and the REST API by reading JWT tokens from logs (as a Granafa authenticated user) or from the Loki REST API without authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36646 | Incorrect user role checking in multiple REST API endpoints in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows a remote attacker with low privileges to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36646</link><description>Incorrect user role checking in multiple REST API endpoints in ProLion CryptoSpike 3.0.15P2 allows a remote attacker with low privileges to execute privileged functions and achieve privilege escalation via REST API endpoint invocation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49803 | @koa/cors has overly permissive origin policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49803</link><description>@koa/cors npm provides Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) for koa, a web framework for Node.js. Prior to version 5.0.0, the middleware operates in a way that if an allowed origin is not provided, it will return an `Access-Control-Allow-Origin` header with the value of the origin from the request. This behavior completely disables one of the most crucial elements of browsers - the Same Origin Policy (SOP), this could cause a very serious security threat to the users of this middleware. If such behavior is expected, for instance, when middleware is used exclusively for prototypes and not for production applications, it should be heavily emphasized in the documentation along with an indication of the risks associated with such behavior, as many users may not be aware of it. Version 5.0.0 fixes this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49805 | Uptime Kuma Missing Origin Validation in WebSockets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49805</link><description>Uptime Kuma is an easy-to-use self-hosted monitoring tool. Prior to version 1.23.9, the application uses WebSocket (with Socket.io), but it does not verify that the source of communication is valid. This allows third-party website to access the application on behalf of their client. When connecting to the server using Socket.IO, the server does not validate the `Origin` header leading to other site being able to open connections to the server and communicate with it. Other websites still need to authenticate to access most features, however this can be used to circumvent firewall protections made in place by people deploying the application.

Without origin validation, Javascript executed from another origin would be allowed to connect to the application without any user interaction. Without login credentials, such a connection is unable to access protected endpoints containing sensitive data of the application. However, such a connection may allow attacker to further exploit unseen vulnerabilities of the application. Users with "No-auth" mode configured who are relying on a reverse proxy or firewall to provide protection to the application would be especially vulnerable as it would grant the attacker full access to the application.

In version 1.23.9, additional verification of the HTTP Origin header has been added to the socket.io connection handler. By default, if the `Origin` header is present, it would be checked against the Host header. Connection would be denied if the hostnames do not match, which would indicate that the request is cross-origin. Connection would be allowed if the `Origin` header is not present. Users can override this behavior by setting environment variable `UPTIME_KUMA_WS_ORIGIN_CHECK=bypass`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50245 | OpenEXR-viewer memory overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50245</link><description>OpenEXR-viewer is a viewer for OpenEXR files with detailed metadata probing. Versions prior to 0.6.1 have a memory overflow vulnerability. This issue is fixed in version 0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49804 | Uptime Kuma Password Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49804</link><description>Uptime Kuma is an easy-to-use self-hosted monitoring tool. Prior to version 1.23.9, when a user changes their login password in Uptime Kuma, a previously logged-in user retains access without being logged out. This behavior persists consistently, even after system restarts or browser restarts. This vulnerability allows unauthorized access to user accounts, compromising the security of sensitive information. The same vulnerability was partially fixed in  CVE-2023-44400, but logging existing users out of their accounts was forgotten. To mitigate the risks associated with this vulnerability, the maintainers made the server emit a `refresh` event (clients handle this by reloading) and then disconnecting all clients except the one initiating the password change. It is recommended to update Uptime Kuma to version 1.23.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-3187 | An issue was discovered in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Mac before 5.7. An authenticated, unprivileged user can elevate privileges b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3187</link><description>An issue was discovered in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Mac before 5.7. An authenticated, unprivileged user can elevate privileges by running a malicious script (that executes as root from a temporary directory) during install time. (This applies to macOS before 10.15.5, or Security Update 2020-003 on Mojave and High Sierra, Later versions of macOS are not vulnerable.)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12613 | An issue was discovered in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Windows through 5.6. An attacker can spawn a process with multiple users as ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12613</link><description>An issue was discovered in BeyondTrust Privilege Management for Windows through 5.6. An attacker can spawn a process with multiple users as part of the security token (prior to Avecto elevation). When Avecto elevates the process, it removes the user who is launching the process, but not the second user. Therefore this second user still retains access and can give permission to the process back to the first user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45292 | Captcha verification bypass in github.com/mojocn/base64Captcha</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45292</link><description>When using the default implementation of Verify to check a Captcha, verification can be bypassed. For example, if the first parameter is a non-existent id, the second parameter is an empty string, and the third parameter is true, the function will always consider the Captcha to be correct.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49802 | MantisBT LinkedCustomFields Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49802</link><description>The LinkedCustomFields plugin for MantisBT allows users to link values between two custom fields, creating linked drop-downs. Prior to version 2.0.1, cross-site scripting in the MantisBT LinkedCustomFields plugin allows Javascript execution, when a crafted Custom Field is linked via the plugin and displayed when reporting a new Issue or editing an existing one. This issue is fixed in version 2.0.1. As a workaround, one may utilize MantisBT's default Content Security Policy, which blocks script execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49488 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openfiler ESA v2.99.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49488</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openfiler ESA v2.99.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the nic parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49494 | DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component select_media_post_wangEdi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49494</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component select_media_post_wangEditor.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49796 | MindsDB Arbitrary File Write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49796</link><description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a limited file write vulnerability in `file.py` Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49490 | XunRuiCMS v4.5.5 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49490</link><description>XunRuiCMS v4.5.5 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5955 | Contact Form Email &amp;lt; 1.3.44 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5955</link><description>The Contact Form Email WordPress plugin before 1.3.44 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5749 | EmbedPress &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5749</link><description>The EmbedPress WordPress plugin before 3.9.2 does not sanitise and escape user input before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5750 | EmbedPress &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5750</link><description>The EmbedPress WordPress plugin before 3.9.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page containing a specific content, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5757 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt; 2.1.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5757</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding WordPress plugin before 2.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5907 | File Manager &amp;lt; 6.3 - Admin+ Arbitrary OS File/Folder Access + Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5907</link><description>The File Manager WordPress plugin before 6.3 does not restrict the file managers root directory, allowing an administrator to set a root outside of the WordPress root directory, giving access to system files and directories even in a multisite setup, where site administrators should not be allowed to modify the sites files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5940 | WP Not Login Hide &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5940</link><description>The WP Not Login Hide (WPNLH) WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6035 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.3.4 - Subscriber + SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6035</link><description>The EazyDocs WordPress plugin before 2.3.4 does not properly sanitize and escape "data" parameter before using it in an SQL statement via an AJAX action, which could allow any authenticated users, such as subscribers, to perform SQL Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49795 | MindsDB Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49795</link><description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a server-side request forgery vulnerability in `file.py`. This can lead to limited information disclosure. Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48715 | Tuleap vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting on the edition page of a release</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48715</link><description>Tuleap is an open source suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Prior to version 15.2.99.103 or Tuleap Community Edition and prior to versions 15.2-4 and 15.1-8 of Tuleap Enterprise Edition, the name of the releases are not properly escaped on the edition page of a release. A malicious user with the ability to create a FRS release could force a victim having write permissions in the FRS to execute uncontrolled code. Tuleap Community Edition 15.2.99.103, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.2-4, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.1-8 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6679 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in dpll_pin_parent_pin_set() in drivers/dpll/dpll_netlink.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6679</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in dpll_pin_parent_pin_set() in drivers/dpll/dpll_netlink.c in the Digital Phase Locked Loop (DPLL) subsystem in the  Linux kernel. This issue could be exploited to trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6538 | System Management Unit (SMU) versions prior to 14.8.7825.01, used to manage Hitachi Vantara NAS products is susceptible to unintended information disclosure via unprivileged access to SMU configuration backup data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6538</link><description>SMU versions prior to 14.8.7825.01 are susceptible to unintended information disclosure, through URL manipulation. Authenticated users in Storage, Server or combined Server+Storage administrative roles are able to access SMU configuration backup, that would normally be barred to those specific administrative roles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6194 | In Eclipse Memory Analyzer versions 0.7 to 1.14.0, report definition XML files are not filtered to prohibit
document type definition (DTD) r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6194</link><description>In Eclipse Memory Analyzer versions 0.7 to 1.14.0, report definition XML files are not filtered to prohibit
document type definition (DTD) references to external entities.
This means that if a user chooses to use a malicious report definition XML file containing an external entity reference
to generate a report then Eclipse Memory Analyzer may access external files or URLs defined via a DTD in the report definition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6671 | Cross-Site Request Forgery on OPEN JOURNAL SYSTEMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6671</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered on OJS, that consists in a CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) attack that forces an end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49417 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setOpModeCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49417</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setOpModeCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49418 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022has a stack overflow vulnerability via setIpPortFilterRules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49418</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022has a stack overflow vulnerability via setIpPortFilterRules.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6186 | Link targets allow arbitrary script execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6186</link><description>Insufficient macro permission validation of The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows an attacker to execute built-in macros without warning.

In affected versions LibreOffice supports hyperlinks with macro or similar built-in command targets that can be executed when activated without warning the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6185 | Improper input validation enabling arbitrary Gstreamer pipeline injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6185</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in GStreamer integration of The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows an attacker to execute arbitrary GStreamer plugins.

In affected versions the filename of the embedded video is not sufficiently escaped when passed to GStreamer enabling an attacker to run arbitrary gstreamer plugins depending on what plugins are installed on the target system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49964 | An issue was discovered in Hyland Alfresco Community Edition through 7.2.0. By inserting malicious content in the folder.get.html.ftl file, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49964</link><description>An issue was discovered in Hyland Alfresco Community Edition through 7.2.0. By inserting malicious content in the folder.get.html.ftl file, an attacker may perform SSTI (Server-Side Template Injection) attacks, which can leverage FreeMarker exposed objects to bypass restrictions and achieve RCE (Remote Code Execution). NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-12873.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 07:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5500 | Frauscher: FDS102 for FAdC/FAdCi remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5500</link><description>This vulnerability allows an remote attacker with low privileges to misuse Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') to gain full control of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 07:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49355 | decToString in decNumber/decNumber.c in jq 88f01a7 has a one-byte out-of-bounds write via the " []-1.2e-1111111111" input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49355</link><description>decToString in decNumber/decNumber.c in jq 88f01a7 has a one-byte out-of-bounds write via the " []-1.2e-1111111111" input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 06:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6181 | An oversight in BCB handling of reboot reason that allows for persistent code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6181</link><description>An oversight in BCB handling of reboot reason that allows for persistent code execution</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48417 | Missing Permission checks resulting in unauthorized access and Manipulation in KeyChainActivity Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48417</link><description>Missing Permission checks resulting in unauthorized access and Manipulation in KeyChainActivity Application</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48424 | U-Boot shell vulnerability resulting in Privilege escalation in a production device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48424</link><description>U-Boot shell vulnerability resulting in Privilege escalation in a production device</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48425 | U-Boot vulnerability resulting in persistent Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48425</link><description>U-Boot vulnerability resulting in persistent Code Execution</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6659 | Campcodes Web-Based Student Clearance System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6659</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Web-Based Student Clearance System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /libsystem/login.php. The manipulation of the argument student leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247367.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50465 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Monica (aka MonicaHQ) 4.0.0 via an SVG document uploaded by an authenticated use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50465</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Monica (aka MonicaHQ) 4.0.0 via an SVG document uploaded by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6658 | SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6658</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ajax-api.php?action=save_attendance. The manipulation of the argument class_id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 23:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50463 | The caddy-geo-ip (aka GeoIP) middleware through 0.6.0 for Caddy 2, when trust_header X-Forwarded-For is used, allows attackers to spoof thei...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50463</link><description>The caddy-geo-ip (aka GeoIP) middleware through 0.6.0 for Caddy 2, when trust_header X-Forwarded-For is used, allows attackers to spoof their source IP address via an X-Forwarded-For header, which may bypass a protection mechanism (trusted_proxy directive in reverse_proxy or IP address range restrictions).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 22:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6657 | SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System student_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6657</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /modals/student_form.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247365 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6656 | DeepFaceLab DFLJPG.py deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6656</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file DFLIMG/DFLJPG.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247364. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48614 | Special:Ask in Semantic MediaWiki before 4.0.2 allows Reflected XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48614</link><description>Special:Ask in Semantic MediaWiki before 4.0.2 allows Reflected XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50453 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. It uses the public endpoint /api/v1/signshow for its login screen. This endpoint returns int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50453</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. It uses the public endpoint /api/v1/signshow for its login screen. This endpoint returns internal configuration data of user object attributes, such as selectable values, which should not be visible to the public.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50454 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. In several subsystems, SSL/TLS was used to establish connections to external services withou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50454</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. In several subsystems, SSL/TLS was used to establish connections to external services without proper validation of hostname and certificate authority. This is exploitable by man-in-the-middle attackers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50455 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. Due to lack of rate limiting in the "email address verification" feature, an attacker could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50455</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. Due to lack of rate limiting in the "email address verification" feature, an attacker could send many requests for a known address to cause Denial Of Service (generation of many emails, which would also spam the victim).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50456 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. An attacker can trigger phishing links in generated notification emails via a crafted first ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50456</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. An attacker can trigger phishing links in generated notification emails via a crafted first or last name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50457 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. When listing tickets linked to a knowledge base answer, or knowledge base answers of a ticke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50457</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. When listing tickets linked to a knowledge base answer, or knowledge base answers of a ticket, a user could see entries for which they lack permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5868 | Postgresql: memory disclosure in aggregate function calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5868</link><description>A memory disclosure vulnerability was found in PostgreSQL that allows remote users to access sensitive information by exploiting certain aggregate function calls with 'unknown'-type arguments. Handling 'unknown'-type values from string literals without type designation can disclose bytes, potentially revealing notable and confidential information. This issue exists due to excessive data output in aggregate function calls, enabling remote users to read some portion of system memory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5869 | Postgresql: buffer overrun from integer overflow in array modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5869</link><description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL that allows authenticated database users to execute arbitrary code through missing overflow checks during SQL array value modification. This issue exists due to an integer overflow during array modification where a remote user can trigger the overflow by providing specially crafted data. This enables the execution of arbitrary code on the target system, allowing users to write arbitrary bytes to memory and extensively read the server's memory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5870 | Postgresql: role pg_signal_backend can signal certain superuser processes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5870</link><description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL involving the pg_cancel_backend role that signals background workers, including the logical replication launcher, autovacuum workers, and the autovacuum launcher. Successful exploitation requires a non-core extension with a less-resilient background worker and would affect that specific background worker only. This issue may allow a remote high privileged user to launch a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50449 | JFinalCMS 5.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to read files via ../ Directory Traversal in the /common/down/file fileKey parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50449</link><description>JFinalCMS 5.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to read files via ../ Directory Traversal in the /common/down/file fileKey parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50446 | An issue was discovered in Mullvad VPN Windows app before 2023.6-beta1. Insufficient permissions on a directory allow any local unprivileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50446</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mullvad VPN Windows app before 2023.6-beta1. Insufficient permissions on a directory allow any local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6655 | Hongjing e-HR Login Interface loadhistroyorgtree sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6655</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hongjing e-HR 2020. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /w_selfservice/oauthservlet/%2e./.%2e/general/inform/org/loadhistroyorgtree of the component Login Interface. The manipulation of the argument parentid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247358 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6654 | PHPEMS Session Data session.cls.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPEMS 6.x/7.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library lib/session.cls.php of the component Session Data Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247357 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6653 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System Create a new Subject subject.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/subject.php of the component Create a new Subject. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6652 | code-projects Matrimonial Site register.php register sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Matrimonial Site 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function register of the file /register.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247345 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6651 | code-projects Matrimonial Site sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Matrimonial Site 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /auth/auth.php?user=1. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247344.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 11:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6650 | SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument cashier leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247343.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6649 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(5)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247342 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6648 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file password-recovery.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247341 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6647 | AMTT HiBOS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in AMTT HiBOS 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument Type leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247340. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>