<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:49:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2337 | Easy Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2337</link><description>The Easy Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'testimonials_grid ' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6560 | Addonify – Quick View For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.16 - Unauthenticated Full Path Dislcosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6560</link><description>The Addonify – Quick View For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.16. This is due the plugin utilizing mobiledetect without preventing direct access to the files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5804 | Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.4.13 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Setting Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5804</link><description>The Conditional Fields for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.4.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpcf7cf_admin_init function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41121 | Custom workspace allow to overwrite plugin entrypoint executable in Woodpecker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41121</link><description>Woodpecker is a simple yet powerful CI/CD engine with great extensibility. The server allow to create any user who can trigger a pipeline run malicious workflows: 1. Those workflows can either lead to a host takeover that runs the agent executing the workflow. 2. Or allow to extract the secrets who would be normally provided to the plugins who's entrypoint are overwritten. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.7.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41122 | Custom environment variables allow to alter execution flow of plugins in Woodpecker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41122</link><description>Woodpecker is a simple yet powerful CI/CD engine with great extensibility. The server allow to create any user who can trigger a pipeline run malicious workflows: 1. Those workflows can either lead to a host takeover that runs the agent executing the workflow. 2. Or allow to extract the secrets who would be normally provided to the plugins who's entrypoint are overwritten. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.7.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41597 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in ProcessWire v.3.0.229 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41597</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in ProcessWire v.3.0.229 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTML file to the comments functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39906 | Remote code execution in Haven IndieAuthClient (GHSL-2024-093)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39906</link><description>A command injection vulnerability was found in the IndieAuth functionality of the Ruby on Rails based Haven blog web application. The affected functionality requires authentication, but an attacker can craft a link that they can pass to a logged in administrator of the blog software. This leads to the immediate execution of the provided commands when the link is accessed by the authenticated administrator. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution (RCE) and has been addressed by commit `c52f07c`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39123 | In janeczku Calibre-Web 0.6.0 to 0.6.21, the edit_book_comments function is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to improper sanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39123</link><description>In janeczku Calibre-Web 0.6.0 to 0.6.21, the edit_book_comments function is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to improper sanitization performed by the clean_string function. The vulnerability arises from the way the clean_string function handles HTML sanitization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 19:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41124 | Puncia Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information via HTTP urls in `API_URLS`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41124</link><description>Puncia is the Official CLI utility for Subdomain Center &amp; Exploit Observer. `API_URLS` is utilizing HTTP instead of HTTPS for communication that can lead to issues like Eavesdropping, Data Tampering, Unauthorized Data Access &amp; MITM Attacks. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.21 by using https rather than http connections. All users are advised to upgrade. There is no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 19:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41599 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in RuoYi v.4.7.9 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file upload method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41599</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in RuoYi v.4.7.9 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the file upload method</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 19:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40400 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the image upload function of Automad v2.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40400</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the image upload function of Automad v2.0.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41600 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in lin-CMS Springboot v.0.2.1 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41600</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in lin-CMS Springboot v.0.2.1 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the login method in the UserController.java component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41281 | Linksys WRT54G v4.21.5 has a stack overflow vulnerability in get_merge_mac function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41281</link><description>Linksys WRT54G v4.21.5 has a stack overflow vulnerability in get_merge_mac function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24970 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the HP Display Control software component within the HP Application Enabling Software Driv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24970</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the HP Display Control software component within the HP Application Enabling Software Driver which might allow escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29080 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the HP Display Control software component within the HP Application Enabling Software Driv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29080</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in the HP Display Control software component within the HP Application Enabling Software Driver which might allow escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41602 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Spina CMS v.2.18.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41602</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Spina CMS v.2.18.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted URL</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41603 | Spina CMS v2.18.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the URI /admin/layout.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41603</link><description>Spina CMS v2.18.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via the URI /admin/layout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41492 | A stack overflow in Tenda AX1806 v1.0.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41492</link><description>A stack overflow in Tenda AX1806 v1.0.0.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41601 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in lin-CMS v.0.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the login meth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41601</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in lin-CMS v.0.2.0 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the login method in the UserController.java component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6908 | Admin Can Escalate Privileges to SuperAdmin Using Manual PUT Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6908</link><description>Improper privilege management in Yugabyte Platform allows authenticated admin users to escalate privileges to SuperAdmin via a crafted PUT HTTP request, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive system functions and data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6895 | Insecure Account Profile Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6895</link><description>Insufficient authentication in user account management in Yugabyte Platform allows local network attackers with a compromised user session to change critical security information without re-authentication. An attacker with user session and access to application can modify settings such as password and email without being prompted for the current password, enabling account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39962 | D-Link DIR-823X AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wireless Router v21_D240126 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39962</link><description>D-Link DIR-823X AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wireless Router v21_D240126 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the ntp_zone_val parameter at /goform/set_ntp. This vulnerability is exploited via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0006 | DB User Password Leak in Application Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0006</link><description>Information exposure in the logging system in Yugabyte Platform allows local attackers with access to application logs to obtain database user credentials in log files, potentially leading to unauthorized database access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27489 | An issue in the DelFile() function of WMCMS v4.4 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via a crafted POST request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27489</link><description>An issue in the DelFile() function of WMCMS v4.4 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39963 | AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wi-Fi 6 Router AX9 V22.03.01.46 and AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wi-Fi 6 Router AX12 V1.0 V22.03.01.46 were discovered ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39963</link><description>AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wi-Fi 6 Router AX9 V22.03.01.46 and AX3000 Dual-Band Gigabit Wi-Fi 6 Router AX12 V1.0 V22.03.01.46 were discovered to contain an authenticated remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the macFilterType parameter at /goform/setMacFilterCfg.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37066 | A command injection vulnerability exists in Wyze V4 Pro firmware versions before 4.50.4.9222, which allows attackers to execute arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37066</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in Wyze V4 Pro firmware versions before 4.50.4.9222, which allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands over Bluetooth as root during the camera setup process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5977 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.13.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (GiveWP Worker+) Arbitrary Post Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5977</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.0 via the 'handleRequest' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with GiveWP Worker-level access and above, to delete and update arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6916 | Zowe CLI --show-inputs-only displays securely stored properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6916</link><description>A vulnerability in Zowe CLI allows local, privileged actors to display securely stored properties in cleartext within a terminal using the '--show-inputs-only' flag.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41107 | Apache CloudStack: SAML Signature Exclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41107</link><description>The CloudStack SAML authentication (disabled by default) does not enforce signature check. In CloudStack environments where SAML authentication is enabled, an attacker that initiates CloudStack SAML single sign-on authentication can bypass SAML authentication by submitting a spoofed SAML response with no signature and known or guessed username and other user details of a SAML-enabled CloudStack user-account. In such environments, this can result in a complete compromise of the resources owned and/or accessible by a SAML enabled user-account.

Affected users are recommended to disable the SAML authentication plugin by setting the "saml2.enabled" global setting to "false", or upgrade to version 4.18.2.2, 4.19.1.0 or later, which addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6907 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6907</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file sort.php. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271932.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:20:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6906 | SourceCodester Record Management System add_leave_non_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6906</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file add_leave_non_user.php. The manipulation of the argument LSS leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271931.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6905 | SourceCodester Record Management System view_info_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6905</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file view_info_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271930 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29736 | Apache CXF: SSRF vulnerability via WADL stylesheet parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29736</link><description>A SSRF vulnerability in WADL service description in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on REST webservices. The attack only applies if a custom stylesheet parameter is configured.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32007 | Apache CXF Denial of Service vulnerability in JOSE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32007</link><description>An improper input validation of the p2c parameter in the Apache CXF JOSE code before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform a denial of service attack by specifying a large value for this parameter in a token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41172 | Apache CXF: Unrestricted memory consumption in CXF HTTP clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41172</link><description>In versions of Apache CXF before 3.6.4 and 4.0.5 (3.5.x and lower versions are not impacted), a CXF HTTP client conduit may prevent HTTPClient instances from being garbage collected and it is possible that memory consumption will continue to increase, eventually causing the application to run  out of memory</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39457 | Cybozu Garoon 6.0.0 to 6.0.1 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in PDF preview. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39457</link><description>Cybozu Garoon 6.0.0 to 6.0.1 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in PDF preview. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on a logged-in user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6904 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort2_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6904</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file sort2_user.php. The manipulation of the argument qualification leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271929 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6903 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort1_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6903</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file sort1_user.php. The manipulation of the argument position leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271928.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40724 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Assimp versions prior to 5.4.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code by inputting a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40724</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Assimp versions prior to 5.4.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code by inputting a specially crafted file into the product.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6338 | FV Player &amp;lt;= 7.5.46.7212 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via exclude Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6338</link><description>The FV Flowplayer Video Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘exclude’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.5.46.7212 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6799 | YITH Essential Kit for WooCommerce #1 &amp;lt;= 2.34.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Install, Activation, and Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6799</link><description>The YITH Essential Kit for WooCommerce #1 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'activate_module', 'deactivate_module', and 'install_module' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.34.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install, activate, and deactivate plugins from a pre-defined list of available YITH plugins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6902 | SourceCodester Record Management System sort_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6902</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file sort_user.php. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271927.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6901 | SourceCodester Record Management System entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6901</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file entry.php. The manipulation of the argument school leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271926 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6900 | SourceCodester Record Management System edit_emp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6900</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file edit_emp.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271925 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7268 | ArtPlacer Widget &amp;lt; 2.21.2 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Widget Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7268</link><description>The ArtPlacer Widget WordPress plugin before 2.21.2 does not have authorisation check in place when deleting widgets,  allowing ay authenticated users, such as subscriber, to delete arbitrary widgets</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7269 | ArtPlacer Widget &amp;lt; 2.21.2 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7269</link><description>The ArtPlacer Widget WordPress plugin before 2.21.2 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5604 | Bug Library &amp;lt; 2.1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5604</link><description>The Bug Library WordPress plugin before 2.1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6205 | PayPlus Payment Gateway &amp;lt; 6.6.9 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6205</link><description>The PayPlus Payment Gateway WordPress plugin before 6.6.9 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via a WooCommerce API route available to unauthenticated users, leading to an SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21527 | Versions of the package github.com/gotenberg/gotenberg/v8/pkg/gotenberg before 8.1.0; versions of the package github.com/gotenberg/gotenberg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21527</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/gotenberg/gotenberg/v8/pkg/gotenberg before 8.1.0; versions of the package github.com/gotenberg/gotenberg/v8/pkg/modules/chromium before 8.1.0; versions of the package github.com/gotenberg/gotenberg/v8/pkg/modules/webhook before 8.1.0 are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the /convert/html endpoint when a request is made to a file via localhost, such as . By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can achieve local file inclusion, allowing of sensitive files read on the host system.&#13;&#13; Workaround&#13;An alternative is using either or both --chromium-deny-list and --chromium-allow-list flags.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21583 | Versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/components/server/go/pkg/lib before main-gha.27122; versions of the package github.com/g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21583</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/components/server/go/pkg/lib before main-gha.27122; versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/components/ws-proxy/pkg/proxy before main-gha.27122; versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/install/installer/pkg/components/auth before main-gha.27122; versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/install/installer/pkg/components/public-api-server before main-gha.27122; versions of the package github.com/gitpod-io/gitpod/install/installer/pkg/components/server before main-gha.27122; versions of the package @gitpod/gitpod-protocol before 0.1.5-main-gha.27122 are vulnerable to Cookie Tossing due to a missing __Host- prefix on the _gitpod_io_jwt2_ session cookie. This allows an adversary who controls a subdomain to set the value of the cookie on the Gitpod control plane, which can be assigned to an attacker’s own JWT so that specific actions taken by the victim (such as connecting a new Github organization) are actioned by the attackers session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6899 | SourceCodester Record Management System view_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6899</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file view_info.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271924.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6898 | SourceCodester Record Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6898</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument UserName leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271923.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 03:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30130 | HCL Nomad server on Domino is affected by a use of web browser cache containing sensitive information vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30130</link><description>HCL Nomad server on Domino is vulnerable to the cache containing sensitive information which could potentially give an attacker the ability to acquire the sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35198 | TorchServe bypass allowed_urls configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35198</link><description>TorchServe is a flexible and easy-to-use tool for serving and scaling PyTorch models in production. TorchServe 's check on allowed_urls configuration can be by-passed if the URL contains characters such as ".." but it does not prevent the model from being downloaded into the model store. Once a file is downloaded, it can be referenced without providing a URL the second time, which effectively bypasses the allowed_urls security check. Customers using PyTorch inference Deep Learning Containers (DLC) through Amazon SageMaker and EKS are not affected. This issue in TorchServe has been fixed by validating the URL without characters such as ".." before downloading see PR #3082. TorchServe release 0.11.0 includes the fix to address this vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35199 | TorchServe gRPC Port Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35199</link><description>TorchServe is a flexible and easy-to-use tool for serving and scaling PyTorch models in production. In affected versions the two gRPC ports 7070 and 7071, are not bound to [localhost](http://localhost/) by default, so when TorchServe is launched, these two interfaces are bound to all interfaces. Customers using PyTorch inference Deep Learning Containers (DLC) through Amazon SageMaker and EKS are not affected. This issue in TorchServe has been fixed in PR #3083. TorchServe release 0.11.0 includes the fix to address this vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38156 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38156</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40642 | Absent Input Validation in BinaryHttpParser in the netty incubator codec.bhttp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40642</link><description>The netty incubator codec.bhttp is a java language binary http parser. In affected versions the `BinaryHttpParser` class does not properly validate input values thus giving attackers almost complete control over the HTTP requests constructed from the parsed output. Attackers can abuse several issues individually to perform various injection attacks including HTTP request smuggling, desync attacks, HTTP header injections, request queue poisoning, caching attacks and Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF). Attacker could also combine several issues to create well-formed messages for other text-based protocols which may result in attacks beyond the HTTP protocol. The BinaryHttpParser class implements the readRequestHead method which performs most of the relevant parsing of the received request. The data structure prefixes values with a variable length integer value. The parsing code below first gets the lengths of the values from the prefixed variable length integer. After it has all of the lengths and calculates all of the indices, the parser casts the applicable slices of the ByteBuf to String. Finally, it passes these values into a new `DefaultBinaryHttpRequest` object where no further parsing or validation occurs. Method is partially validated while other values are not validated at all. Software that relies on netty to apply input validation for binary HTTP data may be vulnerable to various injection and protocol based attacks. This issue has been addressed in version 0.0.13.Final. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41111 | BishopFox Sliver Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41111</link><description>Sliver is an open source cross-platform adversary emulation/red team framework, it can be used by organizations of all sizes to perform security testing. Sliver version 1.6.0 (prerelease) is vulnerable to RCE on the teamserver by a low-privileged "operator" user. The RCE is as the system root user. The exploit is pretty fun as we make the Sliver server pwn itself. As described in a past issue (#65), "there is a clear security boundary between the operator and server, an operator should not inherently be able to run commands or code on the server." An operator who exploited this vulnerability would be able to view all console logs, kick all other operators, view and modify files stored on the server, and ultimately delete the server. This issue has not yet be addressed but is expected to be resolved before the full release of version 1.6.0. Users of the 1.6.0 prerelease should avoid using Silver in production.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5997 | Duplica &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization to Users/Posts Duplicates Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5997</link><description>The Duplica – Duplicate Posts, Pages, Custom Posts or Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the duplicate_user and duplicate_post functions in all versions up to, and including, 0.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create duplicates of users and posts/pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6455 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via ekit_widgetarea_content Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6455</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to a missing capability checks on ekit_widgetarea_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view any item created in Elementor, such as posts, pages and templates including drafts, pending and private items.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39090 | The PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal Project version 2.0 contains a vulnerability that allows Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39090</link><description>The PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal Project version 2.0 contains a vulnerability that allows Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of a user's session, potentially leading to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 19:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39173 | calculator-boilerplate v1.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the eval function at /routes/calculato...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39173</link><description>calculator-boilerplate v1.0 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the eval function at /routes/calculator.js. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload injected into the input field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 19:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30126 | HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by a missing X-Frame-Options Header vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30126</link><description>HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by a missing X-Frame-Options HTTP header which can allow an attacker to create a malicious website that embeds the target website in a frame or iframe, tricking users into performing actions on the target website without their knowledge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 19:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38806 | UAA Failure to Remove Shadow User’s Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38806</link><description>Failure to properly synchronize user's permissions in UAA in Cloud Foundry Foundation  v40.17.0 https://github.com/cloudfoundry/cf-deployment/releases/tag/v40.17.0 ,
 potentially resulting in users retaining access rights they should not 
have.  This can allow them to perform operations beyond their intended 
permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5321 | Incorrect permissions on Windows containers logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5321</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes clusters with Windows nodes where BUILTIN\Users may be able to read container logs and NT AUTHORITY\Authenticated Users may be able to modify container logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 18:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30125 | HCL BigFix Compliance is affected by an internal server error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30125</link><description>The server responded with an HTTP status of 500, indicating a server-side error that may cause the server process to die.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 18:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0857 | SQLi in Universal Software&amp;#x27;s FlexWater Corporate Water Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0857</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Universal Software Inc. FlexWater Corporate Water Management allows SQL Injection.This issue affects FlexWater Corporate Water Management: through 18072024. 

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5625 | XML External Entity Injection in PruvaSoft Informatics&amp;#x27; Apinizer Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5625</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in PruvaSoft Informatics Apinizer Management Console allows Data Serialization External Entities Blowup.This issue affects Apinizer Management Console: before 2024.05.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40628 | Arbitrary File Read in Ansible Playbooks in Jumpserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40628</link><description>JumpServer is an open-source Privileged Access Management (PAM) tool that provides DevOps and IT teams with on-demand and secure access to SSH, RDP, Kubernetes, Database and RemoteApp endpoints through a web browser. An attacker can exploit the ansible playbook to read arbitrary files in the celery container, leading to sensitive information disclosure. The Celery container runs as root and has database access, allowing the attacker to steal all secrets for hosts, create a new JumpServer account with admin privileges, or manipulate the database in other ways. This issue has been addressed in release versions 3.10.12 and 4.0.0. It is recommended to upgrade the safe versions. There is no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40629 | Arbitrary File Write in Ansible Playbooks leads to RCE in Jumpserver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40629</link><description>JumpServer is an open-source Privileged Access Management (PAM) tool that provides DevOps and IT teams with on-demand and secure access to SSH, RDP, Kubernetes, Database and RemoteApp endpoints through a web browser. An attacker can exploit the Ansible playbook to write arbitrary files, leading to remote code execution (RCE) in the Celery container. The Celery container runs as root and has database access, allowing an attacker to steal all secrets for hosts, create a new JumpServer account with admin privileges, or manipulate the database in other ways. This issue has been patched in release versions 3.10.12 and 4.0.0. It is recommended to upgrade the safe versions. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5620 | Authentication Bypass in PruvaSoft Informatics&amp;#x27; Apinizer Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5620</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in PruvaSoft Informatics Apinizer Management Console allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Apinizer Management Console: before 2024.05.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40644 | gitoxide&amp;#x27;s gix-path can use a fake program files location</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40644</link><description>gitoxide An idiomatic, lean, fast &amp; safe pure Rust implementation of Git. `gix-path` can be tricked into running another `git.exe` placed in an untrusted location by a limited user account on Windows systems. Windows permits limited user accounts without administrative privileges to create new directories in the root of the system drive. While `gix-path` first looks for `git` using a `PATH` search, in version 0.10.8 it also has a fallback strategy on Windows of checking two hard-coded paths intended to be the 64-bit and 32-bit Program Files directories. Existing functions, as well as the newly introduced `exe_invocation` function, were updated to make use of these alternative locations. This causes facilities in `gix_path::env` to directly execute `git.exe` in those locations, as well as to return its path or whatever configuration it reports to callers who rely on it. Although unusual setups where the system drive is not `C:`, or even where Program Files directories have non-default names, are technically possible, the main problem arises on a 32-bit Windows system. Such a system has no `C:\Program Files (x86)` directory. A limited user on a 32-bit Windows system can therefore create the `C:\Program Files (x86)` directory and populate it with arbitrary contents. Once a payload has been placed at the second of the two hard-coded paths in this way, other user accounts including administrators will execute it if they run an application that uses `gix-path` and do not have `git` in a `PATH` directory. (While having `git` found in a `PATH` search prevents exploitation, merely having it installed in the default location under the real `C:\Program Files` directory does not. This is because the first hard-coded path's `mingw64` component assumes a 64-bit installation.). Only Windows is affected. Exploitation is unlikely except on a 32-bit system. In particular, running a 32-bit build on a 64-bit system is not a risk factor. Furthermore, the attacker must have a user account on the system, though it may be a relatively unprivileged account. Such a user can perform privilege escalation and execute code as another user, though it may be difficult to do so reliably because the targeted user account must run an application or service that uses `gix-path` and must not have `git` in its `PATH`. The main exploitable configuration is one where Git for Windows has been installed but not added to `PATH`. This is one of the options in its installer, though not the default option. Alternatively, an affected program that sanitizes its `PATH` to remove seemingly nonessential directories could allow exploitation. But for the most part, if the target user has configured a `PATH` in which the real `git.exe` can be found, then this cannot be exploited. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.10.9 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40647 | Unintentional exposure of environment variables to subprocesses in sentry-sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40647</link><description>sentry-sdk is the official Python SDK for Sentry.io. A bug in Sentry's Python SDK &lt; 2.8.0 allows the environment variables to be passed to subprocesses despite the `env={}` setting. In Python's `subprocess` calls, all environment variables are passed to subprocesses by default. However, if you specifically do not want them to be passed to subprocesses, you may use `env` argument in `subprocess` calls. Due to the bug in Sentry SDK, with the Stdlib integration enabled (which is enabled by default), this expectation is not fulfilled, and all environment variables are being passed to subprocesses instead. The issue has been patched in pull request #3251 and is included in sentry-sdk==2.8.0. We strongly recommend upgrading to the latest SDK version. However, if it's not possible, and if passing environment variables to child processes poses a security risk for you, you can disable all default integrations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5619 | IDOR in PruvaSoft Informatics&amp;#x27; Apinizer Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5619</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in PruvaSoft Informatics Apinizer Management Console allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Apinizer Management Console: before 2024.05.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40648 | `UserIdentity::is_verified` not checking verification status of own user identity while performing the check in matrix-rust-sdk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40648</link><description>matrix-rust-sdk is an implementation of a Matrix client-server library in Rust. The `UserIdentity::is_verified()` method in the matrix-sdk-crypto crate before version 0.7.2 doesn't take into account the verification status of the user's own identity while performing the check and may as a result return a value contrary to what is implied by its name and documentation. If the method is used to decide whether to perform sensitive operations towards a user identity, a malicious homeserver could manipulate the outcome in order to make the identity appear trusted. This is not a typical usage of the method, which lowers the impact. The method itself is not used inside the `matrix-sdk-crypto` crate. The 0.7.2 release of the `matrix-sdk-crypto` crate includes a fix. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40704 | Philips Vue PACS Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40704</link><description>Philips Vue PACS uses default credentials for potentially critical functionality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40223 | Philips Vue PACS Improper Privilege Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40223</link><description>Philips Vue PACS does not properly assign, modify, track, or check actor privileges, creating an unintended sphere of control for that actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40539 | Philips Vue PACS Weak Password Requirements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40539</link><description>Philips Vue PACS does not require that users have strong passwords, which could make it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5618 | Broken Access Control in  PruvaSoft Informatics&amp;#x27; Apinizer Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5618</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in PruvaSoft Informatics Apinizer Management Console allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Apinizer Management Console: before 2024.05.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40159 | Philips Vue PACS Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40159</link><description>A validated user not explicitly authorized to have access to certain sensitive information could access Philips Vue PACS on the same network to expose that information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50304 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50304</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management DOORS Web Access 9.7.2.8 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  273335.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38302 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, contain(s) a Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data vulnerability in the DDAE (Starburst). A low priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38302</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, contain(s) a Missing Encryption of Sensitive Data vulnerability in the DDAE (Starburst). A low privileged attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30473 | Dell ECS, versions prior to 3.8.1, contain a privilege elevation vulnerability in user management. A remote high privileged attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30473</link><description>Dell ECS, versions prior to 3.8.1, contain a privilege elevation vulnerability in user management. A remote high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, gaining access to unauthorized end points.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39907 | a sqlinjection in 1Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39907</link><description>1Panel is a web-based linux server management control panel. There are many sql injections in the project, and some of them are not well filtered, leading to arbitrary file writes, and ultimately leading to RCEs. These sql injections have been resolved in version 1.10.12-tls. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for these issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39911 | 1Panel SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39911</link><description>1Panel is a web-based linux server management control panel. 1Panel contains an unspecified sql injection via User-Agent handling. This issue has been addressed in version 1.10.12-lts. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34013 | Local privilege escalation due to OS command injection vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34013</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to OS command injection vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before build 41396.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 13:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31143 | double unlock in x86 guest IRQ handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31143</link><description>An optional feature of PCI MSI called "Multiple Message" allows a
device to use multiple consecutive interrupt vectors.  Unlike for MSI-X,
the setting up of these consecutive vectors needs to happen all in one
go.  In this handling an error path could be taken in different
situations, with or without a particular lock held.  This error path
wrongly releases the lock even when it is not currently held.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 13:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29178 | Apache StreamPark: FreeMarker SSTI RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29178</link><description>On versions before 2.1.4, a user could log in and perform a template injection attack resulting in Remote Code Execution on the server, The attacker must successfully log into the system to launch an attack, so this is a moderate-impact vulnerability.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40725 | Apache HTTP Server: source code disclosure with handlers configured via AddType</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40725</link><description>A partial fix for  CVE-2024-39884 in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.61 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers. "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40898 | Apache HTTP Server: SSRF with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40898</link><description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context, allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62 which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6504 | Rapid7 InsightVM Protection Mechanism Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6504</link><description>Rapid7 InsightVM Console versions below 6.6.260 suffer from a protection mechanism failure whereby an attacker with network access to the InsightVM Console can cause it to overload or crash by sending repeated invalid REST requests in a short timeframe, to the Console's port 443 causing the console to enter an exception handling logging loop, exhausting the CPU.  There is no indication that an attacker can use this method to escalate privilege, acquire unauthorized access to data, or gain control of protected resources. This issue is fixed in version 6.6.261.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3242 | Brizy – Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.4.44 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3242</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file extension validation in the validateImageContent function called via storeImages in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Version 2.4.44 prevents the upload of files ending in .sh and .php. Version 2.4.45 fully patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5554 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.6.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5554</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘onclick_event’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5555 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.6.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5555</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘social-link-title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29014 | Vulnerability in SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32 and 64-bit) client 10.2.339 and earlier versions allows an attacker to arbitrary code exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29014</link><description>Vulnerability in SonicWall NetExtender Windows (32 and 64-bit) client 10.2.339 and earlier versions allows an attacker to arbitrary code execution when processing an EPC Client update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40764 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS IPSec VPN allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40764</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS IPSec VPN allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41011 | drm/amdkfd: don&amp;#x27;t allow mapping the MMIO HDP page with large pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41011</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdkfd: don't allow mapping the MMIO HDP page with large pages

We don't get the right offset in that case.  The GPU has
an unused 4K area of the register BAR space into which you can
remap registers.  We remap the HDP flush registers into this
space to allow userspace (CPU or GPU) to flush the HDP when it
updates VRAM.  However, on systems with &gt;4K pages, we end up
exposing PAGE_SIZE of MMIO space.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6164 | Filter &amp;amp; Grids &amp;lt; 2.8.33 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6164</link><description>The Filter &amp; Grids WordPress plugin before 2.8.33 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion via the post_layout parameter. This makes it possible for an unauthenticated attacker to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6708 | SVG Support &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Authenticated (Author+) Cross-Site Scripting via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6708</link><description>The SVG Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the SVG upload feature in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping, even when the 'Sanitize SVG while uploading' feature is enabled. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note that successful exploitation of this vulnerability requires the administrator to allow author-level users to upload SVG files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5726 | Timeline Event History &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5726</link><description>The Timeline Event History plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 via deserialization of untrusted input 'timelines-data' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5964 | Zenon Lite &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5964</link><description>The Zenon Lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6175 | Booking Ultra Pro &amp;lt;= 1.1.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6175</link><description>The Booking Ultra Pro Appointments Booking Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify and delete. multiple plugin options and data such as payments, pricing, booking information, business hours, calendars, profile information, and email templates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6599 | Meks Video Importer &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) API Keys Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6599</link><description>The Meks Video Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized API key modification due to a missing capability check on the ajax_save_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the plugin's API keys</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6705 | RegLevel &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6705</link><description>The RegLevel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41184 | In the vrrp_ipsets_handler handler (fglobal_parser.c) of keepalived through 2.3.1, an integer overflow can occur. NOTE: this CVE Record migh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41184</link><description>In the vrrp_ipsets_handler handler (fglobal_parser.c) of keepalived through 2.3.1, an integer overflow can occur. NOTE: this CVE Record might not be worthwhile because an empty ipset name must be configured by the user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 01:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>