<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:44:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-30675 | Unauthorized node injection vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability could allow a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30675</link><description>Unauthorized node injection vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability could allow a malicious user to escalate privileges by injecting malicious ROS2 nodes into the system remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30674 | Unauthorized access vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3, allows remote attackers to gain contr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30674</link><description>Unauthorized access vulnerability in ROS2 Iron Irwini in ROS_VERSION is 2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3, allows remote attackers to gain control of multiple ROS2 nodes. Unauthorized information access to these nodes could result in compromised system integrity, the execution of arbitrary commands, and disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30672 | Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30672</link><description>Arbitrary file upload vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (DoS), and obtain sensitive information via the file upload component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30667 | Insecure deserialization vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30667</link><description>Insecure deserialization vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or obtain sensitive information via crafted input to the data handling components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30666 | A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30666</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in the C++ components of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via improper handling of arrays or strings within these components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30665 | An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30665</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability primarily affects the command processing or system call components in ROS, making them susceptible to manipulation by malicious entities. Through this, unauthorized commands can be executed, leading to remote code execution (RCE), data theft, and malicious activities. The affected components include External Command Execution Modules, System Call Handlers, and Interface Scripts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30663 | An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSIO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30663</link><description>An issue was discovered in the default configurations of ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to gain access using default credentials, posing a serious threat to the integrity and security of the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30662 | An issue was discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30662</link><description>An issue was discovered in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia in ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, where the system transmits messages in plaintext. This flaw exposes sensitive information, making it vulnerable to man-in-the-middle (MitM) attacks, and allowing attackers to easily intercept and access this data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30661 | An unauthorized access vulnerability has been discovered in ROS Melodic Morenia versions where ROS_VERSION is 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30661</link><description>An unauthorized access vulnerability has been discovered in ROS Melodic Morenia versions where ROS_VERSION is 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION is 3. This vulnerability could potentially allow a malicious user to gain unauthorized information access to multiple ROS nodes remotely. Unauthorized information access to these nodes could result in compromised system integrity, the execution of arbitrary commands, and disclosure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30659 | Shell Injection vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia versions ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30659</link><description>Shell Injection vulnerability in ROS (Robot Operating System) Melodic Morenia versions ROS_VERSION 1 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION 3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27488 | Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in ZLMediaKit versions 1.0 through 8.0, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27488</link><description>Incorrect Access Control vulnerability in ZLMediaKit versions 1.0 through 8.0, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information. The application system enables the http API interface by default and uses the secret parameter method to authenticate the http restful api interface, but the secret is hardcoded by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 06:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31022 | An issue was discovered in CandyCMS version 1.0.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the install.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31022</link><description>An issue was discovered in CandyCMS version 1.0.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the install.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1292 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1292</link><description>The wpb-show-core WordPress plugin before 2.6 does not sanitise and escape some parameters before outputting them back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1588 | SendPress Newsletters &amp;lt;= 1.23.11.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1588</link><description>The SendPress Newsletters WordPress plugin through 1.23.11.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1589 | SendPress Newsletters &amp;lt;= 1.23.11.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Form Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1589</link><description>The SendPress Newsletters WordPress plugin through 1.23.11.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1752 | Font Farsi &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1752</link><description>The Font Farsi WordPress plugin through 1.6.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1956 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1956</link><description>The wpb-show-core WordPress plugin before 2.7 does not sanitise and escape the parameters before outputting it back in the response of an unauthenticated request, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1958 | WPB Show Core &amp;lt; 2.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1958</link><description>The wpb-show-core WordPress plugin before 2.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or unauthenticated users</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52341 | In Plaintext COUNTER CHECK message accepted before AS security activation, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52341</link><description>In Plaintext COUNTER CHECK message accepted before AS security activation, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52342 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52342</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52343 | In SecurityCommand message after as security has been actived., there is a possible improper input validation. This could lead to remote inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52343</link><description>In SecurityCommand message after as security has been actived., there is a possible improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52344 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52344</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52345 | In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52345</link><description>In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52346 | In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52346</link><description>In modem driver, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52347 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52347</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52348 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52348</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52349 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52349</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52350 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52350</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52351 | In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52351</link><description>In ril service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52352 | In Network Adapter Service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52352</link><description>In Network Adapter Service, there is a possible missing permission check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52533 | In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52533</link><description>In modem-ps-nas-ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote information disclosure no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52534 | In ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52534</link><description>In ngmm, there is a possible undefined behavior due to incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52535 | In vsp driver, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52535</link><description>In vsp driver, there is a possible missing verification incorrect input. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52536 | In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52536</link><description>In faceid service, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23658 | In camera driver, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23658</link><description>In camera driver, there is a possible use after free due to a logic error. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28744 | The password is empty in the initial configuration of ACERA 9010-08 firmware v02.04 and earlier, and ACERA 9010-24 firmware v02.04 and earli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28744</link><description>The password is empty in the initial configuration of ACERA 9010-08 firmware v02.04 and earlier, and ACERA 9010-24 firmware v02.04 and earlier. An unauthenticated attacker may log in to the product with no password, and obtain and/or alter information such as network configuration and user information. The products are affected only when running in non MS mode with the initial configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36829 | The Mojolicious module before 8.65 for Perl is vulnerable to secure_compare timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36829</link><description>The Mojolicious module before 8.65 for Perl is vulnerable to secure_compare timing attacks that allow an attacker to guess the length of a secret string. Only versions after 1.74 are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47208 | The Mojolicious module before 9.11 for Perl has a bug in format detection that can potentially be exploited for denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47208</link><description>The Mojolicious module before 9.11 for Perl has a bug in format detection that can potentially be exploited for denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3437 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Avatar add-admin.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3437</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/add-admin.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259631.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:05:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3434 | CP Plus Wi-Fi Camera User Management improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3434</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CP Plus Wi-Fi Camera up to 20240401. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component User Management. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259615. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3436 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Avatar edit-photo.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3436</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/edit-photo.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259630 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3433 | PuneethReddyHC Event Management register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3433</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /backend/register.php. The manipulation of the argument event_id/full_name/email/mobile/college/branch leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-259614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3432 | PuneethReddyHC Event Management register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3432</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /backend/register.php. The manipulation of the argument event_id/full_name/email/mobile/college/branch leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259613 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3430 | QKSMS Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3430</link><description>A vulnerability was found in QKSMS up to 3.9.4 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259611. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:07:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3431 | EyouCMS Backend deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3431</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EyouCMS 1.6.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.php?m=admin&amp;c=Field&amp;a=channel_edit of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument channel_id leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259612. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31948 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an attacker using a malformed Prefix SID attribute in a BGP UPDATE packet can cause the bgpd daemon to crash...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31948</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an attacker using a malformed Prefix SID attribute in a BGP UPDATE packet can cause the bgpd daemon to crash.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31949 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an infinite loop can occur when receiving a MP/GR capability as a dynamic capability because malformed data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31949</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, an infinite loop can occur when receiving a MP/GR capability as a dynamic capability because malformed data results in a pointer not advancing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31950 | In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ri for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31950</link><description>In FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ri for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt to read Segment Routing subTLVs (their size is not validated).</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31951 | In the Opaque LSA Extended Link parser in FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ext_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31951</link><description>In the Opaque LSA Extended Link parser in FRRouting (FRR) through 9.1, there can be a buffer overflow and daemon crash in ospf_te_parse_ext_link for OSPF LSA packets during an attempt to read Segment Routing Adjacency SID subTLVs (lengths are not validated).</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31291 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.6 - IDOR on Friend Request vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31291</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31296 | WordPress BookingPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.81 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31296</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Repute Infosystems BookingPress.This issue affects BookingPress: from n/a through 1.0.81.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31233 | WordPress Rehub theme &amp;lt;= 19.6.1 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sizam Rehub.This issue affects Rehub: from n/a through 19.6.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31234 | WordPress REHub Framework plugin &amp;lt; 19.6.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sizam REHub Framework.This issue affects REHub Framework: from n/a before 19.6.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31241 | WordPress LearnPress Export Import plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ThimPress LearnPress Export Import.This issue affects LearnPress Export Import: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22155 | WordPress WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22155</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic WooCommerce.This issue affects WooCommerce: from n/a through 8.5.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31236 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.93 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.93.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31260 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31255 | WordPress ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31255</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ELEXtensions ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31256 | WordPress WebinarPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.33.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31256</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebinarPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WebinarPress: from n/a through 1.33.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31257 | WordPress Formsite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31257</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Formsite Formsite | Embed online forms to collect orders, registrations, leads, and surveys allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Formsite | Embed online forms to collect orders, registrations, leads, and surveys: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31258 | WordPress Form to Chat App plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31258</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Micro.Company Form to Chat App allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Form to Chat App: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31306 | WordPress Essential Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Blocks for Gutenberg allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Essential Blocks for Gutenberg: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31344 | WordPress Easy Login Styler  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31344</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Phpbits Creative Studio Easy Login Styler – White Label Admin Login Page for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Login Styler – White Label Admin Login Page for WordPress: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31346 | WordPress Gradient Text Widget for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31346</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blocksmarket Gradient Text Widget for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gradient Text Widget for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31348 | WordPress Super Testimonials plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themepoints Testimonials allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Testimonials: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31280 | WordPress Church Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31280</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin.This issue affects Church Admin: from n/a through 4.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31286 | WordPress WP Photo Album Plus plugin &amp;lt; 8.6.03.005 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31286</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in J.N. Breetvelt a.K.A. OpaJaap WP Photo Album Plus.This issue affects WP Photo Album Plus: from n/a before 8.6.03.005.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31292 | WordPress Import XML and RSS Feeds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31292</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Moove Agency Import XML and RSS Feeds.This issue affects Import XML and RSS Feeds: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31349 | WordPress MailMunch – Grow your Email List plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MailMunch MailMunch – Grow your Email List allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MailMunch – Grow your Email List: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3428 | SourceCodester Online Courseware edit.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3428</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259600.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31277 | WordPress Product Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.32 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31277</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PickPlugins Product Designer.This issue affects Product Designer: from n/a through 1.0.32.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31345 | WordPress Auto Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31345</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Sukhchain Singh Auto Poster.This issue affects Auto Poster: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31288 | WordPress RapidLoad plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31288</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in RapidLoad RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize.This issue affects RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize: from n/a through 2.2.11.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31308 | WordPress WP Import Export Lite &amp;amp; WP Import Export plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.26 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31308</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in VJInfotech WP Import Export Lite.This issue affects WP Import Export Lite: from n/a through 3.9.26.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3427 | SourceCodester Online Courseware addq.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3427</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file addq.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259599.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3426 | SourceCodester Online Courseware editt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3426</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3425 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activateall.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3425</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/activateall.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259597 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3424 | SourceCodester Online Courseware listscore.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3424</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/listscore.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259596.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3423 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activateteach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3423</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/activateteach.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259595.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3422 | SourceCodester Online Courseware activatestud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/activatestud.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 13:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3421 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivatestud.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3421</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/deactivatestud.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259593 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3420 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3420</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/saveedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259592.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3419 | SourceCodester Online Courseware edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3419</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259591.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3418 | SourceCodester Online Courseware deactivateteach.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3418</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/deactivateteach.php. The manipulation of the argument selector leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259590 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52716 | Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52716</link><description>Vulnerability of starting activities in the background in the ActivityManagerService (AMS) module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52717 | Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52717</link><description>Permission verification vulnerability in the lock screen module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4438 | kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent SmsUserConsentModule.kt registerReceiver improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4438</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in kyivstarteam react-native-sms-user-consent up to 1.1.4 on Android. Affected by this issue is the function registerReceiver of the file android/src/main/java/ua/kyivstar/reactnativesmsuserconsent/SmsUserConsentModule.kt. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Attacking locally is a requirement. Upgrading to version 1.1.5 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5423dcb0cd3e4d573b5520a71fa08aa279e4c3c7. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259508.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52715 | The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52715</link><description>The SystemUI module has a vulnerability in permission management.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52382 | Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52382</link><description>Vulnerability of improper control over foreground service notifications in the notification module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52714 | Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52714</link><description>Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the hwnff module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52713 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52713</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30418 | Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30418</link><description>Vulnerability of insufficient permission verification in the app management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30416 | Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30416</link><description>Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the underlying driver module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30417 | Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30417</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in the Bluetooth-based sharing module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30413 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30413</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30414 | Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30414</link><description>Command injection vulnerability in the AccountManager module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30415 | Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30415</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission control in the window management module.
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability will affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 08:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3417 | SourceCodester Online Courseware saveeditt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3417</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/saveeditt.php. The manipulation of the argument contact leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259589 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3416 | SourceCodester Online Courseware editt.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3416</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/editt.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259588.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 03:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6877 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Store...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6877</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Content-Type field of error messages when retrieving an invalid RSS feed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3415 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System addbranches_process.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3415</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file Superadmin_Dashboard/process/addbranches_process.php. The manipulation of the argument branches_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259584.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3414 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System addcorporate_process.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3414</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Superadmin_Dashboard/process/addcorporate_process.php. The manipulation of the argument corporate_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259583.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 20:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3413 | SourceCodester Human Resource Information System login_process.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3413</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file initialize/login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument hr_email/hr_password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259582 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28741 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28741</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in EginDemirbilek NorthStar C2 v1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27620 | An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27620</link><description>An issue in Ladder v.0.0.1 thru v.0.0.21 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the API.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 18:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0406 | Mholt/archiver: path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0406</link><description>A flaw was discovered in the mholt/archiver package. This flaw allows an attacker to create a specially crafted tar file, which, when unpacked, may allow access to restricted files or directories. This issue can allow the creation or overwriting of files with the user's or application's privileges using the library.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3156 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3156</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3158 | Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3158</link><description>Use after free in Bookmarks in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3159 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3159</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3378 | iboss Secure Web Gateway Login Portal login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3378</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iboss Secure Web Gateway up to 10.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login of the component Login Portal. The manipulation of the argument redirectUrl leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 10.2.0.160 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3377 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3377</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24746 | Apache NimBLE: Denial of service in NimBLE Bluetooth stack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24746</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache NimBLE. 

Specially crafted GATT operation can cause infinite loop in GATT server leading to denial of service in Bluetooth stack or device.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.6.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 12:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25029 | IBM Personal Communications code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25029</link><description>IBM Personal Communications 14.0.6 through 15.0.1 includes a Windows service that is vulnerable to remote code execution (RCE) and local privilege escalation (LPE). The vulnerability allows any unprivileged user with network access to a target computer to run commands with full privileges in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. This allows for a low privileged attacker to move laterally to affected systems and to escalate their privileges.  IBM X-Force ID:  281619.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22328 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22328</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10 and 8.11 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  279950.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3376 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System config.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3376</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file config.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to execution after redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259497 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3369 | code-projects Car Rental add-vehicle.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3369</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Car Rental 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument Upload Image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259490 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3366 | Xuxueli xxl-job Template JdkSerializeTool.java deserialize injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3366</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Xuxueli xxl-job up to 2.4.1. This vulnerability affects the function deserialize of the file com/xxl/job/core/util/JdkSerializeTool.java of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259480.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3365 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/users/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259469 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3364 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3364</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259468.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2132 | The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2132</link><description>The Ultimate Bootstrap Elements for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2296 | The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2296</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG file uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3363 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3363</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/borrowed/index.php. The manipulation of the argument BookPublisher/BookTitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259467.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0837 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0837</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the image URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1428 | The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1428</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Free Template Library, Grid, Carousel, Table, Parallax Animation, Register Form, Twitter Grid) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘element_pack_wrapper_link’ attribute of the Trailer Box widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2458 | The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2458</link><description>The Powerkit – Supercharge your WordPress Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 07:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2949 | The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2949</link><description>The Carousel, Slider, Gallery by WP Carousel – Image Carousel &amp; Photo Gallery, Post Carousel &amp; Post Grid, Product Carousel &amp; Product Grid for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3362 | SourceCodester Online Library System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3362</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/books/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument IBSN leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259466 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 06:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2471 | The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', '...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2471</link><description>The FooGallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image attachment fields (such as 'Title', 'Alt Text', 'Custom URL', 'Custom Class', and 'Override Type') in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3361 | SourceCodester Online Library System deweydecimal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3361</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/books/deweydecimal.php. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259465 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21506 | Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21506</link><description>Versions of the package pymongo before 4.6.3 are vulnerable to Out-of-bounds Read in the bson module. Using the crafted payload the attacker could force the parser to deserialize unmanaged memory. The parser tries to interpret bytes next to buffer and throws an exception with string. If the following bytes are not printable UTF-8 the parser throws an exception with a single byte.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2444 | Inline Related Posts &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2444</link><description>The Inline Related Posts WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 05:10:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3360 | SourceCodester Online Library System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3360</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/books/index.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259464.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3359 | SourceCodester Online Library System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3359</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Library System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259463.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3358 | SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3358</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Aplaya Beach Resort Online Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument to leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259462 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1385 | The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1385</link><description>The WP-Stateless – Google Cloud Storage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the dismiss_notices() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary option values to the current time, which may completely take a site offline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2656 | The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vuln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2656</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters, Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a CSV import in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2950 | The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2950</link><description>The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.14 via meta information (og:description) This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the first 130 characters of a password protected post which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3216 | The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modificat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3216</link><description>The WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wt_pklist_reset_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset all of the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3245 | The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3245</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1994 | The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the waterma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1994</link><description>The Image Watermark plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the watermark_action_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to apply and remove watermarks from images.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>